Thank you for watching!
New member audition for Shihetsu Ebisu
Junior High School 2022 begins now!
Thank you!
Shirito Ebisu Middle School, also known
as Ebichu-Gakku
This May, the new members will be
auditioned
The total number of applications
collected from all over the country is
7,000
From there, 10 people who passed the
paper interview were promoted to the
final screening
3 nights and 4 days of audition training
The age and background are different,
but 10 students with the same dream
challenge
I want to be an idol
I will definitely become an idol member
I don't want to be an idol, I want to be
an idol member
Who will be able to achieve their dream?
The bus with the entrance exam students
arrived at the training ground.
The first student is...
Thank you.
I'm a student in the swimming class.
I've been doing swimming since I was in
the fifth grade.
I've been doing piano since I was four
years old.
Yuka from Tokyo, 16 years old, who
specializes in fruit
I want to dance as hard as I can, and do
my best
I want to give my all and do my best
The second student is...
Thank you very much
Yuka from Kanagawa prefecture, 15 years
old, who specializes in fruit
I want to dance as hard as I can
I really wanted to be in the group
I watched the last year's concert
I thought it would be fun to be in the
group
I've come this far, so I want to do my
best
I want to give my best
The next student is...
22 years old, from Saitama prefecture
The youngest of the students who are
challenging for the final evaluation
I want to be able to support everyone in
terms of age
I'm not good at dancing
I'm not good at singing
I want to try my best
The next student is...
What grade are you in middle school?
I'm in the second grade
What is your major?
Handball
I'm aiming for the position of the edge
of the side of the court
A sports girl who belongs to the
handball club
Miumi, 13 years old from Tokyo
I'm 3% nervous, and 7% excited
I don't think I've ever had such a
valuable experience
I'm going to enjoy it
The next student is...
I'm not in elementary school, I'm 13
years old from the first grade
My major is dance, and my specialty is
piano and dance
She just became a junior high school
student this year
Yuria, 13 years old from Osaka
I'm very nervous, but I'll do my best
with all my might.
She's from Osaka, and she's 13 years
old.
I went to see the live performance
yesterday.
I wanted to be on the dance side, not
the audience side.
I'm from Osaka, and I'm 16 years old.
She's from Osaka, and she's 16 years
old.
I think my energy is my strength.
I'll do my best to convey my good side
to the audience.
I came to this audition with the goal of
becoming the best.
Next, she showed us a energetic dance.
She's from Mie prefecture, and she's 13
years old.
She's tall.
I'm 165 cm.
I'll do my best to do my best until the
end.
And...
I came to this audition because I wanted
to be like that because I was so
energetic.
Ruri is 14 years old.
I'm nervous, but I'm looking forward to
it.
I'll do my best.
I'm looking forward to this audition.
The farthest participant is 15-year-old
Yuna from Fukuoka prefecture
I will do my best to be able to return
to the school and I want to be accepted
by Ebichu
Thus, 10 students became the final
candidates for the new members of
Shirito Ebisu Middle School
Good morning everyone
Good morning
We will have 3 or 4 sessions from today
Thank you
It's hot, let's go inside
Go!
First, the orientation for the training
camp was held
The person who explained the orientation
is
We have invited the person who will
explain the orientation
Please come in
Hello
Good morning
We became the morning channel
Shirito Ebisu Middle School
The number 13, Sakura Yuno and the
number 14, Yuna Kukubo
And the number 15, Nanaka Katami
Good morning everyone
Good morning
The person who appeared was
The member who became Ebichu after the
audition camp last year
Sakura Yuno
Yuna Kukubo
And the number 13, Nonoka Kazami
You were crying
Yes, I became stronger
You became stronger
At that time, I was really worried about
whether I could stay
I think I have grown as a member of
Ebichu
I think I have grown a little
One year ago, they actually experienced
audition camp
The three people were visiting the camp
to tell the feelings directly to the
students
It's hot
Thank you for watching
Let's go.
I'm sure they'll react to it.
It's been a year.
I thought it was a year.
Let's go to the back.
Let's go.
Hello.
Before the ten students who are aiming
to become shrimp-chewers,
what did Yuno, Nonoka and Kokona say?
We talk about it every lesson.
After I joined the school,
I had a lot of ups and downs.
I had no experience in singing.
I started singing from the beginning.
It was really hard for me for the first
year.
I was scolded a lot and cried a lot.
I spent those days.
At the end of the year,
there is a university concert.
It was the first time I was in the
queue.
I performed on such a big stage for the
first time as a shrimp-chewer.
I saw the unity of the venue at that
time.
The sunlight was beautiful and shining.
It was really hard for me for a year.
I was scolded and I was really
depressed.
I felt that I had to work harder.
I was really sad when I saw the
sunlight.
I felt that.
When I auditioned for the school,
I couldn't imagine how it would be like
to be a shrimp-chewer.
During the audition,
I participated with pride that I would
be satisfied with the enthusiasm.
Don't forget that feeling.
Please do your best.
I support you.
For the first four days,
I think there are a lot of difficult
things.
I hope I can do my best not to regret
it.
I did it last year because I thought so.
I hope I can do it in my heart.
There are a lot of difficult things in
these four days.
There are always fun things.
Don't give up and do your best.
I love you.
That's all for our presentation.
Thank you very much for listening.
Thank you.
I thought that the people who were
training together a year ago would
change so much.
I thought I should do my best.
I was impressed by the people who were
pushing me.
I was inspired to work with them.
The students who received the idea of
training with Ebichu from the members.
They were asked to train together.
The purpose of this training is to show
the students who are the defenders of
Ebichu.
I will announce the songs that they will
sing.
Let's start.
The same as last year's audition.
The song is the single song of Ebichu
2014, Haitateki.
And.
This song is also a popular song at the
live show.
And.
The same song as last year's audition.
I think it's easy.
I have another song.
I will learn it from now.
The third song.
The third song is.
Thank you for watching!
The relatudal great ebisu junior high
school major debuts single Cinderella
They have to master the three songs they
have learned in three days' training and
show them off
They will be divided into three groups
and will try to solve the problems
Ready, set, go!
We are the X-Girls!
Wait, I'm a little nervous
Ready, set, go!
We are the Okae team!
We are the Riki team!
Now, we will introduce the dance teacher
Thank you
The lessons will start from the
professional dance teacher who is in
charge of the debut
And the dance teacher
Thank you
Since the trainees had practiced in
advance, they all mastered the
choreography.
However...
The person in the center of the circle
will enter
Cha cha cha cha
Ta ta ta ta ta ta ta
Don't cross
It's difficult
Suddenly, the students are attacked by
confusion
It's dangerous
I'm sorry
It's difficult to do it, so I struggle
The performance during the semi-final is
one of the most complicated formations
for many people
Even the talented students who have
progressed to the final evaluation
They struggle with the complicated
formation
That same performance, the coach is
Joachim distorting his eyes
Here.
If you make a mistake in the formation,
you'll bump into someone.
You may hurt others as well as yourself.
Please be careful.
I'd like you to watch the choreography a
little more.
I'll tell you the details later.
I'll tell you at that time.
The first song is a big wall standing in
front of the students.
After the lesson.
They naturally gathered in each unit and
began self-practice.
I hope we can work hard together and
become good together.
I hope we can do something good
together.
I want to work hard with everyone.
The first lesson is a big wall standing
in front of the students.
The second lesson is a big wall standing
I was able to do my best because I had
my teammates.
I was able to show my gratitude to the
team members.
Ruri is good at dancing.
She can do very fine details.
But there are people who have that kind
of attitude.
I was able to show my sense of self-
cultivation.
I was able to create a good feeling with
everyone.
We are all rivals.
We are rivals, but we help each other.
I want to end it so that everyone does
not eat.
Age and background are different.
And 10 people who are rivals.
They started racing toward the same
dream.
Spe Sal21
jin
lov
Thank you for watching!