Yakan to A-I-to-Ru?
Do you have any announcements?
Yes, on November 19th, we will release
our fourth album, Kyusai!
Thank you very much.
This album is based on Kyushu 7th gen.
We have songs from the past, and we have
songs with Kyushu's style.
When we released our first album, we
thought it was the album that our
seniors were releasing.
But recently, we are surprised that it's
our fourth album.
It's supported by fans.
It's our first album, so please listen
to it.
On November 26th, we will have a live
performance at Nakano San Prado.
Thank you very much.
The band is the biggest band in the
past.
I'm very excited.
The structure is very good.
It's good.
The members' opinions are reflected in
the band.
We talked a lot with the director.
We are making a live performance.
Please watch it.
Finally, I would like to ask you to make
tea for me.
Thank you very much.
Do you usually drink tea?
I don't drink tea often.
When I go to my grandmother's house, I
drink this tea.
Thank you very much.
I got a good impression.
Was it delicious?
It was delicious.
I feel good.
Thank you very much.
That's all for today's YAKARUTA IDOL.
Please close the camera.
Thank you very much.
The room is big.
I'm sorry.
I'm happy.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's important not to think.
I'm okay with writing.
I have only one impression.
I made a dish with a whole-face bun.
I got the first bun in their lives.
YAKARUTA IDOL