The title is...
Kanto Idol!
Can you please give us a cute title
call?
Yes!
My three main elements!
Can you show us the three elements you
wrote down in advance?
Yes!
Ta-da!
This is it!
I see.
The third element is sauna!
Oh!
You're really into sauna!
Actually, my father has been in the
sauna for almost 20 years.
That's amazing!
My father used to love family so much.
He used to go to the sauna with his
family.
But he never said he'd go to the sauna
with his family.
That's true.
And idols are like...
What do you call it?
They're like a water-related thing.
They don't say it out loud.
I see.
I think that's what they're like.
But recently, the sauna boom has been
going on.
I'm glad to hear that.
So I'm going to try to get some
information.
Oh!
What kind of information do you get from
the sauna?
I want to know more about it.
I go into the sauna first.
I see.
There are many places with salt in the
sauna.
I go into the salt sauna first.
Then I feel like my pores are opening.
So I sweat faster than I do in the
sauna.
How long do you go in?
I usually go in for 12 minutes.
Oh, 12 minutes!
I go in for 12 minutes and then go in
for 10 minutes.
Then I go in for a bath.
I see.
I think everyone wants to know about
this.
Sauna is only for women.
So it's a bit of a shame.
That's true.
It's not a strange thing.
I may be asking in a strange way.
I imagine it.
I like the sauna.
It's the best.
I can't live without a sauna.
That's it.
How often do you go in?
Not once a month, but once a week.
It depends on the day.
I go in 4 times a week when it's too
much.
4 times a week?
I go in once a week.
That's true.
Please subscribe to our channel!