I'm Manatsu Akimoto from Nogizaka46.
I'm Minami Umezawa.
What's the plan for this time?
This time, we want to show you how
everyone's New Year's is going.
Let's take a look.
Here we go!
I came to the first stage.
I eat octopus.
I eat red bean.
I will do my best this year.
My goal is to go to all the special live
of BUSRA.
Thank you.
I'm here to buy some stuff.
I'm with my mom.
What do you have?
I don't have anything.
Why are you suddenly talking in a cute
voice?
I found a plane.
The illumination is very beautiful.
Hi, everyone.
I've been spending my New Year's holiday
well.
Today is my birthday.
I'm 24 years old.
Wow.
I've been spending my New Year's holiday
in a different way.
I gave my younger brother New Year's
presents.
I had a great New Year's holiday.
I hope I can do more things this year.
So please give me a lot of love.
I hope you'll support me this year, too.
Hello, I'm Renka Inamoto.
I came back to my family's house for the
New Year.
I spent time with my family and ate
meals.
I'm holding my friend's cat, so he's
crying.
I'm Melody and Rizumu.
I'm going home now.
Bye bye.
Hello, I'm Kubo Shiori.
Happy New Year.
I didn't do anything special on New
Year's Day.
I just spent time with this cloth.
I was able to go back to my hometown.
I was able to put my big flag on Sendai
Station.
It was a very fulfilling New Year's Day.
This year, I'm going to spread the word.
I want to spread the word about the
members and the work.
I'm looking forward to working with you
this year.
See you.
Happy New Year, everyone.
I'm Hazuki Mukai.
I decided not to go out for the first
time in 5 days.
I've been out for a walk for the first
My goal for 2023 is to go out with a lot
of members.
After this, I'm going to have dinner
with the members I got along with on
UNDER LIVE.
I've made a good start.
I hope I can spend a lot of time with my
fans and members this year.
I look forward to working with you this
year.
I'm Ayano Yoshida.
I'm back to my parents' house in Oita.
I haven't been anywhere, and I haven't
done much New Year's stuff.
I'd like to introduce my family's cat.
First, Lulu.
She's a Minuet girl.
Cute.
So small.
This is Rune.
She's a Persian.
Cute.
I got two cute cats.
They were very wary of me.
I couldn't touch them last year, but
this year I can hold them.
I think they've grown a little.
I'll do my best to make this year more
fun. Bye bye.
I'm Yudayuki.
Today, I'm going to introduce my pets in
my house.
I think many of you know them.
I have a dog, Aima.
I used to live in Tokyo.
Last summer, I had a drama shoot and a
national tour.
I spent too much time at home.
So I had my family take care of me.
I was worried that they might have
forgotten me.
But they remember me.
I'm relieved.
I'm going to be a family member for a
long time.
I hope you'll watch over me as I grow
up.
Hello!
We're at the cafe in Nikko.
I don't know where we are, but we're in
Okinawa!
My mom is taking a picture of us.
We're going to have a trip!
Hello, everyone. I'm Mizuki Yamashita.
I went to Okinawa with Riria Ito for my
winter vacation.
I went to Okinawa once during
construction, but it was my first time
in private.
It was so much fun, and the weather was
terrible.
It was 19 degrees or 20 degrees, and I
prepared a T-shirt and a jacket, but it
was very cold.
The wind was strong, and it was a
wonderful time.
It was a great time. Bye bye!
Happy New Year, everyone!
Today is the New Year's Eve.
I'm going out with Lily and Yamashita.
I'm waiting for them.
They are late.
I'm waiting alone.
I'll enjoy it.
I'll do my best to be more active in
2023.
Happy New Year!
I'm Tomomi Sakaguchi.
I came to Hatsumode for the winter
vacation.
I got a lot of lucky money.
I'll do my best this year with a smile.
Please support me.
I love you.
I'm Tomomi Sakaguchi.
Happy New Year, everyone!
How are you spending the New Year?
Today is January 3rd, and I'm here to
see the Hakone Equinox.
I'm in the 9th district, and the players
will be playing in a little while. I
can't speak out loud, but I'll be
cheering for them.
Translated by Vortex
Happy New Year!
I'm Endo Sakura.
My New Year's Day is...
at home.
I spend my New Year's Day at home,
I watch New Year's TV until midnight,
I read books,
I spend a lazy New Year's Day.
I didn't leave the house,
I was used to sleeping,
I'm trying to hide it with food.
I'm sorry.
I hope that 2023 will be a good year for
Nogizaka46.
I hope you'll support me for another
year.
I went to the first shrine visit.
I'm in the video.
Bye.
Happy New Year! I'm Seira Ayakawa.
I'm at my grandmother's house today.
I'm a grandmother.
I'm a grandma.
Nice to meet you, Seira.
I'm a year older than my grandmother,
but I'm going to be careful and do my
best.
Do you have a goal?
I'm not going to be discouraged by my
age. I'm going to do my best this year.
I hope you live a long life.
Thank you.
Do you have anything to say to me?
Please support me.
Thank you.
Bye bye.
Good evening, I'm Luna Aish.
I just finished my live performance at
the countdown live, and I'm back home.
I'm here at Hatsumode.
I just finished my visit.
I graduated from high school in 2022,
and I'm 19 years old.
I've been challenged a lot of things, so
I'll do my best to not lose that
momentum.
I look forward to working with you this
year.
Bye bye.
Hello, I'm Haruka Kaki.
I didn't do much during the New Year's
holiday.
I was relaxing at home.
I drew pictures, ate delicious food, and
watched TV.
When I'm asked if I did anything for the
New Year, I really didn't do anything.
I'm a little old, so I'll draw a little
here.
I put on a rabbit doll and tried to
portray New Year's.
How did you spend it?
I'm going to enjoy the winter more.
Hello. Happy New Year.
I'm having a barbecue.
This is a persimmon.
Happy New Year.
I'm going to eat it now.
I'm spending a wonderful New Year's
holiday with my family.
Let's make a fun memory together this
year.
Thank you.
I'm going to eat it now.
This year's New Year's Day, I'm going to
do a lot of homework, write a novel at
school, watch my favorite videos, and
update my Instagram every day.
Please follow me.
Is it wrong?
I'm going to do my best to make the New
Year's Day video a little more fun.
Hello, I'm Haruka Kurami.
This year, I went to my relative's house
and ate mochi and played catch ball.
I'm playing a lot of games.
I want to make the year a year where I
can be like Kurami-chan, my favorite
rabbit character.
Your wishes will come true.
Bye bye.
Hello, I'm Miyu Matsuo.
Today is my birthday on January 3rd, so
I was celebrating my birthday.
I hope I can be able to ride the balloon
in a fun year, both at 19 years old and
in 2023.
Thank you for your support this year.
I'll blow it.
1, 2, 3!
I did it! Bye bye!
Today I came to the center to play.
I came to see the Donsan Monster.
It's beautiful.
I will do my best on the 3rd day.
Hello, I'm Mayu Tamura.
I'm going to go dog running with two
dogs I have at home.
And my goal for this year is to be a
year-old girl,
so I want to be a year-old girl who can
run faster than last year.
I'm going to Matsuo's house for the New
Year's holiday.
I got a matching hoodie for the three of
us.
I'm enjoying eating meat.
That's all.
I'm going to Matsuo's house for the New
Year's holiday.
Thank you for watching.
I didn't notice
I came to eat this in Tokyo for winter
vacation.
I came with Min-chan next to me.
I came with Min-chan, so we will eat
deliciously together.
I think so. Everyone, have a good winter
vacation.
Happy New Year! I'm Yuna Shibata.
I went to my first shrine visit for the
winter break.
I was lucky to get a fortune.
My goal for this year is to try a new
genre of work.
I'll also try to cook more.
I'll do my best this year as well.
I'm Nao Inuki.
Today is a holiday, so I'm going to eat
the osechi my grandma made.
I have a lot of siblings and relatives
here, so I'm going to have a lot of fun.
I'm going to do my best this year
because it's the year of the ox.
I'm going to eat a lot of osechi.
I'm Nobuyo Nagi. I came to see
Hatsushinode.
I couldn't see it because I was
sleeping, but I'm glad my friends saw
it.
I'm Yuriko. I'm going to start the new
year with a bad feeling, but I hope I
can be a good person this year. Bye bye.
Congratulations on your debut!
I'm Miku Ichinose.
I'm here for my first modeling event.
I want to be a big actress like a rabbit
this year.
I'm looking forward to working with you
Happy New Year, everyone!
I'm Nao Tomisato, and I'm a mochi.
I went to my grandfather's house for New
Year's Day.
I ate mochi with my cousins and went out
to play.
I had a lot of fun New Year's Day.
I'll do my best this year, so please
support me.
Congratulations on your birthday!
Happy birthday! I'm Sakura Kawasaki.
I'm in the Chuka-kai right now.
I just saw the hand-wrapped clothes.
This is amazing.
It's a line that says my personality
hasn't changed since I was a baby.
So many wishes to you...
Happy New Year, everyone!
I'm Rino Nakanishi from Nogizaka46.
I've been eating a lot of delicious
food, watching TV, and sleeping a lot
this New Year.
I'll do my best to make 2023 a year
that's even cooler.
Like a rabbit!
See you!
Hello! I just finished the adult
ceremony and changed my clothes.
I'm wearing a kimono and a hoya hoya.
I'm a new adult this year, so I'll do my
best to be the oldest in the school.
I'll do my best!
Happy New Year! I'm Hina Okamoto.
I'm spending New Year's Eve with my
family and Hane-chan.
Say bye-bye!
Bye-bye!
Congratulations on your birthday!
I'm Okuda Iroha, a 5th generation.
I went to Nara prefecture with the
members of the 5th generation.
I went to various temples and shrines
and ate a lot of delicious food.
Did you have a happy New Year's Eve?
Bye bye!
I'm Aya Ogawa.
I'm traveling.
I'm with Iroha.
She's filming me.
Thank you.
I'm in Asuka Temple.
I'm going to draw a fortune.
I got No.40.
Suesho base?
I've never heard of it.
I wonder what it is.
I was there last year.
But I've been going there a lot this
year.
I'm sure it'll be okay this year.
Let's be happy together in 2023.
See you later.
Hello, I'm Satsuki Sugawara.
I went to Yokohama with my friends
today.
I'm riding a Ferris wheel now.
I'm looking forward to it.
Bye bye.
Happy New Year! I'm Hiyoki Mao.
I just came back from my parents' house.
I did a lot of New Year's things at my
parents' house.
I forgot to take this video.
I'm taking this video before I go to
bed.
My goal this year is to leave the house
after I charge my phone.
I always leave the house at 30% or so.
I'm going to run out of battery soon.
I'll do my best to leave the house at
100% charge.
What's the battery level now?
40%
I look forward to working with you this
year.
How was it?
Do you have a goal for this year?
My goal?
Manatsu will graduate soon.
Manatsu will come to my concert.
I'll definitely go.
I want you to watch my concert.
I'll do my best to do that.
I'm looking forward to it.
You still have some time.
You may be able to do something during
the live broadcast.
What is it?
You can ask me anything.
Really?
I'll do whatever I want.
I'll do anything.
I want to have a party with you.
Can I do that?
Why?
I want to go on a world trip.
Can I do that?
I think it's good.
I want to go on a world trip on a
private jet.
I'll go with you.
I'm looking forward to it.
Please do something.
I'll do my best.
We'll do our best this year.
Please look forward to it.
Please.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Bye bye.