The live festival of the summer for 3
weeks in a row
The second one is the birthday solo live
special of Ayaka Yasumoto
It's crazy
All of them are Yasumoto
Yasumoto Tastas start
The love and attention to you
What should I do with the heart of the
jubilee?
Moratorium, moratorium, moratorium,
junior high school student
Add various things to your private Ebisu
junior high school
Ebichu Tastas junior high school student
Hello!
This program is provided by the sponsor
you are watching.
Thank you for coming today!
A special event to celebrate the
birthday of the Ebitune members, a
birthday solo live.
The first solo live in Kobayashi, which
was held last month, was a great
success.
And on July 1st, the second birthday
solo concert was...
Thank you very much.
Ayaka Yasumoto, who turned 18 on June
27th.
How are you today?
I'm nervous.
If I'm nervous, I'll fail, so don't be
nervous. That's my father's advice.
The rehearsal starts 5 hours before the
show.
Good morning. I'm Ayaka Yasumoto, a
junior at C-team.
Thank you for your rehearsal.
This live performance is conducted by
the members themselves.
What did Yasumoto check at the
rehearsal?
Magic! What kind of theme will this be?
I'll do what I want to do now.
I think it will be a live that is so
full of people that it can't fit in.
I made it feel like I could get excited
with the audience.
The theme of this time is to get excited
with the family.
They said they put in a lot of ideas to
make it a live where Yasumoto and the
venue are one.
I'm not saying this to myself, but I put
in a lot of songs that are the same as
Yasumoto's.
I think there are a lot of songs that my
fans will be happy with.
A set list that is similar to Yasumoto's
is likely to be a love story of the
original color.
Thank you for your continued support.
30 minutes before the show
The one who appeared with a high tension
was Kaho Kobayashi
I was surprised at the master's dance
Furthermore
Kaho Kobayashi
Matsuno also supports her
Are you nervous?
Surprisingly, I'm nervous, but I'm
looking forward to it
Good luck!
Thank you!
Matsuno gives her a cheer and finally
goes to the real show
7 p.m.
Many families are gathered to celebrate
Yasumoto's birthday.
Yasumoto is also getting ready for this
day.
Oh, my God.
I want you to be happy.
Will Yasumoto's feelings reach her?
Thank you for watching!
Stardust's, stardust's, stardust's heavy
tune!
Hello!
Today, I've thought of a lot of things
to show you, but I hope you enjoy it and
come back!
Please listen to Chime!
Chime!
I'm still praying in front of the mirror
I'll be stronger than yesterday
If I wear my usual shoes again
Let's step out of the right foot
I'm a little anxious
I want to believe in the future
I can do better
I'm sure
Hey, the sweat flowing
The overflowing smile
Here
I'm here, so I can't stop anyone
I won't look back now
This dream I woke up from is starting
now
Dreams that know their never ending fate
Please subscribe to my channel and give
it a high rating!
The sun smiles at the big-hearted owner
I'm so happy
The water is a hero
You and I, the truth
We have the power to open from the
bottom of our hearts
The light is dazzling
The heart is burning...
I'll show you how I change!
Oh yeah! We are superheroes!
We have the power to defeat anyone!
Even if I cry, I want to believe
strongly!
The heart is burning... I'll show you
how I change!
And now, let's move on to the main event
that Yasumoto has thought of
Yasumoto Ayaka's Sokkuri-san Contest, in
short, Yasukon 1st round!
This is the title of the solo live show
Yasumoto Ayaka's Sokkuri-san Contest, in
short, Yasukon
This is a family-based competition where
4 people who passed the limited-time
screening will decide the winner by
looking for Yasumoto's Sokkuri-san on
the Ebichu homepage
The first round is Bakunon-san
It's similar
It feels strange
The second one is Mitsunari-san
What is this person like?
By the way, what is Sockkuri-san like?
I think he has a similar fashion sense
After that, various Yasumoto Sockkuri-
san appeared
From here?
From the entertainment field?
That's right
In the end, the winner will be decided
by these two people
Thank you for watching!
Now, which team will win?
It's Bakana!
The first YASUKON champion is decided by
Bakana!
Bakana received a live T-shirt with her
autograph as a prize.
They really look alike.
Thank you for watching Open!
I'm surprised.
From now on, I want to make a song that
you can enjoy.
Actually, Yasumoto was listening to
songs that were popular on the blog in
advance to make her family enjoy it.
When I heard what I liked in the song of
the Eiji, I liked the song called
Haitateki and Koyamide Teina.
I can't perform Koyamide Teina at the
live show. It's been a while since I
performed it, so the audience was
surprised.
It's a popular song, so I put it in.
In addition, in the song, there is a
performance that Yasumoto thought of.
Something came out.
Something came out. Isn't this a
souvenir?
And, oh, there is a dangerous button.
A mysterious button on the stage.
What is going to happen?
Yasumoto presents 《Haitateki》 Special
Version
The real deal is us
Celebration
Red and white world
This is the real deal
Red and white
Banyan and hop
Everyone, gather around
Red and white
I changed my mobile phone to a new one
Everything is a lie, everything is a lie
I'm tired, congratulations on your
wedding!
Everything is a lie, everything is a lie
I'm tired, congratulations on your
wedding!
Even when I'm in a slumber
I'll finally be able to say it, so stay
with me for a while
I love otaku too!
Congratulations!
This stage that looks like a dream
We're serious
More, more
We're going to roll up our sleeves
Even if the world is over, it's a
galaxy!
Congratulations!
Don't stop, let's go up
Thank you for watching!
The world of red and white
That's right, that's right
Let's go! Red and white, red and white,
red and white, red and white, red and
white
I'll give you a cup later.
Please sing with me
I got it!
It's a sweet encounter
I'm not sure, but it's my own opinion
It's not a lie, it's not a lie
It's hard to lose to weakness
I can't find it
My torn heart, heart with shCrowd Re
I tell myself once again that
I'm the growing child
in the future
Is It Okay to Say Just Okay?
The 22-year-old girl 이쪽es chili powder
We threats you the whole time
Go on, customers
Char tryin' to blend that chili powder
Please subscribe to my channel!
Thank you for watching!
It was a success!
Ah, sorry.
I have something to tell you.
At the previous handshake event,
the other members' fans came to my
handshake event.
The fans who were lining up at Aya-
chan's handshake event
said that everyone was having a great
time.
They said that everyone was smiling and
going home.
I was really happy to hear that.
I am really grateful to the fans who are
always on my side.
I can't wait to see you again. Thank you
very much.
And I want to thank the members of ABTU
and the staff who always support us.
Thank you always, ABTU members and
staff.
I hope we can spend the next year
together with a happy life.
I look forward to working with you.
And finally...
Thank you for today. It was really fun.
Thank you for watching.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I'll be watching you from the night sky
every day
But you're still too far away
Even if it's just spring, I want to see
the flowers blooming by your side
I wonder if we'll meet again
Ah, the feelings that can't be connected
or separated
are surely the same, aren't they?
Translated by Releska
I wonder if we'll meet again
I can't let go of these feelings
I'm sure we'll be together
I wonder if we'll meet again
I can't let go of our feelings
I'm sure we're together
Thank you for watching!
I can't do it anymore!
Well then, that's all for today.
Everyone, have a good day!
Thank you very much!
And so, the solo live that was packed
with what Yasumoto wanted to do,
closed the curtain of a great success.
Thank you for your hard work.
How was it?
I was nervous.
Thank you for your hard work.
I was so nervous.
I was crying because of the chimes.
I was really nervous.
I was so nervous.
Did you know that I was crying?
I was nervous.
I was so happy.
I was laughing all the time.
You were nervous, right?
I was nervous, too.
But I'll talk to her later.
I'll talk to her later.
Yasumoto has done everything.
Yes! I tried my best!
well......
You Campaign目
I think I was able to create a live
performance that is my style
I'm very satisfied with it
I'm a sleepyhead
Next time is the live festival final of
the summer
Matsuno Rina's birthday solo live
special
The stylish head of the group, Matsuno,
changes her clothes
And finally, she changes into a wedding
dress
This program was provided by the sponsor
you are watching.
Gundam!