Tonight's Ebichu Tastasu is a special
Hirota Aika solo live!
Hirota's first solo live was last month!
The full-scale stage of Ai Ai World,
directed by Hirota himself!
Ai Ai Tastasu, Start!
I'm so into you that I can't stop
What should I do with my heart?
Monotrium, monotrium, monotrium, middle
school students
Add various things to private Ebisu
middle school
Ebisu Justice
This program is brought to you by the
following sponsors.
Hirota is preparing for the stage on the
morning of the live.
What are you doing now?
I'm exhibiting.
I wanted to do this.
What is the meaning of the commitment to
make it to the lobby?
This time, I packed what I think is
cute.
All of them are my exhibitions.
The theme of the live is Aikawaii.
It is a live with a lot of cute that
Hirota thinks.
And this feeling.
I couldn't do what I can do with my own
power.
I feel like I made it by myself.
So, I asked the designer who admires
Hirota to make it.
I wrapped myself in a special costume
and went to the rehearsal.
Then.
What are you doing now?
愀 definitely very big.
I've been wanting to do a live
performance since I was a kid.
I finally got to do it this time.
I'm so happy.
I only asked her to do it.
I was hoping for it.
I'm so happy to cast her.
I'm so happy.
She's perfect for the role of a panda.
She's also very particular about the
song selection.
I wanted to make a song that would make
everyone confused.
I'm going to make it a setlist.
I'm going to have a lot of fun.
I hope you'll be excited.
Where are we?
Aizawa!
Ai Ai...
FANZONE!
Finally, the special live that Hirota is
going to send
Thank you for watching!
I'm going to make it!
Ai-yai!
Ai, ai, ah, ai, ah, ai, ai, ai
Together!
Ai, ai, ah, ai, ah, ai, ai, ai, ai
Ah, ai-yai!
Ai, ai, ah, ai, ah, ai, ai, ai, ai, ai
Ai, ai, ah, ai, ah, ai, ai, ai, ai, ai,
ai
Ai, ai, ah, ai, ah, ai, ai, ai, ai, ai
Ai, ai
To the hamburger, to the pedestrian, to
the food, to the clothes
Subscribe by Maya!
Alarm setting Click!?
I love you, love you, love you, love you
The world of glittering dreams
I love you, love you, love you
Ai Ai, you're the best idol, right?
Please, go to sleep soon
Five more minutes, ten more minutes
I don't have time anymore
Ah, I'm an idol
I have to be cute
I'm Ai Ai
Wow, I'm a bear, a panda-chan
Yeah, I want to love you, definitely
Love, double love
Break it, love, love
We are one, and one is love
Please subscribe to my channel!
Friends
If you debut solo, release a CD,
you'll get 800,000 yen in profit.
Yeah.
800,000 yen is yours.
But if it's a four-member band,
you'll get a quarter.
That's not all.
The sales, the appearance, the karaoke,
the music, everything is yours.
But if it's a four-member band,
you'll get a quarter.
What? The band is a joke, right?
Yeah! The band is a joke!
The band is a joke!
We are one
And we are two
Hey, hey, that's a promise you don't
say!
No, it's a promise you don't say!
Once this song is over, it's just the
usual Pou-chan!
We're friends, friends, friends
Important friends, friends, friends
Friends
Hey, hey
What?
Since we're here, let's make our unit
debut
I'm counting on you
Okay, let's do just one song
Really?
Yeah
Then, music start!
Please subscribe to my channel and
follow me on Twitter!
Hey, aren't you drinking too much?
I want to drink more, Mama
You really are a useless person
I hate you, my tears are running down my
face
Are you crying?
I just got a little drunk
The two of us are in the middle of the
night
This is Uguizuna
A small snack for the party
Fried rice, mixed fried
We're having a handmade lunch
I'm really sorry about everything
What did you just say?
Nothing, I'm going home
Be careful, I'll be waiting for you
tomorrow
This is the last time
You... What's wrong?
Don't tell me... You...
What's going on?
You!
You, you!
You, you, you, you!
You!
You, you!
You, you, you, you!
SUBSCRIBE TO YOUKI FOR MORE BONUS
CONTENT
Ahculature atarata
I want to tell you
I couldn't say this feeling forever
Actually, I'm very lonely
See, immediately
Tears overflowed
Please subscribe to my channel!
Is that merely a voice ただ、 keeping
perhaps I want this song,
I kept always close to the time
that was told me a statements of
aspiring I freezes crying
with confidence of evening 歡喜喜。
In the morning bottle In night bottle
I feel like I'm smelling an adult
The time we spent together is now gone
We didn't even say goodbye
Goodbye
Even if I know it's not going to happen
I keep thinking about it, I want to tell
you
I can't say these feelings until the end
Every time I remember your smile
I remember the gentle memories
That I had with you, so they won't
disappear
If only sadness you knew
Can be kept docked in your heart
And I'll just head forward
I'll tell you someday, until that time
I love you, who whispers softly on the
way home
I'm sure, but still, goodbye
I'll get closer to you
I want to tell you that I can't see you
I can't say this feeling forever
The truth is that I'm really lonely
Look, my tears are overflowing
Thank you for watching!
Please subscribe to my channel!
The shadow of a wheel in the distance,
the waves of the night erased
Cutting through the cold wind, running
away
Someday, these drops will become jewels
Believing that they will be reborn in a
beautiful heart
Becoming a single shining light in the
world
Even if I face a tomorrow without light
Even if loneliness teaches me the way to
sadness
I'm still breathing, I'm still alive
today
Translated by Releska
May it be a blessing to me, the only one
in the world
May it be a blessing to my tears
May it be a blessing to tomorrow
Become the one shining light in the
world
It's okay to cry, just walk towards me
Tears are like a shooting star
Come, be mine, make me come true
And live on
Oh, always
Thank you for watching!
Translated by Jaefine
Hank Gordon! Hank Gordon!
Yes!
Thank you for the encore!
More importantly,
today,
thank you for coming to Aikawai!
Wow!
I prepared a song
for you.
When I was about 10 years old, I was
auditioning to join the agency.
I had voted for this song for the
audition in my car,
but I happened to have the song I voted
for for the audition when I was 10 years
old.
So it's a little embarrassing, but I can
only do it on this occasion.
I hope I can sing with the me of 10
years old and the me of 18 years old.
With her singing voice before her debut,
she showed us a song of memories.
Embrace the miracle reflected in those
eyes
I can't be honest
I've been going around in circles
I don't know the real meaning of dreams
and fangs
I think it's magic to be a wonderful me
I don't need to cry and laugh
I only need you, I love you
I'm with you, with you, I'm with you, in
your side
So you can fly high
You, who looks like you don't want to
lose
Are getting closer to your dream than
anyone else
I want to spread my wings that only you
can do
Embrace the miracle reflected in those
eyes
It's so beautiful, like a dream
Thank you for watching!
Thank you so much.
Yep!
How was Aikawari today?
I thought it was really cute when I
first thought of it.
I think it was the first time I've ever
thought of something in my mind and in
my head.
I'm afraid of it.
I'm often told that I'm different.
But I think there are definitely many
people who find it hard to say that they
like me.
I want to be able to say that I'm
supporting this girl to my precious
person.
Thank you for your continued support.
Hiroto's first solo concert was a
success.
Thank you very much.
I really enjoyed it.
I really wanted to do it.
I'm really happy that I could do
everything I wanted to do.
I want to do my best to make more
opportunities like this.
Thank you very much.
Next episode
Mayama is looking for a property to live
alone
Welcome
Good morning
I'm here to shoot
Why?
Open Ramen Mayama
And the person who missed Ebichu Tastas
On the star dust channel, a low-cost
video distribution site
Ebichu Tastas is popular
I'm a famous person over there
Don't laugh
Ebichu Tastas is available for 400 yen
per month
In addition, a large number of
unreleased special footage will be
released.
I look like a weird face.
For more information, search on Stardust
Channel.
This program was brought to you by the
following sponsors.
Thank you!
Thank you, everyone!