Hello
We are on the earth now
It's just the time to wrap up the tour
Oh, here it comes
Riku is dancing
Today is Father's Day, so we are going
to do a special project
And we are going to do a father quiz
Wow
I'm laughing
Can I say that I'm close to you?
Do you have a crush?
Yes, I do
Really?
But I talk about it everyday
I know what you like and what you don't
like
What about you, Popo?
I don't know
I don't know what you don't like
I know what you don't like
Let's open the father's drawing
Ta-da
Cute
Let's start the first question of the
father's quiz
What is your father's favorite food?
I've never heard that this is my
favorite food
I think it's like that
I eat it everyday
Can you say it?
What is this?
Ta-da
I don't know what my favorite food is
It's a sombran
Cute
What is your favorite food?
I asked Hirota's father
If you could bring one thing to a
deserted island, what would it be?
A boat
A car
The answer is...
Sunburn
Cute girl
I'm very happy to be able to drive a car
I will do my best to get a car soon, so
please keep an eye on me
So warm
So, 0 points
ARis' too
It's over
a sweaty
Next is Kobayashi-san
Ta-da!
It looks like him
My father is very serious
Before we move on to the next question,
I heard that Kobayashi-san recently had
a rebellious period
Yes, I'm actually in a rebellious period
Oh, you're in a rebellious period
What are two of your father's favorite
foods?
Soba and what is the other?
Soba?
What? Soba?
Soba and
Soba!
I knew it
It was tofu
What?
It's the same as Kaho's
I want to eat it together
I eat it too
I got tofu and eat it
Oh
What is the word that your father is
curious about recently?
So
Please subscribe to our channel
No, it's not.
The answer is,
Hello, in the style of Mark Panzer.
Hello.
I don't know what it is.
In my house,
Nancy King Loeb is popular,
so I often say,
Hello.
Recently,
I was moved by Gaho's speech.
I was moved by the fact that
she said thank you for coming to pick me
up.
She said it.
She said something good.
I was moved.
I think you came here because
you think I'm usually rebellious.
I'm glad.
But, I'm trying to say that.
You are.
Why?
I'm trying to say that.
I'll pick you up at Moyoda station.
I'm sorry to bother you.
I look forward to working with you.
So,
Bye.
Hello!
Are you confident?
Confidence depends on the question.
I see.
Here is the illustration.
Oh, no.
Something is wrong.
Only this side is very strong.
I'm not sure.
It's funny.
Nakayama's father answered,
I don't like it.
What is it?
Sashimi.
I have an image that I always eat
sashimi.
Is sashimi made of rice?
Sashimi is made of sushi.
What is the answer?
The answer is...
I don't know about rice!
It's actually rice
Rice!
That's right!
Alright, let's go to the next question!
I asked Nakayama's father
If you could bring one thing to a
deserted island, what would it be?
I got it
She got it
What is it?
She's saying it so easily
That's fast
You can say the answer
Yes
The answer is...no, open!
The answer is...
Someone you can talk to
She's really talkative
When I was in my room, I came back
She came in laughing and said, sorry,
sorry
I was wondering who she was talking to
She was alone
That's what always happens
What is it?
I'm going to get a three-star
I think it's a message from my dad
Even if I talk to my daughter, she says,
What are you talking about?
I'm sad that I can't talk to her
It's not a private conversation
I was talking to my daughter
I'm scared!
I thought it was a secret.
Please tell me when you talk to me.
Ebichu!
The last one is the master.
Open!
I'm scared.
What is the food that Yasumoto-san's
father hates?
Food he hates?
I know.
What is it?
Then, open the answer!
Fish dish.
Basically, he likes meat.
So, when he eats fish, he is not so
excited.
Is it mackerel?
Is it not chicken cutlet?
Which one is the correct answer?
That's the end.
OK, one more time.
This is difficult.
The answer is very difficult.
If I dare to say, it's potato with miso
soup.
Really?
I asked Yasumoto's father.
If you were a member of Evuchu, what
would you do?
I always do this, so I know.
The answer is open.
I want to bring back a lot of sashimi.
I brought it back today.
I brought it back.
Is it correct?
Correct
I asked my dad what I like about Aya-
chan.
His answer was,
She is hardworking and tries her best in
everything.
She talks about her hard times and gives
advice.
She never says anything bad about
anyone.
I want to tell my dad about my hard
times and fun stories.
Let's make a fun family together.
Aya-chan is the winner of the Dad's
Quiz.
The prize is this.
It's a cut-off of a cow's head.
Wow, that's great.
Foreplay