Thank you for watching!
Excuse me.
Believe or not...
So I hope to try to make Pokemon's
zipper look pretty.
There may be some parts that look funny
for the kids,
and others won't look well.
I study the handsome points of the
characters.
I always have a special ap Winter.
Don't be shocked, My
Please subscribe to my channel.
Hello, I'm 16-year-old TAKEUCHI KIRARI
from Hiroshima.
I want to feel more of Tokyo when I live
in Tokyo.
I'm ready to climb the Tokyo Tower.
It's huge. I'm surprised.
I'm a little worried about climbing
that.
But it's great to feel Tokyo.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to the beautiful
office building.
High school students these days are very
shiny.
I've never received a shiny JK before,
so I'm looking forward to it.
I can't believe I'm going to climb this.
I'm going to live in Tokyo from now on.
I'll do my best.
I'm a bit open-minded.
I feel like I'm outside.
My favorite four-letter idiom is
絶対絶命.
My mom says,
I want to be popular,
and I want to be in Tokyo.
My favorite phone is
餅巾着.
Rainbow bridge.
I feel like...
In my hometown, there is a very
beautiful bridge called Setohashi.
It's similar to that bridge, and it
feels like I'm close to it.
Wow!
We just arrived, so we don't know what's
going on.
Wow, we just arrived!
Wow, it's so beautiful!
Wow, it's so big!
It's different from Hiroshima.
Wow, it's so beautiful!
Is that a Budokan?
It's a Budokan.
I saw the sky tree.
There it is.
It's quite far.
What is Hiroshima like?
It's a city that values peace.
While maintaining peace,
nature is also important.
But to make it more developed,
to make it popular among young people,
the city is also beautiful.
It's big.
There is a shopping mall.
I didn't have a bright life in school
life.
I was in a student council.
I don't hate to be in public.
I thought I had a chance.
If I had a chance, I would like to be in
the student council.
If I pass the exam, I will be in the
student council.
I was so happy.
I'm here.
This is my first time to climb the Tokyo
Tower.
I'm ready to be a 4th grader.
I have a big goal.
I will challenge myself to reach it.
I will eat Monjayaki next.
Let's go!
I'm at Tsukishima Monjayaki Shopping
Street.
There are no Monjayaki shops in
Hiroshima.
There is no opportunity to eat.
Even if you make it at home,
you can't make it.
You have to do it on the iron plate.
So...
I thought it was a chance.
I was saying グー in the car.
Tsukishima Monja.
Do you write Tsukishima like this?
No, you write Komachi.
Oh, Komachi.
Tsukishima Komachi Monja.
You're wrong.
Sorry.
Excuse me.
Oh, it's so annoying.
I eat delicious food all the time.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
I'd like to have the most popular one.
Mochi-mete cheese-mon-chee?
Yes.
And I'd like some oyster butter.
Oyster butter?
Yes.
Can I mix the cod and cheese?
Take the soup stock out of the bowl.
Add the cheese.
Yes.
It will be a soft and fluffy rice ball.
It looks delicious.
Let's eat.
This is seafood.
Is it okay to grill it like this?
It's difficult.
It's delicious.
Let's eat.
The cheese and cod roe are rich and
mixed well.
It's very delicious.
It's very hot.
It's very different from Okonomiyaki.
This is Monja.
Cheers!
I'm going to eat Okonomiyaki.
Itadakimasu.
I am a soft girl and I am Big
development.
I want to be a girl who is loved by
everyone.
If I have any problems, I want to be an
idol who can cheer me up.
I made it.
I made it for the first time.
Let's eat.
It's different from the mentaiko mochi.
I can feel the thickness of the mochi.
I can feel the deliciousness of the
vegetables.
I ate a lot and I'm full.
Thank you for the meal.
I'm full.
large meat
I came here with my mother for the 4th
and final exam
I was able to pass the exam safely
I chose this place to convey my
gratitude
It's a good spot
Please subscribe to my channel.
Thank you for watching until the end.
Please subscribe to the channel if you
like.
Thank you very much.
It's a big one!
I'm Kirari Takeuchi.
Thank you for watching today.
I'll keep working hard, so please
support me.
Bye bye.
I'm Kirari Takeuchi, 16 years old from
Hiroshima prefecture.