I want to play my favorite song and tell
my friends that I want to do my best at
Hinata-zaka.
Is it written 49 degrees?
It's been a while since I came here.
This is the third time.
I came here with my high school friend.
I felt like I was breathing a lot when I
got off the train.
I felt like oxygen was circulating in my
body.
Tokyo is hard to live.
Shibuya was also hard.
I went to see my panel store when I was
in Tsutaya in Shibuya.
I felt sick because of the crowd.
I looked around the panel and came back.
Shall we climb?
Let's climb. It's pretty tough, but I
want to climb.
Do you want to run?
When I was a kid, I didn't go to the
Tottori Prefecture to play, so I
basically stayed at home.
I think I watched the videos of
Sakamichi the most.
I've never been to a live concert or a
handshake event, but I watched the music
videos on YouTube and the programs like
the construction of the Norizaka
Building.
My mother was a piano teacher, and I
played the piano since I was about 3 or
4 years old.
I've been practicing with her since we
practiced together.
I think we have similar personalities.
I still practice with her occasionally.
When I meet my mother's friends, they
tell me we have a lot in common.
I think my mother has been a big part of
my positive side.
She is usually kind and funny, but when
we have piano lessons, she gets angry
and cries a lot.
I didn't like her because it was hard to
practice with her.
But I love music most.
I enjoyed playing the piano in front of
people.
I did my best for that.
I think the time when I can concentrate
the most is when I'm playing music.
It's still the same.
Nothing has changed.
Wow! The sea!
It's so beautiful. It's been a while
since I saw the sea.
I've never thought about becoming an
idol because I love them so much.
I was cheering for Miho Tanabe when she
participated in the audition.
I was told that I was waiting for the
result.
I thought I'd take the audition because
of that word.
I never told my family that I had
submitted my application.
When I received a letter from my family
about the second trial,
my mother told me that I had received
the letter.
I told them that I had received the
letter.
最初はやっぱり大学にも入ったばっかだったですし、
反対されるかなと思ったんですけど、 結構応援してくれて、
その時はすごく胸が熱くなりました。
鳥取県出身、18歳平穂 穂です。
私は18年間、田んぼと畑しかないところで育ってきました。
So yesterday, I was breathing heavily
alone at Tokyo Station without knowing
the circle line.
From the second to the final test, I
drank all the pack mothwax in two
seconds.
I drank it desperately without thinking
about the reaction.
Today, I prepared a pack of mothwax
here, so I would like to drink it in two
seconds.
I drank it.
Please remember it as a person who is
not good at drinking.
Thank you very much.
The moment I got up,
First of all, my head turned white.
The moment I stood on the stage,
I was happy to see a different view.
I think the surprise was more selfish.
My first job was to get my name printed
on a uniform.
I was so happy about that.
I was like, wow, I'm an idol.
I've been collecting photos of myself,
so I felt weird about my photos.
Are you really selling them?
You are going to play the proper piano,
right?
What should I do?
I didn't have time to practice the
piano.
I had a blank sheet of paper, but I
didn't have much time to announce it.
At first, I was surprised.
But I wanted to make it a good one.
So I practiced.
It's the second day of practice.
I practiced for hours, so that my mother
wouldn't hear it.
The song I play on the piano is called
Joyful Love.
It's my mother's favorite song.
I think my mother listened to it a lot
when I was auditioning.
I play my favorite song.
I want to do my best on the stage.
I hope I can convey it to the audience.
I've been very energetic since I was
little.
I'm not good at running or exercising,
but I love dancing and singing.
I often go into my own world and perform
at home.
I always sang alone in the bath.
I'm still the same person.
I sing in front of everyone.
I love dancing.
I'm the type of person who gets nervous.
I've been on piano performances since I
was little.
I might have been nervous, but I'm the
type of person who can do it well when
it comes to the actual performance.
I'm full of anxiety.
I can't believe I'm going to enter the
entertainment industry.
I often hear that the world is tough.
But I'm not worried about that.
I don't know what will happen to me if I
go to a good restaurant because I left
the university.
But what I can do now is rare.
I'm not worried about that.
I want to do it in Hinatazaka, which I
wanted to enter.
I want to cheer for my family.
I've been to Koukaido many times since I
was little.
I was here at the Gassho Concert in
middle school, so I miss it very much.
I have no choice but to do it, so I hope
I can enjoy playing while producing the
results of my previous practice.
I was a little nervous.
But I'll do my best.
Thank you for coming today.
I have something to tell you, so I
called you here today.
I wrote a letter first, so please
listen.
To my mother, thank you for coming
today.
When I heard the song, I felt a sense of
joy and love.
I remember that I was told that I had
been given a second-hand test at home,
and that I had been given a envelope for
my stomach.
I thought I would be opposed to it as
soon as I started going to university.
When I heard the words, I almost cried.
My mother's way of speaking during the
audition was,
〈Let's think about it when we get the
chance〉.
I think it was a joke, but I think she
was able to overcome
the long audition and the training
period because of these words.
But I knew that my mother wanted me to
graduate from Konoma University
and get a job.
But I can do what I want to do.
I'm sorry for bothering you so much.
I'll do my best, so I want you to watch
me.
Today, I'm going to play my mother's
favorite song, Joyful Love, on the
piano.
Please listen to it.
《Joyful Love》
Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching.
I think my mother wanted me to go to
university and get a job.
So I thought a lot about it.
She said,
Did you get the job?
That was the first time.
After that, I told her that I could do
what I wanted to do.
She said she would support me if I
decided to do it.
I did.
I want women to be independent no matter
what they do.
It's natural to be strict in this world.
I want them to follow their own path.
I didn't think about what would happen
after I passed the exam.
As the exam progressed, I started to
want to become an idol.
I started to want to become a member of
Hinata Zaka 46.
I thought that I would definitely pass
the final exam and become a trainee.
I think there are many difficult things.
I will do my best.
Thank you.
DonP Show
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven,
eight, nine, ten.
Thank you for watching.
I want to go to university and give up
on it, but I want to give everything.
I will do my best as a member of the
Natazaka46, so please keep an eye on me.
I think I did everything I could, but I
also feel frustrated because I made some
mistakes.
I was able to perform on a big stage
today, but I want to perform on many
stages in the future and see many
different scenes.
I'm 19-year-old Hirao Honoka from
Tottori Prefecture.
I want to become an idol loved by many
people.