Ebichu's videos!
Ebichu Haru Tour goods!
What kind of goods are there?
This time, I will introduce each of them
one by one.
First, this drawer T-shirt.
We are wearing it now.
This is the smallest size.
You can wear it as many times as you
want.
What?
I can't wear it as many times as I want.
You can't wear it as many times as you
want.
It's a good size.
3700 yen.
How do you feel?
It's comfortable to wear. It's easy to
wear.
You can wear it in this season and in
the summer.
I'm wearing a white shirt today.
It's a cream color.
It's better to wear it than a white
T-shirt.
The back is also cute.
Each member color and the back logo are
written on it.
This T-shirt is also painted in the
member color.
This T-shirt and Ebichu's live
performance are not in the same place.
I think it's a T-shirt that will remain
in my memory.
I hope you can get it as a memory of the
2020 DRAWER.
Next is the DRAWER TURL.
This is also a T-shirt with the same
design.
It's smooth.
The fabric is very good.
I think it's cute.
It's cute.
What kind of life do you want to use
this for?
I want to decorate my room.
It's similar to clothes, so I want to
wear it with clothes.
It's cute.
Thank you for your viewing.
Do you have a good way to wrap it?
What?
What is it?
How do you do it?
It's good.
It's like a shrimp-shaped tube.
Like this.
It's a
NONOGA.
I can't put my hands out yet.
Please use this.
Please use it as a support.
Is it done?
I'm sorry.
Some members
have towels
in the production room.
I'm surprised.
I'm always sweating in the tour.
Everyone
is sweating
with the same towel
that we enjoyed the live performance
together.
Please use it
as a support.
Next,
we'll use this
enchantment light.
The pattern is
the same.
It's cute.
Green
orange
yellow
green
red
white
blue
and
red.
After the
9 members,
we still have
a few pens
so we're happy.
Please buy it.
If you can choose
any color,
what would it be?
I like
yellow.
I like yellow.
I like
light yellow.
yellow.
If I could choose,
I would like to buy
yellow.
What color would you like to buy?
I like
pink.
When I was in elementary school,
I was told that I liked pink.
I was happy
when I got pink.
I like white.
I like everything.
I think
everyone is curious about
what color they like.
I like the color
of the members.
I like white.
I think white is the right color.
I was scared.
I really hated purple.
I was like,
purple?
I was like that.
But I like the members
of the group.
So please take care of your health.
Please cheer for us with this 9 and 10.
Next, we would like to introduce the
10th Anniversary Band.
It's a member-colored hit band.
All 10 songs are out.
You can see everyone's love during the
live.
They help us with the old stuff.
It's like a history book.
Next, we would like to introduce the
Elytus Smartphone Straps.
It's cute.
The color is really cute.
It's like a rope.
It's really sturdy.
It's not thin, so it won't stick to your
neck.
It doesn't hurt, right?
It's a good thing.
I'm going to use this.
I'm losing my phone.
I've been losing it a lot lately.
I've been asked to search for various
products.
I'm going to use this from today.
I'm not going to use it because it's
old.
I put my smartphone on the bed at home.
I'm going to use it for a day.
It's not going to work even if I ring
the phone.
I'm tired.
I'm tired for a day.
I'm going to sleep.
You're always doing your best.
I'm going to sleep, so I'm going to
sleep.
I feel like the space of the music room
has been broken down.
I think I've been doing a lot of things.
I'm doing the same with Yuna.
Yuna is crying a lot.
I'm going to make a desk that's
surrounded by my desk.
I'm going to make a desk.
I'm living here, but I'm going to spread
it around here.
I can't say it because I'm tired.
Let's use this to organize things.
This is a table.
This is the table that I always use.
This is the table that other members
use.
Let's open this and assemble it.
The surroundings are cute.
Like this.
And there's a key holder for the strap.
And there's a name on the key holder.
Yes.
Like this.
It's cute.
You can wear it as a charm.
Or you can stand it up.
Yes.
It's cute. You can put it on your belly.
It's cute.
Let's do rock-paper-scissors.
Yes.
Ready?
Start!
Rock-paper-scissors!
Yes!
Go, go, go!
Rock-paper-scissors!
Yay!
Thank you so much!
Rock-paper-scissors!
Hiroto! Hurry up!
Go, go!
Rock-paper-scissors!
I'm a girl!
Oh, no!
I can't hold it!
Rock-paper-scissors!
Yay!
Where did you get it?
I got it!
Rock-paper-scissors!
Yay!
I won!
You can play with your own hands.
How about playing with your family
members?
You can get your favorite member for
1,500 yen.
Let's move on.
Next, we have two colors, elitite and
black.
The color is beige.
I got two colors, and they cost 3,800
yen.
It's so solid!
It's really solid.
It matches well.
It has pockets inside.
It's very useful.
It's very easy to use.
It's nice.
You might get confused when you buy it.
It's really solid.
It's so cute.
It's cute.
The main character of Egi-chu is not so
much.
It's useful for daily use.
You can use it for your daily life.
And...
It's done!
They have just released them but only on
sale at the moment.
Let me see this number...
This calendar..
The round salary, you get 3 sets for
under 4 years, one set including the
bill,
270 bucks.
Also, they also give us this picture
every time.
We're only adding the vamimation on the
cap, but now they sell them for over
5000 yen.
We always say our autographs together.
We're writing comments, so please write
them.
So, we've got all the goods.
It's really easy to use this time.
It's easy to use.
You can use it for daily use.
You can use it for live performances.
I'm looking forward to it.
Everyone uses it.
Please use it a lot.
Please use it.
We can go to many places, so we're
looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it.
We're waiting for you at the venue.
Bye bye.