Thank you for watching!
Nobita-san, please introduce the game!
Nobita-san, it's the White-Haired Bonen
Festival!
Congratulations!
Here you go!
This year's Bonen Festival is a
competition between Kimura-gun and
Shitara-gun.
The game tournament is a prize-giving
event.
The final battle is a one-on-one battle.
Asuka, who will graduate this time,
produced the Yokyo she wanted to see.
Please watch from the corner of the
Yokyo, which has become an old Bonen
Festival.
Let's go!
Stay tuned!
Thank you for watching!
What's that person?
What?
Hiroyuki-san
Please tell us about the sweets that are
popular in the gal
I've been expecting a lot of things on
Twitter
Actually, the sweets that are common in
France are called pudding
I wonder if everyone knows yet
It's a sweet and delicious guy
Everyone knows pudding.
That's your impression, isn't it?
Do you have such data?
It's similar.
It's very similar.
This is how to eat it, which was taught
to me by a German friend.
That expression.
There is a round tool called spoon.
It's easy to eat if you use it.
It seems to be very delicious.
Look this way.
I think pudding is popular, so please
try it.
Thank you.
It's good.
What is this world?
Asuka, what kind of order is this?
This is a gyaru style, and a Jirai-kei
style.
Jirai-kei make-up.
It's a Jirai-kei make-up that makes the
face red.
Hiroyuki was also popular.
Hiroyuki was similar.
It's funny.
It was similar.
It was very similar.
If it's for Asuka.
You've been studying a lot about facial
expressions, haven't you?
I've been studying a lot.
You are very good.
Did you order this?
Yes, I did.
Yes.
I wanted to make a gyaru and Hiroyuki.
That's good.
Iwamoto and Sakaguchi have a gyaru
element.
I see.
Iwamoto is still a cheerful gyaru.
He is cheerful, but sometimes he is
lazy.
Yes.
Sakaguchi is also very sick.
That girl is dangerous.
I studied a lot by watching TIKTOK.
I see.
That's good.
It's good that the three of us dance
together at the end.
Hiroyuki also danced.
I danced.
This is amazing.
It's funny.
Hayakawa was funny.
Shiori is a waste of acting.
That's right.
How was Shinjo?
It was the best.
How was Kou?
It was good.
He is a waste of acting.
He is not a good actor.
Let's play the next game.
Let's play the headphone game.
This is a game where you wear headphones
of the same volume and convey the words
of the topic with the movement of your
mouth.
The points will be given according to
the number of people who conveyed the
topic correctly.
First, the white team Himura-kun.
The game is for Himura-san to
participate.
What's wrong with Himura-san?
When you were here, you were a bit
nervous.
Himura-san's hands are cute.
Hands? Fingers?
His fingers are black.
They look delicious.
They look delicious?
They look like cream puffs.
They're cute.
Thank you.
Please do it.
Himura-san, you're disgusting.
What's that?
What's with those hands?
You were in a good mood.
You're disgusting.
You were cute even though you were
lying.
He can't hear you.
Let's start.
Osamu's pet is Medaka.
Osamu and Medaka?
Osamu and Medaka's pet is Medaka.
Please give us a lot of love.
A shark and a bed are glasses.
Thank you.
Osamu and Betto are...
I don't know that.
I know the first one.
I know that.
Betto is...
I don't know that.
Say it again.
Betto is...
You don't have to say the first one.
Say the next one.
I'm saying it.
Betto is glasses.
Yes, that's it.
What?
I know the first one.
Start.
Osamu's...
Osamu and...
Betto is...
Meikko is...
...hard.
Osamu is...
Osamu and...
Betto is...
...hard.
OK, that's it.
Ah, that's it.
Yes.
Osamu and...
Meiko?
Washio?
Meiko.
Mario?
One more time.
Osamu and...
Mario is...
Meiko.
Makino?
That's it.
What? What?
Let's start.
Osamu and Osanpon.
Mario.
Thank you.
Osamu and Osamu and Mario.
One more time.
Osamu and Mario.
Time's up!
I can't do this.
Let's see the answer.
This is quite interesting.
If you get most of the answers right,
you get 30 points.
What did you get?
Ototto Osanpoiko.
Osamu and Mario.
Osamu and Meiko.
Osamu's bed is hard.
Osamu's bed is glasses.
Please show us the answer.
Osamu's pet is Medaka.
It's a pet.
It's really close.
Osamu's pet is Medaka.
Will the red team be able to turn the
tables?
Let's start!
OK?
OK!
Let's do our best!
Ready, start!
Yumiki's zombie is...
Shah...
Da!
What's going on?
Cute!
Yumiki's...
Zombie...
Shironpi?
Tompa?
Tom...
Bi...
Rompi!
Time's up!
Cute!
This is cute!
Last one!
Yumiki's...
Umiko?
Rompa is...
Komama...
Ta!
Yumiki's...
Umipo!
Rompa is...
Komama...
Ta!
Ya!
Umido...
Sumino!
Konbanwa!
Ya!
Wa!
OK! OK!
Kimu!
Sumino!
Konbanwa!
Ya!
Wa!
OK! OK!
One more time!
Umido...
Sumino!
Konbanwa!
Sa!
Ya!
Time's up!
Let's go!
I don't know this one!
Look this way!
Sumino!
Beauty!
Sumino konbanwa!
Sumino!
Sumino konbanwa da!
Sukream, sukream!
Sukream!
Sumino!
Sumino konbanwa da!
Ya!
Sumino!
Sumi?
Sumino konbanwa!
Konbanwa!
Wa!
Sumino!
But it's not done!
Don't you know this one?!
Time's up!
Let's go, Asuka-chan!
In Tsutsui's...
Tsutsui's...
Tsutsui's country...
Good evening!
In Tsutsui's country...
Yukina...
Country...
No.
Yukina...
Good evening!
Tsuzui's tournament will now commence
It's not over yet!
It's over!
Let's start with Tsuzui
What do you think it is?
Tsuzui and Yukina are
childhood friends
Who is Yukina?
Asuka
Good evening in Tsuzui's country
Good evening
Wa!
I don't understand the meaning
You don't understand the meaning, right?
Good evening in Tsuzui's country
I think good evening is correct
I see
What will happen, Yamashita?
Sea and
Good evening
Ya!
I don't understand anything from here
You got the good evening right?
Yumiki's
Longpa is
Da!
Yumiki's longpa is da!
Please give us the answer
Yumiki's zombie is sha
It's totally different
Totally different
But Ayane's was a bit closer to the
sound
Himura's team got 9 points for conveying
the theme of Osamu to the third person
And the Shitara's team, who only got one
point for Yumiki, only got 3 points
Yumiki's team got 3 points
They've already passed the preliminaries
The national movie all-star is the dream
co-star
Preliminary corner
Enmo Takenama, Asuka Produce's
preliminary is finally the final
What kind of stage will they show us?
Let's watch the video!
You don't sing?
I'm not sure if I can do it, but I'll
try.
I'll try to do my best.
Thank you very much!
Amazing!
This is good. The quality is high.
The same as Kyoshin-Hei.
The same.
It's like a hospital.
It's the scene.
It's a touching scene.
She is kind.
It's really good.
The quality is good.
Is that Mei-chan?
Yes, it's Mei-chan.
I thought Yakubo came.
And Yoda.
Yoda is good.
I couldn't sing because I was in the pot
during the rehearsal.
I'm glad I could sing.
And Yubaba.
Akimoto is good.
I practiced this song a lot in the bath
after the FNS festival.
What are you doing?
It suits you.
There is a flower.
This is a Christmas tree.
It's an ornament.
It's good to make it by hand.
This quality is good.
Did you order this at Ghibli?
Each Yakumo.
It's right.
Ume, this is me.
I didn't say I wanted to do it.
You said it.
You gave me a flower.
I thought it was bad.
Ume did it.
I can only do it.
You did it well.
I'm jealous.
Stop it.
I made it interesting.
Yamashita, it's good.
It's good.
It's bad.
It's like a brown sweater and sandals.
It's good.
It's cheap.
The result is.
It was a great event.
I don't know what is going on.
I don't care about the result.
Everyone is winning.
The winning team is the winner.
Who won?
The winner is.
Kimura Kondo.
Thank you!
And the team that won this time is...
Is it this?
This is...
This is it.
The...
This is the frog that Asuka drew.
Himura-san drew this jigsaw puzzle for
10 people.
Asuka-chan wanted this.
I wanted it.
This is difficult.
This jigsaw puzzle is all white except
for this part.
This is very difficult.
I want to decorate this.
I made 10 pieces, but there are only 10
pieces in this world.
I'll definitely decorate this.
The members of Nuginaka are...
The last message from Asuka, who has
completed 11 years of activities.
Asuka, you are the last one to complete
the recording today.
I'm getting lonely.
I'm finally here.
Do you have any memories of this
program?
I traveled alone on this program.
I went to Myanmar.
I was able to see the whole process of
my growth.
You did things you've never done before.
I've grown as a person.
I was able to see it and watch it.
It was a lot of fun.
Please say a word to the fans who
watched the program.
I was able to show everything I had in
my teens on this program.
I'm sure some people hated it, but I'm
sure some people are the opposite.
That startled me.
Wow...
Everyone in the group at Nobizaka is
great.
You can only see what you really feel...
This message has to reach the people who
are watching
Please subscribe to my channel.
I hope the staff will feel the love and
support they give us through the screen.
I hope you will continue to watch over
us warmly.
Thank you.
Before you give me the bouquet, I heard
that you were naming all the members.
I heard that you were thinking about us.
Is that okay?
I thought about it.
I'm glad.
You said you wanted it.
You thought about it.
Which one do you want to go first?
Then I'll go first.
I'll go first.
It's a little awkward.
It's not like that.
Can I have it?
Mr. Sitara is a man who is good at
language, life, and magic.
What do you mean?
Isn't it amazing?
Mr. Sitara is like Kaiser.
He's a radio host.
He's a man who's good at language.
There are many members who have given
their lives to the words of Mr. Sitara.
I haven't done it yet, but when I was
doing the preliminary announcement in
the studio, he said something very warm.
When I was actually an underdog, I got
some courage.
Magic is scary sometimes.
It's scary?
It's scary sometimes.
It's like magic.
It changes the atmosphere of the place.
It makes me happy.
It's like magic.
I'm happy.
You're praising me a lot.
Then, I'll give you a bouquet.
What?
Himura-san.
What should I say?
Himura-san says,
God is over the ground.
Wait a minute.
It's God.
God is over the ground.
I'm getting off.
I'm a God.
I think you're a God.
It's like the last of Hononoke Himen.
What are you talking about?
Tell me more.
Himura-san is...
He's...
He's so strong.
He's doing a variety show.
He's not running to something.
He's walking slowly.
He's heading for his destination.
He looks big.
He's not fat.
He's not walking to a soba restaurant.
I can't hear anything else.
He's walking slowly.
He's not having a purpose.
Asuka, you did it.
No, I didn't.
But, he's not a normal creature.
I think he's a God.
I think it's strange if he's not a God.
You're laughing.
When I'm told that I'm a normal human,
I feel a little desperate.
What do you mean?
I feel a little desperate at the end.
Thank you for everything.
Thank you.
Keep up the good work.
Please subscribe to our channel.
11th year birthday live, applause!
B-Q News!
The first scene is B-Q News.
Everyone, let's have a good time.
Thank you for watching!
What?
It's light.
Weird face.
What is weird face?
I don't like it.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I did my best.
Bye bye.