This episode of Ebichu Tastas is a
special edition!
It's a special episode!
The three members will be completely
absorbed in the live performance!
We are Ebichu!
Let's go!
Ebichu!
Ebichu Tastas, start!
Ebichu Tastas
Add various things to private Ebisu
Middle School!
Ebisu Middle School!
What is this time? Is it a self-shoot
special?
Yes
Self-shoot?
It is a self-shoot
What is a self-shoot?
Self-shoot is a second time in the past
This is the third time
There is an event that the members want
to do and produce live
In this time, in the order of Hina and
Rina Aika
I did three performances
Yes, self-shoot is
The Ebi-Chuu members themselves become
producers
Of course, the configuration of the live
Until the set list and costumes
It is a live that you can think of
everything yourself
Until now, Mayama, Yasumoto, Hoshina
became producers
And self-shoot has been done
And this time, the third time
Kashiwagi, Matsuno, Hirota will produce
live
First of all, Kashiwagi producer who
produced the first day
What is the highlight and VTR?
Self-shoot produced by Kashiwagi
I thought it would be fun
It became a live like this
Please
October 9th
New Tokyo
Here, self-shoot of Kashiwagi producer
is carried out
At the venue just before the show
Rehearsal was carried out
Yes
Then, the members suddenly ran to the
second floor
What is the live performance that
Kashiwagi thought?
The day before the show
Kashiwagi told the members and staff the
performance
I also exchanged with the family
I was the second person to put the Ebi-
Chuu membership number
I thought I would go to the customer's
house
I don't know if the customer's hand and
eye contact
I don't know, but I thought that the
customer would choose the encore
The live performance that Kashiwagi
thought
Touching with the family
Here is the production plan
A bold production to touch with the fans
What kind of live will it be?
Kashiwagi Produce, next week, start
Thank you for watching!
I want to run away
I'm sure I can make my dream come true
Go! Yashun Masutou Ayaka!
MC Tanto Ayaka!
What's with the crowd?
Still jumping out, the producer of the
shadow of the Oto Line!
No.6 Hirota Aika
I love the train, R.T.R.
I'm a magical mascot
What is this? Is this really a dream?
I'm half-asleep, but I'm still sleepy!
Number 7, Hoshinamire
Starry sky, shining starry sky
Singing happily, the starry sky of
Ebitsu
Born to be idol, Hoshinamire
Number 7, Hoshinamire
Number 9, Rina Matsuno
I've grown about one foot in the air
I want to deliver more songs, until my
voice continues
Number 11, Kobayashi Kaho
I like the sound of the fan
The laughter is blowing, number 11
I want to deliver more songs, until my
voice continues
No.12 Nakayama Riko
I want to eat chocolate again
I love cherries
I love you too
I don't know what to say
It's not a joke, it's a joke, hey yo!
Let's make a rainbow with you
One more time!
Next time, let's go to the night sky
Let's grab the
President Cho's
Thank you for watching!
T guys for real
ーC Mystery is about to startー
ーThe numbers are shown who you choseー
What's it?
What is that?
It's TES Thank you
After that, the song of the Kashiogi
Select continues.
And...
I'd like you to decide the encore.
Nice!
I'm making a heart for you.
Please.
It's so cute.
I love you all.
When I'm unhappy, snive oni
It'll never be forgiven
A message of praise
You're gonna be ignored
Thank you for your hard work.
And the live performance is over.
How was it?
At first, I was wondering what would
happen.
But everyone enjoyed it and did it.
I think I was able to do what I wanted.
Thank you for your hard work.
Next is producer Matsu
I did what I wanted to do
It was fun, so I hope you can enjoy it
Please watch
October 10th
Thank you
How is it?
I'm nervous, but I'm full of things
today
I'm a little nervous, but I'll do my
best
What kind of live will Matsu produce?
Two days before the live
Matsu is meeting with the staff
I'm here
The concept this time is EGC
Ebi's Girls Collection
I want to make it like a parody of Tokyo
Girls Collection
Like a girlfriend who models, Matsu's
theme is fashion show
Here is the production plan
Live in private clothes for the first
time in Ebi
What kind of stage will it be?
Matsu's Produce, start next week
Actually, this park is a place where
Hoshina is located
Matsu is waiting there
I'm wearing Mirei's clothes with the
feeling that Mirei is there
I will do my best
רוצ OS avez mention o
tweebrak
yui
Thank you for watching!
Popo Popochi, Joji, Kishi, Arigatou!
Popo Popochi!
And Munecune song of Matsuno Select
I'm so nervous I can't move
I want to forget you
I fell in love with you
I want to tell you but I'm afraid of
this cowardly feeling
Goodbye, spring is coming
I can't see you anymore
I can't say this feeling I told you
I'm really lonely, look, my tears are
overflowing
The live show is over.
Thank you for your hard work.
I was relieved.
I enjoyed it.
I hope the family will enjoy it.
I'm happy.
The game project has begun.
They have played the demo version of the
game.
The project has been going on.
The new development tonight.
It's been a while.
The game is over.
If you open this treasure chest, be
careful of the monster
What kind of monster is it?
It's here
Hello
The people who came here are Uemoto and
Shibano who are making games for shrimp
What is their goal for this time?
I had a lot of ideas from everyone
before and I was developing it
But the production has progressed a lot,
so I came to report the mid-term
Thank you
Since the production of the game has
progressed, it seems that they will show
something
What is it?
First, please look at this
It's really a game
It's a game
The prototype version of the shrimp game
is completed
Moreover, it was a popular game from the
shrimp team
Now, he will explain how to play the
game
First, pull the green thing in the
middle
Then, release it towards the middle
character
Then, it will fall a lot and become a
gauge and attack the enemy
This is cute
It's amazing
It's a game
In addition, he was very excited before
the prototype version of the game
Before I actually played it, I made 8
characters
This is it
The character design of the shrimp team
members will be announced
The last one is producer Hirota
I like idols myself
I think that I can share it with people
who like idols
Please see
What is the idol live that Hirota likes
idols?
This time, I want to make it a
performance of the idols
I want to make it based on the idol's
live
I want to make it with a lot of
interesting things that I can think of
Actually, Hirota made a script himself
for self-study
This is the script.
The title is KAMI LIVE.
Here is the production plan written on
the script.
In order to entertain the family, Hirota
prepared 400 autographs.
Two days before the live, the members
wrote their autographs one by one.
And then...
The first song I was most particular
about was...
There is a song called KAMISAMA NO
YUUTORU.
I think this song was heard live by
someone.
It's a song from a long time ago that I
wonder if there are still people in the
Ebichu family.
But that song was already from the
beginning.
When the actual show was made, I decided
that I would definitely put this song
in.
I'm so happy that my wish will come
true.
Hirota wanted to put this song on the
set list.
KAMISAMA NO YUUTORU.
A song that is full of idol-like
character that is full of Hiroto.
It was a song that the Ebichu unit sang.
But with the hope of Hirota, all the
members sang it.
And then the show began.
Hirota Produce KAMI LIVE START!
KAMI LIVE! Miracle Magical Project!
Music Start!
KAMI LIVE!
YOU'LL T
Limit
La la la
I can't stop
Oh my love
Come on, let's stop
Let's be honest with love
La la la
Come on, let's stop
Oh my love
The third day of Monday is more exciting
than the class
When the Live.
Bye bye bye!
Love me, love me, smile me, smile me,
baby
If you're crying,
I'll chase after the light and run to
you
Love me, love me, smile me, smile me,
baby
With your smile,
I can make the world, too
I think I was able to do a lot of things
that I wanted to do better than I did
before.
But the first day was no good.
Today was really fun.
Thank you.
Next time, we will analyze the truth of
Ebichu and Tasutas.
When experts analyze Ebichu and Tasutas,
the unexpected side of the members is
revealed.
How do you make the person in front of
you?
And, to those who missed Ebichu and
Tasutas, we will give you a reward.
On the StarLust channel, Ebichu and
Tasutas is being popularly distributed
on the low-level video distribution
site.
I will try to find it.
I can't find it from the heart.
That scene is available for 400 yen per
month.
In addition, there are many exclusive
videos of the unreleased videos.
Now?
For details, search on the StarLust
channel.
This program was provided by the sponsor
you are watching.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye.