Thank you for watching.
The new members of Ebi-Chu, Emma and
Yuna
They were having a full-fledged lesson
for their first live performance on
December 17
However
The broken heart, heart, heart, I'm
waiting for you
I don't remember
This is really hard
I'm really thinking about how many times
I'm going to get angry
Winner of last episode
music Gilur
October 1
Sakura and Yuna have formed the new
members
Just 2 months and a half
Their first stage was decided
Lets cheer
Thank you
That is difficult
Many lessons has already begin
Hina-chan came to the lesson
She is the boss
She was very kind
She was not bossy
They are not attracted to the guidance
of staff
They are happy with smiles
But
She was not bossy
They call the boss already
Our seniors said that we should dance
big
We have to dance big to be born
I think we should do our best
They have a goal
They are motivated by the special lesson
for the new members
Let's start!
Thank you for your cooperation
Thank you
The lesson for the new members is about
singing
The teacher who has been supporting the
singing voice of Ebichu for many years,
Ms. Emiko
She has been watching the singing voice
of the two members from the audition
Let's sing the rhythm of the song
Please subscribe to my channel.
Subscribe
I'm going to do K-Hi-Oh.
This is something everyone does, so I'll
do K-Hi-Oh.
I don't remember the number of times I
did it.
I'll do it properly.
Ayame and Aiko.
Please don't forget me.
Prince.
K-Hi-Oh.
It's Radio 3.
If you learn foundation jużandly, thank
you.
Thanks for watching
Going JAPAN
Meagoo practicing
Priceage use
After the rehearsal
discomfort
senνο
you don't have to have anything
I'd like to I'm really in a lot of
trouble low
it's really hard
The two will be on stage in about two
months.
They will perform their songs in a
number of different songs as members of
Shirito Ebisu Junior High School.
And, as a professional artist, they were
asked to do more than anything.
They always make the voice sound. A-I-U-
E-O.
When you hear the word A-I-U-E-O, you
will think it's A-I-U-E-O or A-I-U-E-O.
In A-I-U-E-O, there are 6,000 people in
the event hall. Even if the speaker
comes out, the 6,000 people can't hear
the voice.
So, you have to say A-I-U-E-O properly.
And, you have to make the sound go out
to the back of your nose.
A-I-U-E-O.
And, you have to make the sound go out
to the back of your head.
A-I-U-E-O.
If you don't do that, you won't be able
to hear the sound.
So, Emma, you have to make the sound go
out to the back of your head.
And, you have to make the sound go out
to the back of your head.
Yuna, you have to make the sound go out
Make it a little thicker.
Make it a little more clear.
That's what we're going to do until
December.
The first live performance that the two
will perform is...
《NARASUYO》
The MAKUHARI MESSE event hall is proud
of its 6,500 people
In front of a large audience, the stage
is not only difficult to sing
but also requires professionalism
Niii
Its because of the gap of Nii.
Don't pretend that you feel we sing out
loud another.
Instead of não snogido, you vocalize
who's singing their heart out.
Say new Sri and tou yourselves.
Niiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiii
So soon
увеличidad
We were telling shampoo where to5 is
necesario.
It was right.
If this is wrong, use the restroom to
wash your face in the bathroom.
Stop.
The song starts off square like this.
That's good.
Good.
Make sure to make it sound.
Repeat this more than 50 times.
, but it still doesn't work.
It's totally out of place.
It's not at all the same.
Nn!
Yes.
Repeat.
She stops crying and natural admires
every move.
Nn!
Yes, yes, yes.
Nn! Nn!
That's it. Let's go.
And Yuna's singing voice has a weakness.
Yuna's voice is good to sound, but the
lower part of the voice that supports it
is weak.
So, I think it's better to do it with
the voice of the mouth than the voice of
the mouth.
I want to sing between the cheeks.
Oh!
Basically, you have to go down and
down....
I think people who say like this, you
have to go up and down.
Yuna, give me the voice.
Little dance
I want to sing with that voice.
The lesson continued for three hours.
The teacher ended the lesson with harsh
words.
Until the November release, you have to
think about the lyrics, the song, the
choreography, and you can't catch up.
So, please look at the notes and
practice over and over again.
Please practice with concentration.
Please learn the work.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
After the lesson.
There are many things that I haven't
done yet, and there are many challenges.
It's hard, but there are many fun
things, so I will do my best.
I was told that it would not reach 6,000
or 7,000 people in front of the
public, so I wanted to make sure that
the air would not leak.
I wanted to make sure that the air would
not leak.
I have about two months left, so I want
to show a good performance with a good
dance and a good song.
Thank you for watching. Please subscribe
to the channel.
Next time, Yuna and I will visit the
senior members' stages for the first
time.