Ebichu Tastas has started!
Tonight, they will deliver a big show
from a big house
They are excited at a mysterious huge
facility
The first guest of the day is a big fan
of Ebichu Tastas
Bingo! Happy birthday!
To you, middle schooler!
Elementary schoolers
Now it's time for the final exam!
Bingo! Happy birthday!
Until the end of the world!
High schoolers
And high schoolers
Let's go!
Never ending
Bingo! Happy birthday!
Add many things to your private Ebisu
junior high!
Ebisu Justus!
This program is brought to you by the
following sponsors.
I, Masu, will be the MC for this show.
Thank you.
What is the theme of today's show?
It's a very bright and sunny day,
but I'll do my best to be as bright as
the sun.
Thank you.
Is that your task?
My task?
It's a personal task.
I see.
Are you okay?
I'm worried about you.
What are you waiting for?
Are you sleepy?
It's very bright.
You're very bright today.
What is the theme of today's show?
What is it?
The theme of today's show is...
It's a big park.
Big park.
What is a big park?
The big park is here.
Is it a parking lot?
I don't know because there is only a
parking lot.
The big park is a place to play.
Do you know what Hoshino is?
I know.
I know something.
Have you been here before?
Who has been here?
Have you been to Hoshino-yama at Kashua-
ge-matsu?
What did you come here for?
We came to shoot the OPV of Saitama
Super Arena.
OPV?
We came here to introduce ourselves
before the show.
Is it like an opening video?
Is that what OPV is?
It's OPAPI.
The opening video of Saitama Super Arena
was shot here.
Mayama, Hoshino, Tashiwagi, and Matsuno
participated in the shooting.
What kind of facility is it?
What is the name of the place where you
have been to?
It's a place where rich people run.
Are you talking about the management?
It's a dream wonderland.
It's a dream wonderland run by rich
people.
Let's go to the dream wonderland.
It's amazing.
It's like an American park.
Wait a minute.
It's a basketball player.
That's too much.
What is that person?
Is that KAIKI?
Everyone, I was waiting for you.
Please decide the shot once.
Of course.
Please look at it.
M-Z 2016
Welcome!
No, it's not welcome
The member who still doesn't know where
to stand, the member who is good at TAS-
TAS, Kaiki Ogata
Kaiki-san, according to the rumors, you
are a very serious person
So this time, you came to Daiken in
advance and took a lot of materials
That's right
Of course
It seems that you have looked into it
What is Daiken?
This is the amusement park that
Ichikawa-shi represents
Giant amusement park
Amusement park?
I think the American style and kanji are
not matched.
Is that so?
What does the giant amusement park mean?
The meaning?
Let's think about the meaning together.
You don't know?
Let's think about it together.
Without much information, they go inside
the giant amusement park.
This is my favorite.
It's a big amusement park.
It looks like a fun game.
I want to play this.
Please subscribe to our channel.
This is Daikei-en amusement park in
Chiba prefecture.
There are game centers, baseball
stadiums, and karaoke boxes in this huge
place.
This is a 24-hour business, the
Wonderland of dreams.
Matsuno-san, what are you going to do
here?
What are you going to do?
I know!
Today, we will be divided into two teams
and battle!
So, this is the game battle!
The teams are here!
The people who have come and the people
who haven't will be divided into two
teams and the small team will also
participate.
I would like to ask you about your
enthusiasm for the match.
Matsuno team, how is your enthusiasm?
These two are good at games.
I have such a talent.
You are good at games!
I'm not good at games.
I don't like to lose.
I know Daiken.
I have no advantage.
I don't lose.
Team Yasumoto, who doesn't know Daiken,
please give us your enthusiasm.
Go!
Wait a minute. Why do you say Mayama?
It doesn't matter. This is different.
But this game is more fun.
Let's go!
Go!
It doesn't matter from here.
Why did you say Kaiki-san is also a
magician?
It's not a good thing.
By the way, the winning team will
receive a luxurious prize.
The prize is here!
The winner team will get a new original
jumper
Look at the back
Original jumper
Who is it?
Whose face is this?
The manager, Mr. Takahashi
He is rich
He is a commuter
Please use it
Let's start the game battle
The first game is here
Let's play this
The famous sumo game
It's a compact but a famous one
So, let's start the battle with a snow
game!
One representative of each team will
challenge a snow game!
Ok, so first, the Matt team! Who will go
first?
I will go first!
Matsuno, you will go first? Why?
I was told by Ogata-san to show the
spirit of the two-legged race.
Today is the two-legged race.
That's right.
Ok, the Yasumoto team! Who will go
first?
Yes!
Yasumoto will go first! Why?
Because I'm a rock!
The first battle is Matsuno vs Yasumoto!
Everyone, step on the snow!
Oh, that's good!
That's good!
That's a good one!
But it's kind of small.
That's right. It's a good game in terms
of size.
That's good, Matsuno!
Matsuno will challenge!
It hasn't started yet!
It's moving!
Did you win?
What?
It's moving!
It seems that he won
What are you doing?
I don't know
Can I ask you something?
If it's too far, I can't see anything
I thought it would move more
The distance is this much
Did you win the result?
Yes
Matsuno won
Next, Yasumoto challenges
I'm happy
Yasumoto, you can do it
Let her do it
Good
You can do it
Nice
Go
You can do it
Good
Yasumoto
You can do it
I won
Matsuno won
Well, this is...
I won, but I don't feel like I won at
all
I'm happy
In the end, the game ended without
knowing the result
Anyway, both of them won, so they got 50
points
The next game is this one, the body
sight game
The second battle is the body sight game
In 30 seconds, press the button that
glows one by one to compete for the body
sight
If you are in your teens, 37 points or
more will be the standard score
One representative from each team will
challenge
Who will go first?
Mayamo, who will go first?
The reason is?
The reason is? It seems fun
I was playing soccer, so I thought I had
a reflex
I see, you have a reflex for soccer
I thought so
I see, I understand
Who will go first?
What is it, Sakurai?
The first is...
It's not decided yet
Mayamo, Mayamo, Mayamo
Mayamo, you are alone
Mayamo, what? You want to enter this
team from the beginning
You are going to enter the soccer team
And the Yasumoto team is decided to go
to Nakayama
I have done it before
I have done it once
You are experienced
I am experienced but I couldn't do it
once
Then why Nakayama?
You have to win
The oldest in the team, Mayama VS The
youngest, Nakayama
Mayama is the first. Can she beat
Nakayama's youth with the skills she
learned in soccer?
3, 2, 1, start!
Nakayama is the first. Can she beat
Nakayama's youth with the skills she
learned in soccer?
Nakayama is the first to beat Nakayama's
youth with the skills she learned in
soccer.
Nakayama is the first to beat Nakayama's
youth with the skills she learned in
soccer.
Mayama's score is only 19 points
Her body sight is over 60 years old
She is in her 48th year of middle school
It's difficult
Mayama, try it
I see
Next, the Kesson team
Mayama
Go, Mayama
Go for it
Next, the youngest, 14 years old,
Nakayama
It's easy
Nakayama, let's go
3, 2, 1
Go
Go, Nakayama
I'm not doing it.
Nakayama also got 19 points, just like
Mayama.
In other words, her body has a history
of more than 60 years.
Nakayama, how was it?
It was fun. I was going like this.
You were wrong.
You were going like this.
So, the team got a draw for a low-level
battle.
No team score.
By the way, who is the most athletic
among the members?
Matsuno
Matsuno?
I heard you are a big fat person
Oh my god
I'm so big fat
How do you feel?
I can move around in a place where there
is nothing
And I'm big fat in the whole movement
The whole movement
Certainly, today is the opening shooting
day
Everyone is gathered, but Matsuno walks
slowly
Everyone is running, gathering, and
Matsuno
I don't want to do something that is
useless
It's useless
Everyone is gathered
It doesn't matter if you play this game,
you are already in your 60s
Well, let's go
What are you talking about?
Let's go
Please go
Matsuno also challenges the dynamic
eyesight game
3, 2, 1, start
The result of the shock is
test the appendectomy ofを
ab 베  habits 11 noise
are in the body
I do not
Start!
Well done Good De had Cat power
Da Haut10
technology
tue
Thank you for watching!
The highest score ever
It's the same as the game we played
before
It was about to break
Amazing
This is the highest score ever
Yay
Amazing
Matsuno got the highest score
But her physical ability is over 40
years old
That's it. original
I want to go out.
Everyone, here it is.
What is it?
It says it's a big system.
Please come in here.
It's like a festival.
There's a goldfish.
It's a goldfish rescue.
That's great.
A goldfish rescue battle.
The third battle is a goldfish rescue.
Everyone, here it is.
It's a competition.
How many goldfish can you rescue in one
minute?
Each team will compete.
The first is the Matsuno team.
Ready, start.
What if you break your voice?
Good luck.
Everyone is broken in an instant.
At that moment, Mayama said...
I'm sorry.
Mayama is gone.
10 seconds left.
Everyone, do your best.
You can't stop.
Mayama is amazing.
End.
Everyone is broken.
2 of them. 2 of them.
Mayama got 2 of them.
Amazing.
Amazing, Mayama.
As a result, Matsuno team only got 2
Mayama.
Now, this is Yasumoto team.
Next, we are Yasumoto team.
There is something I want to say.
If goldfish is put in the orange world,
it will be surprised.
Hey, you are going to go again.
Right?
If goldfish is put in the green world,
the world will change.
It's a story of goldfish.
What should I do?
I'll ask the director later.
Listen to me.
One minute.
Come on.
Listen to me.
It's wet.
Good luck.
10 seconds.
One goldfish.
Put water in it.
Kaho, Kaho, you're in trouble.
Kaho, Kaho.
The goldfish is torn.
Amazing
So, the race is over
The result is one
Matsuno team wins
However
This is really big
Please give me a lot of points
This is the one I mentioned before
The small one is the second one
Small
This is certainly a big one
This is special
Let's give them the same score
So, the challenge continues.
The challenge starts with the Yasumoto
team.
First, we will go to the Yasumoto team.
Ready, start!
Hey, hey!
What's that?
In 5 seconds!
Nakayama is out in 5 seconds.
What?
In 5 seconds!
And next to him, Yasumoto and Hirota
also fall
In the meantime, Chuei...
He's getting it!
He got one!
Awesome!
As a result, there are 2 Chuei!
Somehow, Chuei managed to save 2 Chuei
Next, the Matsuno team's challenge
The Matsuno team, ready, start!
Amazing!
Ah!
The bridge is broken!
Bye bye!
On the other hand, Matsuno is acting
suspiciously
Then...
Oh! Matsuno is going too!
Furthermore...
He gave up!
He's going to lose!
Wait! This is scary!
Kashiwagi too!
He's going to lose!
Matsuno is amazing!
Oh, I got it!
That was unexpected!
All of a sudden!
As the Yasumoto team stands up...
As a result, Kashiwagi got one, Ogata
got three, and Matsuno got four.
They got a lot of them!
Team Katsunoki won!
It's my first time to win this much!
Katsunoki, you suddenly woke up!
I'm so happy!
How are you feeling?
It's my first time to win this much!
How did you do it?
I was sleeping on the top of the car all
the time.
I thought I was going to win, so I got
up.
Ms. Kaiki, you're done.
But I didn't lose.
Please let me win the big one.
I see.
Ms. Kaiki hasn't lost yet.
I thought you were going to drink it.
I'm scared.
The third battle is the victory of the
Matsuno team.
The final score is 50 points.
So, if you add a large circle in the
middle of the shrimp,
the result is 20 point username.
Next episode game battle will be again
later half part.
All the members will thredБG 이건택고から
ды멤버
그런데ish
All the KeepBee's members will be
watched.
That is just kidding.
yes
No,
no,
it is out.
Like
tik
And
I can't go
Mayama is not good
What is it?
Emergency report
The audition of the Ebitiu student
Sakura Ebi's is finally over
Who was chosen by the 10,000 applicants?
Next week, the 4 people who passed the
audition will be announced
Please look forward to it
This program was provided by the sponsor
you are watching
Thank you for watching!