Once upon a time, there was a very
ordinary princess.
The princess in the picture book is a
very beautiful and unreasonable bully.
She is an image of a strong woman who
has been struggling.
This princess does not have a mean
mother or sister.
She is not trapped on a tower or can not
use magic of ice.
She is living a good life.
This is a story of a princess who
admires a princess in a picture book.
Well, I'll go for a walk.
The princess said so and went for a
walk.
Then, a sparrow flew near.
In such a case, it is a standard
practice for the princess to talk to the
sparrow.
Okay, sparrow, let's talk. Come here.
Chunchun.
Baza baza baza baza.
The princess said goodbye to the sparrow
and went for a walk.
The princess went to the rose.
Suddenly, she saw a small hut.
The princess went into the hut.
There were three or four dwarfs in the
hut.
Isn't this a group of seven?
Three or four is a little bit.
No, no, no. Is that so?
What? Well, I don't know.
What is this person doing here?
I thought so. What is this person?
Well, I don't know.
By the way, what should I call you?
What?
He asked my name.
Should I say my name honestly?
Isn't it a little scary?
What should I do?
Is it safer to keep it a secret?
No, it's okay.
But I'm scared to be told that.
Then, just in case, I'll keep it a
secret.
I don't look like a bad person, though.
What?
My name is...
M-Mori.
I'm...
Sugimoto.
I'm Arai.
I'm Tapioka.
You all have normal names.
When a princess and a little dwarf are
in trouble, a suspicious old lady comes
to visit.
I'm sorry.
Yes, who is it?
Hello.
Oh, is this the flow of Shiraiki-hime?
No way.
Miss, how about a poisonous apple?
Oh, I made a mistake.
How about an apple?
Shiraiki-hime is here!
I said poisonous apple.
Did you say poisonous apple?
I said it clearly.
I made a mistake.
Is it a bad apple?
It's bad.
Please withdraw.
I'm sorry to bother you.
The old woman left as if nothing had
happened.
You are...
Are you a person who is after life?
No, I'm not doing anything that could be
targeted.
Oh, I'm a little scared.
There must be something about that
person.
I'm glad I didn't say my real name.
Well, I don't know what's going on, so
be careful.
Thank you.
The princess walked around the room.
Then she found a cart.
I found a shell and even rotten flesh.
It's a cart! Speaking of a cart, it's
Princess Ibara!
I'm sure the needle is stuck and you can
cast a curse that will sleep for 100
years!
And the curse is broken by the prince's
kiss! What a romantic story!
It's wonderful!
When I was touching the cart, by chance,
really by chance, the needle got stuck
in my finger.
Ouch! The needle got stuck!
Maybe I'm the Ibarahime?
Okay, let's sleep.
And so she started sleeping on the bed.
What's with this person? It's scary!
I can't use this bed anymore.
It's a perfect bed, isn't it? That's
impossible.
Excuse me, I'm sorry. I'm in trouble if
I fall asleep suddenly.
Hey!
The princess didn't seem to wake up at
all.
The little one was in a lot of trouble.
Shouldn't we call someone?
What should we do?
It's a problem if she sleeps all the
time.
Let's go find her.
The little one went to find someone.
The princess is sleeping soundly.
Three hours later, the little one
brought the servant to the mansion.
Oh, the princess is here.
I've been looking for you.
Princess, please wake up.
He's not waking up at all.
Did he sleep through the night?
Please wake up.
Prince?
Where's the prince?
He's not here.
What are you talking about, princess?
What?
Oh, I see. I guess I don't need to.
It's time for dinner. Let's go back to
the mansion.
Yeah, I'm hungry.
Mori-san, Sugimoto-san, Arai-san,
Tapioca-san.
I'm sorry for the sudden visit. Thank
you for coming.
No problem.
I don't know why, but I'm glad you came.
You're right.
I didn't get to touch any tapioca.
The princess said goodbye to the little
man and went back to the mansion.
Goodbye!
Then the princess woke up in the morning
as usual, ate three meals and went to
bed.
What was the poisonous apple after all?
Scary!
Happily ever after!
The end.