Hello, I'm Endo Sakura.
Happy New Year!
I'm going to upload my first walk of the
year video.
Is it okay to say that it's my first
time?
I'm still very nervous.
Where are you now?
We'll celebrate your first warm we love
sprouts
Can you see this?
This is Saga Arashiyama
So I'm in Kyoto
I like Kyoto, I wanted to come, I'm glad
Today I walked around Arashiyama
I think I'll wear a kimono and it won't
be different from usual
I'm sorry, I think it will be a loose
video. Let's go
I'm a little hungry.
I want to eat, but it's cold.
It's a little cold.
It's a cold cream.
It looks delicious.
It's cold.
It's a soft cream.
It looks delicious.
Actually, this is the first video of the
new year,
but I'm shooting in December.
It's December now.
It's December.
It looks delicious.
I want to eat something.
Is there anything?
I want to eat Manju.
I love Japanese sweets.
Butter candy.
I found a Yarabimochi.
I will eat it.
Thank you for waiting.
Thank you.
I bought it.
I will walk slowly.
I will walk for a while to find a place
to sit and eat.
There are a lot of gachas.
Cute.
I will make a miniature figure of
Arashiama's scenery.
Please subscribe to my channel.
It's a little...
It's so attractive.
Oh, wait, wait.
Wait, wait.
Bath...
Do you have a bath memory?
What?
It's a little cute.
Thank you for watching.
There are many people.
There is croquette.
Can I buy this?
I would like to have one Kyoto beef
croquette.
Thank you.
OK.
I changed my clothes.
I changed my clothes, so I eat.
It's dangerous.
Thank you.
I'm so happy.
It's so good.
I love croquettes.
I'm done.
I ate it all.
I'm going to eat the warabimochi that I
bought earlier.
This is the warabimochi that I bought
earlier.
It's a little cold.
This is powder.
I ate the hot croquette first and then
the warabimochi.
Warabimochi is also delicious.
Thank you for watching.
Sweet.
This is good.
It's delicious.
I'm sure.
The lady who made this rice cracker
said,
This is delicious.
She put it in.
I got it.
Thank you for watching.
It's delicious.
I ate it all.
It was delicious.
I want to wear a kimono today.
So I wear a kimono.
I'm going to the place where they put me
on.
I can't wear a mask well.
I've been passing by a lot of girls in
kimono.
They are all cute.
Cute.
It's quiet around here.
My hands are shaking.
I'm getting all wrinkly.
It's cold.
It's a fork.
Here.
I'm here.
Okay.
I'm nervous.
Is it okay?
Excuse me.
Hello.
I'm Endo. I made a reservation.
Thank you.
You can choose your favorite clothes.
You can choose any clothes you like.
Thank you.
I'm wondering if I can choose clothes
with so many clothes.
This is a beautiful kimono.
What should I do?
I can't choose this kind of clothes.
What? Wait a minute.
Purple.
Blue is cute.
White.
What should I do?
I'm thinking about what to do.
I'm going to change my clothes.
Yes, I changed my clothes. I changed my
clothes a little.
I can go.
Ta-da!
Wait, I wonder if I can do it with the
wind.
Are you alive?
It looks like this, it looks nice.
Ah, I can see it.
Oh, it's lovely!
It's a nice place!
I'm glad you made it so cute. Thank you
very much.
And now, in front of me is a place
called Kimono Forest.
So I'm thinking I'll go there.
I'm a little embarrassed.
Okay, let's go!
See you!
Wow, look, there are still some leaves
left.
Beautiful.
Wow, it's beautiful.
Shashashasha
It's amazing. Is this a wild spot?
That's right. It's beautiful.
Wow, it's so beautiful.
This is the station.
It's amazing.
It's really growing.
It's cold.
Mm.
Good.
Too Yummy
We made ancestor turnip into a dessert.
Sorewan is satisfied to make the Xelic
juice with bittersweet taste.
Xelic is good for you?
It's delicious.
Thank you for watching.
I ate dango.
It was delicious.
They served hot dango.
I drank hot tea.
I think it warmed me up a little.
But Kyoto is so lively.
I haven't been here for a long time.
I haven't seen so many people like this
since I was in elementary school.
There are many people, so I run through
There are many people
Great!
I think I came to a nice place.
Wow!
It's so beautiful.
Beautiful, beautiful.
It's wonderful.
It's nice.
Kyoto is beautiful.
The townscape is beautiful.
I want to go to a warmer season next
time.
It's cold today.
I feel like I'm only saying it's cold
today.
It's fun.
The god of the knot is a knot.
There is a park.
There are some autumn leaves on the top.
Can you see them?
They are a little orange.
They are cute.
Oh, this is it.
I also have to take a picture.
I'm going.
Oh, wait a minute.
There's someone up there.
Wow amazing
Okay!
It's embarrassing...
3 hours later
Now we are at a slope.
Wow!
There's a slope.
The steep slope.
A crisp tart.
Oh wow!
The candy update.
It's the taste of childhood.
Great.
This video was taken in 2023.
This year's goal...
What is it?
Thank you for watching.
The slope is so steep.
I can't imagine what I will do next
year.
I can't decide my goal.
I have to do my best.
Did you see the light?
I wonder what kind of light it was.
It's quiet around here.
There are a lot of people this time, so
it's very embarrassing to talk.
I'm worried that I haven't been able to
take a good picture.
I wonder if it's okay.
I had a very fun end of the year.
It's the new year now.
Happy New Year, everyone.
I wonder if they are having a good time.
I hope they are having a good time.
I wanted to come earlier and enjoy
autumn leaves, but it was already
December.
So I think it's already gone.
I should say, Manufacturing today is a
wonderful business.
It's a little bit orange.
It's still alive.
But it's good. I like this kind of
autumn leaves.
It's like winter is coming.
It's beautiful.
Click the clinical view
I could take another video at 10 pm
tomorrow
Thank you for watching!
I feel like I can show you my whole
body.
How is it? I like calm colors, so I
chose a dark blue.
The obi is gray? white?
I can see the circuit! I'm sorry.
It's cold, so...
Hey, hey, hey, forgive me.
I added a little red.
I have a red one in my hand.
It's okay. I'm sandwiched here.
I made it cute like this.
I'm glad.
The people who did it were kind.
Thank you very much.
Can you see it?
It's a red leaf.
Can you see that?
The Togetsu Bridge?
I've never seen it before.
Wait.
I want to ride a human-powered car.
Can I ride it?
Hello.
Can I ride a human-powered car?
Can I?
Please.
Yay!
Thank you.
Please.
Yes.
OK.
Is this your first time?
Yes, it is.
Yes.
Yay!
Wow!
It's a nice place, isn't it?
It's a really nice place.
Is this your YouTube channel?
Yes, it is.
I have a YouTube channel called
Nagisaka46.
I think I'll be on that channel.
I'll subscribe to your channel right
away.
Thank you very much.
Amazing!
I came to Kouto because it was a little
cold.
I rode a human train for the first time.
I crossed this place.
It was good and fun.
The brother of the human train was very
kind and funny.
I want to ride a human train again
someday.
I finished the third walk.
It was a little cold.
I'm sorry I'm wearing a coat at the end.
I enjoyed it very much.
It's a loose video, but thank you for
watching.
It's cold.
Please subscribe to my channel.