This week's Ebichu Tastas continues from
last week.
Ebichu Tastas trial part 2
Are you sleepy?
Yes
You are a user
Who will be judged tonight?
Ebichu Tastas start
100 times more exciting emotions
TORO!
I'm so into you that I can't stand it
What should I do with the heart of the
jubilee?
Moratorium, Moratorium, Moratorium,
middle school student
Add various things to your private Ebisu
middle school
Ebichu Tastas
This program is brought to you by the
following sponsors.
Tonight, Castasves'救再犯 gets decided by a
cast of members.
In this trial, Kenji is the prosecutor,
and Kaiki is the lawyer.
The members will decide whether they are
guilty or not.
The judge will give the verdict.
Today, Hirota and Nakayama will be
judged.
And the fate of that person?
Now, let's begin the trial!
The next case is this one.
The cute one is too low.
What is that?
The defendant, Hirota Aikawa, is the
judge.
What is that?
I don't know what it is.
Cute? The hurdle is too low.
Hirota's suspicion.
The hurdle of being cute is too low.
The defendant, Hirota Aikawa,
has a tendency to say that everything
she sees is cute.
Of course, if she really thinks so, it's
not a bad thing.
But there are many cases where she can't
say that it's a
It's not a bad thing if she really
thinks so.
But there are many cases where she can't
say that it's a
It's not a bad thing if she really
thinks so.
So, she's going to base it on the hurdle
of being cute being too low.
Oh!
That's amazing!
You've been saying that Chuu-Ei's face
is cute.
That's all I can say at this point.
I'm not cute.
You're cute!
I feel bad.
So, here's the proof of VTR.
Please watch.
How low is the hurdle of being cute?
Here's the proof.
Touch it.
Okay.
It's cute!
It's not cute.
There was a question mark.
It's cute.
I'm counting.
I'll be watching the game.
You say it's cute no matter what.
The standard of cuteness is strange.
I want to check the standard of
cuteness.
Let's evaluate.
Hirota says it's cute no matter what.
Where is her standard of cuteness?
Let's verify it.
Let's start with the first one.
Isn't this OK?
Oh, it's a cucumber.
I like the color.
This is cute.
This is cute?
Wait a minute.
Which one is cute?
This is not cute.
This is cute.
This is not cute because it's thick.
All of these are better.
I like this one.
I like the color.
This is cute.
It looks like the same cucumber, but
Hirota thinks this one looks cute.
Can he get closer to the truth of the
cuteness that Hirota thinks?
He will further examine the criteria.
I will go.
Is this a bonito?
This is a canna.
Is this a tree?
Yes.
How is it?
It may be different in cuteness, but I
want it normally.
This is not cute.
I see.
Canna is not cute.
This is a mass-produced type.
Mass-produced type.
I see.
I want you to tell me the
characteristics.
To be continued.
Let's go.
This is amazing.
The three types of screws that Hirota
has in front of him are slightly
different in shape and size.
There are many types.
Cute, cute.
Cute?
Which one?
I don't know.
Which one is cute?
The tools are mass-produced, but I like
it.
There are many variations, so I like it.
Which one is cute?
Well, if I say it's cute, it's
definitely this one.
Definitely this one.
If you say it's cute, it's definitely
this one.
Definitely this one.
This is cute.
This is cute, right?
The blue one is cute.
The blue one is cute, right?
There's a blue one, right?
If it's among these, it's like this in
terms of ranking.
1, 2, 3.
Yes.
What's the cuteness?
It's all cute.
But if you say it's your favorite, it's
like this.
It changes.
If you say it's cute, it's cute.
If you say it's cute, it's like this.
This is the top.
I see.
That's all.
To find out Hirota's cute standard, I
showed him various things, but the
mystery only deepened.
So, I decided to ask him about his
particularity once again.
I think it's strange that people who
have decided on this thing called
cuteness, not based on the criteria of
cuteness.
I think that each person has their own
cuteness, and I don't think it's
something that should be said.
Well done.
Now, the verdict.
Is Hirota's cuteness a crime or not?
Here we go!
Innocent! Innocent! Innocent!
Innocent 7 votes, Innocent 0 votes, so
the defendant Hirota is innocent!
In the end, the cute standard of Hirota
remains a mystery, but it seems that he
has a strong commitment, so as a result
of his innocence...
Next, the second trial today
Next, the third trial, the court of
Ebisu Junior High School
Do you know this?
The judge
Next, the fourth trial, the court of
Ebisu Junior High School
I will read the basic documents of the
case.
What is this script?
It's strange.
Anyone can read the basic documents,
right?
I admit it.
The two of you, the defendant and the
scriptwriter,
have been doing the program with Ebichu
for many years,
but you don't have any affection for
Ebichu.
I think you only want a business-like
relationship.
The Te Knowledge Show
Robinson & Co presents
Now it's time to execute personification
on kinds of public school
The
Time of Juk Ryu
No, no, no, no, this is strange
A sudden shock of suspicion
From here, Hirota will be the judge, and
Ogata will be the prosecutor
To pursue the crime of shooting stars
The other day, there was a tour final in
Ebichu
I also stood on the same stage
But the two of them couldn't come to the
venue
They couldn't come.
It's their job.
It can't be helped.
The last day of the Ebitu HALT TOUR,
where O-gata Kaiki also participated.
The shooting star who was working in
Kansai on the same day couldn't come to
the cheering.
In the midst of that, you two sent
flowers to the venue.
Yes, we couldn't go.
We sent flowers.
I also saw the flowers.
However, the flowers are the evidence to
support the
thin-willed suspicion.
What is the meaning of this?
When the shooting star actually checked
the flowers he sent to the Ebi-cho,
Look, there are nice flowers, cute
flowers.
They are totally nice.
Look.
What?
Look at this!
Shiritu Ebisu Junior High School?
What? Where is that group?
It's not there!
But this is really...
When you send flowers,
I'm serious.
The person who sends flowers is the
wrong person.
We said Shiritu Ebisu Junior High
School.
Hey!
Look!
Do you blame Manegi-san?
Please tell him this.
I can't go to Ebichu's live show.
I have to send flowers.
Then I said, okay.
Chuei said, I'll tell you.
You're dirty!
That's right.
Maybe this guy is in Ebisu Junior High
School.
I said Shiritu Ebisu Junior High School.
If this guy says that,
I didn't make it after it was over.
You said that, didn't you?
That's right.
Chuei didn't make it to the live show.
He was rushing to the venue in Tokyo
from Hyogo
just to make up for the members.
Good job!
But I want to say this.
You really didn't make it.
I'll tell you the truth.
I wanted to eat Akashi-yaki, so I took a
train.
I can eat shrimp, but I can't eat
Akashi-yaki.
I can't go to Kansai.
I found a more shocking photo.
Can you see it?
What is this?
This is...
After the concert, I drank with Ogata
and Hiya.
Why?
Why didn't you come to the party with
me?
It's not the time to call me.
I'm angry.
You're angry!
I don't have any excuses.
Please give the defendant the final
sentence.
Did you see that?
So, the final sentence of the defendant
who has never felt love for shrimp.
I really have love.
I will go to your concert.
I will do it.
That's all.
The verdict.
Is the action against the shrimp in the
pot guilty or not?
Everyone, please raise your hand.
I believe in myself.
The verdict is...
・・・I'm sorry.
Hey!
What are you talking about?
自分、彼国的な信仰を、エビチュー愛を証明するため、
一個月以内にエビチューの歌とダンスを完璧に覚えてくれたいもの。
マジで?
Thank you very much.
The song is called 春休みモラトリアの違う。 何で? マジで?
It's been a month and it's been a lot.
Really?
After this, Nakayama will be judged for
that crime
But before that...
Ebi-Chuu, the narrow path to becoming a
lyricist
This project is a project where Ebi-Chuu
challenges lyrics
To be used in a new song
Tonight, we have a big development
related to the future of the project
What is it?
This time, what we are going to do is
We want to write lyrics
But the theme of the lyrics has not been
decided yet
It is a big premise
What is the theme of the song?
Up to now, we have learned about writing
lyrics in various ways
The final goal of this project is to be
adopted as a song during the debut
So first of all, let's think about the
theme of the song that the members will
write.
The theme is important.
If it goes well, we can add the song and
make it a proper song.
Please think seriously.
So, let's announce the theme that each
member wants to write.
First, from Mayama.
Yes, Hikari.
What does this mean?
Hikari is always in our lives, right?
Yes.
So, simply, if it's us, we can be
thankful to Shoumei-san.
During the live...
Wait, thankful to Shoumei-san?
Or, we can be thankful to CYRIUM during
the live.
If it's like, you are my Hikari, we can
do that.
We can do that.
We connected it forcibly.
This is Nakayama.
I was like, is this the meaning of it?
It's like a talk theme.
What does it mean?
I don't really understand the song, but
at the end, I made her think, oh!
You made her think, what is she singing?
I see.
So, the listener is wondering what she
is singing.
So, it's about 3 minutes.
Next is Yasumoto.
The gap.
The gap? What do you mean?
For example, if you are in the middle of
the movie, you are between an adult and
a child.
In this age, you are a high school
student.
Or if your home is between Yoyogi Uehara
and Yoyogi Park,
you may be wondering which station is
the nearest.
There are some stations.
I think there are many people who are
wondering which station to use.
I just got a second one.
I thought of Paton.
Paton is not living in the movie.
So, if you are in the middle of the
movie, you are between Yoyogi Park and
Yoyogi Park.
You may be wondering which station to
use.
Wait a minute. Why did you go to my
house?
I was about to cry.
Next is Matsuno.
Everyone's favorite food song.
You're going to buy food, right?
If it's me, Young Con.
It's a bit difficult.
I'm just going to say what I like to
eat.
For example, if you had a favorite food
that pops up in your head, what would
you choose?
Ramen.
Ramen, ramen, ramen.
And Yasumoto?
Tomato.
Ramen, ramen, ramen.
Mixing various things and making it into
one rhythm.
I want to try it.
Let's try it.
So, if you all choose your favorite
food, will it be like a song?
Matsuno will do it.
Let's all do it together.
1, 2, 3, 4.
Young Con, Young Con, Young Con.
It's a very unique melody.
Let's do it.
Young Con, Young Con, Young Con.
It's good.
Ramen, ramen, ramen.
Mixing various things and making it into
one rhythm.
What are you saying?
What?
It's a different song.
That's what I'm saying.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
It's good.
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you.
It's a very unique melody.
It's really good.
How did you say it?
Let's start with Matsuno.
Young, Young Con, Con.
No, no.
Young Con, Young Con, Young Con.
Please don't make a different version.
They are supposed to decide the theme of
the lyrics, but they are just having a
discussion.
Will they be able to decide the theme
like this?
Let's continue to the next episode.
After this, finally, it's time for the
trial of Nakayama.
I'm the one who's not good at this.
The quickly feverish
The next basic case is this one.
The moment when an adult suddenly
responds.
I think I know.
That girl?
It was that girl.
The defendant, Mariko Nakayama, is in
the front.
Are you sleepy?
Yes.
You are a hero.
The suspicion that Nakayama made.
The moment when she suddenly responded
to adult.
According to the member's report,
Riko Nakayama, the defendant, has
recently become an adult.
There are things that people can't
follow.
So she suddenly responds to adult too
much.
What?
Adult?
There is also a proof video.
Please see the moment when you suddenly
become an adult.
Nakayama was asked where she wanted to
go abroad.
Aurora.
I want to see the aurora.
It's written.
Did you say something every time?
I said a lot before, but I don't think
it will come true.
You still give up.
You suddenly give up.
Don't make me sad.
You still have a chance.
I will not give up.
Nakayama asked if she liked the stars.
Nakayama is doing her best.
You like the stars?
Yes.
Everyone likes the stars.
I don't know much about them.
You're suddenly talking about them.
Nakayama has become an adult.
They kind of passionately talk about her
Yes, that's right. Did you understand?
I understood.
Right? If you suddenly think that you
are the one who is eating, you suddenly
talk about it.
In an adult's way.
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes. It's like, suddenly it's
realistic.
It's a little bit exciting for us.
How about you?
Do you have any real feelings?
I don't know anything. I really don't
know anything.
I'm not sure.
But I'm still doing it because I feel
like it.
Nakayama claims that it is not the cold
that suddenly responds to adult.
By the way, how many people do you think
Nakayama is a mood maker?
I don't know.
ーShe is doing it by herself. ーYes.
ーDo you have any specific story? ー
ーLike, you don't feel good. ー
ーBut, I think... ー
ーYasumoto's testimony is going to change
the whole story. ー
ーI'm not happy when I'm being eaten by
someone. ー
ーWhat? ー
ーI'm sorry. ー
I think it's a burning point.
When you suddenly show off your
tsundere.
I think it's popular.
Do you feel lonely when you're pushed
around?
I do, but I don't feel the joy when I
come.
You feel twice as happy.
I feel twice as happy.
What do you feel?
I don't know. I don't know.
I see.
I didn't know that.
I was troubled by N-1.
Yasumoto says that when Nakayama is
down, it's a burning point.
So, we'll give him a cucumber of his
favorite food and see if he can burn it.
I like it with vinegar.
No!
It's not cucumber, it's vinegar.
This animal is difficult.
I heard it was a herb.
What do you think?
Can I say this?
Please, lawyer.
She is very particular.
It's a human being.
I said it.
I wanted to do it suddenly.
The decision is made.
Is it a crime for NAKAYAMA to respond to
an adult suddenly?
Or is it innocent?
Members, please raise your cards at
once.
Please.
Innocent, innocent, innocent, innocent,
innocent, innocent,
Innocent 7 votes, guilty 0 votes.
The defendant, Nakayama, is innocent!
In the end, Nakayama was judged to be
just a
fortune teller, and was acquitted.
The next episode will be more and more
heated up.
The final episode of the TAS TAS trial.
The suspicions of shock are coming one
after another.
Isn't it already a sexual harassment?
Takayama-san doesn't hate it.
He's used to it.
And the combination of Yasumoto and
Kobayashi.
The suspicions that never change are
discovered.
And the outcome of the trial is...
This program was provided by the
sponsors you see.