In our language, that's called a crouch.
I'm sorry!"
I'm sorry!" Every time I get an answer, I get an answer that's just a slap in the face, and an answer that goes beyond what I imagined.
I wanted to make it wider.
So I wanted to make it wider.
FUKA, BORI
SIDE A
DIG I 01 Creepy Nuts
FUKA BORI is the deepest music content, where music is savored like a luxury item.
SIDE A digs deep into his own music.
By shedding light on the deepest aspects of music, the charms you have never noticed begin to shine through.
Welcome to the deepest music.
FUKA, BORI
SIDE A
The song that became the turning point of Creepy Nuts
To those of us who were once geniuses.
I chose this song because I think that there has been a big change since this song.
I chose this song because I think there was a big change from this song.
Did something big change happen?
I feel that my situation and thoughts have really been accumulating over the past year.
I really feel like things have been building up over the past year.
As you said, Mr. Taninaka
I am sure that this is one of the turning points.
It's one of the things that are building up.
When I finished the lyrics and sent the demo to the rest of the team
I sent the demo to everyone on the team.
I sent the demo to everyone on the team, and they all said to me privately
I thought to myself, "Oh, I feel like something's opening up in this song.
I thought that too.
I also felt that I was able to tell everyone about it.
It sounds cheesy to say that I'm trying to reach a lot of people, but...
I don't know.
If I were to say it like that, it would sound cheesy.
I've been writing the lyrics facing me and me facing each other.
I've been writing the lyrics to "To Us Who Once Were Geniuses" facing myself.
I wrote the lyrics facing myself, but
I wrote the lyrics facing myself, but with a little bit of a side view.
I felt like I was looking at someone outside of myself
When I was writing the lyrics
That's a very poetic expression.
FUKA/BORI
SIDE A
Hints for songwriting
The song itself is the theme song of Teikyo Heisei University.
So you started from the idea that you wanted to have that song?
Yes, that's right.
But, you know, it was pretty much up to me.
I left it pretty much up to them and asked them to make it as they pleased.
We didn't really have any specific orders.
That's right.
I was wondering what I should do.
I didn't have any clue what to do, and I didn't know what to do.
I didn't have a clue what to do, so we decided to make the music video first.
At the meeting for the music video, the director, Taishi, suggested this "road"...
"The road."
So, "the road"...
The "road" or the "path" is like the path of a university or a career path.
I thought about it like this.
And then I started thinking about all kinds of things.
And it became like this.
When you find a clue for a song, you just go with it.
Do you go from there in a flash?
or is it a gradual process?
I'd like to know more about the process of creation.
It's a gradual process.
Slowly?
But it's not until I find that starting point that I really get into it.
I'm having a hard time with this.
I think it's all jumbled up in my head.
It's not that organized.
It's not so organized.
It's like these thoughts that are in various places
I wonder if it comes out in the lyrics.
Putting it into words itself...
Your notes are amazing.
Yes, it's amazing.
The notebooks are just a bunch of notes.
From the beginning to the end of the lyrics.
I've never written lyrics in the proper order in a notebook.
I've never written lyrics from the beginning to the end of a song in a notebook in that order.
I've never written down the words that came to mind, or what I was thinking about, in this way.
I really need to write it down in various places.
You need a notebook, don't you?
I guess so.
Look at all those college notebooks.
I haven't looked at the notebooks I've been using recently.
I haven't seen the notebooks you use these days, but I saw you writing in one a few years ago.
There's a line drawn through it.
Ignore the lines.
I thought he was using it like a free-form notebook.
I thought to myself, "Don't buy a college notebook.
It's like you shouldn't buy a college notebook, in the best sense of the word.
I mean, it's like, the fragments are typed freely.
The letters are big or small...
It's totally different.
Some of the words are so dirty that I can't read them, and some of them I can read.
I write down all kinds of things in this way.
But in the end, this song is the same.
But in the end, this song is one of them.
But in the end, when I listen to this song as well as the other songs
I think it's easy to understand the impression I get when I listen to them.
I can clearly tell that this is the kind of song I'm thinking of.
"Oh, this is the kind of song this is.
I think it's really cool that it comes to you organically and three-dimensionally.
It's not two-dimensional.
The message is conveyed in three dimensions.
I can really understand what you are saying.
I can understand the purpose of the song just by listening to it.
But it's not super simple. It comes from so many different directions and in so many different ways.
I already know what it means, but I can go around it many times, I can taste it in any way I want.
It's not a simple taste at all, it's got 12 layers.
But you can already tell what it's for from the very beginning.
You have both the pop music and the depth of it.
I feel like I can clearly see the arrow pointing in the direction you want to go.
That's why it's very easy to listen to.
FUKA / BORI
SIDE A
When I was writing the lyrics
There was a time when R said that the lyrics come first when a really good word comes to mind.
There was a time when R said that when a really good word comes to mind
That word is so catchy!
I thought it was a great phrase to use as a catch copy.
R said to me, "Now that you've got it, you can go on writing.
And then I hear, "Now that I've got this, I can go on with the writing.
And from there, it's just like that.
I think that's why this song is the same.
You called it a "road" or a "path".
But after the word "katatsura, genius, to us" came out.
But after the word "ka tsuki datta genius us" came out, it was finally connected to the word "michi".
Before that, there were so many different ways to say "the road".
I wondered if there was a word that was unique to me.
This path is one that looks forward.
But in order to see the road ahead...
I guess I was thinking that I should turn my head back.
I don't know the exact order of my brain when I wrote that.
I don't know.
That's true, isn't it?
I'm sure that's true.
It's not limited to college.
I think there are many paths in front of you at any time in your life.
But the choices in front of you are naturally narrower than they used to be.
I think I'm narrowing down my choices.
This is right.
If I hadn't done this, I wonder what I would have done.
We all think about it, don't we?
Of course I am narrowing my own possibilities.
Or to put it another way, when you go out into the world
In other words, it's important to learn what you're good at, what you're not good at, what you're not good at, what you're not suited for, and how you measure up
The older you get, the narrower your path becomes.
I think this is a normal form of growth.
At the moment of my birth, I probably wasn't as good as the others.
I wasn't beaten, I wasn't compared to others.
I was not defeated or compared to others, so I probably could have done anything.
I would describe that state of being as "invincible," "all-powerful," or a "genius.
Then I'd say, "Yeah, but that sounds like a genius.
I used to like drawing.
I used to like drawing... and sports... before I thought I wasn't good at them.
I thought I could do something.
I was friends with a ball.
I used to like to draw, and I used to try sports, and before I thought I was bad at it, I thought I was good at it.
I'm not good at it, or I'm not good at it, or I'm not good at it.
I'm not good at it, or I'm not good at it... and I'm not good at it.
There is a part of you that knows too much about your own size, isn't there?
At my age, I've managed to know my size once more.
Knowing how big you are...
But I want you to try to imagine what it was like back then.
I think it's a good idea to look at various "paths".
"To those of us who were once geniuses..."
These are the words that stick in everyone's mind.
In that sense...
In that sense, I'm glad to know that you're getting it right.
It makes me happy, doesn't it?
We all wanted to say what we were thinking and wanting to say.
but you were able to put it into words.
It's really an invention when that happens.
Like Yanaka just said, "guess what."
"Guessing" is something that rappers and lyrics-writers have in common.
It's something fundamental.
Especially those who write lyrics that become songs.
I wondered if there was something to it.
The same hip-pop group, THA BLUE HERB
There is a group called THA BLUE HERB from Sapporo
The Blue Herb's ILL-BOSSTINO, the MC BOSS, said, "I write a song for every live performance.
The MC, BOSS, makes a song for every live performance. When I say a word in front of the audience, I want to guess what it is.
He said this during the MC, in the songs, and when he talked with me.
Is that true in battles as well?
It's true that even in battles, there are moments when the audience gets excited by the words.
There are definitely moments when the excitement builds up.
In a battle, you have to guess...
I guess the one I don't like to be told.
I don't like to be told what to say.
Because I guess the painful part
Something about the opponent.
Something about your opponent that everyone else is thinking, "Oh!" or "Hmm?" When you guess what they're thinking...
It's a big surprise.
And vice versa.
When things are exciting...
You know, when you get a "aha" moment.
We both say "aha" to each other.
It's amazing. I watched the video of the battle.
The rhythm is overwhelmingly good.
His rhythm is really great.
No, he really has great rhythm.
I can see it when I look at the waveforms from the control room after recording.
For example, there's a song called "Hoichi Style without ears".
For example, there's a song called "Miminashi Yoichi Style," which is a very serious song with a very high level of rap music.
But we recorded one verse of that song without any trouble.
We recorded it in one take, in two takes, and then we said, "Okay, let's go to the next take.
Then you say, "Okay, let's go to the next take," and record another one.
And when we put the two recordings on top of each other, the position was almost identical.
The waveforms were almost identical.
I could have made them all pocal double one.
It wasn't recorded for the purpose of doubling, but the nuance of the words and the rhythm are exactly the same.
I sang a take where I wanted to change the key and the pitch of the song.
The one I sang with the intention of keeping the rhythm the same turned out to have the same rhythm.
The engineer was like, "What the hell is this?
FUKA, BORI
SIDE A
Trying a new sound
I'd like to talk about the track part as well.
I've been reading a lot about how to make them.
I've been doing sampling for a long time, but I've changed my approach to making tracks by having a live band play on the pandora's box.
I've changed my approach to making tracks by having a live pianist play the music.
That depends on the song.
But I don't do "sampling" now.
I don't do "sampling" at the moment. The ratio of live performance to my own computer compositions is different.
Some are completely live and some are completely typed.
It really depends on the song.
For this song, I really didn't have any knowledge of music theory.
I didn't know the concept of chords until I wrote this song.
I don't know the chords, let alone the sheet music.
I didn't really know what a chord was.
So I asked him to teach me a little bit.
This is the first song where I consciously added chords.
But if I had written a song with chords, it would have sounded like...
I was really disgusted by it, and it smelled like a lot of people.
So I decided to do that.
I wanted to do that.
I wanted to take that smell, that smokiness that we originally had, and
By attaching this code
I wanted to take something that had been shaken once before and
I tried to see how I could add color to it once more.
The result is a slightly ethnic feel.
And the weird intro...
I went through quite a bit of trial and error.
I was watching YouTube while taking a break, and I went to a music store.
I saw a video of a trip to a music store.
That's where I first saw the electric guitar.
I was like, "Oh, I've never seen this before," and "Let's try playing it.
I thought the sound of the erexitar was really cool.
I heard a sitar, but I thought it wasn't a sitar.
Finally, I heard a nice smell by this Elexital I.
Yeah, that might be it.
It came out.
I thought it was something like...
I think the beat of "To those of us who used to be geniuses" is a good thing.
I was able to open up the beat of Creepy Nuts exactly as it was.
When we first met, I was listening to various beats.
I was listening to a lot of beats that Matsunaga-san had.
I was sampling at the time, but when I first met him
When I first met him, his sense of style was...
snarky, eerie, etc.
It was weird.
And yet it was so catchy.
I think my rapping was a great match for it.
I thought that my rappka would go well with it.
That's the direction we've been going.
I had my sampling group, Pando, play it for me.
And then we're going to rework it again.
So when it comes to this chord this time
I'm sure Matsunaga-san is even more anxious than I am about how it's going to turn out.
I think you were more worried than I was about how it would turn out.
I know, it's a new way of doing things, isn't it?
The original beat is also very strange, of course.
Of course it's very strange.
It was a pop beat, of course.
And I put my rap on it.
And after that...
And then this Elexital came in.
Yes, at the very end.
Larry was very detailed.
I sent him a demo that I had made with just typing, and he made the chorus.
And then he would rework it and put a rap on top of it.
And then we rewrote it and rewrote it and rewrote it and rewrote it and rewrote it and rewrote it.
We changed the drums completely.
So after the rap was added
"I added a little bit of speed to it," and they came back and said, "Oh!
And I'm like, "Oh, wow.
So you do something with that rally every time.
We would do that rally many times.
If I had the time...
I'd like to do it again and again.
That rally...
My words, my raps...
To my words and my raps.
Yes, that's true.
That's why every time we do it...
It's like a knee-jerk reaction.
I mean, it's like I'm imagining it, and he's like.
"Oh, that's what I'm talking about."
I couldn't put it into words, so I couldn't explain it to him, but he's like.
"That's what I wanted, that's what I wanted in this rap."
I'd get the right answer and the answer that exceeded my imagination every time.
That's what makes it really mutual.
Mr. Matsunaga responds to words with sounds.
So the sound effects, the excerpts, and so on...
Sometimes he adds a little bit of something, sometimes he adds a lot.
Sometimes he adds a little bit of background sound to my words.
I feel like he adds a picture with sound to my words.
So when you listen to our music, you probably get a three-dimensional feeling
the rhythm of the words in your body.
It's like the rhythm of many words.
I think it's the tacha sound that visualizes the rhythm of the words
I think it's the Taha sound.
The sound makes us see the picture more three-dimensionally.
FUKA/BORI
SIDE A
What a sound rally produces
Maybe rap music is a way of singing that contains a lot of information.
It's fun to abstract something with a track.
It's fun to take something concrete and abstract it
It's like painting a background.
It totally changes the way the song sounds.
It's almost like making a cover.
It's similar to making an album cover.
Not this song, but another song I've been working on a lot lately.
I just send them a single loop that's about 5 minutes long, and then I extend it for a while.
R-designate swims freely in it.
I develop it, arrange it, change the top part, change the drums, and so on.
That's how we tend to make it.
But when the rap is added to the first big one, sometimes it gets a little complicated.
Sometimes it's so complicated that I don't understand what it means.
When the recipient doesn't understand the meaning.
The rhythm of the rap is complicated.
They say, "What? Isn't this weird?" Like, "This doesn't feel good.
I don't feel good."
I don't know how I'm going to get it down here.
I was like, "R, maybe you made a mistake."
I didn't feel very comfortable with the rhythm.
But when I was fine-tuning the drums and it just clicked, I was like, "This is what I wanted to do.
There was one moment when I was fine-tuning the drums, and I was like, "This is what I wanted to do.
It wasn't a mistake.
It's the moment when you let the truck catch up with what you wanted to do, and it just clicked.
That's where it gets the worst.
You're like, "I'm sorry.
"I'm sorry it didn't feel good!" And then you go, "I'm sorry it didn't feel good!
I'm like that too.
It's like, "I can't communicate in words
"I'm sorry it doesn't feel good!
I have a lot of trust that they will understand me.
There's also the naivety of trust.
But when I get a complicated flow back, it's like, "Oh, I knew you'd get it.
When the complexity flows and you get a quick response, it's like, "Oh, I knew you'd get it.
Yes, that's right.
"Ah! By eliminating all the drums, you can get rid of all the drums.
"Ah! I'm glad I did it." By eliminating the drums, I thought, "Oh, this is going to be good.
When I heard this song, I thought.
I thought that when the song goes "To those of us who were geniuses once..."
Suddenly, the drums become a bit thinner, like a tom roll.
It's quite shocking.
I thought it was the chorus.
I thought that was the chorus, but then it goes down.
I wanted to make that part wider.
I wanted to make it wide at that point.
I wanted to make it wider.
I wanted to reduce the size of the store.
At the beginning of the chorus, I wanted all the instruments to make a sound.
Did you want to make it wider after the lyrics were written?
No, but I think that was the original idea.
Originally?
No, the first chorus came after the first verse.
Before we wrote the verse.
By the time I got to this chorus.
I wanted to make it wider.
But that's probably why we didn't talk about it.
It wasn't a discussion about how to do it.
But in the rally, right at the chorus...
Before we came to "never before"...
That's the chorus, right?
The bridge before that...
Actually, the title of our song is in the chorus.
The title of the song is often included in the chorus.
This time, the bridge before the chorus...
In my language, that's called a crouch.
I've taken the liberty of using the word "shagami" before the chorus as the title of the song.
But with that shagami, Mr. Matsunaga wants to make it wider.
I want to reduce the amount of information.
It's the widest words I've ever written.
"To us who used to be geniuses" and "To you who used to be prodigies".
I'm directing it to outside of myself.
It's the widest lyrics I've ever written.
and also as a sound.
I think the fact that they are in sync with each other
I think it's a very strange thing that the song is born from the mutual trust between Larry and me.
It's true that the message is broadened there, too.
It's super me.
"If only Masaya1 hadn't laughed at me when I passed him."
Masaya and I went to elementary and middle school together.
I've had local friends come up to me and say, "Hey, that's him, isn't it?
He's a genius who used to be a genius."
The sound and the words open up with a bang.
When the three of us were talking, I thought, "Oh, that's how it's supposed to be.
I don't know if I did it on purpose or if it just happened naturally.
I wish everyone would read the lyric card once as a reading material.
Oh, sure, sure, sure, sure.
It's a real masterpiece as a reading.
It's a movie, really.
A movie?
I really think so.
It's a movie. It's a novel.
FUKA/BORI to be continued...