I wanted to make it wider so that I
could see the answers clearly and beyond
my imagination.
I wanted to make it wider so that I
could see the answers clearly and beyond
my imagination.
Thank you for your time today.
Thank you.
I'm looking forward to it.
When I was a kid, I was too much of a
painter.
I think there was a big change from this
song.
Did you feel any big changes?
I think I've been thinking about my
situation for a year.
As Yanaka-san said, I think it's one of
the turning points.
It's one of the things that's been
piling up.
When I was making the lyrics myself,
and when I sent the demo to the team,
I was really excited and thought,
I feel like it's going to be a little
open this time.
But I also thought about it and I feel
like everyone said it.
It's really cheap to write songs that
reach a lot of people.
What is it?
In my own sense, I've been writing
lyrics for myself.
We used to write lyrics for ourselves.
I wanted to write songs that are a
little different from what I'm used to.
I liked it.
That's a very nice expression.
This song is a theme song of the Hesei
University of Tokyo.
And you started with the idea of wanting
that song.
Yes.
I was like, please make it up to me.
I didn't really have an order.
I was very confused about what to do.
I couldn't find any hints.
When we were talking about making an MV,
the directors suggested the idea of a
path.
The idea of a path, or a path, or a
path, or a path, or a path, or a path,
or a path, or a path, or a path, or a
path...
I started to think about it, and I
started to think about it.
I want to know if you get caught in
other songs and you go crazy or if
you're just going to keep going.
It's just going.
I struggle every time until I find that
catch.
I think there's something wrong with my
head.
It's not so organized.
It's not organized.
I think the ideas in various places are
probably in the lyrics.
The notes are amazing.
The notes are really rough.
I've never written the lyrics in the
right order from the beginning to the
end of the lyrics.
I think it's about thinking about words
that come to mind in various ways.
I wrote it in various ways.
You must have a lot of memory.
Yes, I have.
I haven't seen the notes I've been using
recently,
but I saw it written on a university
notebook a few years ago.
It has a line drawn on it.
I ignored that line and wrote it down.
I thought I was using it like a free-
spirited book.
I thought, don't buy a university
notebook.
I thought it was a good idea to write it
in a good way.
I thought it was a really free short
film.
Was it big or small?
It was small.
But the words were so dirty that I
couldn't read them.
Or I could read this.
I think about it while writing and
writing my own things.
But in the end, this song is the same.
When I listened to other songs,
I felt that it was very easy to
understand.
I think it was a good idea.
There are many parts that clearly convey
that this song is a good song.
I think it's great that it's so organic
and three-dimensional.
It's not two-dimensional, is it?
I understand how the message is
transmitted in three dimensions.
I understand very well.
By doing this one by one...
I understand the purpose of the song,
but it's not super simple.
It's a lot of different ways to express
it.
I know what it means, but I can do it in
many ways.
I can taste it in any way.
It's not a taste that's easy to
understand at all.
It's a great difficulty.
But I know what kind of purpose the song
is for.
That's right.
It's its 되리 saga, its depths.
It's a story that's so easy to listen
to.
I think you can tell the direction of
the sound.
It's so easy.
I remember a very good word, and I
thought the lyrics would go well with
it.
The word is very catchy.
The phrase, catch copy, is wonderful.
I heard it, and I thought, oh, this is
why I can write it.
And then it comes out.
This song is also like that.
I said the path and the path, but after
the word came out,
I finally saw the path.
I thought that the path was connected to
the world.
There are many expressions that come out
even if they are unknown.
When I thought that there was no word
for me,
I thought that the path was to look
forward,
but I thought that I should look back
once I looked forward.
I thought that I should look back once I
looked forward.
I don't know the order of brain-stomach.
That's right.
The path to go forward is not limited to
college.
I think there are various paths in front
of you at any time in your life.
Of course, it's more natural to have a
choice in front of you than in the past.
I thought I was narrowing down and
narrowing down.
But what would have happened if it
weren't for this now?
Everyone thinks about it.
There are some parts that narrow down
the possibilities themselves.
On the contrary, the fact that you learn
the ways of the world,
such as getting, increasing, and moving
forward,
is what makes the age increase.
And the path gets narrower.
I think this is the shape of normal
growth.
The moment I was born, I probably didn't
have a soil,
I didn't lose or get compared to others.
I thought I could do anything.
I thought I was a genius.
I used to like drawing.
Before I started playing sports, I
thought I could do something.
You became friends with the world.
But when I realized I was bad at it, I
stopped.
There are parts where you know too much
about Minotake.
I realized I was bad at it, but I kept
going.
I wanted to imagine the feelings I felt
at that time,
and try out different ways.
That's why I chose the name, Genius.
It's a word that everyone says.
I'm happy to feel that I'm receiving a
good response.
We all wanted to say it, but R made it
into a word.
It was a real invention.
エ Buddha而生
今柳さんが言ってくれた言い当てる 言い当てるっていうのももしかしたら結構ラッパー
とかまーあの歌詞書きの人のなんか根源的な特にこう 楽曲になるものを歌詞書いてる人
だってなんかあるのかなってそうですねそのね同じポップグループで札幌のザブルーハー
ブってグループがいてブルーハーブのあのいるボスティーノさん mc
のボスさんがその毎回ライブとか
楽曲作っていくお客さんの前で言葉するときは言い当てたいんだよ mc でも曲でも僕
と喋った時も言ってくださっててそれってこうバトルとこでもそうってするわけですかや
っぱりそうですねバトルの部分でも言い当てる
ことによって盛り上がる瞬間もやっぱ確かにありますねでもバトルの言い当てるは言われ
て嫌な方がいいんじゃないか その言われて嫌なとこが痛いと言うといいやてるね対戦相
手のなんかみんながあとかって思ってるところをパンと言い当てた時にドカンってなるそ
うですよ逆もありますからやっぱり盛り当てる時はやっぱりあの言い当てられたとかねっ
てなる時はねお互い
すごいですねでもあのバトルのなんか動画も見させていただいたんですけど
あと的にリズムがいいですね
当たり前でしょうけどリズムすごいですよねリズム本当すごいですねこの人 マジリズム
すごくてレコーディングしてコントロールルームから波形見てるとわかるんですよ
あの例えば
耳無しポイチスタイルって曲があったから むちゃくちゃリズムに対してシビアな曲
超ラップがハイレベルの曲なんですけどあれワンバーサーかスーパーサーツルーってとっ
たんですよ
スルーとバーって1本でツーってとってじゃあ次のテイクいきますって言ってもう1本と
じゃないですかとって
2本重ねたらほぼ一緒だったのに1がその波形がほぼ一緒なんですよ
ボーカルダブルにしても大丈夫ぐらいそれはダブル目的にとった方がいいんじゃないかっ
てもう1本音コタバルニュアンスとかリズムはまあまあキーとかとかそこら辺のピッチ感
を変えようと思って歌ったテイクがリズムを同じにしようと思って歌ったのが本当にリズ
ムが同じだったっていう
すごいちょっとみんなぞあってエンジニアが何これみたいななるっていう
I also worked on the track part.
I read a lot about how to make it.
I also did sampling.
I did live performance and band
performance.
I also changed the way to make the
track.
It's well-established.
I don't do sampling now.
It's different when you play live on
your computer.
If you play live, you can play live.
It depends on the song.
I didn't know much about music theory.
I didn't know the concept of chords
before I made this song.
I didn't know chords.
I was taught that.
This is the first song I consciously
made a chord.
But if I made a song with a normal
chord,
it would be a terrible smell of my body.
I was thinking about what to do with it,
so I made a song with the smell of my
body.
I tried to make it more authentic by
adding this structure.
I watched YouTube while I was on a
break.
I went to an instrument store and saw a
video.
It was my first time to make a song like
this.
There was this instrument called
エレキスタール.
I was like, I'll try it out.
I thought the sound of エレキスタール was
really cool.
I heard スタール but I didn't think it was
スタール.
And then I thought エレキスタール had a good
smell.
It was amazing.
That was one of the most creepy beats
we ever made.
then I realized it was open.
When I first found the sound,
I had CYO-MOG play the instrument.
I saw the rich sound Massu was producing
when I was sampling
and I realized it was의 kinda strange.
It cannot be collection although this is
somehow strange or creepy...
I don't like it, but it's catchy.
I think my rap goes well with it.
I thought so when I was making the first
song.
We've been coming in that direction.
We've been playing the sample from the
band.
We're going to reassemble it again.
And when this chord comes out,
I wonder what's going to happen.
I think you were more nervous than I
was.
That's right. It's a new way of
thinking.
And this is the original beat.
Of course, it was a strange but pop
beat.
And I put on a rap.
That's after that.
I came in with Elkish and R.
Oh, that's the last one.
The rally was pretty small.
I sent a demo that I made with only the
introduction.
I made a chorus.
And I made a demo with that.
I made a demo, put on a rap, and then
re-made it.
I did it several times, and I changed it
from drum to song.
So after rapping, I added some sense of
loss, and then I came back.
At the rally, I do it every time.
You do it many times.
If I have time, I want to do it many
times.
The rally is...
It's my words and my rap. It's
Matsunaga's answer.
Oh, that's true.
So I'm always on my knees, and I'm not
imagining things.
And I'm like, that's it.
I couldn't explain it in words, but I
wanted to do it like that.
That's the perfect answer and the answer
that goes beyond imagination.
That's really...
・ ♥
Listeners
Rappers have a lot of information.
It's fun to see how the tracks are
abstracted.
It's like drawing a background with a
specific object.
It's totally different.
It's like making a cover.
It's similar to making an album cover.
It's fun to see how the tracks are
abstracted.
In other tracks, there are quite a few
that send one loop for 5 minutes.
R is for swimming freely.
I add a
development and add it to that.
If you change the upper body, you can
change the drums.
I often make it like that.
Sometimes it's too complicated and
doesn't make sense.
When I can't understand the rhythm of
the rap, I thought it was weird.
There was a moment when I thought it
wasn't pleasant.
I was wondering how to make this sound.
I thought I made a mistake.
It was a rhythm that didn't feel good.
When I adjusted the rhythm, it was a
good sound.
But I wanted to do this.
I was surprised.
I wanted to do this, but I was stuck in
the track.
That was the most dangerous part.
I was like, what is this?
I'm sorry.
I can't tell you the beat in the
language.
I'm sure you'll understand.
I'm not sure if I'm going to die.
With the hard rule-by- muchís of things,
I feel relieved and don't get Core
acceptable.
I was like, I'm gonna take all the beats
and drums out of that.
I was like, this is gonna be so good.
What I thought when I heard this song
was...
When we were in TESAI, we suddenly
turned the drums a little bit.
It's getting a little thinner.
It's pretty shocking.
I was like, I'm listening to this.
I thought it was the chorus, but it went
down there.
I wanted to record that part.
I wanted to make it wider.
Wider!
I wanted to make it less informative.
I wanted to make it sound like a small
child in the beginning of the chorus.
Did you write the lyrics for the song?
No, I didn't.
Did you write the lyrics?
I wrote the first chorus before the
verse.
chorus.
I wanted to make it bigger.
But I think that was before the chorus,
not before the chorus,
but before the chorus,
before the chorus,
but before the chorus.
In fact, in our songs, the bridge is
often included in the chorus, but this
time, the bridge before the chorus.
In my language, it's called shagami.
I use the title with a shagami before
the chorus.
But in the shagami, I want to make
Matsumoto-san's song wider and less
commonplace.
The lyrics, which kyarsh earnest Empire
reached out to those under the control
of프레종,
symbolized wider generally Luke and
Endel.
But in reality, I have already raised a
wide bar in monotony between the lyrics
that are
affectively long and restrained, like in
this song,adsacing that 전 세계
정말繊細になった時代の歌詞,
which stick in my guts and my song.
Thank you for watching!
I tell people like me that they should
pretend not to,
and that I was kind for a kid when my
face festivals stopped.
It reminded me of my middle school
friends in elementary, middle and high
schools.
We would get世界 opinion from my friends
and consider the average personal-like
personality.
Everyone would turn come face to face
with this fact.
I tell that...
When we were talking, we were like,
Oh, that's what it is.
We were doing it on purpose.
It was natural.
I want everyone to read it as a reading
card.
That's true.
It's a real masterpiece as a reading
card.
It's a movie.
It's a movie novel.
I want everyone to read it as a reading
card.