Hello, everyone. I'm Mayuka Sasaki from
Pico-All-Ram.
I'm Anna Yamamoto.
Today, we're going to introduce what we
bought at Costco.
Yay!
I wanted to go!
We finally went to Costco.
It's been about three years.
We've been saying it for a long time.
Finally!
I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm happy.
Are you looking forward to it?
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you. I'm looking forward to it.
I'd like to introduce it right away.
What I bought this time is...
Ta-da!
Yay!
Can you see it?
I can't see it.
Jaguar...
Can you see it?
Come here.
I saw it.
That's crazy.
That's crazy. Look.
That's amazing. Look.
There's more behind you.
Wow!
Oh, it's not over there.
That's amazing.
I really bought too much.
I bought too much.
I'd like to introduce what I bought at
Costco.
First of all, here.
Yes.
Jagariko.
I bought it.
I love Jagariko as a snack.
I love IKORABU.
I like the salad flavor the most.
Well, it's a salad.
It's zero calories.
There are 12 of them.
Wow, that's great.
I'll give it to everyone.
The Jagariko who hides my face is...
Yes.
Goodbye.
What's next?
This is...
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!
Hahaha.
That happens sometimes.
The cheese is...
The cheese is falling apart.
Thank you very much.
This is yogurt.
It's Chichias yogurt.
What do you think this is?
It says Setouchi.
Sharp.
Where is Setouchi?
What?
What does that mean?
It's Hiroshima.
Yes, that's right.
I've been eating this since I was a kid.
Have you seen this girl?
Chibou?
Not a girl.
Chibou.
Is this a girl?
Is it a boy?
It's Chibou, so it's a boy.
Yes.
There are three flavors.
That's nice.
It's a little different.
You eat yogurt in the morning.
People still think you're Hiroshima
Yunka.
I wanted to feel Hiroshima, so I chose
this.
This is also quite heavy.
What's next?
This is...
Ta-da!
It looks heavy.
It looks delicious.
Richam.
Is it called Richam?
Yes, it's like Spam.
It's not Spam.
It's Richam.
What is this?
You bought it.
I wanted to eat Spam.
I put Spam in it once.
I thought it was healthier.
So I chose this.
It looks delicious.
A lot.
This is also a dumbbell.
Great.
It's really heavy.
It's delicious if you eat it with
mozzarella cheese.
It's definitely delicious.
I love this.
Great.
Next.
I don't think this will end.
I'll eat it quickly.
This is the one I dropped earlier.
This is the pizza that I dropped.
This is a dream.
I want to eat this alone.
I can do it with a watch.
You are wonderful.
You are sloppy.
Next is this.
I've always wanted this.
This is strawberry milk.
This looks delicious.
This is popular.
Is this popular?
I've seen it before.
I love strawberry milk.
I like strawberry-flavored strawberry
milk.
This is the best.
You can adjust the concentration of your
own.
Next is this.
This is a cheese.
I eat a lot of cheese.
This is burrata cheese.
I love this.
I ate about 10 of this this summer.
I think I eat a lot.
I love this kind of cheese.
The inside of this cheese is very soft.
This is also mozzarella cheese.
This is like raclette cheese.
I love this.
I eat this.
I was caught.
This is a cheese that you can put on top
of the cheese.
I see.
This is the best.
I've always wanted to eat this.
This is a shell in.
What is that?
This is a famous product in Costco.
This is a famous product.
This is cream cheese.
Everyone buys this.
I haven't eaten the purchased video.
Did you eat it?
I ate it.
This is delicious.
Thank you.
I like watching the purchased video of
Costco.
This is a basic product.
I want to eat this all the time.
I want to eat this.
Let's eat this later.
What is this?
This is this.
This is a croissant.
I love croissants.
This is like a bread in Costco.
This is very cute.
This is a lot.
This is the back.
I don't have anyone to show me the back.
This is good.
This is good on the outside.
This is cute on the back.
I wanted to eat croissants.
Please put a black croissant on it.
This is a black croissant.
I bought this because I wanted to eat
it.
This looks delicious.
Please call this a croissant.
I understand.
This is still in the back.
This is cold.
What is this?
This is a mixed fruit.
This looks healthy.
This is a strawberry, pineapple, red
grape and peach.
This looks delicious.
This is cold.
This is a great frozen product.
This is great.
This is convenient.
And this is a light color.
This is heavy.
This is like a grapefruit.
This is also a product introduction of
COSTCO.
I see.
You are very interested in COSTCO.
I don't write in Japanese.
This is also a product with 12 items.
This is a product that everyone eats.
I like you.
I like you very much.
This is a mashed potato.
I like mashed potatoes.
What is this?
This is a powder.
This is a powder that is mixed with
milk.
This is a powder that is mixed with milk
and fried in a frying pan.
This is English.
This is an English manual.
You do your best.
I will do my best.
Yes.
You bought this.
Is that so?
Yes.
I also put this in.
Did you put this in?
Yes.
This is a seaweed flake.
This is delicious.
I took a video of BEEF SHELL FISH in
Korea.
At that time, the food was spicy.
But I ate only rice and seaweed flake.
This is delicious.
I love this.
I can eat this forever.
This is a product that disappears
quickly.
This is the best.
And this is a mango.
I thought this was a mango.
This is a mango.
Call it a bear.
I bought a mango.
I have always liked mangoes.
You bought this after you went to
OKINAWA.
No, I bought this before that.
I bought this when I was in AKADAKE.
Is that so?
AKADAKE was 4 or 5 years ago.
So I bought a mango.
This is a mango.
I am happy to have this much.
This is me.
I eat hot pot every day in winter.
I have the image of eating this often.
Yes.
This is delicious.
I can eat this hot pot.
This is an everyday hot pot.
I eat this.
This is getting more and more.
This is amazing.
What do you think this is?
I already know.
This is written on the package.
This is a pillow.
I bought this.
I made a mistake and fell asleep.
I'm happy.
This is the case.
There is no one who loves pillows.
This is a pillow that breaks.
You will sleep with this from today.
Don't get your neck wrong.
This is ASMR.
I'm going to fall asleep.
Do that on the IKONOIJOI channel.
This is amazing.
I didn't think this was so big.
I want to eat this.
This is amazing.
This is big.
I'm very funny today.
I have to be funny today.
You are funny when you are here.
Next.
This is heavy.
Is this heavy?
This is also a dumbbell.
This is a mickey mouse.
Everyone loves this.
This is a popular mickey mouse.
This is a four-type ZAKURO.
I think someone drank ZAKURO.
I also had this at home.
I was taught to drink this at first.
I can drink various drinks from now on.
You are carrying this.
I'm cool.
This is a smoothie.
This is a candy.
This is a bread.
This is the last.
This is the most exciting.
I wanted both of these.
This is cute.
Is this cute?
This is bread.
This is the opposite.
This is the best.
This is baked a little.
This can be baked at home.
This is the best.
I want to make bread.
But this is difficult.
This is difficult to knead.
I want you to sell all of this.
This can be stored in the freezer.
You don't have to eat all of this.
This is half.
This is the best.
Why do you say that?
This is four.
This is cute.
Why do you show me the back?
The back of the bread is cute.
That's all.
Wow, a lot of food.
It's a party, so let's eat some.
What do you want to eat?
There are only a few things you can eat.
I can't eat pizza.
Let's drink this.
I bought milk at a convenience store
every time I drank this.
Great.
This is not Costco.
This is a convenience store.
Let's move on.
Cheese is delicious.
You are delicious.
You are delicious. I know.
Thank you.
I want to eat this.
This one too.
I think I can eat this one and this one.
Can I eat this?
Sure.
Eat, eat.
Eat a lot.
It's not good for the members.
That's true.
I've always wanted to see this.
Is that the one you open with your
mouth?
What?
Switch-type gummy.
Switch-type gummy?
Itadakimasu.
What?
It's good!
It's good? I haven't eaten it yet.
You're eating it first.
I'm eating it first.
Let's eat.
It smells really good.
It's good!
It's amazing.
What does it taste like?
Cream cheese?
It's written on it.
Oh, I wrote it down.
It's good!
I want to eat it with a snack at 3
o'clock.
I feel happy when I have this in the
refrigerator.
There's a lot.
It's the best.
If I had this at home, I would eat it
all in a day.
I agree.
I want to drink it as it is.
What if you drink it?
Wait a minute.
It's good!
It's not a transparent container.
It's not cute.
I'm not going to eat it.
We just drink it.
I want to drink it regularly.
Milk.
I haven't seen it.
It's okay.
It's amazing.
It looks delicious.
Do you know what it is?
It's a radish.
I haven't eaten anything since this
morning because of the plan.
I'm so hungry that I'm full of
motivation.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I think I put too much milk.
Let's try it.
Did you put too much milk?
No.
Really?
I put too much.
But it's delicious.
It's delicious.
Wait, it's almost gone.
I think so.
I should have ordered 100.
I hope it's in the regular bottle.
It's delicious.
It's good.
It's a good match.
It's good to put cheese in it.
You're a genius.
Am I?
I'll call you Dr.
Call me Dr. Anna.
Wow!
It's great!
It's great.
It's shining.
It's the best.
You're shining.
It's good.
So...
I'll eat it.
Wait, it's definitely delicious.
I love it.
How is it?
Delicious.
It's so delicious.
I'm not the type of person who talks.
I think it's the best to eat with
croissant.
I'll eat this one first.
It's fluffy!
It's good!
It's so good!
It's light.
Can you eat it right away?
I can eat a lot of Wassan.
It's a collaboration between cheese and
Wassan.
A collaboration.
Do you need a plate?
I'm good.
It's really good.
It's the best.
It's just our meal.
I like it when people eat it.
Me too.
This cheese is delicious.
It's definitely delicious with salad.
This cheese is almost gone.
It's too delicious.
It's delicious.
Can I eat this for the rest of my life?
You can eat it.
Thank you for watching.
So we ate it!
It was delicious!
I'm so happy!
I wonder if this happiness is enough.
I'm worried that I might wake up
tomorrow.
But we were able to share it with
everyone.
Please buy it!
Let's buy it at Costco!
It's definitely delicious!
Please subscribe to this channel and
like the video!
We're waiting!
Please!
This was Mayuka Sasaki and Anna Imamoto!
Costco!
The best!
Bye bye!