Ebichu's video!
Ebichu's video
Good morning.
The sun is so bright.
I was walking to the station when I got
here.
But there was no one.
It was like a red carpet.
It was scary.
Good morning.
This is the fan club event.
The fan club event was held in the
countryside.
It was a bit cold.
Wait a minute.
FC.
Good morning.
We are the staff of the fan club.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Let's go.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Boys and girls.
Welcome to Pacifico Yokohama.
Kiss?
It's Kyun!
The first part is over!
Minami was a little dirty, so I was
kicking her.
The first part is over!
It's over!
Lovely lovely!
Kyun!
Is it a Japanese TV show?
Welcome, ladies and gentlemen!
What's in your heart?
Let's have fun!
Let's get started!
Let's end it!
It was fun!
Let's meet at the next tour!
We're usually...
Can you see us?
Maybe not.
I think you can see us.
Please keep it to yourself!
Let's get started!
It's a wrap!
Lolita's back-up.
It's scary!
What's your dream?
I'm wearing a suit.
I've been dancing since I was a kid.
At last,
ebi-chu,
I'm very happy to be able to gather
the girl-kidsbie ends and get here.
I'm quite short.
This suit...
This suit is limited.
This suit is good.
It's spacious and comfortable.
This suit is cool.
I think it's cool to have someone who
gives you when you don't want it.
Of course, I'm really grateful that you
do something for me.
For example, recently, the manager is
waiting for me to cut it by myself.
The in-law will come with me.
I think it's really cool to have such a
great hospitality.
I hope that you can become a person like
that.
dB°C I'm wearing Lolita right now
Actually I Frei A Mask
I brought brilliant Lolita
I felt the
strong
Lolita
in the
sense
that I had
a long time
.
I've never
done it
with a wig on.
I have
this kind of
strong
wig on.
I know
that it suits me.
My
favorite is
cute.
I think
it's cute to show
what I like,
so I'll do my best to be
cute and cool.
I have a lot of
things I want to do.
I'm going to try it.
Wait a minute.
So,
this time,
I tried
the first half
on a
manor.
Anyway,
this is a really cool suit.
Is it a suit?
It's really cool.
I like this skin texture.
I watched
the movie
and
watched
Takarazuka
.
I tried my best
to be cool.
How about you?
So,
I'm cool, right?
I'm cool.
If I were a man,
I'd
have a good
man.
I want to do
a woman walking
on the shadow side.
I'm
a man.
I'm enjoying dancing
like that.
Even in the performance,
I change the way I say the lines
and the way I walk.
I'm doing it, so today I'm completely
enjoying it like a man.
Everyone, wait a minute. I don't know
what to say.
That was Hoshina.
So, the costume for the second half of
the fan club event is this Lolita
costume.
Cute, cute.
It's not easy to wear such a frilly
costume, so I was very happy. Thank you
very much.
At first, everyone was surprised, but we
sang it with a little more cuteness than
the usual singing style.
The cute I think is that I like to see
cute girls. So, I saw a lot of cute
girls on Instagram.
I saw a lot of cute things, like cute
K-tube and lovely K-tube. I think I'll
be cute, too.
I think my cuteness is very wide.
I think I'm cute because I'm very brave
when I see cute girls.
I want to absorb a lot from now on.
Cute!
It's like this.
It's so pink.
I was going to wear a different costume,
but I thought I'd do it. So I chose this
costume.
I'm Akashi Arigato.
I rarely dance, so I've never worn a
suit.
I'm glad it's fresh.
The cool I think is that I think it's
cool to be influenced by people.
I want to be a person who can be
influenced by people.
I'll do my best.
Cool
I'm Minata Kashiwa
I tried on Lolita's costume
I'm a little embarrassed
It's like a cute
This is my finger heart
I'm sure I'm going somewhere
I think it's cute
Everyone is cute no matter what
I think people who laugh a lot are
I think it's nice to smile
I'm really enjoying it from the bottom
of my heart
I think it's cute
I'll do my best
I laugh a lot
I'm not trying to laugh
I'm having fun
I'm having fun from the bottom of my
heart
I want to laugh
I'm going to sunbathe
It's time for a shower
Perfect!
Can't spare my face anymore
I'm allowed to mainly listen to the
singing
I am wearing a men's costume.
I am wearing a Kobayashi style.
How do you feel?
I'm the tallest in the group, so I feel
that suits me.
I am wearing a men's costume, so I feel
I think I'm cool.
I think it's cool to believe in yourself
and move forward without being trapped
by anything.
So I transformed from a man to a woman.
My hair is not straight now, so I
usually have long hair and bangs.
It's the first time I've had long hair
and bangs.
I feel like I've become a different
person when I do a live performance.
I had a lot of fun and I was able to do
it.
I don't have anything to do anymore, so
please keep an eye on me.
My favorite part of being cute is...
I want to be a person who is full of
cuteness from the atmosphere,
appearance, and personality.
I think that's cute.
I want to be cute like a pet or a dog.
I'm a little angry that I'm called a
Golden Retriever.
I'm trying to be cute like a Golden
Retriever.
How do you feel about wearing a men's
suit?
What?
What do you think about wearing a men's
suit?
I'm wearing a suit today.
I heard that the performance and singing
style of the men's suit is also a bit
manly.
I just took a live video, but I don't
know how to pose cool.
It's very difficult.
It's difficult to wear a men's suit, but
I was able to do it.
What do you think is cool?
I don't know what it is.
I don't like it.
I want to go back to being a girl soon.
I transformed and became Lolita.
I think the most important thing is that
girls are cute.
I'm very excited and excited.
I think it's important to think that you
are cute.
I'm confident when I say cute.
Everyone is cute.
I'm the cutest.
Please pose cutely.