Ebichu's video
The first day of the concert
Good morning, we are Asano-chan and
Shizue and Ryo-chan
Nice to meet you
Ebichu's video
Who is the chocolate from?
It's chocolate from someone. It says
sweet.
Can you see it?
I can see it.
It's Valentine's Day.
Thank you. I heard someone say
chocolate.
It's written Valentine's Day chocolate.
I'm going out.
She is excited.
Everyone is excited.
I'm going to get a massage.
You're tired.
Thank you for watching!
We are very grateful to the audience who
came to the concert.
We are very grateful.
Thank you very much.
Where are we?
PANZING!
EriChu!
Let's go to Japan!
PANZING!
It's summer, isn't it?
How was it?
It was fun.
It was fun but I don't remember.
You don't remember?
I was looking at the seats and I was
looking at the seats, but I don't
remember.
I don't remember.
I want to enjoy the world of light
green.
I respect Hinata.
I'm scared.
Let's do our best.
Let's do our best!
How was the power of the secret?
It's over.
The event is over!
This year's event is finally like this.
That's right.
It was like this.
Everyone, I'm wearing a home party at my
house.
Everyone is wearing cute pajamas.
It happened like this before.
Oh, my brother?
It doesn't matter at this time.
Even if you are a girl, you are a girl.
You are genderless.
I'm a brother.
If you want to see the details, please
enter the fan club.
You can see it in full.
The content is like this.
What was fun?
It was fun.
You sang today.
Yes, I sang.
I'm going to dance.
I'm going to sing.
I'm hungry.
Did you enjoy the event?
It was fun.
Have a good dream.
Bye bye.
Happy.
Please subscribe to the channel.
I hope you enjoy this video.
If you like this video, please subscribe
to my channel.
Thank you for watching.
I'll tell you my heart
Ah, I'll sing until you hear it
There's something I want to deliver to
the world
Let's go!
Shine기 siinä
Joy! Joy! Enjoy!
Let's both run n' jump
Didn't realize it wasn't over
Party Surviver
It adds more Krit이랑
But we're still not satisfied
In another mission, additional battle
Until the last breath
Thank you for watching!
I'm looking for a perfect girl who's
perfect for a princess.
Your Highness, that's me.
Please make a contract with me.
Please make a contract.
Cinderella of the
Fantastic
Season 1
Up this way
I fell in love
I want to tell you, but I'm scared of
this cowardly feeling
When I let go of my unwavering feelings,
will you smile gently at me?
I can fly with your eyes
Na na na na na na
Look at the sky, run around
I'm in love with the city, I'm going
crazy
No one is looking at us, we're getting
closer
Stop, the lip-sync is over
Don't be nervous, cheer up, cheer up,
more and more
I want a lot of things, I want to be a
star
I want to be the one I like
At this point, their red hair would do a
lot of damage, so there are해서
It's where they put something like a
This voice is your umbrella
Let's raise your volume
Because my heart is beating
Your noise is a sweat
I want to light up my heart
Let's raise our volume!
Thank you for watching!
I think it's beautiful
Every time our hands touch
Every time we reflect on each other
We feel the same way
Anytime, anywhere
Anywhere, loving you, baby
Thank you for coming here today.
Will you keep loving Ebichu?
Thank you.
Please keep supporting Ebichu.
That's all for today.
Have a nice day!