I forgot something.
This is my bag.
I'm an idol.
And the third one is...
The third one is...
Fashion!
Heart heart
I love fashion
But when I was in elementary school
Before I joined the group
I only said to my mom
to make my hair cute
But
I started to do this
When I was in the 5th grade
I got a lot of make up
from Ponytail
So
When I was in the 6th grade
I didn't do much make up
But I was really into hair
I practiced braiding and braiding
by myself
And during the live show
I was told by everyone
that I did make up
by myself
I'm really happy about that
Also
I'm still into hair
So I do it before the live show
But when the members
are having trouble with their hair
They ask me
to do it for them
I'm really happy about that
So I always do it for them
You do it for Chi-chan too?
I do it for Chi-chan too
Chi-chan
doesn't do all the hair
She helps a little
and does the back
and the back of her head
and does the back of her head
and she suggests
what to do
I do almost everything
for Nanaha Aoyama
for Chi-chan
You do everything?
Yes
That's amazing
I liked her hair
but I've been into
make up since middle school
I've been really interested
in make up
I didn't know much about
eyeliner and mascara
but I tried it
and my eyes
were really good
I'm happy
that I can get more and more cute
I'm learning how to do make up
Oh really?
Yes
I can hear a lot
from the makeup artists
I want to do
a show like that
I want to do it
but I still
can't draw
eyeliner well
So
I think
I'll use an hour
for eyeliner
when I do make up
Listen to Kamio
Let's do it
I'm doing it
today
but my eyeliner is too good
I was like
Oh my god
I can draw so fast
I learned a lot today
You girl
It's okay
well
That about,
us a forever
That's all
Thank you
so much
Thank you very much.
I'm glad if you come.
I was saved by a junior high school
student.
The sponsor of this program is...
Kurobushi
Makki
Tabasan
Kaniroi-san
Masuo-san
I sent it with a offer.
Thank you everyone!