Watch this video.
Thank you for watching.
No.
Not a single one.
What's going on?
What's wrong, Doctor?
It's terrible.
My invention has been stolen by someone.
What kind of invention is that?
It's a great invention of the century.
It's a medicine that makes you a super
idol.
A medicine that makes you a super idol?
Yes.
I drank it and tried to become a super
idol.
Who stole it?
I'm not here!
I'm suspicious.
I'm the assistant of this lab.
There are only you and me in this lab.
Someone might have sneaked in.
Of course, that's true.
I have a good idea.
I have a good idea. Please wait a
moment.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
What is that?
This is my invention.
Name it.
It's a medicine that can tell if you're
the culprit.
A medicine that can tell if you're the
culprit?
Here, drink this.
This?
Drink this.
Thank you for watching.
Delicious!
Oh, it's a treat!
There's still more!
But...
It doesn't seem like you're the culprit.
I told you!
I am looking for a girl who is worthy of
this genius.
Professor, that's me.
Let's find the culprit together.
Let's find it. Let's find it.
So, it means that someone sneaked in and
stole it.
Who is it?
Professor, there's a letter here.
What's that?
Try reading it.
What's that? Try reading it.
I received a drug for becoming an idol.
From the monster 2014.
Monster 2014?
Is that the culprit?
Oh, there's another letter.
It says 2.
Look at this.
Izuki Senpai
Rika Mayama Senpai
Natsu Anno Senpai
Ayaka Yasumoto Senpai
Aika Hirota Senpai
Hoshina Mirei Senpai
Suzuki Hirono Senpai
Matsuno Rina Senpai
Kashiwagi Hinata Senpai
What the hell!
Hey, isn't this...
...the Senpais from Shirito Ebisu Middle
School?
Who are they?
Inside this...
Kaijin 2014.
But how is he the culprit?
But isn't this 2 a hint?
2...
What?
2?
From 2 to 2
Paper?
There's paper
There's paper?
There is
Something
Should we write something?
Yes
Okay
Shiritsu Ebishuugaku 6th single will be
released on June 4th!
Wow!
The way you look down is...
Okay, the title...
The title is...
Butterfly Effect!
This single is one of the 10th
anniversary of the anime, Noita-Mina,
which is scheduled to be broadcast from
April 2014.
曲なかなのフェルギュリンアンチュース
We've decided on the opening theme!
Wow!
This is it! Don!
This one?
Put this on
Shirito Ebisu-yaku Spring Sony Music
Labels
Ruki Tour 2014
Reborn Chocho Bon and Settora
April 27th, Osaka
Osaka
This is a lot of information
I'm happy, but the person who stole the
medicine
That's right
These two
I wonder if it's a hint
I wonder
It's related to 2
2?
But the number 2 is a
Let's draw various 2 shapes on paper
2 shapes?
Let's draw a 2 shape
What is it?
It's like 2.
It's like someone who eats fast.
Who is it?
Thank you.
2.
2?
This...
This number 2...
This number...
How do you write?
Number 2...
Something is number 2?
What is it?
Before you write,
let's look up a lot of things.
Let's think about it.
Number 2.
Height...
Number 2 is big.
I...
I'm a little...
What?
Number 2
Number 2 is the person who is in the
second line.
The person who is in the second line?
The person who is related to the second
line.
line?
I think this is a hint.
This is...
What is it?
2.
Let's draw 2.
Should I just draw it normally?
2.
Let's try drawing it in various shapes.
This is in various shapes.
2.
Maybe I'll get some hints.
Can I just write it normally?
Like kanji?
Oh, I see.
I'll write 2.
Can I?
I wonder who it is.
Hint?
You should think about it too.
I got it.
2.
The person who was born in February.
There might be someone.
What is it?
Mizuki?
Mizuki was born in February.
Is she the culprit?
What is it?
2.
The person who was born in February.
What else is there?
I wonder if there's anything else.
2 and 2.
What is 2?
I can't think of anything like 2.
Until February.
Until February 22nd.
Like February 22nd.
What else?
How do you write 2?
How about writing 2 in Roman numerals?
Roman numerals?
Do you understand, Professor?
I'll try a new one.
Wait, I have to think.
I wrote 2 in Kanji.
I didn't write in Katakana.
2 is...
Katakana's 2?
I'll try.
Katakana's 2 is this 2.
This is Kanji's 2.
Is that so?
Oh, the same?
The same!
I'm not good at studying.
Wait, 2.
2.
I'll try in Roman numerals.
Thank you for watching!
Roman? I'll write it down.
I wrote it down.
I wrote it down like this.
There are two 2s.
This is Kanji, and this is Katakana.
And then...
Roman numerals. Let's write it down.
Roman numerals are...
2.
This...
Oh, yeah.
Wait.
I think I can think of something.
Please write it down.
This is...
Is it like this?
Let's read it normally
It's okay to read it normally, right?
Wait a minute
Did everyone understand?
Let's read it together
1, 2
But I don't understand that
This is...
I...
Should I forget the number and just read
it normally?
What do you think it is if you just read
Um... the alphabet...
I?
Yeah.
So, in other words...
So, there are two I's?
So, I got it!
The culprit is Ayai-san!
You've seen it well.
Ayai-senpai!
That's right, Doctor.
I took the medicine you invented, the
super idol medicine, from your nose.
From my nose?
Now I'm a super idol!
I'm going to read the color of the
southern school's home door.
The red leaf is green, the white is
blue, the prince's hair is purple, the
prince is red, the western is orange,
the komagome is yellow, the honkoma is
green.
Well...
Please, take me to the doctor.
Wow, is this the effect of the medicine?
No, but this is different. This is a
normal Aya-senpai.
It's painful.
Aya-senpai?
Kiki-sama...
That medicine is not just a medicine.
You got me.
Very very very very very.
You are...
Ashita Mana.
No, Ashita Mana.
Ashita Mana!
Please stop messing around, Hikari.
Sorry.
The medicine that makes you a super
idol.
There is no such thing as a useful thing
in the world.
To become a true idol,
you just need to have the support of
your fans and hard work.
So, we can go to China without you.
See, everyone, tomorrow is the day.
Tomorrow is the day.
Doctor, what is the medicine that you
stole?
It's a simple, scary, murderous virus
that if you take that medicine, you'll
become a monster.
What? Murderous virus?
Why are you doing this?
Why are you leaving me?
It's just an interior design.
Idiot! Why are you leaving me?
Nyu-ba!
Japan!
Hello everyone!
Hello!
I'm Shichie Bishuuwaku, number 11,
Kobayashi Kaho.
I'm Shichie Bishuuwaku, number 12,
Nakaayama Riko.
So today, we're starting a different
program from last time.
How was it?
Today, we have a guest, Hiroto Aika-
senpai.
Hi everyone, I'm Ebichu's mascot, number
6, Ayai-ko and Hiroto Aika.
Nice to meet you.
Can I ask you a question?
Please.
What's wrong?
It's okay.
This program is asking for your
questions.
Please send your questions to social
streams.
At the end of the program, we will
answer your questions.
Please send your questions.
We are waiting for your questions.
The first part started differently,
right?
I was surprised.
I was nervous.
Nuba.
Riko-chan is always a doctor.
She's a female doctor so she's a good
doctor.
It was the opposite.
That's why it was fun.
Her hair was like a girl's dress.
It was a little voluminous.
It was a little tight.
It was fun.
She was laughing.
Aiyai's panda.
It was cute.
It was like a mask.
And this.
Aikawa's Shinkansen.
It was cute.
It was number 6.
It was amazing.
The two were cute.
It was nice.
It was the same flower.
It was all flowers.
It was cute.
It was like a monster and a monster.
It was like a villain.
The way she laughed was fun.
She was laughing.
It was fun.
Everyone was like that.
It was cool.
It was like a mountain.
It was amazing.
I like the home door.
The home door?
The one with the green.
The color.
There was a different type of metal.
I want to see it today.
Amazing.
I understood it well.
Did you look into it?
Yes, I did.
Amazing.
Aiyaiya.
Is this tea?
This is amazing.
It smells good.
It's in.
Tea?
It's a little red.
Amazing.
Is it sweet?
It's amazing.
It's three times sweeter.
Amazing.
I'm surprised.
It's beautiful.
Do you want to try it?
It's warm.
It's good.
It's tea.
I want to eat this.
Eat it.
I want to eat it.
It smells good.
It's a cookie.
We can eat to whatever we want.
Let's eat together.
Let's eat it all together.
Thank you.
We all eat together.
Bye bye!
It's good.
It goes well with tea.
You just said a good thing.
There's a question in the place where
Yuka is eating.
What is it?
Question.
Ta-da.
Is there a place you want to go on a
tour?
Just the two of us.
But...
Where is it?
We want to go anywhere.
We've been saying this for a long time.
Please subscribe to our channel.
We want to go to the cherry blossom
garden.
We love cherry blossoms.
Let's go to Yamagata.
Yamagata.
That's the second one.
Boa wants to go to Oita.
We want to go to Kyushu.
We want to go to Oita.
Oise?
We want to go to Kyushu.
We want to go.
We want to go by plane.
We want to cry.
We can get consomme soup.
I like it.
It's delicious.
When you're flying,
you drink tea.
It swells.
When you bring candy,
it swells.
Let's try it.
Let's do it.
It's fun.
There was a tour announcement.
So we can go.
Maybe.
We can start in Osaka.
We can go to Osaka twice.
We can go to Osaka.
I like Osaka.
It's fun.
I've never been there.
Okonomiyaki.
Negi-yaki.
Takoyaki.
It's delicious.
The ice-dough is delicious.
The hot fried bread
has soft cream.
It looks delicious.
I want to eat it.
I'm curious about the TARZ.
I'm curious.
I'm excited.
There's a new song.
The costumes.
I'm looking forward to seeing the songs.
The first new song.
The first single.
We're the first ones to participate.
I'm excited.
The voice and the chorus part.
I wonder if the two of us are different.
That's what I'm looking forward to.
I'm curious.
I think everyone is looking forward to
it.
Next song.
NU'VER.
I'm into dancing lately.
Is there a song you recommend?
Dance?
I'm into dancing lately.
What is it?
NU'VER.
But it's just a song you recommend.
Yeah, like a song you like in the album.
I like the song, but I like the
choreography.
I heard it's hard to dance.
I haven't danced yet. I'm a little bit
slow. I'm so fast at memorizing the
dance.
I was crying when I couldn't remember a
song.
I can't remember it at all.
It's hard. I can't remember the dance.
You say that a lot.
I say it a lot.
What other song do you recommend?
What song do you recommend?
But you dance, right?
I think a song that's easy to dance to
is good.
There's a song that's just right.
What is it?
I'm nervous.
I think I can dance to it.
How was it?
I wonder what it was.
It was easy for everyone to dance.
It was cool.
It was difficult, but we did our best.
It was fun.
It was fun to dance with everyone.
And also, run more.
That was hard.
That was fun.
Run more.
When we all remember it.
You put your hand on the ceiling.
We're doing it with a lot of energy.
It was fun when we were dancing to run
more.
It was fun.
Run more.
How do you feel about it?
Well, I don't think we can change the
topic here.
We can't change it?
Finally, Sunday is the first week we've
been waiting for.
That's right.
How do you feel about Sunday?
This week, I'm going to be with Mizuki
and Mayama.
Both of them have their own unique
personalities.
But this time, I'm going to be with Aya
and Mirei.
They're completely different.
I'm really looking forward to it.
What would you like to do if you were to
be a producer?
There are a lot of things I want to do.
But one of them is a live performance
with only cool songs.
I think it's fun to do it with a man in
a live performance that's not a shrimp.
And...
Po-chan said she likes to do it with a
man in a live performance.
I like takoyaki, and I think it's fun to
do it with a man in a live performance.
But I don't know if it's okay.
I think it's fun to do it with a man in
a live performance.
Next, the Falafel Hold King.
We all draw pictures and present them
during the live performance.
It's fun!
It's so much fun that I can't decide.
But I don't know what will happen if
it's too much.
I think I'll be very worried if I'm left
to it.
It's fun!
The Falafel is fun!
What will you do if you become a
Falafel Hold King?
I want to run on the stage like a sports
event.
It would be fun if you really do it.
If you have an image so far, I hope you
have fun.
That's also important.
Thank you for your viewing.
But you like cucumbers, right?
So we all made a cucumber morning drink
party.
Cucumber festival.
Litter Produce.
That's a good idea.
The costume is green.
Cucumber.
Everyone is green.
It's fun.
It's fun, isn't it?
I don't know what it's going to be like
for the family.
I'm sure you'll have fun.
I'm looking forward to it.
質問? 何だっけ? アイエイがエビチューに入って、一番楽しかったこととか。
えー!一番楽しかったことなんだろ! でもいつも楽しいんだけど、
でもエビチューってさ、いろんな曲がある。 だから知らなかった。
自分ってこういう声も出るんだなって思う。
こういう風にできるんだなっていうのがいっぱい知れたのが楽しいかなって思う。
でも二人ももっとね、いろんな自分を知れるんじゃないかな。 そうか! そうだね。
今からやって、めっちゃリッターがクールな感じになるかもしれないしね。
なんたらどうすんの? イメージが!
私がクールになったらどうしよう。 今ちょっと髪の毛クールだった。
楽しいよね。 楽しそう。
自主で今回一部からマヤマヤがプロデュースしてくれるじゃん。
Let's listen to her voice on the phone.
I want to hear it.
Let's hear it.
I'll take it.
Okay.
Wow, she's coming.
Wow.
Hello?
ets Brian Sorry
ets Brian
Hello?
Good work, good work!
Is this connected?
Hello? This is Hirota
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
Hello?
We were talking about the school
festival
Yeah, we were
You were watching?
Yeah, we were playing games
You're so funny
You know, you're going to do a part of
the show
Yeah, I'm going to do it
It was a corner to listen to your
enthusiasm
Yeah
Yeah, yeah?
Are you going to do it?
I'll do my best.
Just that?
Because...
It's like a joke?
It's going to be like that.
There's no...
Family...
I'm glad I heard it.
I'm going to make a joke.
I'm not going to do it.
I don't have a cosplay, but...
I'm going to do it.
It's a little different again.
It's like Mayama.
I hope you enjoy the Ebichu world in
Mayama.
It's a big deal.
Then, both of you.
Mayama.
Let's talk.
Hello.
Good evening.
Mayama.
You can talk to me now.
Hello?
Kaho?
I'm talking to you now.
I'm nervous to call you.
I'm nervous.
Mayama,
I can hear your voice!
It's because you're on the phone.
What's the question, Mayama?
I was watching you.
How were the three of you at Nuva?
Nuva, right? It's Nuva!
I was going to go out with Nuva when I
got a call, but I couldn't get out.
I'm laughing at the phone.
Nuva!
It's popular.
I wonder if it's popular.
Hello?
Can you hear me?
I have to get closer.
Yeah.
Riko?
Yes, it's어요.
Riko? Yes, it's Riko.
It's a cucumber.
No, it's not!
No!
It's the current Kaho-chan.
The current Kaho?
I'm the senior.
Which is which?
I don't know.
I wonder if it's this scary.
It's Aiyai.
It's not Aiyai.
It's Aikari Hirota.
It's Riko Nakayama.
There's a grandma on the phone.
What's going on?
What's this?
It's funny.
I don't know.
I'm Hinota Aika.
There was a girl who looked like Hashida
Mara.
I made a mistake.
What's your name?
I'm Hinota Aika.
I'm Riko Nakayama.
I'm Kobayashi Kamo.
It's time to say goodbye.
Goodbye.
Cut it. Thank you.
Please look forward to it.
Yes.
Thank you. Good luck.
Thank you. Bye bye, Mayama.
Bye bye bye.
Bye bye.
Mayama, thank you.
Thank you.
Bye bye.
The phone is so funny.
I get nervous when I'm on the phone.
Really? I can't see your face.
What if you're angry?
I get nervous.
While we were coming here,
we got a job.
A job?
Yes, a job.
I was like, bring it to me.
I think it's for the two of us.
What is it?
It's written here.
It's a job for Kahoriko.
What is it?
Kahoriko will be doing a special report
on Sunday.
Wow, a report.
What's your feeling right now?
It's for us.
It's a report.
There wasn't a report.
I'm glad that the two of you came on
Sunday.
I'm glad you came.
This report will be broadcasted on the
next episode of Sora's Kahoriko.
That's great.
So go to Sora on Sunday and report.
Next time on Kahoriko...
...is going to be a long one.
What are we going to do?
I'm excited!
We have to be reporters.
It's a bit difficult, but...
We'll do our best!
I'm excited!
Amazing!
We'll be reporters.
How are you feeling right now?
I'm practicing.
I'm practicing for the report.
I'm going to practice.
Okay.
Today, how was it?
Today, it was fun.
Today,
Please tell us how you felt today.
Today, I watched the first video of
Kaoriko.
The second video was a little rough
because of the bad tempo.
I watched Kaoriko's hard work.
I'm very happy to be able to appear.
I'm looking forward to the next video.
I'll check the world.
Thank you very much.
You watched it.
That's right.
That's great.
It was fun. I'm looking forward to it.
Do your best. I'm looking forward to it.
I'll do my best. I don't know if there's
a Gari-ben or not, but I hope there is.
I'm getting excited.
I'll say goodbye here.
Then it's about time. That's right.
It's the end of the corner.
The time is...
The time for the end of the experiment
has come.
Thank you, Hiroto Aikawa Senpai.
Thank you.
Keep up the good work.
I will.
Bye bye.
Thank you, everyone.
Wow, I'm surprised.
Should we bring this microphone?
This one?
Let's use this microphone.
How do you feel now?
Please bring it.
I only said this.
Let's think about it a little more.
Let's go a little more like a reporter.
Then bring the camera.
How do you feel?
I'm surprised.
I'm looking forward to it.
How was it today?
Today...
It was a little different from usual.
It was a different appearance from
usual.
I was a little nervous.
I was nervous.
Acting.
Acting was a little...
I was wondering if it was okay.
It was okay.
It was fun.
It was fun to change the mood.
I want to do it better.
Then, do another one.
Next time...
Sorry.
Okay, then...
Thank you for watching the program until
the end.
We are Shirito Ebisu High School, No.11
Kobayashi Kahori and
Shirito Ebisu High School, No.12 Riko
Nakayama.
We are
Sol, Hiro, and Kahori.
Bye bye.
Bye bye!
Next time, we'll be looking forward to
the next episode!
See you next time!