Yakan and A-i-do-ru?
I love anime games.
That's a long time ago.
The first time I touched a game was when
I was 4 years old.
That's early!
Nintendo's Wii was the first game I
played.
I've liked games since I was little.
What's your favorite game?
I'm into Apex.
I love FPS games.
Do you communicate with each other
online?
Yes, I do it with my friends in the
game.
I also do it alone.
Do you have a special account?
I don't know.
I don't have a special account.
I have to tell you that.
I'm into games.
I don't have a special account.
Do you know your gender?
I don't know my gender.
I don't want people to think I'm a girl.
That's an extra thing to do when you
play games.
I just want to play games.
I'm completely alone in my private life.
I'm in this game to enjoy it.
Do you watch anime?
I watch anime.
I've been watching anime for a long
time.
I haven't said it, but I've been
watching a lot of anime since I was in
middle school.
Why do you like anime?
I like cute girls.
I'm an otaku.
I like the color of the hair and eyes
that are not realistic.
I like the voice and the appearance of
the characters.
I admire them.
I've always liked pre-cure since I was a
kid.
I like anime.
I get energy from anime.
Can you tell me your favorite anime?
I like the anime called Isekai Seikatsu.
Do you think you can appear in an anime
as a voice actor?
I don't have to appear in an anime.
I want to appear in an anime.
Voice actors are great professionals.
I don't think I can be in the anime.
It's a painful story.
I want to be a voice actor.
I think it's better for professionals to
appear in an anime.
I think it's good.
I want to be a voice actor in Kyushu.
I would be happy if I could be a voice
actor.
I see.
I want to see Seta without a limiter.
I'm often told that I'm different from
Seta.