I love boy manga.
I wrote my graduation thesis in Jump.
What?
The best grade manga was YuYu Hakusho.
I love boy manga.
Hello, I'm Honoka Akimoto, a member of
Team Shachi.
Where do you think I am now?
I'm at the studio!
Isn't it amazing?
And it's the Jump! Editing Department.
When I was recording the nightclub,
I was told that I love boy manga and
jump.
I was brought here by the studio.
Yay!
I'm so happy!
When I left the elevator,
I saw a dream world.
As far as I can see,
all of these are made here.
I'm impressed.
I came to such a place.
I'm going to talk about Jump.
I'm going to call him.
He is Sugito, a member of Dr. Roboco.
Nice to meet you.
Sugito Sugito
I'm so happy.
I read Dr. Roboco every week.
I laugh every week.
Miyazaki-san will be happy.
It's really interesting.
What is it called?
It's not a jump homage.
It's a parody.
A parody that doesn't feel any
discomfort.
It's a lot of fun.
It's not just about One Piece.
There are many things.
The most interesting thing for me was
the model of the human body.
The model is Anmika.
That's the most interesting.
I was impressed.
Anmika was very happy on Instagram.
It's not just that.
It's really interesting.
I came all the way here.
Can I go inside?
I will guide you.
Thank you.
Yay!
I will guide you.
I arrived at Sugita's desk.
Look at this!
There are many Roboco!
I'm really curious about this.
Roboco is really made of many goods.
There are also such things.
Yes, Bandai-san has been making many
things for us.
We have been making a lot of things
since before the anime.
The design is also very good.
Yes, it is.
I'm sorry, I noticed that.
Are you making my design?
Yes, I am.
I wrote Roboco on the third edition of
this magazine.
I wrote it on behalf of the editorial
department.
I'm glad. Thank you.
It was written in 2022.
It's quite recent.
Yes, it is.
It's very recent.
Thank you.
So you're in charge of the Robocop's
fighting scenes now?
Yes.
What did you do before that?
I was in charge of the promised
Neverland.
So that's how you got the promised
Neverland?
Yes, you know it well.
Do you know about the promised
Neverland?
The promised Neverland was made into a
movie.
I'm sure everyone knows about it, like
Keiko Kitagawa.
It's a gag manga that doesn't have any
serious feeling.
Yes, it's a gag manga.
I was in charge of both of them.
I was still a serialized manga artist at
the time.
I see.
That's how Robocop was born.
Yes, Enotachi was...
Yes, I was pretty good at that.
I really loved that.
You know the promised Neverland.
I've been reading it.
I've been talking about the promised
Neverland with the people in the editing
department.
Really?
There were people who read it.
Robocop was also in the anime in
December.
Yes, it was in December.
I watched it a little.
It was a PV.
I watched the PV.
I didn't expect the voice actor of
Robocop to be Chocopla.
It was Matsuo from Chocopla.
It was perfect.
Yes.
I was asked to come to Miyazaki-san's
place to record a program on Fuji TV.
I see.
I was told that Robocop's voice was like
Matsuo from Chocopla.
I was told to call me if I was in the
anime.
I auditioned properly.
I see.
I liked the director.
It's a short program, about 5 minutes.
It's a 10-minute program.
Yes, it's a 5-minute program.
It's easy to watch, so please watch it.
I want to say what I like.
Robocop's cover is full of jump lines.
Can I see it?
I really like it.
This is a parody of Chainsaw Man.
Is this a Death Note?
Yes.
This is a Death Note.
This is a foot bath.
It's a jump plus.
I recently watched Hunter x Hunter.
Did you just release it 2 hours ago?
I watched it.
I saw it on the Internet 2 hours ago.
I checked it.
The promised Neverland was also in the
first part, right?
Yes, it was in the second part.
The cover of Neverland was not the first
part.
It was in the third part.
It's a parody of the jump cover.
Jump cover?
Who is this?
This is where my mother was.
I was impressed that I could play with
the cover.
Thank you very much.
I'm addicted to it.
Thank you for promoting it.
I want to see it.
Can I see these details?
Is there anything that motivates you
when you work?
Like, something that motivates you?
Like, something that motivates you to
decorate, or something that motivates
you to do this.
What motivates me?
But I don't have any colors like this.
I was doing this with my teacher.
I was doing this because I thought it
would be nice to have my senpai do it.
But recently, I've been doing a lot of
it.
It's a little messy.
I like that.
I like it when everything is decorated.
I've been liking this Roboco lately.
I like this Roboco.
It's cute.
This Roboco.
And this one that the artist gave me.
Wait, wait, wait.
This is the latest one.
Lux Bell.
Can I have it?
Yes.
Lux Bell.
It makes me happy.
It makes you happy.
It makes it interesting.
Is this a snack?
It's a snack.
It's a ramune.
I'm surprised that there are so many
funny elements.
There's a desk.
Do you have more things?
Like editors.
I have a manuscript and a desk.
I have a lot of documents.
It's a weekly serialization.
What kind of time is it?
When will it arrive?
It's a serialization.
But I make it in a week.
Do you check it immediately when it's
sent at night?
That's right.
It's a week.
Otherwise, it's a big day of the week.
It's hard.
That's right.
I'm doing it.
I think it's because I have love.
You are a model for a character called
Black Clover.
That's right.
I think you appeared in it.
I'm a character called Kahono in the
temple.
Thank you.
Today is the day off for the editing
department.
There is a person in charge of Black
Clover.
You can see the manuscript of Black
If you like, you can see it.
Is that okay?
I want to see it.
Please.
I'll go and see it.
Thank you.
Thank you for watching.
It's amazing.
Fukuda-kun is preparing the manuscript
now, so please wait a while.
I'm looking forward to it.
I really love the picture of Tobata-
sensei.
He is very good.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
It's overwhelming.
I see.
I was a fan of him before he debuted, or
before he made his debut in Black
Clover.
Is that so?
His picture is very cool.
Have you ever seen it?
No, I haven't.
I saw it in a magazine.
You have it, right?
Yes, I have it at home.
I'll show you the picture of the
serialization.
It's amazing.
Fukuda-kun has prepared it.
Thank you for waiting.
I'm Fukuda, a Japanese chef who is in
charge of Black Clover.
Fukuda-san, I'm Hanoka Akimoto. I'm
getting a lot of energy every week.
Thank you. I can do my best because
Ashita is doing his best.
That's right. Ashita is always doing his
best, so Kaba-sensei is doing his best
every week.
I hope you can see the final of his hard
work.
I prepared about 3 items.
Is it a center column?
That's right.
I will explain as it is.
There was a manuscript that displayed
the verb of the recent jump.
I think I can show you this manuscript
directly.
Wow!
This is the cover.
It's amazing!
It's this size!
It is a manuscript displaying the verb
of the 27th year of the 21st century.
It's cool!
The muscles are amazing!
It's amazing!
Do you want to touch it?
I won't touch it!
There is Yuno below.
Yuno is drawn in this size and can be
put on like this.
It's a waste.
I want to show this too!
I made various products with this.
I see.
It's cool!
Recently, I have been drawing with
Copic.
There are many artists who can paint in
analog.
I think he is one of the best artists.
What's going on with the people who
choose this?
I don't know.
Do you draw with a pen?
Yes.
I see.
I was in charge of Oda-sensei.
He is good at analog.
I asked him how to draw.
But I didn't know anything.
I didn't know what he was saying because
he drew in 4 colors.
It's amazing.
I see.
He is a professional.
It's cool!
I like his facial expression.
Recently, I have been drawing with
Mr.Sawa.
I have been watching his videos.
He is getting closer to recent
illustrations.
He is getting better at drawing
techniques.
I think that's why he is getting better.
I like the battle scene.
It's powerful.
He uses a lot of pieces.
I like that.
Mr.Sawa is very good at battle scenes.
He is always looking for a cool scene on
the screen.
I think that's why I can recommend him.
Magic is something that moves.
I think it's amazing that he can express
it with just a picture.
But it looks like it's moving.
I think so.
You have seen a lot of his
illustrations.
Is he one of the best?
He is one of the best in the world of
manga.
He is the best.
He is proud of himself.
He can draw fantasy manga with a jump.
He is a person with overwhelming drawing
ability.
Is it difficult to draw fantasy manga
with a jump?
But I think everyone is overlooking it.
He doesn't have the ability to express
it.
He is a person who has magic.
He is a person who can draw only with a
black and white pen.
I think he has a lot of drawing ability.
That's amazing.
Thank you.
We have one more question.
The final chapter of Black Rose has
recently been released.
Can you show us the special set color?
That's right.
It's a two-piece set.
I've never seen it before.
It's like this.
It's exciting.
Please subscribe to our channel.
This is the final chapter of the autumn-
winter tour.
This black is the final chapter.
This is it.
It's cool.
I don't need this.
This is very rare.
It's a vegetable.
This is a soft one.
By entering the final chapter, we could
see the costumes of the ASTAR and Mio.
Yes, it was.
It was a cool experience.
I was worried about drawing each frame
so beautifully.
It's amazing.
Each background is an artwork.
I think this painting is very convincing
even without a background.
It's amazing that you can draw each
frame in a week.
It's a miracle.
It's cool.
You are a Yuno-fan.
I'm sorry.
I didn't say that.
You said that you were a Yuno-fan.
I'm a Yuno-fan.
I'm getting the energy from you.
Yuno is a good person.
He is cool.
He is a genius.
He is a good person.
He is born to be a genius.
But he is a good person because he
recognizes you.
I love Yuno who loves you.
That's right.
I love you the most.
I love you who loves me.
I will say that from now on.
Thank you very much.
It's amazing.