Hello everyone, I'm Ruri Aoi from UCCA.
Thank you for your support.
Today, I'm going to eat gummies.
I love gummies.
I'm an idol who loves gummies.
I eat gummies a lot.
This time, I'm going to eat...
The gummies I ate today...
I'm going to eat gummies.
I'm so nervous.
What should I do?
I don't usually talk to myself.
I'm talking too fast.
I'll do it slowly.
By the way, do you know that gummies are
easy to make?
Oh, you don't know that.
I didn't know that.
But I'm going to show you how to make
gummies easily.
I'm going to make gummies.
Please subscribe to my channel.
It's juice.
Gelatin.
White and transparent...
A bowl that can be used in the
microwave.
A mold.
A measuring spoon.
I'm going to use this to make gummy.
Yay!
I love gummy!
I will clean my hands.
I will clean my hands to cook.
I will cook safely and enjoy.
My hands are clean.
I love gummy!
I changed my clothes to apron.
I think I look cuter in this way.
So, I'll make it now.
I'll mix 70ml of juice with 2
tablespoons of sugar.
I'll make grape juice first.
I heard someone saying that I'm scary.
I'll measure 70ml and put it in.
I'll put it in. I did a little flying.
7!
I did it well.
Next, 2 tablespoons of sugar.
I like it.
It smells like grapes.
Is this enough? Too much?
It's okay.
It's the amount of starch.
I think it's better to put in more
sugar.
I put in a lot.
I'll mix it.
Is it mixed?
I finished mixing.
I'll wrap it and heat it in the
microwave for 1 minute.
I'll put it in.
Put it in the bowl and heat it for 1
minute.
Ready, go.
It's warm.
It doesn't smell yet.
Super Lully Tango
Hello everyone!
I'm Lully Aoi.
I've been practicing winking lately.
When I finish a song during a live
performance, I try to close my eyes.
But no one notices.
Why?
Because no one is watching me.
Please watch me.
Thank you very much.
15 seconds left.
I have 15 seconds of free time.
I'm wearing a cute dress today.
I'm a girl.
And I'm wearing a bra.
The apron that looks good on me is a
home-made one.
I'm done.
I'm going back.
It looks delicious.
It smells good.
I'm going to eat it.
Next, I'm going to add gelatin and mix
it well.
Please mix it well.
I'm going to heat it for 20 seconds.
I'm going to eat it.
Oh, it's 20 seconds.
Super Lullityme
Today is braiding.
How is it?
I don't braid much.
Does it look good on me?
I've been braided.
I haven't done it much lately, but I did
it after a long time.
It's over. Lullityme
I'll open it.
I got it.
Be careful, it's hot.
It's turning white.
The smell of grapes.
I'm going to put it in a mold.
Next, I'm going to put it in a mold.
Please look.
There are many cute molds.
I'd like to make a cat mold.
It's a little messy.
Oh, but...
But...
It's a little messy.
It's like a melted gummy.
I've never melted it before.
How is it?
It's looking good.
It's done.
I'll put this in the fridge for about 30
minutes.
It's easy.
I'll make pineapple.
Next, I'd like to make pineapple.
I'll dry it.
It's Super Lulu Time!
It's always the same.
What should I talk about next?
I'll talk about the gummy I met
yesterday.
I met a gummy with a cherry flavor
It was released a while ago, but I
finally met it.
It's really delicious.
It's chewy, but it tastes like cherries.
I love dark cherries.
I think it was made for me.
I like fluffy gummies, too.
I'm glad.
Thank you.
I haven't eaten it yet, but I've seen a
black gummy recently.
I still wonder what the black gummy
tastes like.
I'll get it and solve the mystery.
I want to be a gummy-loving idol.
That's what I'm thinking.
I have 6 seconds left.
I'll wink.
We matched? OK!
OK, it's done.
I'm going to cool it down.
Let's warm it up in the microwave!
Yes, it's time for Super Lully Time!
I was very nervous at first.
I'm getting closer to the end of the
show, so I'm starting to loosen up.
The staff first told me,
I'm nervous today, I'm not going to make
it.
I'm doing great today as well!
Well, I have 40 seconds left, so what
should I talk about?
What do you want to know about me?
Well, recently, my fans have been
saying,
Lully Numa, I'm going to fall into my
swamp.
They've been saying that kind of thing.
I hope a lot of people who are watching
this will be swamped.
I hope you'll know about Aoi Lully.
I'm Aoi Lully, the best!
I'm Aoi Lully!
I'm Kiyoki! Thank you!
That's all for my speech.
I'm embarrassed. I'm embarrassed. I'm
embarrassed.
I have 10 seconds left.
What should I do in 10 seconds?
I'm leaning on my shoulder today. I'm
sexy, right?
I'm going to be a good girl. It's time.
Next, I'd like to put it in my bear's
mold.
After all, cooking is rough.
Speed?
Hand skills?
I'm surprised at my skill.
I think you're cooking normally.
I think so, too.
I haven't done it yet, though.
OK.
I'll cool it down.
I love gummy.
I have 30 minutes, so I want you to know
more about me.
I will answer more and more questions.
Let's get started.
Start!
Cat
Sake
Juice
Egg
Tamagoyaki!
Mushroom!
Gymnastics!
Gymnastics Festival!
Uka!
Shabekuri 7!
Tokyo Revengers!
Baymax!
Kakyoin!
Jet coaster
Salmon
Bread
Salt
Apple
Aoi
Magazine
What?
Momotaro
Aoi
Marumoto
A refrigerator
LINE
Ichiji
Shichiji
Dog
Reiji-uchi
Kako
Isukara ochiru
Eve
Nameko
Cabba... Lettuce
Daibukaijo? Jingu
Pino, Apapiko
What is your favorite food?
Tomato soup
What is your favorite anime?
Ponytail
Osaka Lover
When is the best time to go to the
beach?
December
What is your favorite place?
Pe
Train
I like car
Where do you want to go?
Hokkaido
What is your favorite place?
Strawberry
Favorite word?
Pink
Short pants
Favorite season?
Winter
Eyebrows 1mm down
Cap
To be big
I love gummy
I've finished 50 questions.
Did you know about me?
I knew!
Thank you very much.
I think you've learned a lot about me
by watching my additional information.
Thank you very much.
I love gummy.
30 minutes have passed.
I don't know if it's solidified.
I'll take it out and check it out.
Cat...
Isn't it amazing?
It's like a pig.
Cute.
It's very nice.
How is it, everyone?
Isn't it amazing?
It's a lot of gummies.
Look at this.
Purupuru
The problem is this one.
I don't know if Christmas tree is
solidified.
Can I get it?
I'll do it right away.
I did it!
It looks good.
It's solidified.
This is a gummy.
It's done well.
The ones on this side are transparent.
This one is a little smooth and matte
gummy.
I'm looking forward to eating it.
Please subscribe to my channel!
How is it, everyone?
It's going well, isn't it?
It was very easy and fast.
How is it? It looks delicious, doesn't
it?
Well, first of all, I would like to eat
it as a representative.
I'm sorry.
It's easy for everyone, so please try
it.
I'll eat the bear.
I'm sorry.
I'll eat it.
Mmm-hmm-hmm-hmm-hmm-hmm-hmm-hmm-hmm-hmm-
hmm.
Well, it's...
It's more elastic than I thought.
I thought it was like jelly.
I love the feeling of puffing, but it
tastes like an apple.
Oh, it's a lot of gummy.
The gummy I make myself is a little
different, isn't it?
Love.
I'm in love with gummy.
Well, I feel like I'm not going to eat
it. I'm sorry.
But I thought, well, I think I'm the
best.
I thought I was a genius at making
gummy.
I felt that it was a little thinner than
the ones on the market, so if you think
it's good,
I think it's a little different if you
add a little more dark one or sugar.
The texture is like a slightly soft
gummy, but this bear was slippery
around, so it was like a 4D gummy.
Then I will also have this pig-like cat.
I just ate the grape flavor, but the
grape one has a stronger taste than the
apple one, and it was a little hard.
So if you like hard things, it might be
better to do it a little longer.
I feel like it has a gummy-like
elasticity.
The grape flavor is also strong and
delicious.
I love gummies.
I love gummies, so I think it's natural
that you think it's delicious.
So, I'd like to tell you that it's
delicious to eat it with the kind Shirai
who is always kind to me.
So, please.
Yes, I'll eat it.
This is a beautiful and cute girl I
haven't touched, so please eat it.
How is it?
Gummy.
It's a gummy, isn't it?
It's delicious, isn't it?
Gummy.
Oh, this is delicious.
It's delicious.
It's a very, very gummy, isn't it?
The texture is pretty similar, isn't it?
I put in a lot of sugar, but it's
surprisingly sweet and easy to eat.
It's delicious.
I got it.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
I love gummies.
Thank you for watching this video.
This gummies are very easy to make.
Anyone can make it.
You can make it with the juice, gelatin
and sugar at home.
Please try it.
If you have children, you can make it
without using fire.
Why don't you make it for your children
or give it to them as a gift?
I learned today that it's easy to make.
I hope you can make it and eat a lot of
gummies.
Please try it.
Thank you for watching.
Please subscribe to my channel.