Good evening, welcome to Doreski
Tokoresuki MC, I'm Araichi Iwai.
I'm Kumada Akane.
Thank you for having us.
Today's guest is the first time on the
show, the first 6 members of Stardust
Planet, vocal and dance group, UCCA.
I see.
I've been taking acting lessons at
SPARTANA recently.
What is it?
I can't tell you yet, but I've been
taking acting lessons at SPARTANA.
What is it for?
To improve my acting skills as a voice
actor.
Oh, as a voice actor?
Yes.
Not to be on stage?
No, I'm taking acting lessons to improve
my acting skills.
I see.
After all, voice actors are also called
acting.
That's right.
I thought I had to learn live acting.
I've heard that the scariest episode
you've ever been scolded by someone.
Why are you asking that all of a sudden?
I've been told a lot, and it's like,
you're so dark!
I thought, you're so dark.
I thought, you might be a little dark,
but I don't know what to do.
So I've been fighting against that
lately.
I know, I know.
The producer of the show said,
You're not funny.
I was thinking of killing him.
You're so strong.
I didn't think about it at all.
I thought I'd kill him somewhere.
If I become famous, I'll show him off
and kill him.
This is dangerous.
But you haven't done it yet, right?
I haven't done it yet.
Oh, you haven't? But you still have a
grudge against him.
I don't forget things like that.
Oh, really?
I don't forget about Mr. Spaldara.
I just want to hurt him later.
I don't think you're asking me to think
about this teacher, but if I'm told to
do it, I'll do it someday.
Let's do it like that.
I'll do my best.
Then, let's start today's show.
Music Variety Dresky and Koresky
What is this?
Today's guests are the UCCA members!
Thank you!
Good evening, we are UCCA!
I'm Ayame Kawase.
I'm Moa Serizawa.
I'm Ruri Aoi.
I'm Rina Yuki.
I'm Sora Wakane.
I'm Riju Murahoshi.
Thank you for coming!
First, we will introduce UCCA.
The first 6 members of Stardust Planet.
As a vocal and dance group, they have a
strong singing ability and musical
talent.
They have a variety of solo music
collaborations.
They will have a major debut on November
16th.
They are expected to do better in the
future.
They will have a major debut soon.
The name UCCA has a deep meaning.
Yes.
Until 2019, I was active under the name
Sakura Ebisu.
There was a surprise that I was renamed
after a live performance.
I didn't know that I had a name.
Suddenly I was called UCCA.
The reason is that I was born in the
Sanagi family.
So I was UCCA from Uka.
So you've been in Sanagi all along.
That's right.
You were a Sanagi unit.
I will continue to be UCCA.
I will talk about the charm of UCCA's
group.
I summarized the charm of the program.
This is it.
It is a youth novel with a literary
group concept.
The work that UCCA plays is a feeling of
excitement.
It is a feeling of excitement.
It is a youth song that is encouraged,
irritated, and nostalgic.
It is a youth song that is accepted by
the same generation.
What is this?
This is a beautiful summary of the
charm.
I see.
You always write a song.
This is a poetic feeling.
I wrote a song that I thought was
poetic.
You wrote a song that was poetic.
This is a youth novel.
The image of our group is youthful.
This is a youthful feeling.
Each person is different.
Who is the most beautiful?
I have a favorite.
I like RINA's sleeves.
You look more girly.
Her sleeves are voluminous and cute.
She is cute.
I was chosen by myself.
I couldn't say I didn't like it.
I don't like girls like Kurione.
Kurione is cute.
I like Kurione.
I see.
This is a concept from that point.
This is a youthful element.
You are in the middle of your youth.
You are in your mid-to-late years.
Have you ever had a song that you
sympathize with?
I have a song that I support.
I listen to this song when I'm having a
hard time.
I was encouraged by this song.
I see.
I don't think I'm singing.
Don't say such a sad thing.
I see. You are trying to be creative.
Which one is this?
Hello, viewers of Dresskid and Koreskid.
I'm Kitone.
I'm Yuki Yamazaki, Kitone's bassist.
I'm Hana, the vocalist.
I'm Shunsuke Hirano, the guitarist.
This time, we released a new limited-
edition single, No One Knows, on
November 2nd.
The song, No One Knows, is a song about
a young man who is just leaving his life
behind.
The music video illustrations and
animations were drawn by the mangaka,
Shouichi Taguchi, and I think that you
will be able to feel the world of this
song more deeply by listening to it with
Taguchi-san's work.
So please check the music video.
Yes, we will update the latest
information on the official Kitone
homepage and official Kitone Twitter, so
I would be happy if you could check it
out.
It was very fun to have you call us for
the first time before and to have the
same Saitama reaction as the Buddha's
prayer.
That's right.
So, I'd be happy if you could call us to
the studio again for some opportunity,
including these new songs.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Then, please enjoy the new song, No One
Knows, by Kitone.
That's all from Kitone.
Dore Dore
From here on out, this project
will be a new attraction with various
talk themes.
DORE KORE BOX!
We'd like to talk about the topics that
came out of that box.
Please pull it out.
Here we go.
Go ahead.
The first one.
It's the first one.
How to eat food you hate is...
Aoi Ruri's talk theme.
What food do you hate?
I'm not good at eating peppers.
There are many members who are not good
at eating food.
I want to overcome it by thinking that I
can eat delicious food anywhere.
I think you did something to make it
possible to eat peppers.
What is it?
On TV the other day.
That's a good information.
I'm sorry.
I can't remember that at all.
Please remember it.
Please search for it.
You can eat peppers that you saw on TV.
What food do you hate?
I hate pickles.
I know that.
You know?
I can't eat anything but eggplant and
cucumber.
I can't eat eggplant and cucumber.
It's disgusting.
Pickles are crunchy.
It's like a food that an old lady eats.
It's delicious.
I can't eat it.
I can't eat shiso.
It's a little addictive.
I can't eat it.
What was the name of the pickled shiso?
Shiba.
Shiba-zuke.
That's the worst.
You have mixed the two.
I can't eat it.
What is it?
I have a lot of food.
The food I hate the most in the world
is.
It's the worst food in your world.
Everyone in the world hates it.
I hate it.
What is the food you hate in your world?
I hate steamed rice balls.
Steamed rice balls?
It's rare.
I hate steamed rice balls.
Do you hate steamed rice balls?
I hate it.
why?
I can't eat it.
It's delicious.
It tastes like soup stock.
I ate it for the first time in a
restaurant.
I hate milk, but I can't eat it.
You can't eat it.
I can't eat it.
You can't eat steamed rice balls.
You can't eat creamy food.
I'm not good at it.
I'm not good at milk food.
You can't eat steamed rice balls.
I hate steamed eggs.
I hate eggs.
You can't eat eggs.
I hate it.
What should I do?
There is a lot of milk in it.
I can eat it if I don't know it.
I can't eat it if it tastes like eggs.
What about pudding?
I like caramel pudding.
You can't eat it unless you mix it with
pudding.
I'm not good at it unless I eat it while
thinking about caramel.
That's hard.
What else do you hate?
I hate sushi.
You can't eat anything.
I like to eat what I like.
I like hamburger, fried chicken, and
ramen.
You are a child.
You are a boy.
Please play the next song.
Yes.
Speaking of autumn, Riju-chan.
Me.
Speaking of autumn, do you like autumn?
I like autumn.
My birthday is also in autumn.
I really like sweet potato tempura.
When I lived in Shizuoka, there was a
garden.
My father was growing sweet potatoes at
home.
I ate it as tempura.
That's great.
I really like it.
It must be delicious.
It's definitely delicious.
Can you eat sweet potatoes?
I can eat it.
That's good.
I like tempura.
Speaking of autumn, how about you?
I like chestnuts.
Can you peel it?
I can do this.
What is this?
I can do it with a knife.
What kind of food do you like?
I like chestnut rice.
It's a pain in the neck.
Please make it.
Please peel it.
I also peel the chestnut.
Please put it in a soup and boil it.
I have never done it.
You have never done it.
I'm a food expert.
Please try it.
I want to try it once.
It's not easy to do.
I understand.
I will read a message from the viewer.
This is from the viewer.
Thank you.
Good evening.
I met you for the first time in the
summer.
I knew this program on YOUTUBE and was
addicted to your conversation.
I watched the archive.
I like anime and voice actors.
I knew your name, but I didn't recognize
you.
I didn't think you were so attractive.
I will continue to watch your
activities.
What is the most attractive thing you
have recently known or recognized?
I am glad you recognized me.
Thank you.
Is this from Akane?
No, it's not!
It's not!
I am here!
This is...
You are being hot-tempered.
No, I am not!
You are not sending me a message.
I am not!
Please use hashtag if you are here.
I am being used as a bait.
This is also a secret.
This is not good.
This is scary.
What is it?
It's a new attractive thing.
Attractive thing?
Drum?
I usually sing and I play drums in my
music.
I've been playing drums for a long time.
But when I wanted to be better at
singing, I wondered what kind of sound
the drum was making.
I couldn't hear the sound of the drum.
I watched a YouTube video of someone who
played the drum with a
microphone and kept watching it, and I
could hear the sound of the drum.
And I realized that drums are good.
You're doing it right.
I didn't know you were doing this here.
You didn't know.
That's good.
I think it's a chair.
What kind of chair?
I don't get tired of a good chair.
I've never sat on a good chair.
This is no good either.
Is this a normal chair?
It's hard.
I don't get stressed just sitting down
like this.
I sometimes have a chair that's better
than sleeping.
Really? Did you buy it?
I bought one.
It's completely different.
How much is it?
130,000 yen.
It's expensive.
There's a higher one.
It's like an office chair.
Is it a big chair that you can sit
comfortably on?
Is it a chair that can be held up to the
top of your head?
It's 300,000 yen.
It's an office room.
But it must be relaxing for those who do
it all the time.
I guess so.
If I do this, my body will be over.
It will be over.
That's right. This may end.
It will hurt after about two hours.
How many stickers should I give to Yaji?
It's the same as giving it to Kumada.
I'll give you three.
Isn't it too little?
Three? But three is not bad.
It's not bad.
Are you happy?
I'm happy.
That's right.
I'm sending it to Kumada.
No, no, no.
That's not what I meant.
Yaji exists.
Is that so?
If Teletama is not careful, I'll tell
you.
Is that so?
Yes.
I'll give you three stickers.
We are looking for messages and
requests.
Please send it from the official website
of the program.
Please.
Do you know the Teletama app?
Yes, you can enter the quiz in this app.
If you can answer the question, you will
get a gift from the guest.
Please download the app and try it.
Kumada Kokuchi chance.
Yay!
If you can answer the question, you can
enter the quiz.
Thank you.
The quiz about Saitama.
Yes.
Here we go.
Can you read this name?
It is a city with a rich nature.
It is convenient to commute and school
in about an hour from Tokyo to Shinma.
What is the name of this town in
Hikigun, Saitama Prefecture?
Oh, yes.
Namekawa...
Namekawa-cho.
Wait.
Which one?
Namekawa-machi.
Is it okay to say machi?
Machi is fine.
Really?
Do you want to change it to cho?
Yes.
Machi?
Machi.
Which one?
Namekawa-cho...Namekawa-machi?
Machi.
The correct answer is Namegawa-machi.
Too bad.
That's not the answer.
It's Gawaka.
Namegawa-machi.
Gawaka.
I'm frustrated.
Thank you.