Thank you for watching.
Thank you.
I came to the school.
I had a meeting after school.
Thank you.
The new members came to the lesson room
during the break.
What are you doing today?
I'm going to practice my
At the live show the other day
What?
This year's fan meeting is decided!
The three of us will have our first fan
meeting!
The summer fan meeting is decided!
Last year, it was cancelled, but this
year, it will be held on August 21!
So, the new members will perform their
first live performance!
Just two days after the performance, the
lesson has started!
Good morning!
The three of them are the three members
of the group, Kashiwagi, Kobayashi and
Nakayama, who are assigned to teach the
three of them.
First, they warm up!
Stretching with the other
I'm a high school student.
I'm a ballet teacher.
Then there is a more powerful scene.
I don't know if I'm good.
One step.
I'm not doing anything.
On the other hand.
I'm going up a lot.
I'm keeping it there.
Wait.
I don't want to.
In a comfortable atmosphere, the free-
dancing starts.
I'm going to move to the left.
Here, the education staff is also
supporting.
I'm going to check the choreography with
Manchurian.
I'm sorry. I missed it again.
I'm sorry.
No!
This part we advance
Only double the shape
This part
Here
Yuno
She is instructed by the teacher
All the way to the waist.
Yes!
Once they are each
It was so hard for Yuno to control the
length of her limbs.
She maintained the paid attention to the
darkness next to her limbs.
Thank you for your viewing.
Yuno only turns her arms four times.
Yuno only turns her arms three times.
I feel like I'm a little late for the
next one.
If I remember something at the same
time, I'll be a little late.
I can proceed at the same time.
OK.
Good job.
Theилась the movement of shooting and
shooting theHim organic movement
we look at the angle of the hands and
the bustling
absolutely natural hand300 degrees
and legs
when the timing People have fallen
I have
returned
and such
was not up or up
But she is satisfied.
Hayate players are working hard against
bye bye bye bye.
However, the quality required to stand
on the stage as a professional is
different.
During the live, all members are
gathered together for the first time in
one performance.
Only a small difference greatly affects
the performance.
If you drink water, you'll make a sound.
I'm tired.
My arm hurts.
My right arm hurts.
Yuno is a bit late in terms of physical
strength.
But he still does his best.
Thank you for watching.
I'm not good at dancing, but I'm good at
dancing.
I'm not afraid of the cold wind.
I want to be with you.
I'm not good at dancing, but I'm good at
dancing.
I want to be with you.
The first lesson of three hours is over.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
Then, she ran to Yuno's place right
after the lesson.
I forgot to bring the microphone here.
I used my thumb to take the distance
between the jaw and the face.
I think I was asked to take this.
Basically, the microphone is here.
I started singing from the top.
I can see that I'm already far away.
I always come here.
Divide the frame, too.
I've done this many times.
Mmm
with an更 hot to solve the problem to
minimize the battling
They all want to do the same thing.
I don't want to miss the timing.
I'll do this when I'm practicing.
私はこの部分を修正しました。
頑張ってください。
必死に、分からないなりに 暗いついてきてくれてるのを感じました。
間違えたことはレッスンだから 恥ずかしくないと思うので、
先ほどここ間違えたから次にこうしようというのが分かるから、
間違えちゃダメだって自分に思い込みすぎちゃって、
次に何だっけ?って、自分の頭の中で慌ててるのかなって感じたから、
何か一つ一つ一緒にやっていったりとか、これからどんどん一緒にやっていければいいか
なとは思った。
9 members of the shrimp team have been
selected.
They have become members and are going
to the family event for the first time
in a year.
Next time, the formation lesson.
The path to the first live will
continue.