New Year's special!
Cheers!
This week's Ebichutastas is Ebichutas'
5th year special!
That legendary project is a one-night-
long revival!
That's terrible!
Furthermore, the Super Super Arena
University Gala was held the other day.
Ebichutastas, start!
Ebichutastas
Add various things to private Ebisu
Middle School
Ebisu Justus
Sponsored by Holland.
This episode of Ebichu Tastas started in
July
We are going to cross the age together
I want to sleep
Wait a minute
Today is December 24th, Christmas
Is this a holiday?
I came here for Christmas
It's like a rock bed
On Christmas night, Ebichu Tastas has a
big party
Members will be excited in party mode
Ebichu Tastas will start the party
First, we would like to have this person
who is a shrimp lover take a toast
Akiyama-san, please come in
It's a sports day
A shrimp lover serious sports day held
in Hachioji in October
The guest of honor at that time was
Akiyama Katsuo-san from Hachioji Tourism
Association
This time, it is a venue that has
nothing to do with Hachioji
He rushed to us for a toast greeting
while busy
Mayama-chan
Thank you
The color is
The gift was a hand-made helmet with the
color of the member
I wonder if this is necessary for a
toast
What are you doing?
You are the longest
I'm a Toro
You are really done with beer
It's still the beginning
We talked about Mr. Kakao
Today, we are going to have a toast in
Hachioji Castle, a castle
It will be a long story, so I will make
it short
I don't want to have a toast
I would like to have a toast in that
room
That room?
So, Akiyama-san original toast Hachioji
Castle version
Cheers!
Thus, the 5th Year party starts with the
strong Hachioji color.
Next. Have you ever thought of something
else in 2015?
We will produce what you have left on
the list.
Nakashimaki!
One person shabu-shabu and one person
yakiniku.
I can do one person karaoke and one
person pasta and one person curry.
But I couldn't do meat.
You can go to the yakiniku by yourself
You have the courage
There is a school on weekdays so you
can't go
You can go when you become a pro-chuu
I will wait until I become a pro-chuu
I will wait until next year
Sorry, did you really think about being
a pro-chuu?
You suddenly became a pro-chuu
I knew it today
Next is Yasumoto
What did you do?
I took a CD jacket in the center
I see
It was a single with a member in the
center
There was a photo of the jacket
I was very happy and my family was happy
I was very happy to get a poster and
decorate the school
I was in the center of the poster
This is a arrow
When a customer came to Ayaka's house,
my father introduced me to the photo
I put an arrow on it
It's also a photo of a ghost
There are 8 people in the center so
there is no center
Even if you try hard, you can't be in
the center
I know there is no center, but I want to
be in the center
I want to be happy again
Yasumoto produce's Yasumoto Center
jacket photo shoot
I want to be cute like a flower
Like a pollen
I want to be a pollen
Yasumoto wants to be a pollen, not a
flower petal
What kind of photo will it be?
Like this?
It's like this
Like a flower
It's done
Like this
Open your hand
Flower petal?
I'm sorry to say this, but you should
put a flower petal on your coat
Amazing
It's a little hard but you should put it
like this
Yes, yes, yes
How is it?
It's good
You shouldn't do anything with pollen
And so, the shooting of the
movie, it's perfect
Then, maybe, maybe, for the great person
You should appeal to Yasumoto
I wanted to be a mentor again
Please
Mr. Akiyama, can I ask you a favor?
Yes, what kind of favor?
Great person, great person of Star Dust
Then, I will also
In the place of Mr. Akimoto's father
I will also ask you a favor
Please
Who is Mr. Akimoto?
You are mixed with Mr. Akiyama
Yasumoto
If you stay as it is, Mr. Akiyama will
be the center jacket
I wanted to say Akiyama
Ebichu Fastas Daibou Nenkai Special
Next is
Nagaemariko presents N1 Gunpla
After this, the legendary project is
resumed
The Nenkai is very exciting
But before that
Sakura Ebis is in the front line
Sakura Ebis was announced at the One Man
Live in January next year
Before the announcement to the fans
It was also passed on to the members
Here is the situation at that time
I'm very happy to do a live on January
17 next year
Furthermore, big news
Do you know the priority broadcast?
There is an app called priority on the
smartphone
One of them is the regular Sakura Ebis
What! The first regular radio program of
Sakura Ebis starts
I'm crying
Are you crying?
I was surprised
This time, the first radio recording is
very advanced
The recording pattern is a little public
Hello everyone who listens to priority
on the smartphone
We are Sakura Ebi's
The way to the idol of Sakura Ebi's
This is the first time to broadcast
Our own radio show has started
How is everyone? Are you nervous?
Are you nervous?
Only 5 people appear
The talk is fun with the most advanced
member, Mizuha
I understand
However, Mizuha is in charge of the
progress
Not yet
Is it normal time?
If you work harder
I want to tell everyone's good things
I want to be a middle school student and
watch the experiment
First radio recording
There is still a lot of food, but while
doing regular, it is a talk
This radio program will be broadcast
from Monday to Monday
Please check
In the future, we will continue to stick
to Sakura Ebi's
Nakaayama Riko presents N1 Grand Prix
Legendary project that makes Nakayama
laugh
N1 Grand Prix
Last time, Matsuno won the game
N1 knows, but N1 does not know
If you think Nakayama is funny, give a
cucumber
The number of cucumbers you get will
decide the winner
Now, the person who wants to go
Can't you read it?
Kobayashi, good
N1 Grand Prix, first Kobayashi's
challenge
It's a story from when I was on the
train home
I made a mistake on the train
I have a good name
I have a good name, so I want to say it
Kobayashi, one step forward
Good pace
Hirota came
Hirota's challenge that Nakayama's pot
is not known
Please subscribe to the channel
What is he doing?
Oh!
What is this?
All of a sudden!
Let's go with the last one!
I can't lose!
Now, the last one!
The thief!
The thief cat in the movie!
Oh, the same thing!
Isn't it the same?
That's terrible!
Come on, come on!
Please come back!
Oh, no!
It's a chance!
The cloak!
The cloak is flowing!
What if you turn around?
Oh, but...
I'm losing!
There was a point!
Let's go!
Go, Joo E!
IPHTY48 kendara
미 Visual
This is the current situation
So the second N1 Grand Prix
The entertainer Chuu-ei who got 6
cucumbers won
So what happened?
Akiyama-san gave you the cucumber
I gave it all
What?
That means
The order has changed
The winner is Akiyama-san
The reverse point
Akiyama-san
By the way, what does this mean?
I did my best
I gave advice to buy the effort
You gave advice
That's the most important thing
The second N1 Grand Prix
Akiyama-san won the reverse point with
39 cucumbers
After this
The biggest school game in Ebichu
Saitama Super Arena Super Speed
1,2,3
Ebichu Saitama Super Arena 2 Days
Super Speed Special
Super Speed
So this time
We came to Saitama Super Arena
We came
I was waiting for this day
I'm here
You are here
Do you know what day is today?
What?
Today is the 2015 university festival of
Ebichu
All attract stars are here
December 12th
Do you know what day is today?
It's the birthday of King of Comedy
Kondo
That's right
I know you live around here
No
It's my birthday
Sorry
I forgot
It's my birthday
I'm not happy
We are more excited than you
Yes
Let's go
Who is it?
Say something
I'm excited
Let's go
It was good
Ebichu's biggest live show
The 2015 university festival of the
forgotten years
Ebichu's All attract stars
The special news
The live show that was held on December
12th and 13th
The first train
5.30pm
The live show has finally begun
It's going to be a big show
Behind the scenes
Thank you for watching!
I want to see your amazing eyes
I'll take over the world like a wind
While waving my hand in the wind
I'll shout out my heavy feelings
Let's dance over ten thousand Vocaloids
Let's transform and visa
Thank you for watching!
Look, my tears immediately fell
At the end of the live, the members
appeared on the truck and went around
the venue.
Thank you for watching.
The live performance is over, as they
become one with the family
And they are going to perform live
performance after the live performance
Come here, Ebichu
Good job, good job
Good job, everyone
It was exciting
Kaiki san said something like, what are
you going to talk with the members?
I can't say it in words, so I can't say
it
You're nervous now
And we shook hands
We all moved
We shook hands but did anyone notice?
Yes, we did
The top
Hoshino noticed
These two were doing it in red
Yes
They noticed
Really?
I don't know who it was, but the staff
thought it was Siren
They didn't notice
So we'll do it again tomorrow
Good luck
Everyone, do it today
Do it today
And prepare for tomorrow
Do it properly
That's important
I understand
It's over
Thank you
So the first day is over
December 13th
The live performance was also very fast
I'll do my best to put my gratitude on
the stage
Here we go
Where are we?
Saiga
We are
Thank you
I'll make you forget your past
Love me, love me, smile it, smile it,
baby
Because your smile will make the world
smile
Thanks for watching!
Over 20,000 people were invited in two
days
It was the most amazing live performance
in the Eri-Chu market
Thus, the last school performance this
year ended in a great success
Thank you for your hard work
How was it?
It was great!
I was really nervous.
I was really studying for two days.
It was really fun.
I'm not sad.
I'm going to grow old.
Thank you so much.
This was us, Shilt-E-Mishima.
Bye-bye.
Thank you.
Let me taste the cream!
I'm going to regret this later.