Ebichu's video!
Good morning, I'm Maya Marika.
Thank you for the rehearsal.
Thank you.
I'm going to sing a song.
Please sing.
Are you okay, Maya?
Yes, I'm fine.
This is the costume for the first part.
The first part is a very relaxing
costume.
I'm nervous, so I made it a relaxing
I've been eating eggplant recently.
I used to remember eggplant just by
looking at this color combination.
I recently learned that this combination
is very good.
This is the costume for the first part.
This is the first part before the live
show.
As you can see, I'm nervous.
I'll do my best.
Maya, you can do it.
I want to ask Maya Marika how she is
doing.
How are you feeling now?
I have my microphone.
I'm very excited.
How are you feeling now?
I'm also excited.
I'm happy to be on the train.
I don't know what song you're going to
sing.
I've been repeating the theme song and
the new song.
That's right.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you.
It's the coldest day today.
That's why it's so cold.
It's very cold and warm.
Please enjoy the cold weather.
Thank you very much.
This is the report of Maya.
Who will make you do the trick?
Maya Marika.
Thank you very much.
I'll go then.
D Aboriginal people's
Thank you for watching.
The second part of Mayamania Level 6 is
a dress like this.
This time, I'm wearing a raw band and
it's an apostix live, so I'm wearing a
chic image.
Why did the first part feel like that?
Because I'm nervous.
I think the second part is also a little
bad.
Both are cute and my favorite, but I
tried dressing the second part.
I'm nervous. I'll do my best.
Mayamania!
I'm nervous.
Mayamania is about to start.
That's all from the scene.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Mayamania is about to start.
Rika-san, everyone is like...
What should I do?
Do what you like.
Rika-san looks so happy.
It was so nice.
Aya-san's mission is perfect.
It was cute.
The last part of the song was the
encore.
Yuki-san was so brave.
Yuki-san was brave?
I'm tired.
Thank you.
I feel like I'm used to freedom.
Really?
Do you want to do it tomorrow?
I'll do it tomorrow.
I'm not in the mood.
I'm done with My Mania Level 6.
Thank you very much.
I was very nervous, but it was really
fun.
I sang with acoustic for the first time
in a live band.
I sang a lot of cover songs with the
fans of the Shinsen Mayama Band.
I was very happy to be able to sing and
play.
The rehearsal was changing little by
little.
It was a live that made me think that
music was fun.
I hope you enjoy it.
I'm looking forward to seeing you again.
Thank you very much.
Please subscribe to my channel.
To those of you studying residence
studies and middle school in F ikke i
wake up early
From now on, we will be holding the
Satan's solo live, My Anpanmania!
Thank you for watching!
Turn around and start running again
today
So it's my baby
This world is for you, so keep going
Spin, spin, and run again today
It's my baby
Sparkling, sparkling, sparkling eyes are
narrow
I'll wrap you up and run away
It's my baby
The moon is burning like it's about to
collapse
It sinks into the red moon
A dirty smile on my chest
In a heartless spotlight
But if you shed blood and tears
I'll cut it off and pray
I'll dye you red today too
This life that was born under the sky
that was set back
Even if I struggle so much, I can't
reach it
A kind world
I have poison, I will purify it
Liar Mask
If I could tell you this feeling
straight
Would I change a little?
The blowing wind blows the petals
I will carry it to the future I've never
seen before
I will sing against the fate that I
can't erase
Only now, only now, these feelings will
reach you
Even if the unceasing sadness is cut off
by the song
I can never go back to the swaying song
I'm a new hero
I think that what I think is the most
important hope for me at this concert is
that I can say it again tomorrow.
Please come and show me your energetic
face again.
Thank you very much for today.
Thank you.
See you again.
I feel like I can see you getting
smaller and smaller
Red Bye Bye
Please subscribe to my channel!
Our future will surely be bright and
wonderful
Like that summer sea, it will be calm
and gently enveloped
It will be like a mother
Like I'm shopping on a date, I'm with
you
Bye bye
Keep your voice down
Goodbye, bye bye
See you tomorrow
I was in the middle of choosing
I want you to hear it in the city where
the big wind blows
Hey, bye bye
Thank you for watching.
Let's make a starry night again
Let's sing and dance with words
Let's play with the bamboo of our
feelings
Come on, bye bye
Goodbye, bye bye
See you tomorrow
Take care, everyone! See you again!
I want you to turn around and look back
I want you to hear me getting smaller
Goodbye, bye bye
See you tomorrow
The one who's going to be my hand is
getting closer
I feel like I can reach you melting into
the sunset
See you tomorrow