I was so happy to sing.
I couldn't stop crying even though I was
so good.
There are people who think that there is
only us.
Thank you for your cooperation.
We have a special guest with us today,
Mr. Takeya from Uberworld.
Thank you.
I started playing electric guitar when I
was in the first grade of junior high
school.
I used to copy boy bands like Bach, Blue
Hearts, etc.
I was into drums when I was in high
school.
I liked indie bands like High Star.
I was copying those bands.
When I was 20, my friend invited me to a
2MC band,
a high school cultural festival, and
they were announcing the winner.
There were no vocals, so it was okay if
the vocals weren't from the school.
My friend and I were invited to sing for
the first time when I was 20.
At that time, I sang a copy of a band
called Minor League.
That's when I woke up to be a vocalist.
I started singing pretty late.
I started singing when I was 20.
And I've been singing since then.
So you wanted to sing Minor League
directly?
I liked music in Minor League.
Do you know about Minor League?
I got the information for the first time
this year.
It's amazing.
It's hardcore.
I don't think everyone knows it, but I
liked it too.
I liked the feeling of screaming with a
death voice.
There were almost no people around us
who knew that.
So when we started to make a band, we
had a lot of people around us.
They introduced me to a singer who knew
the song.
They asked me if I could sing. I
remember all the lyrics, but I've never
sung it.
But when I tried it, I was like, why
haven't I noticed the fun of vocal when
I've been doing music and guitar and
drums?
It was shocking.
Until now, I had trouble with the lack
of vocals in the band.
I didn't have a good vocalist, and I
thought I wouldn't be blessed by the
members.
I didn't think I would have the time to
do vocal in my music life.
From then on, I was stuck.
The live was only for one day, but the
next day I formed Uber.
So I started playing.
It was a real opportunity.
Yes, it was.
I was surprised that I didn't plan to
start playing vocals from the beginning.
I think a lot of people want to sing
from the beginning.
I didn't have that idea.
I had the image that I would sing.
You liked music, and were you interested
in making music?
You were playing.
I started making songs from the 11th.
I wrote the lyrics and made the song.
The one who sang it was the second
senior.
You didn't write it to sing yourself.
I didn't like it.
I have a sister, but I always sing for
her.
I thought music was about singing for
someone else.
I was lucky to have such an invitation.
I thought it was fun to sing like this.
It's fun. If you get into it, it's like
a minor league.
Because of that...
I guess I got a little stronger.
That's true. That's probably true.
This song is especially...
I was good at it.
You were good at it?
This death voice thing.
Can you still do it now?
I don't do it anymore in my own songs.
I don't get into it.
But I really like to sing like this.
As you said earlier, you may have been
trained for this.
You've been doing this for a long time.
I didn't have the habit of practicing
singing.
I had the experience of practicing
singing for the first time.
I didn't have the habit of practicing in
the studio.
I didn't go to karaoke.
There were two vocals.
One of them was a vocalist.
We were in the countryside.
We parked our car in the middle of a
vast field.
We opened the door for the driver and
the female driver.
We went outside.
We played loud in the car stereo.
We were singing in the car.
We were so into it.
We sang for 3-4 hours, until we got a
sore throat.
We practiced like that.
I didn't like my voice.
I wanted to have a husky voice.
I sang like I was trying to get a sore
throat.
That's after we got to different cities.
There was a voice training studio I knew
at the time.
I went there.
I said, I want to get a sore throat.
Mr. Tsuyoshi Nagabuchi had a tequila.
He drank it and shouted out in the gym.
There's an episode about a sore throat.
I'm going to do that.
I asked the teacher if I wanted to get a
sore throat.
I'll do it for now.
I asked the teacher to hold it in until
I could sing well.
And this is the voice I'm singing now.
I didn't hate it, but I admired husky
voices.
The rough death voice, the sound of the
waves.
Is there a good part of it that you were
told to stop?
I think it was good.
I'm sure it's not this voice right now.
・C메ー fan tutte
I really like my voice now.
I've been able to like it.
That's important.
I've been able to like it for the past
two years.
I haven't been able to like it that much
until then.
The UBER WORLD was formed because of the
Minor League.
How did you know that the UBER WORLD was
formed with your local friends?
I've known the bass and the guitar since
I was 3 years old.
You've known them since you were in
kindergarten?
Same as elementary school.
I had 4 drums and a guitar.
It was a house with a two-way street
that you could hear if you screamed
loudly in my room.
I knew him, but I knew him when he was
15 years old.
Saxia...
He was in elementary school.
So most of them are neighbors?
They're childhood friends.
Completely.
Amazing. They're all very close.
They're really good guys.
I think I'm the most grumpy person.
Like a warehouse, he just wraps me up
like this.
That much? And you've been making music
all this time.
But do you have any fights?
I've had a lot of fights.
But I think I was the last guy in middle
school.
That was a long time ago.
I haven't had a fight since then.
I have a lot of opinions.
I have a strong bond with bands.
When I have a fight with bands, I have a
fight with the record company.
Even if there is a party, we talk
together.
I can't make friends.
We have the same will.
We have a lot of differences, but we
have done something well.
I think people other than me could have
held it in.
I love the Air Jam generation.
Like the Bluffman from Air Jam.
And the backdrop bombs.
I love backdrop bombs.
I think it's because of the Carnera that
we have the saxophone in our band.
Oh, I see.
The first band I copied was Minor League
and Backdrop Bomb.
Scaffold King.
Scaffold King is cool, too.
I was covering them.
When I was about to start a band, I
thought I wanted a saxophone.
At that time, Seika was with me.
He said he had bought a pachinko.
I said, I'm going to start a band, but I
want to buy a saxophone.
I started playing saxophone when I was
20.
It's been 21 years now.
So I was really nervous.
I had about 5 original songs.
In the first song, I only played one bar
of the interval between the first and
second.
After that, I just played the saxophone
and played the chorus with the sequence
button.
I've been doing that for about 5 years.
If I don't have him, I can't make the
sound of Uberworld.
It's so cool. I love it.
Thank you.
I often say this, but...
That legacy I've brought to Uclears that
year
It's not about singing great songs
But the one I've taught to Seika
I've told him to play the sax right now
zdrow Rose
Seika suffered aswell
We first played it together
Like the kick of the bass drum
When I changed the rhythm I made, it was
so severe that I pointed out
I realized that it was better to leave
it to someone else to exceed my
imagination
Recently, I haven't been involved in it,
but I've been hoping to give a rough
draft of something like a memo
I'm looking forward to what kind of
impression it will have and what kind of
arrangement it will make
It's a band's mess, isn't it?
It's like it's shifting
I don't think I want to be written for
lyrics
I was frustrated when I got ideas
I understand
Even if you get ideas, you have to
finish them in a different direction
Now, I'm really in the first episode
Hiisan
I ask the members about the guitar, and
I talk to them.
I talk about the lyrics and the story of
the bass.
I ask them what they think the
conclusion should be.
I'm not talking about one song, but
about six members.
I think about six things.
I think I've also seen that kind of
flexibility.
I think what they like is generally
good.
They really like different things.
But they know what's good about what
they like.
I think I'm sure they'll believe that.
You're in a good state.
The band is having fun now.
It's so much fun.
When I saw Tsudawa's video, I thought it
was great that he said,
I love Uber World and I won't lose to
you guys.
I'm really happy to have met such a
thing.
The band is the best. I think it's
really good.
I haven't heard any legendary artists'
music.
I can only do what I like.
But you value what you like.
I've heard all of them, and I think they
don't suit me.
I understand that I don't fit into them,
so I only make what I like.
Live houses played for visitors for me있는
the music I like.
During masukur barely any listeners,
network communication means
I like music that go out with the back
story
It's really interesting...
If you would let me look the documents,
I listened to your song, Tick, and it
was really good.
I thought, oh, it's really good.
It's a great experience to see a live
performance with no audience.
But it was so good that I couldn't stop
crying.
I wanted to be a good artist like this.
It's been like that since I debuted, but
I'm so happy to see Tick again.
I was able to impress people by the fact
that there were no customers.
Did you tell them that you were happy to
see them?
I did. I asked them about it and they
sometimes contacted me.
They were just fans, not interested at
all.
They even answered my phone.
They were like,
I'm in the hot spring in Ishikawa.
Good luck.
They were such a pain in the ass.
But I wanted to make them my fans.
That's amazing.
You did that for them.
I guess I did.
Thank you for watching.
I've been hanging out with my fans since
my debut.
That was quite a shock.
I sometimes exchange contacts with my
fans in the city.
If there's someone I find interesting,
I'll tell them to contact me.
I exchange contacts and go out to eat.
I think that's what I like about
artists.
I think he might have thought I was a
weirdo.
Or he would call me and ask me to come
on the show.
I think he would have thought I was a
weirdo.
I have a strong impression that fans are
very important to Takuya.
When I saw the video of him talking to
Kenta Wanima,
I thought that if he did it for a long
time, it would be for his own good.
If he stopped on the way, the audience
would remember the best time in their
minds.
That would be good.
Thank you.
I thought that if I continued to do it,
it would lead to destroying the
audience's dreams.
So I thought that if I continued to do
it, it would be better to stop when it
was for my own sake, not for the
audience's sake.
I thought that was a great idea.
I still think that fans are still very
important to me, and I'm also very
important to them.
In the past two years, fans have been
unable to meet each other.
When that happened, I wanted to see
their faces as a way of communicating.
I often get videos.
I got comments like, what kind of
Uberworld is it for you?
I realized that it's definitely...
There are people who think that there's
only us.
That's what I felt.
I thought that this person's life was
like Uberworld.
I wanted to carry that burden.
I thought that I couldn't quit at my own
pace.
Where do I feel like the people who have
been chasing me so much are going?
I really felt that way recently.
When I talked to Kenta on the radio, I
really thought so.
I have some artists that I like.
I can still be in love with them because
they don't exist.
That's right. They're made up.
If I could still be there, I wouldn't
think it's cool.
The most powerful thing I felt was the
Tokyo Dome men's festival.
And among them, 45,000 men...
They were so loud and loud.
They were so sharp.
I wanted to make them feel the best.
I wanted to make them feel like they
were going to die.
But now, I don't feel that way.
I don't want them to feel that way.
I make my own life, such as live shows,
physical training, mental training, and
physical condition.
It's simple, like eating, exercising,
and so on.
That's amazing.
So I don't want to run away from that at
all.
My goal is to continue my life because
it's their life.
I'm determined not to let go of that.
It's a recent story that I did a radio
with Kenta at that time.
I've decided to continue to have a good
condition for the rest of my life.