Ebichu's video
I'm Monoka and I'm fishing
This time, I'm at Musashinoen in
Suginami-ku
As you can see, I'm going to fish
This is my first time to fish
I'm worried about fishing alone, so I
asked Riko-chan to come as a supporter
Thank you
Why did you want to fish?
When I was a child, I went fishing when
I was traveling
But I was still young, so I couldn't
fish at all
I got tired and went to a different
place on the way
I want to fish until I can fish
I want you to fish today
I will do my best
I will go fishing
I'm going to fish
I'm fishing
I did it
I was fishing when I was a child
How old are you?
I was 7 years old
It's long
Let's compete
I'm scared
I'm afraid I'm out of concentration
How much food can you put on?
I will put it so that it does not fall
Is this too little?
I don't know
That's about it
I'm very good at fishing
I don't know how much food I can put on
I was fishing a while ago
I don't know how many there are.
I wonder.
If you bend it, you can see it.
Yes, I can see it.
I'm waiting like this, but I realized
that I lost my bait.
There is.
I have caught a fish.
I can't see the fish.
I'm going to get a fish by reducing the
amount of water.
Do you like fish?
I went to the fish market.
I see.
I can't see the fish.
I'm going to check the bait.
I lost my bait.
I can't see the fish.
I can't catch fish if I don't increase
the amount of water.
I'm waiting for the fish to come out.
I wonder if there are fish.
I'm going to eat fish and eat rice.
The weather is nice.
It's warm.
I'm waiting for the fish to come out.
I lost my bait.
Why?
Did you eat fish?
I can't eat fish if I don't increase the
amount of water.
I'm waiting for the fish to come out.
I can't catch fish in the sea.
You don't say that you can't catch fish
in the sea.
I don't say that.
I say that.
It's not a fishing spot.
I'm not sure.
I was five years old when I went to the
sea.
I was fishing in the sea.
I dropped my shoes in the sea.
I was scared.
I was scared of the sea.
I'm scared of the sea.
I like it.
What happened on the way home?
I don't know.
I don't remember.
I remember the song that KUTSU played.
I don't remember what happened after
that.
It was a good five-pointed bell.
Yeah.
I was so happy.
I'm a rain woman.
I'm a cloud woman.
It's here.
It's so close.
You this way.
I'm sorry.
I'm a little too excited.
I'll show you.
I'm sorry.
It's heavy.
Thank you.
I lost.
Wow.
I was surprised.
It's fast.
I'm sorry.
I have to hold it.
I think the bigger one is better.
I mean, the bigger one.
I have to hold it.
I'm sorry.
I'll give it to you.
Oh, there it is.
Thank you very much.
The end of the fishing.
I finished fishing with Nanaka.
The result is...
Rinko caught one fish.
I won.
I caught it. Thank you very much.
How was it?
It was a moment.
I couldn't catch fish in that moment.
It was difficult.
I'm glad.
I couldn't catch fish.
It was difficult.
I couldn't catch fish in the evening.
I want to revenge.
Let's do it again.
Let's revenge.
I will go fishing.
I'm hungry.
Let's eat.
It looks delicious.
It's a stew pot.
There is a dumpling.
It looks delicious.
It's a crab cream croquette.
I want to eat.
Nanaka will report the food.
I ordered my favorite dumplings.
I will eat my favorite dumplings.
It looks delicious.
It will collapse.
I will eat.
Please eat.
It's hot.
It looks delicious.
It's delicious.
It's crispy.
It's the most crispy I've ever eaten.
There is a lot of filling inside.
It melts in your mouth.
It's really delicious.
I'm a village boy.
Riko, please eat Japanese food.
I will eat the first place's katsu
curry.
I will eat the curry.
Can you hear the sound?
It's crispy.
The curry is sweet.
The thickness of the meat is good.
I think it's the first place.
It's delicious.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye.
It was delicious.
It was good to eat curry.
Let's eat again.
What should we do next?
Please subscribe to our channel.