The 3rd edition of the live festival of
the summer
The 3rd edition is completely focused on
Matsuno Rina's birthday solo live
I'm doing it to make you guys cry
Matsuno's feelings are contained in the
solo live
But...
The waiting Tastas, full of anticipation
and anticipation, starts now!
Let's activate the
Moratorium Moratorium Moratorium
Junior High School Students
Add various things to your private
school
Junior High School Students
Moratorium Moratorium
This program is brought to you by the
sponsor you are watching.
A birthday solo live to celebrate the
birthday of the Ebitune members
This is the first birthday solo live by
Ayaka Yasumoto and Kaho Kobayashi.
And then, on July 19th...
The third one is...
Good morning
Rina Matsuno, who just turned 18 3 days
ago
Nice to meet you
Are you nervous?
I don't know
I don't feel like today
I'm like, what should I do?
My heart hurts
My heart hurts when I came here
The first solo live
The audience is not calm
The second solo live
I'm alone
The weakness finally speaks
The radio booth was designed for this
stage
Let's listen to the song
I want to see cool Rina
I want to listen to summer songs
Candy Rocker
I want to sing a song that is famous in
Japan at the end of the BGM.
Everyone, an Indian откation is attached
to the theme of the live.
The Inananda Video Show.
It is a radio program where you can
watch the live show and wait for the DJ.
Moreover, this kind of performance is
also available.
The costumes are four poses.
I think it's something that the other
two people haven't done.
It's all failed except for the last
encore.
Matsuno's stage as a fashion model is
also paying attention to her costume.
I'm going to make everyone cry at the
last encore.
This word is full of love.
Ta-da! Ayu-san!
She is a free and unrestrained figure
that is usually shown on the show.
Matsuno was waiting for her as a solo
artist.
I hope everyone can enjoy it and I can
enjoy it too.
It's not easy.
It's 7 o'clock in the afternoon.
Her tasered hair filled entire hall.
Everyone is here.
Let's do our best!
Where are we?
In Chicago!
Let's do our best!
Thank you!
Hello!
Yay!
Finally, the Lina Radio Show has
started!
I'm Matsuko, the DJ!
I'm so happy to have so many families
here!
There are so many blue lights!
I'm so happy!
So, let's get to the song!
I want to see Rina's cool performance.
I want to listen to the exciting summer
song.
albums from each province
Ladies and gentlemen, I give it, Dora-
Rose!
1, 2, 1, 2, 3, 4!
I'm a girl who's a little unique
I'm not a girl who's too easy to get
along with
Even if my head is messed up, I won't
give up
I'm a mama
Let's go!
Ging Ging Gira Gira Giga
Guru Guru Gura Gura Guru Gura
I'm a girl who's a little unique
Thank you for watching!
I'm a Johnny Depp guy
Thanks for watching!
Can you look down? Can you look down?
Thank you for watching!
The stairs leading to the subway's exit
Are covered with marks of the subway's
exit
I'm not interested in you
The sunset is getting dim
Look, the words in my eyes
Are the words of my feelings
I raise my head
Naturally
The pit starts to cran
The last of you
I can't help it because I love you
The night we become one
I just have to come out in my dreams
The cake of tomorrow is about to end
I'll wave my arms with a feather
I can't help it because I love you
I'm crying, I'm crying, I'm crying
The rain is falling down
I'm just waiting for it to stop
Somehow I'm getting nervous
I'm running out of breath
I'm crying, I'm crying, I'm crying
I want to hear your voice that I hold
tight to the end
I can't help but feel that my breath is
about to stop
I can't get over my feelings for you
I want to hear your voice that I hold
tight to the end
The venue is full of excitement from the
start.
They are making a live show with fans.
And...
They are changing their costumes.
Matsuno's special costume, a summery
dress.
She's a little flustered at the
beginning of the song.
She's waiting for her usual partner, so
the venue is also calm.
Please subscribe to my channel!
My heart is pounding, it's so painful
It feels like there's a secret
I love you, I love you
But I can't take a step forward
I definitely want to tell you
My feelings are so honest
I'm crying, I'm crying, I'm crying, I'm
crying
With all my heart
I wept I wailed
But all I can do is the standard
Wild truth
No matter how much the person is
I'm sorry
Everyone discover that
I don't understand
That the world ended
So I die
I know
Do you know
your fault
I said
Yay!
I'm getting excited!
How was my costume change?
Thank you!
The highlight of this costume is the
flower crown.
And these shoes. They're sparkling.
Can you see them?
Well, let's go to this corner.
The corner of 《Can You Do It?》
Here again, to the RINANAN Radio Show
This corner is a corner where the
manager and the members give a topic and
I can do it or not
If you think you have cleared the topic,
you are blue
If you think it's no good, the family
will judge with red cyrilium
What kind of topic will they challenge?
Wait, today...
I'll do it
Someday, I will...
Yasumoto Aikawa's theme is...
Can I sing a song in a fast-forward?
The first attempt is from Yasumoto
The theme is to sing a fast-forward song
The second attempt is from Yasumoto
I'll do my best
The result is...
Oh, I did it!
You cleared it!
Thank you very much for your
cooperation!
What is the next challenge?
Will this kanji be able to call me
someday?
Why is this voice coming out? I don't
understand
It is written as rich in fish
Aji?
What?
Matsuno wants to answer the fans
What? It's a fish?
It's a bit unfair, but the judgement
is...
Then, I will read this half-word, or not
read it, please give me the judgement!
It's a bit unfair, but the judgement
is...
As a DJ, she succeeded in making the
talk corner exciting
Well then, I would like to go to the
next song
The live will be in the second half
She appeared in a new costume, a
birthday solo live T-shirt
She designed a special costume for
Matsuno
Thank you for watching!
On the way home, I walked with you with
a smile
You were laughing at my stupidity
The adult's escalator started to climb
up
But I don't want to remember those
memories anymore
Ready, set...
Is it okay for me to be stupid?
Is it okay for me not to know everything
now?
I felt something in my chest
I'm sure I'll tell you
I'll go to see you
Through the покупétry
A premonition of a new season
The hot sun, the scent of this summer
Summer is about to begin
The clouds floating in the sky
Are they waiting for someone?
I want to see you!
The rainbow in the sky after the rain
Thank you for coming today! This is the
last song!
Thank you for watching!
Lastly, a gift from the most generous
Frisbee.
The king visits the faraway moonwed
seat, hoping that the gifts will reach
the faraway throne.
Huh?
Thank you for coming to the Miu-Nandelia
Show today!
Yes, this is the Nenanan Relio show.
I will do my best to become a regular.
Yes, please continue to support me.
So, until the day we meet again, bye
bye!
The live is over.
Then...
This is what she is waiting for before
the concert
I'm going to make you cry at the last
encore
How will she respond to the family's
expectation?
About two years ago, she showed her
magical dress at a live show in Ebichu.
If I practice, you will teach me
Someday I will be able to have a lover
Don't make me say it from a girl
I will always be waiting
I want to tell you about the
wonderfulness and the children someday
I'm glad I was able to see the full
version of the game.
I hope you enjoyed it.
Thank you for watching.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I wonder if I can make up with you
I wonder if I can study hard someday
someday
I wonder if I can go on a vacation with
you someday
I wonder if I can go to the park with
I wonder if I can have a wonderful
family someday
Thank you very much.
This is how Matsuno's first solo live
show closed the curtain in the midst of
warm blessings.
How was it, Matsuno-san?
I was nervous.
I wonder how it was. I wonder if it was
okay.
There's someone over there.
Who?
I did it!
Matsuno-san, you did it!
It was beautiful! I had fun!
I'm glad. I had fun with Riko. I'm
happy.
The blue siren I saw from above was
beautiful.
Good job!
It was good.
Really?
Was it successful?
I was so nervous that I was going to be
on stage alone.
I was worried before I went on stage.
But I was quite nervous.
Please show us 4 poses.
4 poses?
Please show us.
I think I could do better than I
thought.
Thank you for your hard work today.
What we can't do now is...
Women's strength!
The first Ebichu Women's strength
competition.
Who will be the best at women's
strength?
I had a stomachache during the meal with
my friend.
Who is the most powerful?
Hey! Oh!
This program was provided by the sponsor
you are watching.
Can I say something? The theme is girl
power.
What? Girl? Girl?
Girl power? No.
Hora! Hora!
Everyone!
Why are you crying?
She cried!