Ebichu no Douga Toka
Let's decide on my favorite beef bowl!
So, last time, when Mayuma-san and I ate
the first cup yakisoba, we talked.
Oh, right. It was when we were talking.
Today, we're going to talk about our
first encounter.
Thank you for having me.
So, today, we're going to talk about
beef bowl.
Have you ever eaten beef bowl?
Have we ever had it?
I've never eaten it before.
It's the only beef bowl that my mom
makes.
It's like a mother's homemade beef bowl.
But beef bowl is quite...
The Naniha is very different.
That's true.
It's like a mother's homemade beef bowl.
I'm not really familiar with beef bowl.
Where am I?
Is it Matsuya?
Today, we're going to talk about
Yoshino, Sukiya, Matsuya, and Nakao.
Nakao?
I didn't know Nakao has beef bowl.
I didn't know.
It was like udon.
I usually only eat udon.
We're going to compare the beef bowl
from these four restaurants and find the
beef bowl that we like.
We're going to find it and...
And then...
In the end...
On the last day, we're going to go to
the restaurant and try it.
We're going to try beef bowl by
ourselves.
I see.
So, this is tasting.
Yes, it's tasting.
In the last video, I said that I might
not have eaten beef bowl in Rikko's
room.
That's how this project started.
I see.
What was it?
It's a
beef bowl restaurant.
It's a beef bowl restaurant.
So, let's eat beef bowl by Sukiya.
Yay!
Sukiya beef bowl.
Sukiya is delicious.
Shall we open it?
Yes.
It smells good.
It looks delicious.
Thank you very much for your viewing!
It's full of ingredients.
I just like it.
Let's eat.
It's a real meal.
I'll eat the meat first.
You eat meat first?
It's beef bowl.
It's delicious.
I'll taste the original taste.
How is it?
It's delicious.
I'll eat.
It's refreshing.
It's like this.
Rice and meat.
Beef bowl is...
I don't usually eat it.
When you eat meat and rice in a good
balance,
It feels like a accomplishment.
It's true.
It's hard to balance.
You have to remember the taste.
I remember the taste.
I'll eat it alone.
It's refreshing.
It tastes like pork.
The onions are crispy.
Beef bowl.
It's like this.
It's delicious.
I want to eat this with onsen.
I want to eat onsen with onsen.
It looks delicious.
It's refreshing.
Next.
Thank you for the food.
Thank you.
Next.
What should I do?
Yoshinoya Matsuya.
I have a friend.
I'll choose Yoshinoya.
I'll open it.
The onions are big.
It's big.
I see.
I think the most delicious is the onsen.
I think there is a lot of meat.
I see.
The taste of the meat is good.
It's beef bowl.
I'll eat it.
I'll eat the meat first.
How is it?
It's different.
It's sweet.
I think the meat is sweeter.
I'll eat it.
I'll eat it with rice.
Do you like it?
I think Yoshinoya will like it.
I think it's fast to eat.
I'll eat it.
It's delicious.
The onion is delicious.
This taste.
Is it a sauce?
I like the taste of that.
The onion is delicious.
The taste is different.
I like Yoshinoya.
I think Yoshinoya is better.
I think the taste is strong.
If you like it, you'll like the sauce.
Was the onion delicious?
The onion was a little soft.
It's different.
This is different.
This is fun.
Thank you for the food.
Thank you.
Next is Matsuya.
I'll eat Matsuya.
Matsuya
I'll open it.
By the way, I like Matsuya.
I like Matsuya.
I didn't expect rice and meat to be
separated.
It's good.
It's completely different.
Thank you for waiting.
I was waiting.
I'm glad you came.
Please eat.
I will eat.
I'll eat the meat first.
I like it.
I'm glad.
The taste of the meat is stronger than
the taste of the sauce.
I like the taste of the beef bowl.
I like it.
It's very delicious.
I like it the most.
I'm glad.
I say that every day.
I like it the most every time.
Can you choose?
I have decided.
You can choose.
I like this sauce the most.
It's really the best.
I've been eating the best.
Delicious.
This is my favorite.
Is it your favorite?
I'm glad.
I'm eating three stores now, but it's
completely different.
It's completely different.
I've never really cared about it before.
Certainly, you can tell by the level of
eating.
For now,
Matcha?
I feel like it's matcha.
It's the same.
Lastly,
Nakau?
I've never eaten it before.
Me too.
Nakau.
I'm going to eat Nakau beef bowl.
What is Nakau beef bowl?
I've never eaten Nakau beef bowl.
I have the image of udon.
I only eat udon.
I thought there was beef bowl.
I think this is a little different.
It's a little thick.
The aroma is the strongest.
I'll eat it.
It's amazing.
The aroma is strong.
I'll eat the beef first.
How is it?
It tastes strong.
I want to eat this with rice.
It's beef bowl, so please eat it.
There are few people who eat only beef.
Yoshinoe and Matsuya are sweet.
This is
It seems to go well with Benishogatari.
I'll eat it too.
It's the first time.
It's Japanese soup stock.
It's delicious.
This is amazing.
The taste of the soup stock is strong.
It's amazing.
It's delicious.
I'll eat it.
It tastes different.
It depends on the restaurant.
The way of making soup stock and soup
stock are different.
The thickness of the ingredients, the
way of cutting, and the way of leaving
the texture are different.
I don't have a lot of things to say.
It's a taste of Arista.
It's like a strong taste.
It's like a soup stock.
It's the darkest color.
It's dark, but it's a little different
from what it looks like.
It's good.
So we compared the four-point beef bowl.
They all tasted different.
First of all, where is your favorite?
I'm a Matsuya fan.
When I compare the four types of food,
I think they all have their own
characteristics and they are delicious.
I'm lost.
The stable one is Matsuya.
I want to eat this in the future.
Nakau.
Nakau was delicious.
I want to eat this with udon.
Arisa.
What about you, MINE?
I'm lost between the two.
I think it's different if you eat at a
store.
I'm lost between the two stores of
Matsuya and Nakau.
You're the same as me.
We have similar taste.
What is your favorite Matsuya?
I think it's Matsuya.
The meat was thin and had a strong
taste.
The soup taste is similar to the sweet
taste of home.
I like that it has a strong taste.
I didn't have meat, so I could eat it
refreshingly.
I think Matsuya is good.
I want to eat this in the future.
Please do.
I'm looking forward to it.
I like udon.
I'm happy.
Please enjoy it.
I want to go to Matsuya alone.
I want to go to Matsuya.
I'm going to go to Matsuya, which I
liked the most among the four types of
udon.
I want to eat udon alone.
I want to eat udon and go shopping.
I'm going to go shopping.
Thank you for
Let's eat!
Topping is...
Pororo and...
I chose the fresh egg.
I'll eat it simple.
It's delicious.
It's really good.
It's better to eat it with toppings than
eating it as it is.
It's really smooth.
The wind is strong.
I went to the restaurant by myself.
This time, I topped the pororo and onsen
egg.
I put the miso and ginger on top.
I put the miso and ginger on the beef
bowl.
It was really delicious.
I ate it with fake arts.
I thought it was the best to eat beef
bowl on top of other food.
I was able to eat it.
I can eat it quickly.
I feel like I'm eating alone.
I had a wonderful experience.
It was delicious.
Thank you for your viewing.