Please subscribe to my channel.
Let's all grow old together
Thank you for your help this year
The new year is coming, the new year is
coming
Mayama-yama, master
Hoshina, freshly made
Gyoza-pan, Mariko
Nee-san, and O-ran
Thank you for watching!
Let's all grow old together
30 minutes left!
Isn't there more?
Bye!
Thank you for watching!
I took these off.
From today.
Thank you!
I can feel it.
We've heard a lot of things.
But something totally different
happened.
Those who watched the live broadcast
will know what happened.
We suddenly became serious.
We became serious.
We showed our TV-like side.
When I was about to do something, a
Gunpla came out.
I was like, did I have a Gunpla?
I was a plastic model.
Why did you have your hair cut today?
Today is New Year's Eve.
The make-up room is always crowded.
Many people come and go.
I was the only one there.
I was bored with the make-up artist.
I used a hair iron.
I tried it for the first time.
I was done.
The make-up artist was next to me.
I said, look at this.
It's disgusting.
I couldn't say anything other than
disgusting.
I kept saying disgusting.
I have an idea.
New Year's Eve, smooth hair.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
My hair is smooth, too.
Let's do our best today.
What does that mean?
Thank you.
We have a lot of plans today.
How are you today?
Today?
We have two new members this year.
Last year, there were three new members.
Five younger members, five older
members, and five older members.
We were supposed to do our best with 10
members.
But we have a Cinderella time.
We're broadcasting this year's live
broadcast in two parts.
It's half at once.
I feel nostalgic.
It doesn't change much from now on.
It's okay.
There are age-related problems.
Next year...
Will there be a corner next year?
There will be a corner.
We're totally motivated next year.
I'll do it.
This time, too, we're going to do a
super chat.
We also broadcasted it on YouTube this
year.
Are you watching?
The law of the jungle.
Please leave a comment and a devil
charge on YouTube.
Can you see the comments now?
I can see it.
I'm watching YouTube.
There's a little lag.
Everyone is half Ebichu.
It says half time here, too.
It's not half time.
I think there are a lot of people who
are in the audience.
There are a lot of red cards.
I'm watching while eating Toshikoshi.
I'm jealous.
The master's hair is not smooth.
It's a good argument.
It's amazing that the iron is so smooth.
What did you use?
It's a default iron.
It's not that smooth.
I was surprised at first.
It's so straight.
He also did his beard.
I didn't hear about my beard.
It's a diagonal.
I'll explain one of the highlights of
this project.
Ebichu usually sings and dances.
Who is the fastest runner?
Among the ten.
I don't know.
TVK is broadcasting this year.
It's the 50th anniversary of the
opening.
50m run.
Is that so?
If it's the 100th anniversary, it's
100m.
It's a long story.
It's about 70m.
If it's 400m, it's 400 years.
It's the 50m run.
Who do you think is the fastest?
Who?
It's Mayamayama.
I used to play soccer.
He looks great.
He looks like he's running fast.
He's not finished yet.
He's the fastest.
I think everyone in the family is
watching Ebichu.
I think that's what's going on.
You can vote for the winner.
You can participate in the QR code.
High-tech.
High-tech?
It's like now.
You can participate in the QR code.
You can vote for the winner.
If you get the right answer, you'll get
a great present.
I want it.
There's a great present.
I'll tell you about it later.
Can we vote?
Of course.
You know the result.
You can get it.
You forgot.
Let's see what it is.
Please show us.
Please watch the video.
Please watch it and guess what it is.
Cool!
Who is this?
It's a dad.
Some people say they are looking forward
to it.
It was really bright in the morning.
Isn't it cool?
It's a healthy image.
It's cool.
The new car is also the best.
Look at the drone.
Thank you for watching!!
It's so cool!!
It's like a warm up
I want to see it
Look at this
Oh my god
It's perfect
I'm massaging
Mayama-san was sleeping wrong
She was sleeping wrong
Her front part was painful
Around her collarbone
What's wrong?
Mayama
Stretching her arms
So cute
She's so stiff
They are wearing member's color jerseys
Everyone looks fast.
Yeah, they look fast.
So, this is the first round of the
people who will be out.
It's Maya Marie.
Wow.
Out of the 10 people, who is the
fastest?
Wow.
Please tell us your predictions.
Everyone has a lot of predictions.
Usually, the fastest is Hoshina Kazami
and Sakurai.
Wow.
But the masters have different
predictions.
But isn't it difficult to think about it
in this video?
Well, from now on...
There's no hint, right?
I thought about it, but looking at the
video,
the people who are in this race and the
people who don't know yet,
the master is definitely in this race.
It was a good thing that I was
motivated.
Good thing?
Was it good?
There was a lot of atmosphere in the
restaurant.
It was a good thing.
It was like a monomi-san.
So, the voting has already started.
Wow.
Who is the master?
Hoshina and Tsubie.
Wow.
I see.
Thank you.
I didn't think Hoshina was fast.
I was good at it.
I see.
I'd like you to vote for the QR code
that's on the screen.
I'll remember it.
There are a lot of Hoshina.
I heard that Hoshina is fast.
She's fast.
She's always a cheater.
Cheater?
Wow.
I want it.
I want Tsubie and Hoshina.
It's true.
It's like a battle between the two.
It's like a battle.
I don't know.
I'm sad.
The master was excited.
I don't know.
I'll tell you what happened earlier.
The first place winner will get a black
coat with your autograph.
It was really warm.
It's good.
It's rare.
It's the only one in the world.
I want it.
It's a good one.
Please vote for it.
I was going to guess, but I was going to
the location.
I'm the only one who doesn't know.
I see.
Tsuchiya Karen, who appeared in the last
program, is going to a certain event
this time.
Let's call her.
Karen.
Is it coming?
What? What?
It's coming!
Wow, nice sound!
It's so good!
It looks so good!
Wait! Wait!
You're just eating it!
It's so good!
Karin-chan!
Is it recording?
It's recording!
Karin-chan?
Karin-chan!
I'm sorry.
It's so good.
Is there a food report like that?
I know it's good.
There's no food report like that.
Soba is soba, but is it Okinawa soba?
That's right.
Karin-chan, is it Okinawa soba?
I'm Tsuchiya Karin!
Nice to meet you!
That face!
I'm eating Okinawa soba.
That's great!
It looks good.
I'm drinking beer.
What are you drinking?
That's fast!
So, what are you doing?
So, this is...
We're at the Rembrandt Hotel, Atsugi's
party.
Wow!
This is...
Atsugi-san!
The hotel staff!
Thank you for coming to the hotel!
Rembrandt!
Rembrandt? What language is that?
French?
That's right.
We're eating Okinawa soba.
Kamine-san, you've never eaten Okinawa
soba, right?
Why are you deciding?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I've never eaten it.
Ah! Ah! Ah!
You've never eaten it, right?
I want to eat it.
Please bring it here.
Right?
No, don't drink it!
What? It's actually interesting.
There's no point in talking about it.
It's like a middle-aged man's story.
Let's leave the fun aside.
I'd like to introduce you to the head of
the Rembrandt Hotel, Kanemura Syuko.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Kanemura Syuko, the head of the
Rembrandt Hotel.
Nice to meet you.
I'm not going to say anything.
I'm Kanagawa Prefecture's Atsugi City.
We're holding an event for Okinawa's
gourmet music.
We're doing a live performance today.
We have singers Minami Kizuki and Yu
Ishigaki from Amami Oshima,
and Kuina from Okinawa,
and the Acer team,
and the ukulele player Ebaku from Atsugi
City.
It's a luxury.
This is an event that really feels like
Okinawa.
Why is it called Atsugi and Okinawa?
Thank you.
Atsugi and Itoman are the best of
friends.
We're holding an event like this.
We're holding a bar called Bar
Rembrandt, which is a new Okinawa
concept.
We're holding a renewal of the bar.
We're so excited!
We're doing our best to make it happen.
I was able to use the bar in the
dressing room.
It was so nice.
I'm so happy. I want to come again.
Let's go together next time.
Karen is eating the food that we're
having at the event.
We're having Okinawa soba.
Y Lan, a mobile gaming and video game
publisher.
He is trading with a client in Okinawa.
So, after this, we will have a countdown
event.
After that, I will also do a little
live, so everyone, let's meet again
later.
Don't drink too much.
It looks really fun.
It's good.
We are doing it without alcohol.
It's Shira-kun.
Karen-chan's timing of speaking is very
funny.
She doesn't speak when she's supposed
to.
I didn't expect that the chopsticks
would come out when she was pulling out
the noodles.
I've never seen that before.
Everyone is saying that the comments are
good.
Okinawa soba is good.
Orion beer is good.
It goes well with this.
Orion and beer.
It's a refreshing beer.
So, let's go to the commercial.
Please, Chanyu-san.
After the commercial, there is a project
that comes every year.
This year, I will also be a one-shot
Barbie.
I want it.
Thank you for watching!
So, the coming devil.
It's almost time.
Is it over?
Can I say it?
The coming devil.
The devil inside the house.
Live broadcast special.
We are doing it.
We are doing it freely.
So,
We introduced you earlier.
Ebi 50.
The race is getting closer.
So,
You are the most popular.
Thank you so much.
What should we do?
We are not the two.
Of course, we are the two.
I don't know.
Isn't it strange?
We don't have to see it.
We can't change it.
The master threw the bench coat.
We can't see it.
What's wrong?
When we predicted the race,
The result was the same.
Aya or Yuno,
Which one is slower?
We were competing.
You are fast.
We don't know yet.
How was it?
When you were told that you would run 50
meters.
I thought it was a lie.
Why did you run 10 meters?
We are in our teens.
Students run, but adults don't.
It's a big deal.
I felt muscle pain the next day.
It was good.
It may be the result.
Who has muscle pain?
What's that?
Because you run.
That's right.
You may run.
Shishiro and Mariko run 200 kilometers a
month.
How is it?
I want to run.
I'm still running.
You were running on the side.
I don't see other people.
I'm not trusted.
Mariko is a stage person.
She is always moving big.
She is slow because she moves big.
Is that so?
We don't know yet.
2022 is coming soon.
I'm looking forward to it.
We are going to celebrate the New Year's
Eve.
Rei, do you have a question?
I jumped again this time.
What kind of jump?
It was the most intense jump I've ever
done.
Can you see it?
I was worried that I wouldn't come.
I'm afraid of heights.
I want you to pay attention to the
master.
I heard the scream of Danma Zuma.
I'm tired.
I want everyone to jump together.
I want to see it.
Let's go.
VTR, please.
Are you ready?
3, 2, 1, Fight!
How to do it!
So, we're back with the 3rd episode of
the Shinshun Jump!
Look at this!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I can see it on the camera.
Stop it!
This time, we're going to do a long
swing in Haiji.
It's like this.
It's called the Chanyon Swing.
Let's go!
It's amazing to see it from here.
Can you do it?
No, no, no.
You made it well.
What is this?
Awesome!
The water ischefter rowboat
Oh my god!
I'm getting adrenaline rush.
You can sit down with all your weight.
Oh my god!
I can't do it.
Hurry up, master.
I'm getting adrenaline rush.
No luck.
I'm trying to get close to you as much
as I can.
But I can't.
The new year is coming.
Thank you for coming in 2012.
I'll start from 5 seconds ago.
10 seconds left.
What is this?
5, 4, 3, 2, 1
It's amazing!
It's the best!
I hope you enjoy the new year!
I'm so excited.
How was it?
It was so much fun.
I'm so happy.
Let's go again.
See you.
I knew it.
Congratulations.
Happy New Year!
I'm sweating a little after watching the
video.
But it was my first time to go to such a
place.
I thought I did a good job.
I was in the middle of the tube rally
for about 5 minutes and the master
didn't come at all.
I was going to fall down in 3, 2, 1.
I couldn't move from here.
I was scared because I was standing in
the opposite direction.
I was afraid that the master would come
here.
But the staff helped me.
But I was invincible.
I'm glad.
I will do the Devil in the Great Hall
this year.
I want to do it.
March 21st is the day of the Shunbun.
It's a holiday.
I will do the Devil in the Great Hall in
Kanagawa Prefecture.
I want to do it.
We will do a great content.
The content was very popular.
The guest is BMK and KANEN.
The tickets are being pre-ordered.
March 22nd is so soon.
Everyone is so happy.
KANMAI DEVIL.
You just said the title.
The signal is bad.
Everyone is saying happy new year.
NATALIE also posted an article.
It's the next day of YUNA's birthday.
Some people are looking forward to
seeing the content this year.
We have to prepare a birthday party.
Everyone is waiting.
If the staff is in a bad mood, they do
this.
What is this?
Let's eat rice cake.
When I was dancing, three people did
this.
I didn't know how to do it.
And everyone's fingers are different.
I don't know which one is which.
Some people are waiting for the lottery.
We are waiting.
Some people are waiting to get in.
It seems that the next KANEN will be
broadcast.
Let's call out together.
KANEN.
Oh, live?
The legs are moving.
Oh!
Thank you.
Kamune-san, that was a nice jump.
The countdown event has just ended.
The guests who were on stage today have
also been left on stage.
Thank you.
Please listen to the master.
Minami Kizuki, who was a guest on the
show,
and Yusuke Ishigaki, who was a guest on
the show.
Do you remember, Master?
Of course, of course!
What's with that person's maw?
Thank you very much!
Please come again!
Thank you!
It's already the beginning of 2023.
Kizuki-san, do you have any goals for
this year?
This year, I was able to spend a
wonderful New Year with everyone who
loves Shima,
so I want to sing more excitingly, while
also making Shima more exciting.
Thank you for such a wonderful goal.
Thank you.
Ishigaki-san, do you have any goals for
this year?
I started my solo activities in 2022,
so I hope to go to various places in
2023 and meet various people.
I hope to meet everyone again somewhere
and sing together.
Thank you.
It's a really good goal.
Tsuchiya Karen's goal for this year is
to not get drunk and take a taxi.
I'll do my best.
I'll be in your care.
I'll be in your care this year too.
Everyone, thank you for staying on
stage.
Thank you.
Can I talk?
If you talk, you can hear someone's
voice.
I'm ready.
Here.
Karen-chan is gone.
She's gone.
Whose picture is this?
It's a picture of the other person.
Ah!
I'm glad.
I'm really worried.
She's gone.
I didn't expect everyone to leave the
stage.
I was wondering what they were doing.
She's gone.
Karen-chan, Karen-chan.
I'm sorry. I'm going to do my mini live.
I'm looking forward to it.
I drank a little while ago, but I'm
fine.
I agree.
Basically, I always drink.
She's gone.
I'm sorry for the inconvenience of live
broadcast, but I will do my best to
sing, so please take care of me.
We'll be right back.
We have to connect the lines.
I'm excited.
What will she sing?
The guitar will play a note.
I'm excited.
We'll play a song that we wrote
together.
Please listen to Shingen's song.
The soul of the warlord who suddenly
appeared in the hall
The story of Shingen-kun who covered his
head
Thank you for watching!
The only problem I have is
I'm losing confidence in my isn't great
I wanted Ramen in the past
Thank you.
I sing, but I don't know the guitar
Sorry, the Gibson's sound is echoing
From the TV room now
Don't worry, if you're fine
Let's talk about something useless
This world is always
That's enough to blow away the night
rain
Shingen-kun is busy today as well
Thank you very much.
Cute voice.
We will continue to make this even more
exciting.
We will end the broadcast here.
We will return to the studio.
This was Tsuchiya Karin.
See you again.
Thank you very much.
Shingen was busy at the end, but I know
him well. He's not that busy.
He's good at pretending to be busy.
That's why he's so smooth.
Let's watch the video of Ebikoju.
I want you to guess more.
I'm the one who will win!
Please watch the video!
Scroll down and click on Simulation
mode.
Turn off blur and soft light.
Thank you for watching!
I'm so excited to run 50 meters for the
first time in years.
I'm not sure if I'm a starfish or a
lizard.
But Mirei is a leopard.
I feel like I'm being chased by a wild
animal.
I'm looking forward to seeing how she
will run.
I was a relay racer in elementary
school.
But I was a runner-up, not a time
runner.
I'm not a fast runner. I just want to be
a racer.
I know who is the fastest among the
members.
But I've never run with them.
I'm looking forward to seeing who will
be the fastest.
I'm a woman who is always running on
average.
I'll do my best to surpass that.
I'm an average woman at 8.1 seconds.
I want to show that I'm not that kind of
woman.
I'll do my best not to be the fastest.
I think the strongest are Nonoka and
Mirei.
My goal is to beat Aya.
I'll do my best to beat her.
I want to beat Mirei.
I heard that she is a leopard.
What is stronger than a leopard?
I don't know.
I think a cheetah is the fastest.
I'll do my best to be a cheetah.
I haven't run recently.
I'm worried that I'll fall.
Strong?
I heard that Nonoka and Mirei are fast.
The members are making fun of me for
having a bad motor skills.
I'll do my best to get back at them.
I'm young and I'm winning.
I'll do my best.
I want to be the 6th.
I was playing soccer.
I was in a position called a side back.
I can be a side back because I'm fast.
I was in that position.
I was spraying.
I'm strong in the game.
I think I'll win.
My rival?
My rival is myself.
I'm good at fighting.
I was fast if I was a member a year ago.
I'm a new enemy.
What is it?
I got a message from the coach that I
should practice more.
I heard that Mei is also a fast runner.
I want to win.
So I will practice more.
I got a message from the coach.
Really?
How did he reply?
He said, I am great.
I can't run with my muscles next time.
Is it starting?
Wait, wait, wait.
Wow, I don't get it.
Who will it be?
The start dash is also important.
It's the volume.
There's also a momentary power.
The start dash is fast, and the
acceleration comes later.
I think I can run.
You look like a fast runner.
I feel like I'm chasing a camera.
White jersey is strong.
She is the most popular one.
Watch out!
She hasn't started yet.
You like her.
I like her.
Thank you very much.
That was a good hint.
That's right.
I could see the movement of the body.
Well, well, well.
I wonder what it is.
I think I understand why he's not a
lucky guy.
He's trying his best to stand up.
Before he runs.
He was already behind.
If it was just the video, Shishio would
have been faster.
He's fast.
And Mariko was a relay racer.
Yes, she was a relay racer.
She wasn't chosen, but she was a relay
racer.
She was a relay racer.
Let me run.
She wanted to try.
So, we have the graph.
Hoshina and Subiru.
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you for the vote.
I will definitely win.
Hoshina is a little faster.
I see.
In the comments, they say that Non-chan
is a fast racer.
I see.
Well, well, well.
So, we have the final news.
I'm looking forward to it.
I want you to vote more.
It's a commercial.
Gyoza-Pan, please.
That's my favorite sound world.
There's this place I always wanted to go
to,
and I realized concurrently that it's
unnecessary.
And after a short walk around town,
this was my first dent?
So little
Is there something inside?
Nothing.
Thank you very much.
So, we are continuing with Toshikoshi's
live broadcast.
Ebijuu-chan is doing 50m, right?
And Nee-san did Toshikoshi's jump.
So I thought I could do something in
honor of 50m.
I ran 50km!
So, I did 50km!
What? Really?
I ran from Odawara Castle to here.
Today?
Not today.
Today is impossible.
And I did it all by myself.
Wow!
You can take a selfie like this.
You run like this.
Isn't it amazing?
You can talk like this.
It was a fun trip.
Let's see the video.
Please.
This is Odawara Castle.
I'll go to the inn from here.
Let's go!
The viewers are surprised.
It's longer than a car.
The smell of alcohol changed.
Follow Yusuke's turn.
That's right.
10kg.
I'll weigh 10kg.
It's amazing.
10kg when it's rolled.
I'll weigh 7kg.
It's amazing.
It's good.
It looks good.
Of course, the grilled soba is the best.
Delicious.
It went faster.
I think I went off the track.
You hit the little one.
Hoshino-san was acting arrogant too
much.
She is so aggressive.
Hoshino-san was being beaten too much.
Hoshino did things weird since this
morning.
He is giving a long stroke.
His stunting technique is also very
good.
I'm having fun.
He's a master of youth.
20 km.
We've come 20 km.
It's the first time I've run 20 km.
This is an unknown territory.
It looks easy.
It's a lonely journey.
I'm a little nervous.
There is no one to talk to.
I wish you had called me.
I have no choice but to talk to him.
Matsu!
How do you feel?
Matsu is in a good mood.
Tora-suko Shonan Ohashi!
Shonan Ohashi! Here it comes!
Beautiful!
It looks comfortable.
Cute!
The view is nice.
Are you tired?
Of course.
I'm sure.
It's a little hard.
It's a little easy to ride a bicycle.
Thank you for watching.
The players are already passing by.
I'm going to take a picture of this all
by myself.
I'm going to put a pigeon on it.
I think everyone will run by themselves.
Wait a minute.
I'm going to take a picture of this all
by myself.
It's getting tight around here
We're here!
Churchill!
We're in Churchill!
It's so nice!
Wait a minute!
I'm being sucked in!
We're in!
Wow, it looks good!
You already ate it?
I don't want to eat it.
I knew you'd eat it with soup.
I'm doing it! I'm doing it!
I ran a lot.
When I eat ramen, I get a storm.
I'm running to the next restaurant.
I was told I was stupid.
Youth!
It's Uji-sama station.
I searched on Google map.
I wrote the name of the station.
Yogyoji hill.
This is Yogyoji.
We have to go around a long distance.
This is the Yogyoji hill in Kakone
station.
Thank you for watching.
I'm not a mountaineer.
Finally, we are in Yokohama.
Please subscribe to my channel.
It's getting cloudy.
32.1
It's around here.
It's just passed from Odawara Castle.
Nearby,
Kumizawa Castle.
We're here.
Kumizawa Castle is amazing.
Did you sleep on the way?
No, no.
In this season, the sun sets suddenly.
We've been to many ramen shops.
Look, when I was running,
the child disappeared.
What should we do?
The child disappeared.
We can't help it.
We should look at the map.
We can go to Hakone Station by car.
But we can't.
We have to go back.
We're lost.
We're in a dangerous place.
It's about 45 km.
We want to go 50 km.
We've been wandering around.
We're lost.
There's a station in Totsuka.
Let's go.
We've come this far.
We were lost.
To go 50 km,
we could have gone by car.
But we had to go 60 km.
Google said so.
We took the subway from Totsuka Station.
We took the subway to 5 km.
We thought we could go 50 km.
We went to the end.
Can we go?
Of course.
We wanted to go 50 km.
I want to go 50 km.
Let's watch the video.
We're at Totsuka station.
Totsuka station.
We're going to take the subway.
From here, we'll go to Gumihoji.
It's about 5km from there to the ship.
I heard about it, so I took the subway.
Gumihoji.
Let's go to Gumihoji.
Thank you for your viewing.
I think so, too.
By the way, I can't speak anymore.
I can't speak.
I feel like I'm in a TV show.
It's nice to be on TV 24 hours a day.
I think so, too.
Look.
We're going to the Kansai station.
We're at the Kansai station.
We're here.
We're almost there.
Hang in there.
Have you ever seen this?
This song is playing.
I've heard it.
Have you?
It's so close.
It's right there.
It's exactly 10km.
50km.
How long did it take?
It's coming.
Thank you for watching.
Phew!
Once again, SINAUYAtier 4
You did a great job!
I have a story to tell.
I've heard a lot of compliments.
I think I did a good job.
I was doing my ankles later.
Like this.
I was licking it.
I have to take care of it.
But I didn't know.
I was fine when I was shooting Ebichu.
But the next day, my legs hurt.
I couldn't walk.
I went to the plastic surgery.
I took a picture of my ankles.
This is my ankle.
Fortunately, I didn't have a fracture.
But I have a physical injury.
I was born with a physical injury.
When I came to the office, everyone was
surprised.
They asked me if I was a master of 2F.
I thought I would come someday, but I
was still a master.
How are you feeling now?
I recover damage from this kind of
injury very quickly.
I think you're looking at people's rent-
a-game early in the year.
I was happy to be able to play a game
for the first time.
I want to show it to everyone.
I was told that the bones were very
beautiful.
The density was good.
I'm glad you're all right.
Congratulations on your recovery.
I'm going to run 51km next year.
I'll be your phone partner.
Please.
If someone talks to me, I think I'll be
able to use my power.
I'm motivated when I talk to people in a
ramen shop.
The voting for EBIKOJU is about to end.
Please come with me.
Please vote for me.
Let's go.
Before that, let's do a commercial.
Everyone, please come to the third Mayan
Mountain.
So, there you have it.
The debut in the hall.
It's like a water fountain.
You get caught in it.
By the way, you've measured 50 meters,
right?
Yes, I have.
You were fast.
I was really fast.
I was chosen as a relay race at school.
You're a steel pipe from there.
You used your deep sea ability to go to
the steel pipe.
Do you remember how many seconds?
How many seconds?
I think I was 7.5 seconds.
That's fast.
7.12 seconds is fast.
7.5 seconds is really fast.
Then, is it a lie?
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
In the end, Hoshina and Subiee won.
It's a tie.
Damn it.
Thank you, everyone.
I wanted to get a medal.
So, what's your choice?
I thought about it a lot.
Hanae team!
You're a super dark horse.
You didn't say the rule of running
straight.
You should run around the track and be a
super horse.
I didn't say that.
Is there a sportsmanship?
No, there isn't.
You should run for 1 minute.
You're a steel pipe.
You were fast in the interview.
Hana-michi's teacher is like a martial
arts interview.
It's a serious interview.
So, everyone's predictions are like
this.
30 seconds left.
There aren't many viewers.
What are we going to do if we win?
That's true.
What are we going to do?
The biggest bankruptcy in history.
That's true.
It's not surprising.
Sorry, Aya-chan.
It's a secret, but what is the vote for
Hoshina?
Believe me.
The vote is a vote.
Finally, it's over.
Thank you.
She will be released soon.
I'm looking forward to your predictions.
I'm excited.
50 meters is fast.
I don't have time to blink.
Please announce the result.
Let's see the race of fate.
Believe it or not, it's up to you.
It's up to you.
It's like a city legend.
I'm nervous.
I was nervous before.
Thank you for watching this video.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Dance, dance, dance.
Thank you!
I'm curious.
Here it comes!
Wow!
What is it?
Yay!
Wow!
That was fast!
I was in the middle of the screen.
Did you just slip?
What happened?
I think I got a cramp.
We can't see ourselves running.
What is this V-judgement?
I didn't see anything.
Someone was watching us.
We were so close to the finish line.
Riko ran away from something.
She was in front of us.
Riko was in front of us.
She was screaming.
I was so excited.
Starring at YouTube YouTube Volume 5
I became a member of YouTube.
Wow, that's great.
Wow, you're the best.
I did it.
You were the best in the 4th grade.
Yes.
What did you say?
I was the best.
I'm very frustrated.
What did I do?
I watched Netflix and was lazy.
I think I was good.
But I was the best in my heart.
It's important to have a heart that
doesn't give up.
I'm still young and I'm not weak.
It was fun.
I'm glad I proved that I have good motor
nerves.
I'll do my best.
I'm glad I did this.
I'm glad I did it.
That was close!
Her leg is getting slow.
You said you got slow.
She's grabbing on tight.
It's so tight!
Even google can't adapt to this!
But this is cool!
Thank you!
I talked to Nanoka on LINE after that.
I talked to her the day before.
I told her that I was talking to her in
my family.
She said, I think you are amazing.
She praised me.
She said thank you.
Is she being bullied?
But she said she had a 10-year age
difference.
She said she didn't have any.
She said it was the difference between
10 years and 10 years.
But she said she would come the next
day.
She was encouraging me.
She was being bullied.
Is that right?
It was a good game.
I didn't understand at all.
I thought HOSHINA and SUBIE were the
same.
Congratulations to those who voted for
SUBIE.
Congratulations.
I will give this to one person.
I will go to the commercial.
I won't go.
I will read the comments.
It was a good game.
I said congratulations to CHIITA.
It's an old game.
It's like CURLWIST and BENJONSON.
I'm glad I trusted you.
NON-CHAN was fast.
HOSHINA was ahead of the game.
But SUBIE accelerated from behind.
I don't want to make excuses.
I forgot how to run when I ran for the
first time in 10 years.
I was running.
I was good at starting.
I was wondering how to run.
I thought my body was too heavy.
What did you run away from?
I was chased by something.
I was happy.
You were fast.
I wanted SUBIE to run at a different
angle.
CHIITA appeared on the stage.
I wanted SHISHO.
SHISHO?
SHISHO couldn't run straight.
I will go to the commercial.
Please wait.
Good!
Good! Good!
Good! Good! Good!
It's the new year!
It's a great start of the year!
It's the start of Rei's jump!
I look like a traveler at the end.
I'm 50 years old.
Ebi is 50 years old.
So, it's 2023 again.
It's the year!
When you turn the year,
you get a lot of things.
I like it.
I just opened it.
You're so random.
Are you sleepy?
You're like this since morning.
I want to have a lot of things.
It's the second time in Hinagawa.
I have to put a lot of things on.
You have to compete with the master.
I think the gift is...
I'm doing this live.
The first thing you put is a gift.
Ebi's year-end goal.
My year-end goal is...
I want to be a rich person who is still
selling.
I want to be rich.
We have a song called Emotion.
I want to sell more.
I put my feelings into it.
You may not have a license,
but you can sell at a high price.
It's like a left-hand drive.
Where is it?
I want to aim for that.
I want to sell more.
You're a good idol.
Left-hand drive is...
I'm...
It's like this.
I want to do more for the first time in
my life.
Today, I'm in this room.
It's my first time.
It's my first time running 50km.
I did it because I had a chance.
I think there's more.
I'm in a good year.
I haven't done much yet.
I want to do more for the first time in
my life.
Finally, Ne-san.
I'll return the book I borrowed from the
master until I graduate.
What is it?
It's my goal.
I'll graduate at the level of the Grand
Slam.
Graduation?
With an iron pipe?
A continuation.
I'll break the window glass.
It's not like that.
I'll graduate.
I see.
Everyone is surprised.
It's your first time, right?
It's this atmosphere.
I'm crying.
I didn't think it would be like this.
What should I do?
You'll graduate at the level of the
Grand Slam.
I'll graduate on that day.
I haven't contacted you at all.
I'll be there on March 21st.
That's right.
I'm getting a shock.
It was a big announcement.
You'll be surprised.
I didn't mean to cry.
I cried because it was a strange
atmosphere.
I'm lonely.
There are so many people graduating.
I want everyone to come.
I have a question.
Is it Kotobuki Taisha?
What?
I'll change the subject.
The children are a little...
There is no possibility.
0%
Please tell me.
MAMINAP doesn't have that.
Don't worry.
The Grand Slam will be held on March
21st.
It's the last day.
Let's do something.
What?
We can only do it at that time.
I want to do something.
I'll put a steel pipe at the end.
It's not a bike.
I'll retire.
There are many people who will go to the
Grand Slam.
Thank you.
I don't know what to do at the end.
I don't know what to do.
I want to make a lot of money.
I want to enjoy this program with
everyone.
Is the book you are borrowing a book
called Naoshika?
Yes.
I have been borrowing it for 4 to 5
years.
Everyone is borrowing it.
Kamune graduated.
Do you have a regular customer?
Certainly.
I'm sorry.
Do you have a regular customer?
Yes.
It's like I'm deciding the regular
customer.
I'm not involved at all.
If you have any complaints, please tell
the producer.
Why are you so angry?
I have been a master for 6 years.
It's been 6 years since March.
That's amazing.
I graduated from elementary school.
I was in the first to sixth grade.
Congratulations.
It was a live broadcast.
Congratulations on the opening.
There is a mirror opening.
Congratulations.
I want to do that at the end.
Please prepare.
Metal Izawa.
We will send it to you.
Thank you.
There is a notice from Ebichu.
On February 12, 2023,
At Pacifico Yokohama National Hall,
We will hold a limited fan club event.
Please check the details on the homepage
and SNS.
It will be a fun live.
Please come and visit.
Pacifico Yokohama National Hall is a big
place.
It's a two-day event.
It's a two-day event?
If you join the fan club now, you can
make it.
Please come and visit.
Let's go in.
I didn't join.
I will pay the membership fee.
I'm here.
The fan club is a one-day event.
It's a secret.
I don't know if I'm going to join.
So we're going to break this with a
bang.
I'm looking forward to it.
I hope you all have a good year this
year.
First, I'll show you my singing and
dancing.
It's like opening a mirror.
New Year's first.
Then, please.
Let's go!
Yuku Devil!
Gulu Devil!
One more time!
Yuku Devil!
Gulu Devil!
Let's go!
Thank you for watching!
I hate you!
Wow!
It's so...
It's so cute!
What's wrong?
It's a happy year!
Happy year!
Wasshoi! Wasshoi!
Soresore! Soresore!
Okay, sis!
Let's have a great year this year too!
Cheers!
See you!
Happy New Year!
What should I do?