Nice to meet you. I'm Rika Ishimori from
Gunma.
Today I came to Gunma Park.
There is a basketball court, so I will
play basketball with my sister and
father.
I'm going to the right.
I'm going to the left.
Nice shoot.
Pay up.
Oh, back set.
Oh, it's in.
How is it?
Nice shoot.
Did you get in?
Yes, I did.
I'm back home, so I'm going to make
dinner for my family.
I've been interested in cooking since I
was a kid, and I've been helping out
with my mom and dad's cooking.
Today, I'm going to make my mom's
favorite food and have everyone eat it.
It's chicken breast.
I'm going to use this chicken breast to
make the main dish.
I made a sashimi sushi and a sashimi of
a starfish.
I'll soak the sashimi in the soup and
leave it for a while.
I'll put the batter on the sashimi that
I seasoned earlier.
I'll fry the batter.
I used to work part-time at a small
Italian restaurant, so I often make
risotto at home.
I had my mom and dad make risotto the
other day.
I'm glad they said it was delicious.
My favorite food is miso soup.
I love miso soup. I love it so much that
I can live with just miso soup.
The next thing I like about miso soup is
tempura.
I don't have much chance to eat tempura,
but I'm shocked when I eat it sometimes.
I also like pickled vegetables.
I've never learned to dance, and I'm not
physically strong, so there's a lot I
can't do.
I'm very anxious.
I played basketball in the park earlier.
I was in a bad mood and quit basketball
when I was in junior high school.
I'm worried that I'm okay because I'm in
a bad mood.
I want to be stronger and contribute to
Sakurazaka46.
It looks like this.
It looks really good.
It's done like this.
I'm going to have my mom and dad eat it.
It's delicious.