The members' individuality explodes!
Ebichutas Fashion, the second half of
the game!
I'm going to eat some potatoes.
Coordination battle between members with
serious shopping!
Transform into a curry at the fashion
show!
It's different from usual.
Ebichutas-tas, start!
Do you understand?
Ebichutas Fashion
The second half of the game!
Ebichutas-tas, start!
Add various things to private Ebisu
Middle School!
Ebisu Justice!
This program is brought to you by these
sponsors.
The second half of the Coordination
Battle, which is held at the Diversity
Tokyo Plaza.
The four teams are divided into pairs
and each team coordinates each other.
The winning team will be presented with
the clothes they chose.
Last time, these two teams finished
shopping with this theme.
And this time, the second half team's
challenge.
First, let's talk about the theme of the
coordination.
Let's start with the C team.
I want to make it look like an adult.
Kaho is a forest girl, so I want to put
together the clothes in black.
I've always wanted to do that.
And Kobayashi's usual clothes?
One, two.
I want to be in the forest, so I want to
be like a boy who looks like a boy in
the forest.
That's not a forest, it's a park.
I'm a balloon man.
Kobayashi's theme, which is like a
balloon craftsman.
A balloon man.
I see. So one balloon will be
misaligned.
Next, Yasumoto. Her clothes are also
balloon craftsman like Kobayashi.
The theme is...
Yasumoto, let's go.
A balloon man.
Excuse me.
That's right.
It's a new style.
I want to finish it.
It's the last one, but let's finish it.
A pop and playful coordination.
That's a good word.
I want to add a lot of colors.
This is going to be a summer balloon.
Summer balloon?
It's going to be a summer balloon.
Will the balloon code be the key to the
game in the second half?
The budget is 30,000 yen for the fair.
Let's start shopping.
First, the C team went to find the
clothes that match the theme.
Can you see the E-hive?
I can see it. Which one?
Which one?
E-Hype World Gallery is a casual brand
that is conscious of European culture
Kawaki is cute
This is cute
Cute
What about black?
E-Hype World Gallery
I'll choose check
Check 9
Check pattern that can not be missed in
balloon code
While the balloon is progressing
steadily
Looking for clothes to express mature
Kobayashi
Same
First, choose a popular long cardigan
I hate it
Mom was looking
What is this? Cardigan?
It's warm
Kobayashi, which is warmer than it looks
How to finish
The two of the D team are
It seems to be a lot
We go to Wigo, which often goes from
Fulan
I don't know what to choose
This is men's
I think it's cute if a girl wears men's
Moe
It's a catch
Let's make a decision
Have you decided?
I decided
Yasumoto, who is also in the balloon
code
On the other hand, Kashiwagi
Wait
I said it was a pop, but it seems to be
a pop
I'm struggling with the pop theme I
chose
I'm really in a hurry
At that time, the C team
Which one is better?
I choose both
Kode is considering the center of the
store with mature clothes
This is it
I don't like this
I don't think it's better to check this
I don't think I'm the one who chose it
I'm like a grandpa.
I'm white.
The more she gets impatient, the more
she gets shy.
Kobayashi's choice of clothes.
A girl's hand?
5500 yen.
Hey, this is 5500 yen. What should I do?
Let's keep it for now.
What will happen?
The first team that finished shopping at
that time.
It's time to eat at the cafe.
What will happen to the shopping?
But the balloons are over there.
That's right.
The balloons are solidified.
What should I say?
I think Kaho will make balloons
seriously.
Ayaka will put in the story.
I feel sorry for her.
Yasumoto predicts that something will
come up.
It's like Halloween.
At that time, Yasumoto.
It's very cute.
This is a mask.
Hinata.
Which do you like, salmon roe or shrimp?
Salmon roe or shrimp?
Shrimp.
I like shrimp.
Then I'll choose shrimp.
What?
This is very cute.
Even though it's a story, Yasumoto has
put in sushi.
What kind of finish will it be?
Hinata, there is an egg.
What should I do?
I'll choose shrimp.
At that time, the city team is a new
store.
I can read it.
This is small.
This is definitely a waterfall.
Kobayashi, who continues to meditate, is
in the corner.
There is no waterfall.
Kobayashi is thinking of an adult act.
I've never been here.
It's about time to go shopping
I wonder if this is good
Is it like a balloon?
What should I do?
Balloon
I'm really scared of balloons
Ayaka
I want it to be blue
Let's do this
It's pretty bright, isn't it?
The cashier is finally getting ready
But
I've got everything, so I'll give you
15,000 yen
Me?
I've already got a little over the price
Seriously?
What should I do?
1900 yen and 1900 yen
It's about 2500 yen
But Ayaka's hat is a little...
So, the shopping is over
I'll come back to buy it later
And the C team
They were still shopping
I'm tired
My glasses
Yasumoto was also checking her round
glasses
It's like a balloon
What should I do?
Do you know what black is?
Can I borrow a hanger here?
Hanger?
Yes
How many minutes is it now?
I think it's been 5 minutes
No way
Matsuno is still determined to buy it
I'm going to match it with black
I'll go with this
I've decided
I'm glad
They went around the shops and finally
finished
Now both teams are finished
But the unexpected development is...
Here they are
Welcome back
Why?
Why is Matsuno waiting?
What?
I was scared
What happened?
The price went over 30,000 yen
I had to pay
I discussed with the staff
Thank you for watching
How much do you get after a gi Gone
Can I have a drink?
You have a lot of bags
Now, the coordination announcement
What is the most fashionable pair?
Before that
Ebi-chu Game Quest
Finally, the trial version of the Ebi-
chu game is completed
When you actually play it
Various enemy characters also appear
So this time
The boss character that appears in the
game
Introduce in quiz form
Then, the first boss character quiz
This character is the leader of a club
What kind of club is it?
It's a star-shaped star
Star-shaped?
I don't know just by this character
design
It's a bee
If you often see the design in the game
I know
After all, is it that?
Please show me the flip
Tennis ball
Dangerous tennis ball
It's close
The answer is
Killer bee tennis ball
Killer bee tennis ball?
What is Killer Bee?
It's a tennis ball for bees
That's how you attack
That's right
Based on this
I hope you answer the next question
Boss character quiz second question
This boss character, Masuo Edogawa
What club is he the leader of?
Please think together
The four are in this kind of answer
Killer fish swimming
I can't do it on the law
It's a good place
Matcha swimming
I wonder if I should wear it
Please subscribe to the channel
The answer is
The head of the bodybuilding department
of Synchronized
What the hell!
You're a fool!
The game of Ebichu has been created with
the world view
The story that concerns it is going to
be released soon
Ebichu Game Project, please wait for the
next news
Ebichu Fashion Show will begin after
this
Who is the best member of the fashion
coordination battle, Ebichu?
They coordinate each other's clothes in
the room for two weeks
What kind of finish did they get?
I will announce it
I changed my clothes
I got it
It's a good feeling
It's a suspicious group
EGC Ebichu Girls Collection
The top batter is Hoshina coordinated by
Hirota
The theme is me
Hoshina who transformed into Hirota
appears
Amazing
Awesome
So cute
It looks like Hirota
It looks like Voyager
Please spin it
It's like Hirota.
Great!
Next, Hoshina coordinates Hirota.
How did she finish the cute and mature
Ai-Ai?
Next, Hoshina coordinates Hoshina.
It's cute.
It's like an adult.
It's different from usual.
It's different.
What did you throw?
I can see the customer.
It's cute.
It's a big coat.
It's completely filled.
There are various kinds of coats.
There are many kinds.
It's cute.
It's a unified feeling.
Next, Nakayama coordinates Mayama
The theme is cute Mayama
She is full of energy
What is that behind?
It's a fluffy bag
It looks like a rabbit
There are many small things on it
Next, Mayama, who always leaves it to
the staff, coordinates Nakayama with the
staff.
She looks very tall.
She looks like an adult.
Is she a soldier?
She's got a hijab.
She has a high neck.
She's cute.
She's very cute.
Who should I say hello to?
Next, Kobayashi, who was meditating.
How will Matsuno change with the theme
of balloon shoulders?
What?
It's written in English.
It's Kobayashi.
It's good, isn't it?
This is it.
It looks good on anything.
It's a good fit.
Next, Matsuno's work, which imitated the
tears of the particular person.
What is the appearance of an adult-like
Kobayashi?
It's an adult-like Kobayashi.
It's cute.
It's like a cat.
How to walk.
Oh, it's so cool!
Oh, yeah!
I'm not sure at all, but it's cool!
But it's sharp.
No, no, no.
It's weird.
You should cut the eye.
Sorry, sorry.
It's a training.
Next, Yasumoto who is a high-class
student of Kashiwagi.
What is the pop fashion that she was
worried about?
What is it?
It's Hina.
Hina?
Is it a lot of Hina?
What is it?
What are you wearing?
You're dancing like a dance.
Is it a mochi?
Please subscribe to our channel.
The way she looks is wild.
She looks cool.
The last one is the cashmere dress that
Yasumoto made.
The finished look of balloon coat is...
It's cute.
What's this?
She has a bottle of empty bottles.
It's not good to get in the way
And the hat
The hat is cute
It's cute to leave a balloon
That's all for the coordination
Here are the points that the members are
particular about
How is everyone?
Look at these two
It's cute
It's like Hirota
It's like a fluffy thing
This is
First, it's fluffy
It's like walking
Like this
You hide it
This is also very adult-like
I've never seen Hirota like this
It's different from the other ones
I made it cute with this check
I was confused with black
But it's cute for adults
So I made it like this
How is everyone?
It's cute
I said it's fluffy
I was going to make it like this
You decided from this
And
I made it like this
So that you can see it
It's advanced
Next, Nagayama
It's a shuttle neck
It's shiny
I didn't put the necklace in the hat to
make it look good
I see
I took it off
You didn't ask the staff anything?
I didn't ask anything
I believe you
I think these two are very different
But
Rina-san made it
And
Rina-san said it's cute if you wear it
like that
It's a suggestion from Matsuno
I don't know
I don't know if it's different
Which one is better?
The one with the band.
The director is very good at this.
Next, Kato-san. What's the point?
I think it's better to wear it with the
riders.
Riders can buy it for less than 30,000
yen.
This is the best.
It's amazing that it's going to be like
this from here.
It's like this person's child.
Let's go around.
I'm hungry.
There are blue, blue, red, black and
black.
There are about three colors.
I see. Blue, red, and black.
Your hands are like snakes.
It's cute.
I can't help but be interested in your
hands.
This is the last one.
This is the back theme.
It's warm and kind to hold this glove
and bottle.
Isn't it a budget?
It's a budget.
I chose a men's knitwear.
Is this men's?
It's a men's.
These glasses and hats are for the
balloon teacher's school uniform.
I see.
The school uniform for the teacher.
Based on these points, they will be
reviewing the other students'
coordination.
The pair that gets the most points will
be the winner.
Will they be...
The first place?
The first place is...
Day Team Yasumoto-Kashiwaki pair!
57 points!
Congratulations!
What do you think the prize is?
What is it?
You don't know the prize?
Lastly, we would like to announce the
prize.
The prize is...
The prize is announced by the special
judge, Kaiki Ogata.
This is AiAi who coordinated with
Hoshina-san.
Congratulations!
Please take this prize.
It's a prize.
That's Ogata.
I'm not in love with you.
I see.
You're a scary shrimp-chewed Tastass.
The coordinate battle won by the winner
of the battle is...
Yasumoto and Kashiwagi.
Balloon Kode may be popular.
Next episode of shrimp-chewed Tastass
is...
Shrimp-chewed Tastass News.
Pick up the incident that happened in
Tastass.
That strange temptation is also a
source.
The winner of the Tastass is...
Thank you for watching.
And to those who missed the shrimp-
chewed tastas.
On the Star Dust channel, a video
distribution site,
shrimp-chewed tastas are being widely
distributed.
Thank you for watching.
If you want to enjoy the game, you can
get a free shrimp-shaped tastasus for
400 yen a month.
In addition, there are a lot of
unreleased video clips.
For more information, please search for
the Stardust channel.
This program was provided by the sponsor
you are watching.
My guitar is going to sound like this
today.
It was delicious.
Wait a minute.
I'm scared.
Good.
Thank you.