This week's Ebitu Tastas is a special
edition
Ebitu's first handmade birthday party
For Yasumoto and Kobayashi who were born
in June
The members thought of a surprise
Wait a minute, I haven't caught up with
you yet
A surprise that cannot be understood
But it's a mouth
Furthermore
Then who will say it?
The star is a big lie
What is the truth?
Will the birthday party succeed?
Ebitu Tastas start
The next program is...
We will add various things to private
Ebisu junior high school!
Ebisu Justus!
This program is brought to you by the
sponsors you see.
Ebisu!
The taste is beautiful.
Yes.
Thank you for watching.
We are going to be MCs for today's show.
Nan, are you okay?
I'm fine.
I was a bit nervous but I'm fine.
I was a bit clumsy but I'm fine.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm here.
You're here?
You're here? What do you mean you're
here?
You're like a housewife.
You've never been here, right?
No.
I was worried so I came here again.
And you two are off today?
What's wrong?
Kobayashi is...
The microphone is...
It's being recorded.
It's not because of my blood type.
Really?
I thought I'd be a model if I had blood
type.
Actually, today's theme is shrimp
churros and birthday party.
For Yasumoto and Kobayashi who are
celebrating their birthday in June,
we're going to have a secret birthday
party.
Oh!
Yay!
I see.
For Yasumoto and Kobayashi who are
celebrating their birthday in June,
we're going to have a secret birthday
party.
The broadcast date starts 5 minutes
before Kobayashi's birthday.
The broadcast date is just right for
Kaho-chan's birthday.
Kaho-chan is 15 years old on June 12th.
Yasumoto-san is...
Let's remember the birthday.
When is Yasumoto's birthday?
On June 7th.
It's June 7th.
That's right.
I always check on Wikipedia.
You check on Wikipedia?
It's convenient.
It's been 5 minutes since the broadcast
started.
That's right.
The broadcast date will be changed soon.
It's Kobayashi's birthday.
Let's celebrate together.
Let's count down.
I can't speak
15 years old
Your voice is thick
It's good that you are a girl
I'm happy
Ayase's voice is high
Let's do a handstand with Kobayashi
Why?
Take off your clothes
Take off?
What is this?
Ready, go
Wow
Can you see my skirt?
It's okay
The members will have a secret meeting
to think of a surprise for the two
At that time, the main characters
Yasumoto and Kobayashi, who are not
known at all, are
recording with the organizer, Kaiki
Ogata, and Kobayashi Jiji Taidan. Of
course, this is a secret project
I want to do it freely. Because it's a
digital project, I want to talk about my
grandfather's story first. It's a
digital project. It's a real story
I want to talk about what kind of
surprise is good. Clip. Clip. Clip.
Clip. I prepared a clip. Let's write it
all and decide.
What kind of surprise will the members
give to Yasumoto and Kobayashi for the
birthday of the important members?
I would like to go from Mirei-chan.
Thank you. Yes, please.
It's a treasure hunt surprise. Oh,
surprise. What is this? It's a treasure
box. It's a treasure box that appears in
the pirate world.
What is a treasure hunt surprise with a
strange illustration? I put a paper in a
room or something like this and ask
where to go next.
I hide a present and reach it. Oh, but
it's okay.
I can go to the entrance of the house
and go to the right. I'm looking forward
to adventure. I see. Let's go.
Ta-da! Cake!
You give her a cake.
Yes, but I really wanted to make it.
You want to make a cake from the
beginning?
It takes a lot of time to make it from
the beginning.
I think this is good.
It's good.
This is good, isn't it?
I want to make a cake that members
quarrel and tell a story.
I want to make a cake that we do in
April Fools.
What do you mean by that?
We always do that.
I and Hinata quarrel.
I and Taima quarrel.
It's a common story.
Are you two good at quarreling?
Who will go next?
Rina.
Matsuno.
Rina is different.
How to open it.
What's wrong?
What?
Takiyui and...
Takiyui's is not right
It's more difficult
I'm sorry
So, when Takiyui and Chuei fight
I see
This is also good
Yes
It looks scary
It's scary
This is good
It's good
Who's next?
Kashi
Good
They are looking for treasures, cakes,
fights and surprising surprises
After this, they will be surprised by
the surprising surprises
Kashi
Good
Wait a minute I want to appear in the
hot-pot noodles
Kashi appears
What does Kashi mean?
Wait a minute, I'm sorry, I haven't
caught up with my head yet
What does that mean?
What is this?
This is the lower eye
My imagination hot-pot is
The head is blue
It's rough
The mouth is round
The eyes are big
Like a butterfly
Like this
It's like a butterfly
Hot-pot is probably like this from above
But this is also a surprise
Why is this?
Why?
What is particular about hot-pot?
Especially
There is no particular answer
It's not an answer that can be avoided
I can't help but be curious
I thought you would be surprised
If you look at it
It's about what you are really doing
I wrote something until the end
The surprise god who took the most time
to think
Please
I'm going to make a prank video. I'm
going to write about it.
I'm asking you what kind of prank you
want to do.
You're going to make a prank video.
You're going to write about the ball you
threw.
That's right.
I had a lot of ideas.
I thought we could make a surprise video
together.
You want to connect it well.
Yes.
The surprise that the members of the
Ebitu team thought with their hearts.
But does this really come together?
Meanwhile, Yasumoto and Kobayashi, who
are doing a charity foundation without
knowing that it is a fake project,
are...
The theme that you two are going to talk
about today is compliance within the
company.
Compliance is a complex in the world.
It's a complex.
I'll say it slowly.
What is a complex?
It's a complex.
Without a doubt, they were discussing
compliance.
To be continued.
After this, the surprise is coming.
The fire is really beautiful.
And, the hot dog is coming.
But before that...
Ebichu Game Quest
The game project is on the way!
The game project that was suddenly
announced during the show
Finally tonight, a new development
awaits!
It seems that the plant is outside.
This?
What is this?
Wait, what is the contents?
There is.
The contents of the box.
There is something written inside.
I will read it.
I'm really sorry for the members who are
not united.
Everyone will participate in making a
game during the break.
Think about what kind of game you want
to make.
It will definitely appear here.
If you get a paper, it will be good.
I want to hear the sound of the paper.
Everyone, look at this.
Please look forward to it.
I onboarded!
Nice to meet you all.
Hello.
I'm Kato from Natsume Atari, a game
production company.
Natsume Atari, a game production
company, is the one who made the game of
shrimp.
They make home-made game software and
game apps.
Why did a professional game maker visit
the shrimp factory?
By the way, animals are grown-ups.
We're going to make a shrimp game.
We came here today to get your ideas on
what game we should make.
Thank you for coming.
First of all, what game does Shirota
think of?
This is the game I'm thinking of.
It's called shrimp play.
It's a game where you decide who plays
the game.
I think it'll be fun.
It's fun.
There's nothing like this.
Next, it's a game that Kashiwagi thinks
of.
Kashiwagi came up with a lot of ideas.
Which one is your favorite?
It's a game where you gather everyone.
I'm just going to gather my face.
There are various expressions on the
face.
Is that a real anime?
It's okay if it's real.
I'm a little scared of real.
It's a game that's fun to gather.
What's going on?
You have to put a lot of sauce on it.
And then you have to mix it.
How is it?
I'm sorry
The game that Kobayashi thinks of
The idea that I thought of is
A mini game plus a story
I want to put a lot of things I want to
be
If you look at this, it looks like a
flat person
This is a temporary
So, not only Ebichu, but also characters
that the members think of
The last is the game that Nakayama
thinks of
Riko-chan's drawing
I was laughing so hard
Run away from the heat of the winter!
The heat?
The shrimp will attack us with the heat
The three of them
But they won't attack us with the heat
And they will go through the trees
They will be the obstacles
If you get caught by the shrimp, you
will lose
The title is the heat of the shrimp
The shrimp is hot
The four of them came up with ideas
What are the professional reviews of the
game?
The ideas that we received today
We will bring them back to the company
And we will consider them
Thank you
It's our first time
The shrimp game project
Please look forward to the future
development
The first handmade birthday party of the
shrimp
To celebrate Yasumoto and Kobayashi
They will summarize the ideas of the
surprise
I want to summarize this
What should we do?
Fighting is good
Mayama is like a person who likes
fighting
Fighting is inevitable
What about Matsu?
Takiei and Chuei are fighting
And I don't know why
The members also start fighting
And Takiei comes out
It was a surprise
If the members are fighting
It means that the members are not there
For example
At the opening
They are playing around
Hina is playing around
The atmosphere is a little
Hina cries and comes out
I see
And then
The man comes back
I see
The man
Where is the treasure?
If you take out the cake
Happy birthday
It's good
Thank you
It's the first time I've said such a
thing
I often say it
To summarize everyone's opinions
First of all, the shooting star fights
When the kashiwagi jumps out
He appears as a man
And when you look for treasure
I found a cake
It was a surprise
In the flow of seeding
And from here
Add surprise
I don't like fighting
I don't like it anymore
I want to wait
If you do it, you have to wait for the
real thing
Mizocchi will chase you
You have to wait in front of Glen
Challenge
I'm sorry for the manager of the status
But it's amazing
I feel like I can go back
I know everyone is excited, but I'll go
back a little more
Because it's a great front
I'm sorry, I lost
Nagaraposhi-san, shouldn't you say sorry
and go?
Wait a minute, I'll chase after you
I was talking about what to do when you
were left
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Here is the flow of the surprise
First of all, the members and the
members who are excited at the opening
of the program and the chuei are cut off
Then, the manager Mizocchi took out the
temporary jacket that caused it and
removed the seat of the temporary
jacket.
And for some reason, the three of the
temporary jacket, the chuei, and
Mizocchi appear in a hot pot and start
treasure hunting
And so, they find a cake and say, Happy
Birthday!
And that's how it goes
had a dream
The two of them are done with the
location.
Wow!
So we're going to do it a little bit.
We don't have time.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So we really have to practice now.
We're going to practice.
After the recording of the fake project,
Yasumoto and Kobayashi head to the
members.
The car with two people on it at the
venue where everyone is waiting.
We've arrived.
Then, everyone, please stand up.
Stand up.
The rehearsal is over.
Thank you.
Bye.
I'm not sure
Please stand by
It seems that he doesn't feel suspicious
I'll take a photo of you and the talk
block
I'll wait
I'll start
Please clap your hands
5 seconds before the end
4, 3, 2, 1
After that, the surprise will begin
Now, the show has started!
Ebichu Tatas!
Today, I'm going to introduce you to my
friend, Rika-san
Mic, mic, mic!
Is everything okay?
Are you okay today?
I'm worried about you
It's okay, I'm just a little nervous
Let's introduce ourselves
I'm the flow star, Takiguchi
Juu-Ei! Juu-Ei!
It's too long
It's too long, right?
No, seriously
It's not used, right?
What are you guys?
It's not what you say
Then who says it?
The camera is not free
I'm really worried
Why are you angry?
I'm talking to you guys.
What's wrong?
You haven't made any progress.
No one's going to say anything.
Why?
It's not what you're saying.
No one's going to say anything.
Why?
I'm fine.
Shut up!
I was just doing my usual stuff.
This is weird.
I'm fine.
She's sweating.
What's going on?
She's fine.
Let's touch her.
She's still sitting.
What's going on?
Are you okay?
She'll be back soon.
Please wait for her.
She's sweating a lot.
She's still sitting.
What's going on?
What??
What is this??
Where is hidden treasure?
Who is??
I found it
Happy Birthday To You!
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday dear Ayako!
You two, erase it!
It's a prank!
Wipe it! Wipe it!
Okay!
It's a prank!
Are you angry?
I'm not angry!
You can't hear it, right?
So, the prank was a success!
For the two who haven't been able to
swallow the situation yet, they've
organized it.
Which part surprised you the most?
I'm not feeling anything!
Calm down.
I really did it, didn't I?
I?
When I felt like my head was going to
fly off, I was scared.
Where?
I'm really scared of Takeru-san.
Where did you get surprised, Yatsumoto?
When Hinata said,
I thought, stop it.
Why are you fighting here?
I thought, you idiot!
That's also a part of the plan.
Kashiwagi is going to make an excuse to
go outside.
That's right.
When you said, it's real that a
I'm glad it wasn't real.
Didn't you think it was weird?
I didn't think so.
So, when they put a birthday party in
the shrimp,
I bought a hot dog.
The hot dog celebrates it.
Next time, it's finally time for the
birthday party.
A mysterious surprise is waiting for the
members.
What is this?
And...
The members' feelings...
This program was provided by the
following sponsors.