New members of the private school Ebisu
Middle School have been selected from
over 7,000 applications.
The final screening will begin.
Nine members remain.
The first one is...
St Carrie.
Nonoka brings out a victory of Living
Life Review.
N vorbei no Yokomo.
I'm quite nervous but I like to have
fun.
The second one is...
I'm looking forward to this.
Thank you for watching.
Yu-no 14 years old, from Nagoya A-gyo-
sho, Stardust
I'm nervous, but I'm really looking
forward to it
Yu-no 14 years old, from Nagoya A-gyo-
sho, Stardust
Mei is 15 years old and she is confident
in her K-pop dance
I want to keep working hard on my own
The fourth person is...
It's a song that agency had prepared for
Self-Being
Aika, 18 years old, a big fan of Ebichu
I was so nervous that I couldn't sleep
last night
The fifth person is...
An idol
Rin, 18 years old, came from Ishikawa
prefecture to become a dream Ebichu
I will definitely become a member of
Ebichu
The sixth person is
Moana, 13 years old, is the youngest
one, but I'm looking forward to what
kind of lesson I'm doing
I couldn't sleep because I was too
excited
The 7th person is...
Double dutch
Double dutch is her specialty
Sports expert girl Mai, 16 years old
I'm very nervous
I want to do my best
The 8th person is...
15-year-old Kokona is showing her
dynamic jazz dance.
I'm very nervous, but I'll do my best.
And...
The last one is...
I'm hungry.
How long have you been doing this?
I haven't been doing it recently.
I quit in September.
September?
Rina, 13, who showed her my-paced side.
She is also a junior high school
student.
I want to go home after I come back.
I want to do something that only Rina
can do.
Hello, everyone.
Hello.
Thank you for joining us for the
training camp.
I hope you enjoy it.
Thank you.
The 9 trainees from among 7,000 trainees
will compete in the 3rd and 4th day of
auditions.
It was a good experience to remember for
the rest of my life.
I want to be an idol that everyone longs
for.
I want to be a
I want to be a walking lesson
Ueki Miyu sensei is teaching models at
Tokyo Girls Collection
I want to show you how I walk
First, let's check how the students walk
Please
Thank you.
Now, let's start the second group.
Let's go!
Thank you.
The third group, please.
Go ahead.
Thank you.
They have passed the audition.
They walk beautifully, but...
I want to make sure that my aura
disappears when I'm a cat.
Looking back,
Rina's back is definitely cat-like.
What I was most interested in was the
movement of the hands.
Some people have a slight difference in
the hand swing.
I want them to use their bodies as
evenly as possible.
Looking back on this,
Nonoka's left and right arm swing width
is different.
How do you change the way you walk?
For walking, you should walk straight.
You have to walk straight.
And what's the point of walking
straight?
When you look from the front, your legs
should look like a single line.
So put your right knee inside.
When you actually put your knee inside
while walking,
you should walk straight.
Knee-in
When you put your knee in...
She walks straight without moving her
body.
The way she walks in front is also
beautiful.
But in the middle of all this...
3. She got on first.
Yuno's legs don't move.
Put your feet in the knee and lift your
heels.
That's good.
It's easy to get a cramp. Close your
legs straight.
Don't get a cramp. Move your legs.
One, two...
The instructor repeatedly points out...
...that she practices with her knees in
mind.
Then...
One, two...
Yes, that's right. It's getting better.
One line. It's getting better.
Her walking style has improved.
She walks with a crab stick.
She walks with a beautiful model.
Next lesson is...
Let's do a pose.
Especially for those who want to look
cute.
Thank you.
If you use your hands around your face,
you'll look cute.
Is there anyone who wants to look cool?
Oh, that's good.
I think it's good to add some gestures.
The neck is also fashionable.
I think the hair is also fashionable.
Think about the pose you like,
according to the teacher's advice.
Finally, one by one on stage.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
The
I
Pose!
Go ahead!
Turn around and pose!
Thank you!
Thank you for watching.
Thank you.
Pause.
That's it.
Alright, thank you.
And still, any one of them handled all
these difficult tasks?
Start!
Impressive.
Shake hand
Yes
Thank you very much.
Walking with his knees on the inside
The last pose is the only one in the
country with a cool pose, Aika
What kind of pose will he do?
12thmeet
Let's start
G
Thank you for watching!
The lesson is over.
I'd like to end it here.
Please stand up.
It was your first time, but you improved
so much.
I'm looking forward to your future. Good
luck.
Thank you very much.
It was fun, walking like a model I've
become used to
Kia Ō- yourselves.
one, and then one, It made you feel
Rosen
Normal
ujemy
ár
w
as if you were drifting.
So I venomous
And...
My legs are already broken, but it's
really hard to fix them.
It hurts a lot, but I want to be able to
do well like everyone else, so I'll do
my best at home.
Thank you for watching.