It has started! Ebitu Tastas!
This week's Ebitu Tastas is Ebitu Tastas
Refresh!
To make sure you can enjoy the entire
tour, we have prepared a variety of
refresh programs as a reward!
And then, while the members were
recording, they fell asleep!
The shocking development is...
《Ebichu Tastas》start!
With this expandable elementary school,
King Cl
and his pure
education students!
hes rich
his
Monotorium Monotorium
Middle school student
Let's add various things to your private
Ebisu middle school
Middle school student Ebisu Dastus
This program is brought to you by these
sponsors.
Recently, I have no eyes at all.
I can't understand why you say that.
I'm crazy about this.
I'm into it these days.
I'm on a HADOL tour, so I'm going to be
a massage machine with no eyes.
Today, we are visiting Yokohama
Hakkeijima Sea Paradise!
Yay!
This time, you can enjoy 4 aquariums and
various attractions.
Yokohama Hakkeijima Sea Paradise is full
of attractions.
What kind of theme will be added to the
shrimp
I will announce today's theme.
Today's theme is refresh.
Refresh!
I think everyone is tired from the tour.
Yes, during the debut, she is currently
on a tour around the 14 cities of Japan.
To heal the members who are tired, we
have prepared a special project.
We, Nagareboshi, have prepared a variety
of refresh programs.
By the way, what is everyone's refresh?
For example, when you are tired, can you
ask me a question?
Please tell me how to refresh when you
are tired.
Going to karaoke with my mother.
Eating delicious food.
Drawing pictures.
Why do you skip one?
Mayama?
And stepping on the shiko.
Mayama has a good idea.
What kind of shiko do you do?
I wake up in the morning and shout out
loud.
After that, I don't know if I'm going to
shout out.
You don't have enough explanation.
I don't know what to do.
I wake up from the bed and shout out
loud.
I can't see my family.
Don't step on the shiko when you wake
up.
The first program prepared by
Nagareboshi is to help the members who
are tired during the tour.
The first program is a big laugh.
I'm excited.
You can laugh and relax.
You can laugh and feel refreshed.
So today, we have a comedian.
And we will laugh and feel refreshed.
The first program is a big laugh.
Who is the comedian who came to help
them?
Yeeeeeex
I'm Nagareboshi
Let's introduce ourselves
I'm Nagareboshi Takeuchi
I'm Koneayuki
Let's do our best
Don't open it by yourself
Today is also interesting
Please stop
We are from Gifu prefecture
Gifu is a minor prefecture
It's not a famous prefecture
There are famous prefectures
Marathon runner Takahashi Naoko
Kyu-chan
That's Gifu prefecture
Mr. Marikku
There are many
And famous buildings
Building, building, world heritage
There are many
I think Gifu can be famous
I thought of a theme park
to make people interested in Gifu
A theme park of Gifu?
What is it?
Gifu-Ni-land
Is it okay?
I'm watching you clap
Thank you
I'm grateful for Gifu-Ni-land
I thought of Gifu-Ni-land
I also thought of mascot characters
mascot characters of Gifu-Ni-land?
Who is it?
Hello
What's this?
I'm the closest to Gifu prefecture
I'm Nagano Ken
It's not the next Ken
It's the next Ken
My body is Matsumoto Castle
My head is made of Nozawana
Cute
I can't see the picture
What is this hand?
It's a parking lot
I can't see the picture
Today, I'm going to introduce you to
many attractions
You are scary
What did you say?
It's far from an attraction
How far can you run?
It's already started
What is this?
Be the feeling of Kyu-chan
It's a full marathon
Why is it a full marathon?
It's not an attraction
You are very tired
You are breathing with your shoulders
Don't take your face out
Don't show your face
I saw it
Is there no attraction?
Next, many famous attractions of Gifu
are approaching
I will stab the knife in front of me
I'm scared
What is stabbing the knife?
Making a song
Turn
It's a world heritage
It's broken
Hand power
Nice hand power
I just pushed it
Next attraction
It's Nagano Ken
Sorry
It suddenly jumps out
What are you doing?
What are you planning?
You think it's a enemy
Are you OK?
I'm sorry
I stabbed the wrong place
Are you OK?
How did you fix it?
What happened to your hand?
Look
An electronic Gifu parade started
Why is there a parade?
It's hard to say
Thank you very much
Cute!
How was it?
I can take off my cheeks!
You can take off your cheeks!
You can't take off your cheeks, right?
You can take off your cheeks?
It means you ate something delicious.
That's true.
Your cheeks are about to fall off.
My cheeks are about to fall off.
I can take off my eczema.
You can take off your eczema.
I don't know what that means.
What does that mean?
It means you had fun.
I refreshed myself!
You did it!
That's great.
The members were very excited about the
shooting star's full-on comedy.
To refresh themselves, they will be
divided into 3 teams and each team will
have a chance to experience a program.
First, the voice-over therapy team.
Mayama, Hirota, Hoshina, Nakayama.
These are the four members.
Voice-over?
Voice-over therapy.
I'm going to be on the show today.
You are?
That's great.
Next, the Mu-no-kyoji team.
Yasumoto and Kobayashi.
Yes.
What are you doing?
I'm scared.
What are you going to do?
Mu-no-kyoji.
I'm scared.
And lastly, the heart detox team.
Matsuno and Kashiwagi.
Heart detox.
The title is so familiar.
What is it?
So, as you can see, the three teams
are...
I don't know what kind of program it is
just by the name, but what is the
content that makes me curious?
First, the team of 無の教地, Yasumoto
Kobayashi's recommended combination.
So, the team of 無の教地 is here. We are at
the hotel C Paradise Inn.
We are at the hotel. What do you think,
Kobayashi?
A haunted house?
Why?
Are we in a hotel?
Are we okay?
Master, you have a good reception.
Actually, we will let you sleep here.
Are you sure?
I asked if you are sure.
That's right.
That's right. 無の教地 is basically sleep.
Take a rest and refresh yourself.
Can you bring an eye mask?
That's a good idea.
Hurry up and bring it.
An eye mask is a good idea.
So, let's head to the room that
Kobayashi prepared for the night.
It's so nice.
It's so relaxing.
I'm lost.
It's so spacious.
It is.
There's a cat over there.
So cute.
It's so relaxing.
But, you should take a good rest here.
Okay.
Yasumoto's room is next to yours.
Shall we go?
Good night.
I will do my best.
Next, we went to the room that Yasumoto
had prepared
But actually, this project...
Thank you for watching!
Oh, you noticed me?
What's wrong?
Can't I sleep?
No, you can't.
You were so energetic.
I was like, really?
Actually, this is a prank.
When you say you can sleep,
I will watch you and Yasumoto-san
to see how you react.
I see.
I can't react.
I can't do that.
You are completely in sleep mode.
Yes, I'm in sleep mode.
Actually, just sleeping is a lie.
When you say you can sleep during the
recording,
Kobayashi will find out what kind of
behavior you will do.
This is a prank to see how you will
react.
He is fast.
Very fast.
He looks like he is dead.
He is holding his hand.
Do your students usually sleep like
this?
Yes, they sleep quietly.
Do you think they will sleep?
I don't know.
I think they will sleep.
But I think there is something.
I don't think they will sleep.
5 minutes later
The voice of Yasumoto is in the middle
of the night
As expected, Kobayashi is in the middle
He is not able to sleep
So
Let's call him
Let's call him and ask him if he is
really okay to sleep
Maybe he is still in doubt
Let's call Kobayashi
Watanabeuh from N absolutely can't stop
laughing
Could it be...
?
It's not working at all.
I found a lot of mistakes.
Why do you look so sad?
I'm afraid of the camera.
You're so cute.
What do you think I feel when I imagine
how you feel?
I'm not sure if I can sleep.
I'm worried.
You're worried.
There was a mysterious call.
I really don't know what to do.
I don't know anything about the
disciple.
Even Master Yasumoto can't read the
future.
What kind of action will Kobayashi take
after this?
On the other hand, the voice therapy
team is...
What do you think it is?
I'm scared.
What kind of action is it?
What kind of action will the voice
therapy team prepare?
It's over there.
I did it!
The members are too happy to speak out
loud.
But they are going to use the screaming
machine, Leviathan, to speak out loud
from the bottom of their stomach.
I want to ride it.
I want to be a serial killer.
At the same time, the Mu's teaching
team...
I think we met at the C Paradise in
Naraoke.
I think we are doing the most innovative
way of teaching.
Isn't this C Paradise?
It's not.
You came here on purpose.
The dolphin is...
I'm sorry.
Because there is a dolphin.
That's all.
C Paradise.
It's dirty.
The topic here is the sleeping episode
of Kobayashi.
Did you ever sleep?
I did once.
You did?
I was crying.
And Riko was laughing because her face
was crying.
There was a huge difference.
I see.
I was really upset.
This is the actual video of that time.
The sleeping episode of Kobayashi
I just woke up.
You just woke up?
What about you, Nakayama?
I messed up the time.
Good morning.
I'm tired.
She is looking for Kobayashi.
Nakayama is sleeping.
She is like a human.
I'm laughing because you are crying.
I thought only Kobayashi was sleeping.
But I was sleeping too.
Why are you laughing?
I'm happy.
When Kobayashi is sleeping,
I want to ask her to do a sleep-talking
prank.
What kind of prank will she do?
Do you have any good idea?
You don't like it?
I think it would be nice if I could give
her something she likes.
What do you like?
I like dumplings.
There is a dumpling here.
Just right.
It's a coincidence.
It's amazing.
It's good.
I'm looking at it with the lid closed.
I'm sorry.
I want to draw a graffiti.
I want to do that.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to wake up with a refreshing
morning.
I'm sorry.
This is the first time I've ever had a
prank like this.
Yasumoto is going to challenge her first
ever wake-up prank.
The plan is to try to wake up with the
smell of Gyoza, which is a favorite food
of Kobayashi.
If she doesn't wake up, she will
scribble on her face.
If she wakes up, she will say good
morning to her.
Then, something strange happens to
Kobayashi.
It sounds like a strange sound.
It sounds like a real sound.
It's a strange sound.
It's not a strange sound.
If she wakes up, she will say good
morning.
The two who Kobayashi decided were
completely a joke are finally going to
the prank.
After this, Yasumoto will challenge the
first ever sleeping prank.
What will happen to Kobayashi?
Kobayashi is sleeping without knowing
the prank.
Finally, Yasumoto, the mastermind,
attacks.
What will happen?
I want a person who knows nothing else
!!!
As another one
This is the photo taken at the hotel.
Good morning.
Mr Kobayashi!
You woke up.
Good morning.
Sorry to bother you.
How are the dumplings?
They're really good.
What did you say?
Can I have one more?
Can you eat it?
Actually, we...
We saw you sleeping in the room next
door.
We saw you in the room next door.
How long did you sleep in the futon?
It took more than 10 minutes.
It took more than 10 minutes?
I had a dream.
What kind of dream?
I had a dream when I came here.
A girl I didn't know came out.
She had a potato.
She had a potato?
I was conscious of it.
You remember that much?
That's amazing.
A girl with a dumpling instead of a
potato.
She's the type of person who wakes up to
the sound of something.
I see.
I did something that was a waste.
What do you mean?
I think it was a wake-up prank.
I wanted to get pranked.
So, she will continue the prank while
she is sleeping.
Thank you for your viewing.
Please watch again.
It stinks!
I woke up.
I was doing it for a long time.
Kobayashi is bad at it.
I can't stand it at all.
It stinks.
I was surprised.
The smell of ink.
Please.
What is this?
A youkai is eating gyoza.
I drew a gyoza on my chin.
Is this a gyoza?
I see.
Please eat.
Mmm, nice gyoza.
Thank you very much.
They seem to have enjoyed the meal,
leaving the refreshment aside.
Next time on Ebichu Tastas, we will have
a refreshment episode of Ebichu Tastas.
Nakayama, Hoshinaga, Hirotaga, and
Mayama are all screaming.
On the other hand, Matsuno and Kashiwagi
are screaming for some reason.
What on earth is going on?
Our game, Shitsugeki, has been released
by the Buso-Fuuki Association of Ebisu
Junior High School!
Please try playing it!
Let's go to the shooting range!
Super macho!
This program was provided by the
following sponsors.
Thank goodness!