Ebichu's video
Movement of a
I'm really sorry
But look, look at the sky
I want to be able to do it
I'm working hard, I'm working hard
What?
Here it comes.
Tenkai Pin!
Karin-kun, happy birthday!
Karin, Karin, happy birthday!
Thank you!
I think it's a very nice chair.
I'm not dead.
Manaprafest was also a very moving
stage.
I'm crying because of the love of the
Tohoku group.
I don't know what you're talking about,
but I'm crying.
Thank you very much.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
3, 2, 1.
I'll do it with a great smile.
Smile, smile, smile.
It's so cute.
3, 2, 1.
Thank you.
The first participant is this person.
Welcome, everyone. This is the Akita
City Cultural Center's big hall.
Mr. Yomuin, we are really happy to have
been able to enter the Akita Cultural
Center.
I'm glad to hear that.
Oh, it's the place where Ms. Satokagura,
the live-hage, will be performing.
I want to see the live-hage for once.
Live-hage? Stop saying that like
sashimi.
What? I don't understand.
You know, it's kind of...
Then, do you have the grilled live-hage?
Do you have the steamed live-hage?
Wait, wait.
Don't fight until you come to Akita.
Hahaha, the new students this year are
in good spirits.
The live-hage is over.
It's over.
It was cool.
I was surprised to see it for the first
time.
I was the first to see it.
It was the closest.
The power of the
Taiko was amazing.
I was very impressed.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm going to show you the performance.
Let's go.
That's it.
I'm going to show you the performance.
Let's go.
It was cool.
I was very impressed.
I'm going to show you the performance.
I sweated a lot during rehearsal.
It's really cold now.
So I'm going to wear a parka.
Go to the bathroom.
Hurry up.
Sorry.
Hey.
Sorry, Kanoi.
Sorry.
How many hours have passed?
It's not that painful.
No.
Let's go.
Where's the kick time?
I'm sorry.
There is no big white one.
There it is.
This is good.
What?
Thank you.
It's a chance to get a finger-in-the-
finger.
Shiritu, F-shichiyu, Kukkut.
Then, it will come out.
Will you get angry?
I was a little angry.
After that,
I will do a rehearsal of the opening of
the Coddy.
What?
Shiritu, F-shichiyu, Kukkut.
It's coming out.
I will get a finger-in-the-finger.
I've been watching Kamisoul Brothers
since then.
It's very interesting.
Please.
Shiritu, F-shichiyu, Kukkut.
It's coming out.
I was a little angry.
Thank you for watching.
I'm sorry.
I'm here.
Again.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I can't see anything because it's dark.
Thank you.
I took a good picture.
I can't see anything because it's dark.
Turn around.
It's very dark.
I can't see anything.
Thank you.
Thank you for watching.
Know your elementary school friends!
Today, we invite all the pads Мы are not
changing the
Thank you for watching.
That's all for the photo shoot. Thank
you for your time during rehearsal.
Now, please enjoy the live performance.
The second round is over.
5 back jumps.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
I'm done.
Let's take a deep breath.
How do you breathe?
Breathe in.
Thank you for your viewing.
I'll come in naturally
I got it
Then I'll try to wear it
Haa
I wore it
I'm tired so I'll do this
I'm tired
We couldn't do it last year
It's really grateful that we can do a
big live once a year
First of all, thank you to the
environment
Thank you to the audience and viewers
Even if there are various things, we are
perfect on stage
We are the idol of Ebichu, so let's
enjoy
Are you tired?
Where are we?
Aichi-chan!
We are Ebichu!
Let's go to the song Ebichu!
Thank you for your hard work!
SENTRAL FILM
I got this from Kobayashi CFO.
How is it?
This is a painting by Kobayashi CFO.
One of the world's most important
connections.