I'm a high-class idol.
And the third one is?
The third one is the character.
I like to write.
Not a letter, but a pen.
I haven't heard of a pen and a pen for a
long time.
I can write a strange letter.
What is it?
Recently, there are some things that are
reversed in the live broadcast.
When I made an announcement, I was told
that it was reversed.
I thought about what to do, and I
thought I should write all the letters
in reverse.
I wrote it so that I could write the
letters in reverse.
Can you write the letters in reverse
right away?
I can write it.
I want you to write something.
Then I'll ask you to write the title.
Nightclub and idol.
Please write it.
Will it be in the live broadcast?
Let's go.
Nightclub and idol in reverse.
I'm impressed by your ability.
I'm impressed.
Is there an idol-like letter when you
make an announcement?
I can write it.
It's a cute letter.
What did you write?
Please write an idol-like clip.
Please follow Takaichi Hoshikan SNS.
You always write your name too big.
I write it with a lot of momentum.
It's cute.
You like writing letters.
I want you to write something like that.
I'm in the industry, so I can write a
lot of questions.
I'm waiting for your question.
I wrote three letters.
I'll take a break before the end.
It's a big challenge for me.
I want you to make sure you don't miss
this time.
anything.