The last episode of the Ebitutastas
trial
Everyone, pooping is not normal
This time, the shocking verdict is
Ebitutastas, start!
Add various things to private Ebisu
Middle School
Ebitutastas
This program is brought to you by these
sponsors
The news of the change of broadcast time
of shrimp-chewed castas
From October, shrimp-chewed castas will
start at midnight.
Do not miss it!
Castas trial to pursue various
suspicions of the members on the stage
of the court
In this trial, the prosecutor is the
prosecutor and the defense is the
defense.
The members will decide whether to be
guilty or not by multiple decisions and
the judge will give a verdict.
These three people are being judged this
time.
What kind of
The next is here.
Oh, thank you!
I know.
I wonder if everyone knows this.
Then, the defendant Ayaka Yasumoto is in
the front.
Yes.
I thought that was it.
What is the content of the old man's
According to the testimony of the
manager and the members, the defendant
Ayaka Yasumoto's old manism has evolved
and has destroyed the image as an idol.
So, even though he is an idol, he is a
man who is old and smelly.
And I have prepared a witness.
Witness?
Then, Matsuno will give a decisive
testimony that will deceive the
Ayaka said it was rice before.
I said I know a good store, so I'll go.
And then, taro is prepared.
Oshibori.
Then, Kenya Ayaka asked me if I could
wipe my face with this.
I said I only do the three.
But, it's always like that.
It's always like that.
Do you wipe your face with the Oshibori?
By the way, is this true?
Yes.
Somehow.
Did you admit it?
By the way, do you wipe your face with
the Oshibori?
Not at all.
It's strange.
Normally, with my family,
With your family?
Yes.
I wipe my face with the Oshibori with my
family.
With everyone?
Yes.
This is a beauty tip I want to recommend
to women around the world.
What is it?
Wiping your face with wet tissue and a
towel
Is that a beauty method?
Wiping your face with a towel?
The number of old men in the country is
decreasing
Director
Oh, Begode
I think there is an idol-like side to
old men
What do you mean?
Recently, I often wear something
I'm wondering from the members
Can anyone testify against that?
I can't
Please wait for a moment
Wait a moment
Yasumoto often wears something
These two people will testify
I was thinking of watching the members'
blog
I saw the members' blog
I thought that the blog of Ayaka was
different from usual
Then I took a picture with a fashionable
feeling
I wondered what this was
I tried a lot of aroma
Aroma?
Aroma is a common thing for girls
What do you mean?
A fan gave me a present
I said that I should buy other things
Yasumoto gave me a present
I don't give money
You got it
I got it, so I'll try it
I did it with that feeling
I didn't think I would do it seriously
I'm proud of that blog
There is still a judge
Begoni
Recently, she has been using vegan
rollers
Vegan rollers?
It's not recent
Next, Hoshina
Can you testify against the idol-like
side of Yasumoto?
It's not recent, but I've been using it
for a long time
I used it too much
It should be made of iron
It's sagging
The iron is sagging
You know the meaning of it
I'm already doing it
I did it too much and my face was
swollen
You're using it wrongly
I don't know the meaning
I see
Everyone says that I'm doing it too much
If I say too much, it will be cut off
It will be cut off
Is that true?
My dad often tells me that I have a
round face
I'm worried about it
Because I'm small and thin
Even if I'm told that I'm too round, I
think I'm wrong
But when I'm too thin and my face is
round
When I'm told that I'm too much, I think
I don't have to do it
Let's continue
What's wrong Kenji?
There is a testimony that the old man is
going further
Here is the testimony of Hirotana
I took a bath for 3 minutes
3 minutes?
You took a shower in 3 minutes?
It's like a prison
You didn't wash your body in 3 minutes
So I don't know what's going on
What's going on in the bath?
It's like it's dirty
It's dirty
I washed my body
Did you wash your back?
I washed my back with a towel
Old man
The situation is very bad. What will be
the verdict?
Ready, go!
It's not fair
Wait a minute
I want to meet the old man
The innocent is 4 and the guilty is 3
The defendant is innocent
It's not fair
Why?
Even though there are many old men's
evidence, why are they innocent?
There may be old men
But they are also doing something like a
woman
Old men don't do vegan roll
They don't do adult roll
I think it's better to make a new idol
of the genre of old men or old women
You mean it's better to have an old man
idol?
That's better
But the gender will change
Ayaka Yasumoto is innocent
From now on, they will aim to be a fair
and honest old man idol.
Next, the second trial today.
The following case is here.
Walu Gaki Giwaku
Then, the defendant, Hidaka Kashiwagi,
is ahead.
The true story of Walu Gaki Giwaku, who
was caught by Kashiwagi.
According to a certain manager's
testimony, the defendant, Hidaka
Kashiwagi, works on many mischievous
acts.
Sometimes it is beyond half of the
mischief, and causes a lot of trouble to
many people.
Therefore, he is charged with over-
mischievous acts.
I will do my best. Of course, I have a
testimony.
I see. Then, please, Kenji.
This is a trouble that the manager of
Ebichu is causing to his family.
What did you say?
It's a poop.
Poop?
Wait, wait.
What?
It's a poop.
But, what did you call the poop?
Poop? Wait, but that's not just me.
Poop is normal.
Why do you say that about me?
Everyone, poop is not normal.
First, let's hear the testimony from the
manager of the victim.
You wrote poop on the back of a tape.
I didn't do that.
What?
Did you do that?
You put the tape that says poop on the
back of the tape?
No, I didn't.
I've seen it before.
I'm sure that the tape is a poop.
No, it's not.
It's impossible.
Mayama, please come here.
Mayama, do you remember that you put the
tape that says poop on the back of the
tape?
Then, please come here.
It's not just me.
Mayama is also suspicious.
So, let's ask the members who are going
to be a co-pilots.
The testimony of the next treasure is...
Please look forward to the next episode.
When we were performing...
That's right!
What is it, everyone?
Listen, this is really...
It's a little bit hard.
You're going to go over here yourself.
What is it, Hiroto-san?
Before the performance of the fan
meeting...
Why is everyone standing?
Everyone is the witness.
Before the performance of the fan
meeting...
They prepared a water cannon and...
We were in front of the stage...
We were in a place where we couldn't get
wet...
They brought a big water cannon and...
They ran over us.
We were all...
The culprit is the principal.
Ayaka is the principal.
The principal is...
Hina was aiming at the principal.
Ayaka was aiming at the principal.
Ayaka was in the middle.
Hina was fighting.
Before the performance.
Then the principal shot Ayaka and...
Ayaka was shot here.
What was it?
It was a bad writing
The other members' bad words continue to
rise.
It's not me!
The judge's attention is on the one who
will be justice.
Who is the member's worst bad writing?
The principal!
The principal is the principal!
So the judge is the principal and the
worst bad writing.
If not, the culprit will be the one who
will be justice.
Then the members will be the one who
will be guilty.
So the principal is the one who is
guilty of being too mischievous.
The punishment is over.
After this, the trial of the TASTAS is
over.
That was a waste.
The biggest battle in the shrimp market
has started.
What is this?
The trial of the obayashi is so intense
that it has never happened before.
What crime did she commit?
The next basic case is this.
A
I know who it is.
This is also a crime.
It's already a crime.
It seems like everyone knows who it is.
I understand.
So the defendant, Kobayashi Kaho, please
come forward.
It looks fun.
What is the truth of the suspicion that
the crime card will be raised soon?
The defendant, Kobayashi Kaho, is too
concerned about others' eyes.
He tends not to say what he likes and
dislikes.
This is causing trouble to the members
around him.
The defendant, Kobayashi Kaho, will be
charged with not saying what he
dislikes.
Defendant.
Applause.
That's how much trouble he's causing.
I see.
Defendant, what do you think?
Do you intend to endure it?
I don't really care about it.
But if I take it, I'll have something I
dislike.
Then I'll be like...
Like what?
What do you mean?
Be clear.
Kobayashi Kaho is not clear about it.
He has such a testimony from the
defendant.
When we went to Hokkaido for a live
performance, we were in a team and we
were going to eat together.
I really don't like that.
But this is the truth.
It's the truth.
I didn't like fish.
At that time.
You were like, let's eat sushi together.
When I asked if it was okay, he said
yes.
He used a lot of words like that.
When we went to eat sushi together, he
just looked at me.
What does that mean?
He said no when I was in front of him.
Aika said let's go and took me to ramen.
It was embarrassing.
You wanted to express that feeling?
At that time, I was wondering who was
the most pitiful.
The principal was pitiful.
The principal of Fuji who appeared
again.
What happened?
Yasumoto's testimony.
The principal noticed Kaho and invited
me to ramen.
I didn't like the principal.
I'm sorry
Did you hear that?
I see
Running with the principal and the two
of them is
It's a little bit like an old man and a
two-person
It's a little bit like an old man
It's as good as eating
It's as good as running with the
principal
That's right
That's clear
That's true, that's strange
I felt sorry
I'm sorry
The aura is already waiting alone
Because everyone has a career
I've been doing this all the time
Everyone is waiting
I'm sorry
So I bought it around there
I'm eating a small seafood bowl bento
It's amazing
I'm in a sad aura
That's sad
Do you have any other statements?
Yes
Yasumoto
Well
Here again, Yasumoto
What kind of statement will come out
this time?
Kumayashi-san is not only hateful
I can't even tell what I want to eat
I'm sorry
Yasumoto, please.
I know what I want to eat.
I know this person too.
I want to say, please give me something.
But I think it looks delicious.
I want to appeal.
If I say I want something, I will get
it.
I want to say please give me something.
Hirotaka is also in the lead.
The members' testimony is endless.
There are events in the dressing room.
Everyone is surprised.
Can I get this?
Everyone says, is this okay?
Everyone takes pictures without
permission.
When we get along,
Muneo and Ayachan will drink tea without
Aya.
That's right.
A new situation has appeared.
That's a different crime.
Hirotaka, that's a possibility of being
punished.
That kind of friendship is also
possible.
But everyone takes permission that is
not necessary.
I take permission to do something that
is against the law.
I see.
I want to get along with everyone.
Nakayama.
The testimony of surprise from Nakayama,
who is the closest person to the person.
The trial of the turn-out is in full
swing.
Kao-chan is trying to make Riko feel
better.
What do you mean?
It's completely different from this
crime.
No, no.
I don't hate it.
She is trying to make Riko feel better.
What do you mean, Nakayama?
I don't hate it.
I can't say anything bad.
Kao-chan went to the country of dreams
together.
Riko didn't have anything to do the next
day, so I went to Odaiba together.
I said, okay.
When I got home, I asked what time it
was tomorrow.
But I was tired.
That's good.
That was a waste.
That's right.
In a formal way.
Nakayama, stop it.
Let's go to Harajuku together.
I'm tired.
What's wrong?
Nakayama, please tell me the situation.
Nakayama is excited.
The person who was watching the first
round of the game explained the
situation.
After Riko finished her work, she said
she wanted to go to Harajuku.
She said yes.
After she finished her work, she said
she was tired and wanted to go home.
Riko said she wanted to go to Harajuku
by herself.
She said she wanted to go to Harajuku,
but she lost everything.
She was so lonely and said that.
I see. I understand.
Let's ask the defendant.
She hasn't answered yet.
She was in a situation where she
couldn't decide.
She was different.
She was told to go to Harajuku.
She was still lost, but she decided to
go to Harajuku.
I was wondering what to do.
I didn't think it would be so serious.
I was surprised.
Let's be clear.
Did you say yes or not?
I didn't say yes.
Please show us how you did it.
They were different.
They showed the same situation.
Did Kobayashi say yes?
I'm going to Harajuku tomorrow for a
hairpin party.
That's good.
Do you have any plans to go to Harajuku?
I don't have any plans, but I'm not
sure.
What should I do?
Don't you have any plans?
I don't have any plans.
Can we go to the party together?
Sure.
She said yes.
She was surprised.
If you say it's okay, it will make you
feel like you're going to be in trouble.
If you say it after that, it will be a
big deal.
You're a troublemaker.
Let's go to the dreamland together
again.
I'm going to say I'm going to go.
That's not good.
I'll answer it with tempo.
Now it's time to decide. How will the
members judge Kobayashi?
Please.
Thank you.
One of the six innocent people will be
guilty.
Wait a minute.
The chief defendant Kobayashi Kaho will
go to ramen with the principal.
That's right.
That's really bad.
Why is the past trial over?
If there are any new excuses, we will
continue to answer.
Sakura Ebizu is on the front line.
Sakura Ebizu is a research unit in the
shrimp industry.
They succeeded in their first live
performance.
A new trial.
This day, Sakura Ebizu came to the
studio in Shimokitazawa.
They will be guests on the radio program
of the idol special group Shimokita FM.
I'm not nervous.
They are on the radio for the first
time.
Will they be able to get through it?
The live broadcast starts.
We are Sakura Ebizu.
When the MC gives them a fork.
What do you eat if you can only eat this
for the rest of your life?
Shimesaba.
I went to a sushi restaurant and it was
delicious.
I eat at home.
At home?
I eat every day.
Sakura Ebizu is a guest who makes a good
talk.
That's all.
We are Sakura Ebizu.
The battle is over
They will be close to Sakurai B's
Next time
Ebichu plus Naka-yama-Riko
Naka-yama's plan for Naka-yama
What is this?
And
Naka-yama-Riko
This program was provided by the sponsor
What is this?
The pot is strange
I laugh at strange places
I do missions
See you next week
Bye