Please subscribe to this channel!
We have a problem!
What is it?
Today, we have three people who can
solve our problems!
It's so beautiful!
It's shining!
Look at this!
We've come this far.
We've walked a lot.
I'm tired.
I want to stretch.
Me too.
The teacher is here!
Let's call her!
Ms. Asakura!
Hello!
Hello! Nice to meet you!
Nice to meet you!
This is our first collaboration.
Really?
Yes!
I'm sorry, but I'm a little nervous.
Wow!
Hello!
Today, we're going to help you with your
problems.
Nice to meet you!
Let's make it soft!
I'm so happy!
I'm going to be a complete person!
I'm Karen Tachibana. Nice to meet you!
Nice to meet you!
I'm Karen. Nice to meet you!
I'd like to ask you a question.
I've been wearing a cat-like collar all
the time.
My neck is a smartphone neck.
It's a roll-shaped collar.
That's right.
I've been doing this for a long time.
It's like a stretch that sticks to the
shoulder blades.
I've never stuck to it.
I've tried this kind of thing.
I don't know much about it.
I'd like to have a stretch that can
improve it.
I see.
Do you study a lot when you're a
student?
Or do you watch a lot of smartphones?
I think it's a smartphone.
I heard that my luggage is very heavy.
I'm wearing a Boston bag today.
I don't think it's that far.
I don't know much about it, but I think
it's because my luggage is heavy.
But I'm sure I have a smartphone.
I'll look at it.
Do you usually hold it in your right
hand?
Yes, I do.
Which one is the Boston bag?
Right.
I see.
The right side of the paddle is rolled
up.
I see.
There's a cat-like collar.
I don't care about it that much.
I'm going to do some intense training.
I think my shoulders will hurt.
Let's solve that problem with a stretch.
Really?
Do you know a little about Tawaku?
I'm a big fan of him.
Really?
I happened to watch his YouTube video
about half a year ago.
I was watching a video of people making
a phone call in the middle of a big
city.
I thought it was really interesting.
I was watching a video of the army.
I happened to hear this story.
I was happy to hear it alone.
Really?
I was excited to see who was coming.
Three men came.
Really?
I'm glad I'm a YouTuber.
It's funny.
Let's do our best today.
It's a tough day.
That's right.
You're an idol, so you'll be fine.
I have to do my best.
I've prepared a lot.
Thank you for your continued support.
Hello, I'm FUJITANI MIU.
Please call me NAKKI.
Nice to meet you.
I have a question.
I hold the microphone with my left hand.
My left hand is very cold.
What should I do?
I see.
Only your left hand?
I have a problem with my right hand.
I feel very tight. I want to lower my
hand.
I hold the microphone with my left hand.
Which part of your body is tight?
My elbow?
I don't know.
I hold the microphone with my left hand.
I see.
Muscle strength is important.
The microphone is heavy.
Yes, it is.
Muscle strength is important, but it is
difficult to enter the stage if your
body is stiff.
Is your body stiff?
Yes, it is.
It's stiff.
Can you do a banzai?
Yes, I can.
Can you go further?
I'm good at it.
You are good at it.
Am I good at it?
You are not good at it.
I'm not good at it.
I'm frustrated.
Do you have any other problems?
I watch my smartphone too much.
My neck and shoulders hurt.
Thank you for your viewing.
I watch your videos a lot.
Yes, I watch your videos a lot.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Look over there.
Your head is in front of you.
No, my neck.
Your neck is long, so your head is in
front of you.
No, my neck.
Your neck is long, so your neck is
called a straight neck.
Straight neck.
It's a lot of pressure on your neck.
You need a lot of muscle strength.
I see.
Even if your body is stiff, it's a lot
of pressure.
Today, let's do a good stretch around
the neck, the biceps, and the arms.
Thank you very much.
I'm Kichita Shinju.
Please call me Shinju-chan.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
My problem is that my body is stiff.
But I don't care about that today.
I want to surprise them.
Ogata-re-san, would you please cooperate
with me?
Let's do it.
Thank you very much.
How do you want me to do it?
She really believes in anything.
She's pure, so she really believes in
anything.
I'll show you a stretching that doesn't
work.
It's a stretch, but it doesn't work.
That's it.
I was going to do about 10 of them
today.
I heard your worries and did about three
of them.
It's completely different.
It's a strange feeling.
It's the best.
What about the last one?
I have something I want to do last.
I like manga.
I always do girls.
I like girls, too.
Let's do it.
Which one do you want to do?
I got it.
That's great.
Let's do this together.
I'll do it normally, so please decide.
Please stop for 30 seconds.
Let's do it.
Please.
I hope it works.
I can do it.
I'm good at lying.
It looks delicious.
Yay!
So, let's start the stretching!
Thank you for your time!
Thank you!
So, let's check your body's hardness.
First, check your body's hardness.
Open your legs and stretch your knees.
Can you reach your right hand?
Please try it!
Let's do it together!
Oh, it's hard!
Karen is...
Well, well, well...
Shinji and Lucky are...
Lucky!
Lucky is...
Okay, let's go back.
Well, okay, it's hard.
It's hard.
Let's check the second one.
First, keep your legs shoulder-width
apart and put your right elbow in front
of your chest.
That's right.
Raise your left elbow up.
Your face is facing forward.
If your elbow is higher than your nose,
it's okay.
Should I lower my nose?
You can't lower your nose.
I think it's better to raise my nose.
Shinji is...
Okay.
Oh, my God!
Is this human?
I don't know.
Wow!
Karen is amazing.
It's pretty hard.
Oh, my God!
It's not human.
It's a cat shape, but it's a roll.
Oh, my God!
It's a roll.
It's hard.
The last one is a return.
Put your hips on the edge of the mat.
Then, open your legs as much as you can.
If your legs fit in the mat, it's okay.
Good luck!
This is suspicious.
How is it?
Put your hands in front of you, put your
chest out, and see if you can sit down.
Please tell me if this is easy.
How is it, everyone?
It's easy.
It's hard.
Thank you. Let's get back to the
starting position.
You guys are pretty hard.
We're going to do 10 stretches.
It's getting harder and harder.
Let's do our best.
First of all, please sit down and look
up.
Yes.
If you learn from the front, you'll be
able to put your arms together.
Bend your knees slightly.
Let's do it with all your might.
Put your hands out in front of you.
Then your back will stretch.
I'm so nervous.
Stretch your elbows and keep them
straight for 30 seconds.
If the middle of your back stretches,
it's okay.
My chest hurts.
Then bend your elbows slightly.
Okay, let's go back.
It's warm.
The collarbone is not moving much.
If this area is hard, this stretch will
hurt.
I think that's why it's connected to the
tiredness of your arms.
I see. It's amazing.
It suits you.
It's an order made.
Let's move on to the second one.
The second one is four times as much.
When you're ready, put one leg on the
right foot.
Put your right foot forward.
I'm not a human.
Put your left foot behind you.
Move your back to the floor.
It's my first time doing this.
Then your right hip will stretch.
Keep it for 30 seconds.
Start.
Relax your core muscles.
One of the key points of taking an
instructor class is that they mindlessly
refer to their own hash.
It hurts!
Does it hurt?
Yes, okay, let's do the other side.
Left foot forward,
both elbows are bent,
and take 30 seconds.
Start!
Okay, let's go back.
This time, we'll do the stretching on
the back of the thighs.
Stretch both feet.
After stretching,
hold your hand at the tip of your toes.
If you can't reach it, hold it at the
tip of your toes.
Bring it as far as you can,
and take 30 seconds.
Start!
Stretch the back of your thighs.
I feel like I'm listening.
Good.
It's stretching, isn't it?
It's stretching.
Okay, let's go back.
Next, we'll do the back of your thighs.
Let's do this in the same direction as
me.
I'll explain how to do it.
If you lie down, put your hands behind
your head.
Okay.
Bend your legs like this.
Good.
Like this.
Keep your legs like this.
Can you keep it?
What are you talking about?
Keep it for 30 seconds.
Start!
I'm about to get a cramp.
What?
I don't want to do it.
No!
OK, let's start with standing.
Have you been doing it for a while?
Yes.
I'm getting a cramp.
Next, let's do arm exercises.
Bend your knees slightly.
It's like squatting.
Put your palms in front of you.
Pull your fingertips towards you.
It hurts!
Keep it for 30 seconds.
It's working!
I'll do this all the time when I'm on a
date.
It's amazing. It hurts.
It hurts.
This part is stretching.
That's right.
Is there a reason why you bend your
knees like this?
It's easier to stretch if you bend your
knees.
Oh, really?
Oh, that's true.
That's great.
Okay.
Next, we're going to do it one by one.
I said lucky, but if you have a
microphone, your hands will get tired.
I'm going to stretch my index finger and
middle finger, which are especially hard
to stretch.
GALPIECE
Cute.
I'll do this for 30 seconds.
GALPIECE
Cute.
GALPIECE is popular.
GALPIECE
It's working. It's working.
It's working.
It's fun.
There are four left.
Three is the face.
It's a pretty small face.
First of all, it's a little
embarrassing.
I'm going to do my best to make the
lower lip look good.
That's all.
Keep this for 30 seconds.
Let's go.
Start!
You can open your mouth and talk.
Your lips will come forward.
Where does this work?
Around the neck.
Around the chin.
It's a straight line that works on the
face line.
Under the chin.
The more you put it out, the more it
works.
If it doesn't work, the soup is not
enough.
It's not enough.
I'm putting it out a lot.
I'm tired.
Okay.
Next, I'm going to fix the weight around
the eyes.
I often have heavy eyelids in the
morning.
I'm going to fix that.
Push the little bit above the eyes with
your fingers.
Then raise it up.
Pull your chin and raise your hand up.
It's like looking at the front.
Keep it for 30 seconds.
Cut.
Please try to make your eyes bigger.
Yes, that's right.
You can't look at the white part of your
eyes,
but you can look at the upper part of
your eyes.
You can see the swelling around your
eyes.
Hahaha.
It's hard.
Okay, that's good.
It's not bad.
Wow.
It's so light.
It's easy to see.
Now, let's look at the upper part of
your eyes.
The eyebrows are important for the size
of your eyes and facial expression.
Please pinch your eyebrows.
Okay.
Please pinch your upper and lower
eyebrows and pull them out.
Like this?
Make your eyes bigger and keep them for
30 seconds.
Start!
Make your eyes bigger and keep them for
30 seconds.
Wow, good!
You are good at it!
I'm enjoying it!
Pull your eyes like this.
Okay, it's done.
This is the last stretch.
Let's do our best!
Put your left hand out like this.
Put your right hip in.
Keep them for 30 seconds.
開始!
How do you feel?
Is this the side of the belly?
Yes, it is.
And around the arm.
The side of the left side.
And the inner thigh.
I think it's a
Yes, it's okay.
Wow!
So I did all 10.
How was it?
It was really light.
The eyes are really easy to open.
Really?
I can go anywhere.
I've never done this before.
I've done a lot of moves.
Which one was your favorite?
From all the stages?
The eyes were really easy to open.
Yes, it was.
This one?
Yes, this one.
It was cute.
It was easy to move.
It was fun.
I can't show it in the park.
How about you, Emi?
I didn't ask you.
Why?
Well,
I was doing a stretch
that was not effective at all.
It was a prank.
Yay!
What?
Who did you do it for?
This one?
What?
Where?
I heard it.
Really?
Try it.
I heard it.
Really?
It was a lie.
It was a lie?
No, it wasn't.
I really opened my eyes.
Really?
I'm embarrassed.
Why?
Where did you think it was a lie?
In the gym?
What?
This one?
I didn't hear that
I was doing it wrong.
Really?
The last one?
This one?
I've never seen it.
It was effective.
It was the fourth one.
The first one?
From this one.
I couldn't do it at all.
I couldn't do it.
I couldn't do it because it didn't work.
I couldn't do it because I didn't have a
good feeling.
That's right.
It was amazing.
It was really good.
You were telling me something.
Even if I ask you a question that's hard
to answer,
you always answer it.
I didn't doubt it at all.
It was amazing.
Really?
You knew it was a new challenge?
I said I wanted to do it.
I was asked to cooperate this time.
I see.
I succeeded.
I was surprised.
I didn't know it was a collaboration.
We're both pure.
That's right.
I didn't expect it to be a
collaboration.
You're kind.
I'm sorry I didn't ask you.
But the first one was really good.
I was listening to the recital.
I'm sorry, but I'm glad.
But it was fun.
I'm glad.
Is this the end?
But...
From the fourth one,
It was a prank.
The first one was real.
Everyone, check your shoulders.
Check your shoulders.
I hope you can do it together.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you very much.
Please try it.
Bye.