Hello.
Please come in.
Thank you.
As a result of the paper selection,
only 50 people have made it to the
second screening.
Moreover, they are going to squeeze in
from here
and the new members will be decided at
the final screening.
Thank you.
The studio in the city.
The second screening of the manager and
label staff begins.
Who are you?
I'm a college student.
What year are you?
I'm a third-year student.
You're a third-year student.
How old are you?
I'm 21 years old.
You're 21 years old.
When did you start doing this?
I joined when I was 16.
I'm 20 years old.
You're 20 years old.
Let's sing a song.
Okay.
The main part of the screening is
singing and dancing.
I can't stop smiling
My dancing heart can't stop
I'll keep moving towards you
Run, run, run
I'll keep thinking about you
You're not a stranger
You're not someone else
Without hesitation
I just want to believe in you
Life is a red-hot airplane
I'll fly with a wish
In the wind, as much as I can
I just keep going
Don't be distracted by the mental
breakdown
Don't cry when you're a
budget driver
Listen, listen, you're a talented person
You're a 1.5 million dollar driver
What's your specialty?
Today...
Oh, right.
Then, please show us.
There are also students who show off
their specialties.
Next is...
Can I have a pasta?
How old are you?
I'm 13 years old
What is ballet?
Is there anything you can show us?
Like this
How much do you do ballet?
I haven't been doing ballet for a while
I quit in September
You quit in September?
She is a bit slow
ー ー ー
ー ー
I don't go around explaining these
trials and trib setup.
?
Where did you learn the song?
I learned it for a while now...
May I ask how long have you been
singing?
about 5 months
And she showed her confident expression
in the camera test
Thank you very much.
colors on the list
Many students select songs on the list
as
Everything was fine.
Every time I see you for the first time
I can't stop watching you
Thank you
My parents listened to my songs since I
was a child
You have parents?
Yes
Producer
K softer
The students are challenging for the
audition with all their might
After the evaluation
I was nervous
My sister...
We were in the same audition
I want to do my best for my sister
I was so nervous
I couldn't sleep at all
I'm not studying at all, but I'm doing
my best
You don't understand anything, but I
want to do more
I think I'm getting there
Is who is the final challenger?
Next episode Connie continues for the
second round
The final of all the girls
I want to be an Reformer
I thought this is the last chance
At the same age
To be continued...