Experts will editorial
Theiding the emotions from the silent
And the other members are thinking
something измен
Also there will be zweety-sweety music
And next, she heard a
Scary
A horror movie
Members were very much interested
I will show you both the front and back.
Rebichu Tastase Start!
We will show you many things in private
Ebisu Middle School
Ebisu Tastas!
What is the thing that you can't show
your true self?
This program is provided by the sponsor
There are some parts that I overacted
Are you overacting?
Ebisu Tastas has started!
Thank you!
I will show you my true self
Hello!
The costumes are new
It's a new song
It's amazing
What costume is this?
Superhero
That's why everyone is wearing a cape
Matsuno said that Ebichu Tatsuta has
started
It has started
What do you mean?
It should have started
It has already started
What is the member who is confused by
Takiue's statement?
Actually, 15 minutes ago
It's bad
This is the meeting with the staff
before the recording
It's 3 o'clock
Please
Please subscribe to the channel
Why are they shooting this scene?
The road trip has started
Takiue and Chue of Nagareboshi
It's hot
And the 6th episode of Kaikyo show,
Ogata Kaiki
What does this opening mean?
It's different from the usual opening
This time the theme is truth
They are trying to show their true
feelings
So they are using a hidden camera
They are using a hidden camera?
Yes
Kashiwagi-san is writing something
Is he writing a book?
Yes
The theme is truth
They are using a hidden camera to find
out their true feelings
The expert will analyze it
They will find out what the members are
thinking
Did they start from the meeting?
I don't know
We were shooting the meeting secretly
No
The theme is truth
Hurry up
They are looking into the members' mind
They are shooting the meeting secretly
What will they find out?
The expert will analyze the truth of
Ebichu
The analyst is Amon Nijihiko
He is a professional of psychological
analysis
Let's start the analysis
First, we will analyze the truth in the
position where they were sitting
First, they will analyze the truth in
the position where they were sitting
Ebichu members are sitting in front of
the producer
What will be the truth?
What will they find out?
I'm scared
The power relationship in the group
I didn't know
coastal
What?
Basically, Ebichu is like everyone is
together.
That's right.
But there is no leader.
No.
By the way, is there anyone who thinks
that I'm the leader?
Don't say that.
What is the name of the person who is
the leader?
Mayamaka Hoshina.
I thought it was Yasumoto who was not
stabbed at all.
I see.
Yasumoto thinks that way.
I want to be like that.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm sure you will take responsibility
gradually.
That's good.
Yasumoto is the leader who is just self-
proclaimed.
Then, who do you think is the leader?
According to the sitting order now, I'm
the leader unconsciously.
That's right.
By the way, I'm the leader.
I think that I have the most power in
the group.
Actually, I sat in this seat.
I didn't expect it.
Matsuoka.
I'm sorry.
I'm the leader.
Leader.
Matsuoka, the leader.
How is it?
I've never thought of it.
Really?
But it's true.
Matsuoka is a type that goes to the
end of the road.
He can go to the opposite side with
anyone.
I think he has a talent.
Matsuoka was the leader unconsciously.
Here is the scene.
The position of the leader is the
position where the producer and the
person face each other.
There is a sense of self-awareness of
the leader.
And the position of the producer, who is
the best, is on the right side.
That's the same as the producer.
Or something like that.
Something more than that?
That's somewhere.
That's something more than that.
The act of sitting in front of the other
person is the expression of the
psychology of the representative.
And seeing the other person on the other
side of your wrist is psychologically
the strong consciousness of the other
person and the other person.
He Pak artic jou so concepts filled
Still his body's
This is a scene where he is threatening
the person in front of him.
This is the scene where he is
threatening the producer.
Is there something like this?
There is a sense of threat.
He is threatening the producer.
He is very sharp.
He is pulling his hands on his chin.
I am the one who is evaluating the
situation.
He is saying something bad.
I am evaluating the producer.
This is a live performance.
There is a sense of threat deep inside
his heart.
We can expect today's performance.
There is a person next to him.
He is the leader.
Let's call him the leader.
How is it, Mato?
I don't like it.
You don't get along with each other at
first.
It's not like that.
By the way, the leader behind you is
also a leader.
I'm scared of the leader behind me.
The leader behind you who controls the
shrimp in the shadow.
He will know that in a sitting position.
What is the person?
The person behind you is...
This is...
This is A.
Why is it A?
There is no A.
I thought so.
Everyone agrees with this.
I don't know, but I agree with it.
This position is...
The leader and the producer look at each
other objectively.
Moreover, the leader is immediately
seated in this seat.
I see.
The leader behind you is the leader of
the members.
While looking at the producer on the
right, the leader is also in the field.
What is the truth?
The leader is...
He's waiting for the right time to make
a mistake.
Wait for the right time?
Next is Sawa.
I'm scared.
The boss is here.
He's here.
He's waiting for the right time.
When you were chosen as the lead, you
said you were scared.
Do you have any feelings?
I have an image of a
Do you know what a
So you're hiding inside without going
out, right?
I'll do it.
Isn't it a little different?
It's close.
It's kind of right.
I feel like I'm answering.
When the members' power relations are
known,
psychological tests are carried out.
In addition,
I will investigate the true psychology
of the shrimp.
First question.
First of all, please write about
yourself and Fuji.
That's it.
It's okay to write freely.
You thought about it, didn't you?
Let's write about yourself and Fuji
freely.
With this psychological test,
The members' embarrassing faces are
clearly visible.
What do you know about this test?
In this test,
You'll know your narcissism.
How conscious are you?
You'll know.
This psychological test will reveal your
narcissism.
How to describe yourself to the best
Fuji in Japan.
We'll see through the narcissism.
First, the 8th place.
It's the last.
It's not the best narcissism.
Please announce the 8th place.
The 8th place is...
Nakayama.
This is the picture Nakayama drew.
It's very simple.
In the case of Nakayama,
One of the points is that he drew
himself at the bottom.
And he said he drew himself very simply.
I don't think it's simpler than this.
I can't draw well, so I can only draw
this.
In a good way, he's a very humble
person.
He's not very self-centered.
I think it's okay to have a little more
confidence in a humble person who
doesn't go
It's just the truth, but the best of the
best in Japan, Fuji-san and himself
The best of the best in the world, the
narcissist is revealed
Next, the seventh place
The seventh place is Kobayashi-san
I did it!
Kobayashi-san!
Well, Kobayashi-san
Kobayashi-san is also a humble person
Kobayashi-san wrote himself small at the
foot of Mt. Fuji
Because of his humble nature, he is a
narcissist
And also, Sensei, what is this
It's a forest, I drew a tree
He doesn't know how to climb the top
He's a little lost
Oh
If you climb that mountain, you'll get
tangled in the hair
It's a miracle
And the sixth to fourth place of the
narcissist is as you can see
After all, he wrote himself small at the
foot of Mt. Fuji
Because of his humble nature, he is a
narcissist
There are three remaining members
Who is the person he loves the most
among them?
This is great, the narcissist's best
three
The leader and the back leader are
remaining
Yes
The leader and the back leader are
remaining
Yes
It's really like that
The third place of the narcissist
ranking among the members is
The third place is
The third place is Matsumoto-san
Yay
Show us your drawing
This is Sensei's drawing
Matsuno Noe, who drew himself climbing
Mt. Fuji
What is his true psychology?
He climbed to the eighth place
He climbed to the seventh or eighth
place
He thought that his era was coming
The leader
He climbed
He climbed to the top
But he is relatively small
He is so humble that he doesn't show his
ambition
I see
But he has ambition
He climbed the stairs of ambition
But ambition is important
The last one is the leader of the team.
The Narcissist is the best of the
shrimp.
Please announce the winner.
Kashiwagi or Yasumoto?
Which one is it?
Narcissist No.1 is...
Kashiwagi
The first one is Narcissus
Here are the two pictures
They are placed near Mt. Fuji and draw
themselves big
But Kashiwagi is drawing himself big so
Narcissus is more likely
Narcissus is the best among the Eri
The teacher has a message for them
Yasumoto and Kashiwagi are not touching
the mountain directly
They are floating in the air
What does it mean?
It means that they are not in the air
I see, they are not in the air
You are so bad
The second psychological test
We have prepared some tools
The next one is the psychological test
They will choose the tools
What are they?
Let's start the diagnosis
Choose the tools you like
Let's go straight
The members are having a complex
The class president looks good
Ready, go
Good
You are not in the mood
The class president is powerful
He looks good
Yasumoto is like BEMU BELA BELO
Hiroto looks good
Mayama is scared
He doesn't know who he is
Mayama matches the costume
What do you know?
You can tell which one is complex by
which one you wear
What does it mean?
It's not like you wear glasses and your
eyes are complex
Really?
Thank you for watching
From the place where the child was
hiding,
he will read the complex that the person
is holding.
What kind of worries does he have?
Analyze the truth.
First of all,
The person who chose the wig and hid his
head.
Yasumoto and Hoshi.
What about Mayama?
He also goes into the wig group.
He hides his hair.
The person who chose the wig.
He has a complex to the charm of women.
Not like a woman?
I think I'm not sexy enough.
That part is a bit complex.
It's right.
Yasumoto.
Hoshino is the most feminine among the
members.
He is aiming for the girl.
He is the most feminine.
I'm sorry.
Can I not look at Yasumoto?
Please look at me.
Next, Hid his eyes.
Matsu and Kobayashi.
And Mayama's complex.
Eyes are the person's personality.
The complex is that he can't show his
true self.
He is acting a bit too much.
Are you all being forced?
He is the one who is the most reluctant.
Kobayashi is the one who is the most
reluctant.
Really?
The party shoes look the best on him.
Party.
You just said party.
Boss, are you acting?
What?
You are acting.
I'm acting.
Mayama is acting too?
I can't read Mayama's expression.
Next, Kobayashi and Nakayama are hiding
their flowers.
And Mayama's complex is...
Flowers represent the social evaluation.
So the complex is that they are not
recognized as adults.
I want to be recognized.
They are still under the age.
I still want to think that way.
But I can't believe that the other
person is the same age as me.
What is it?
Mayama is full of complexes.
Even if it's a lump, it's a head, eyes,
nose.
That's amazing.
What? My shoulders are shaking.
Are you laughing or crying?
Which one?
Mayama chose a tool that can cover all
faces.
The true truth was a lump of complexes.
Ebichu Game Quest
Ebichu's game project is in progress.
Last time, the prototype version of
Ebichu's game was finally announced.
Ebichu members will appear as characters
in the game.
So this time,
Ebichu members' character design was
announced.
We have created 8 characters.
We will announce them.
First, Mayama.
First, Mayama's character, who likes
Ebichu the most.
Here it is.
It's cute.
It feels like an anime.
I understand.
Mayama will understand.
Next, Hiroto's character design.
Here it is.
It's Ai.
It's like Ai.
It's cute.
I'll do my best in this game.
It's similar.
Is it a hair style?
Next, Matsuno's character design.
Matsuno's character design.
Here it is.
It's cute.
It's clean.
It's popular.
It's popular with this kind of
character.
It's popular with people who like this
kind of character.
Ebichu's half-up ribbon is cute.
It's cute.
It's like a person who can do it.
I did it.
I want to see it.
Next, Kashiwagi's character design.
Here it is.
It's cute.
It's a good character.
It's like a globe.
It's really strong.
It's like a person who can do it.
It's like a mysterious globe.
It's strong.
It's cute.
It's amazing.
By the way, the other four members
Everyone
What is the character design of these
four people?
It looks like this
What is the character design of these
four people?
Mia-chan
The hair is like a bow
Tico is cute
Yuchan is dangerous
But Kaho is cute
Kaho
Ayaka and Kaho
They are very friendly
The game producer is also very excited
about the members
I'm very happy that you've said so far
I'm going to brush up a little more to
show you guys
Thank you
Don't miss the latest information
Next time, we will perform the ultimate
test that reveals the true psychology of
shrimp
Basically, it's about expressing love
Oh my
The members are in love with the members
in the dream
In addition, in the psychological battle
to read the mind
What is the member today?
And to those who missed the shrimp-
chewed tastas
The shrimp-chewed tastas are being
released on the Star Dust channel, a
low-cost video distribution site
Where is the shrimp-chewed tastas?
I don't know
I don't think you'll find it from the
beginning
That scene is available for free for 400
yen a month
In addition, there are a lot of
exclusive videos that are not released
Now?
For more information, search on the Star
Dust channel
This program was provided by the sponsor
you see
Thank you