Everyone, please wait for it.
Please wait for it.
I'm going to watch the music video of
this costume and star.
I'm looking forward to it.
I was looking forward to it.
You were looking forward to it, too,
right?
Yes, I was.
I was looking forward to it.
Let's watch it!
Everyone is cute.
Is this the thumbnail?
Isn't this the thumbnail?
It's a new world.
It's really good.
Let's go.
Start!
Wow!
It's amazing!
So cute!
Wow!
Kiyoshi-chan!
So cute!
Ah! Witz!
I got it!
So cute!
Ah!
What was that?
Cute.
Wow!
I didn't see that.
It's still the first one.
Wow.
What?
I want to see it again.
This is cute.
It's really different.
It's really cool.
This is cute.
We took this.
We did.
Cute.
Isn't it really cute?
Oh! You succeeded!
Thank you!
the end
thanks for watching
That was your face!
Oh my god!
Wow!
What a cute face!
So cute!
Everyone is dancing.
It's colorful.
Wow.
It's coming out.
It's cute.
Amazing!
Awesome!
Wonderful!
You are terrific!
It's me!
I love it!
This is amazing.
Amazing!
Everyone is so cute.
It's like a world view.
It's like a new world.
It's like a gap between clothes and
casual clothes.
It's fashionable.
I wonder what everyone thinks.
I want to hear your opinions.
Everyone's opinions are changing, so
please watch it many times.
It's so good!
It's so cute!
Please watch it many times!
Oh, I forgot to put on the sticker.
Can you put on the sticker?
Yes.
I put on the sticker.
Everyone!
Nyaho!
Oh my god!
My ears are bouncing!
It's a Joshua movie!
I heard the word Joshua movie from a
fan.
Are you guys feeling better?
Who is next to you?
I'm sure you can tell by the voice.
You don't know?
Who is it?
It was Aki-chan.
I'll be back.
Only behind.
Wow, amazing.
In what range can you say?
In what range...
What kind of atmosphere did you make it?
It's different from usual.
I'm happy.
Thank you for watching.
I think it's good.
It's not for people who will be 22 next
year.
17 is cute.
Yes, it's a zero.
18 is good, too.
17 is cute.
That's right.
Like 17 of flowers.
Good luck!
It's close!
I'll make a joke a little more.
Look at this angle.
It's not good.
I don't have a good position for the
camera.
What's for lunch today?
Did you bring your lunch?
I'll introduce you to my lunch box.
Which one is it?
It looks delicious.
What is this?
I'll eat it.
I found a box.
There are three boxes.
I found a book of MBC.
I found a book of KOROKO.
There are two types of this.
What is this?
Can I open this?
I will open this.
I found a bag of noodles.
I found it.
I'll give you some.
This is a lunch box.
I'll give you some tea.
I'll have some tea.
I can hear someone's voice.
Who is it?
Whose laughter is it?
It's so chewy.
I got a bento.
Let's eat.
Be careful not to spill it.
It's so good.
Shrimp.
Hi!
I'm doing a lot of things right now.
I'm waiting for you.
I made a video of the movie.
I'm going to try to write Hiyoi's
autograph for 20 seconds.
I'll try to write Hiyoi's autograph.
I usually write with my autograph or a
poster.
But this takes the most time.
This is my autograph.
I'll write this in 20 seconds.
It might be a little sloppy, but I'll do
it.
Ready, go!
8 seconds left.
16 seconds.
18.
19.
I finished in 20 seconds.
Hiori's autograph is...
1, 2, 3...
3 seconds.
I wrote 3.3 seconds.
Yeah!
Good morning.
I was shooting a rising movie.
Rising movie?
Yes.
Takibara's...
Oh, I see.
I wrote 3.3 seconds for how many times I
can write the autograph in 20 seconds.
I'm so fast.
So, I'll try.
I wrote 3.3 seconds.
Yaho! Good evening to everyone who is
watching Tokiwara!
I have a report for you!
I've been able to get rid of my eye
drops in one shot!
I always did this and always got it off.
I've been able to do it in a few days.
I've been able to get rid of my eye
drops in a long time, but I've suddenly
improved!
I'm looking forward to it!
Hi!
What did you eat today?
Oh, eye drops!
You're good at putting eye drops on your
eyes.
I'm good at it.
I often put eye drops on my eyes because
they dry out.
But I can do it.
I thought you were always good at it.
I don't put eye drops on my eyes.
That's right.
I've never seen you put eye drops on
your eyes.
That's how good I am.
I haven't taken it off since I got the
eye drops.
Isn't that great?
You're good at it.
I can feel the distance.
I feel like a demon.
You're good at it.
I ate Chinese food for lunch.
I ate shrimp with sesame sauce.
Sesame sauce was really good.
I ate while saying,
I love you all.
Have a good Wednesday and a good night's
sleep.
See you next time!
I'm going to do my best to make
everyone's left ear pop.
I'm going to make my left ear pop.
What's the latest story?
I went to see the movie Asura Odaiko.
I have a manga that has been remade.
It's interesting.
I like basketball.
I watched a match of basketball this
year.
It was interesting.
I bought a movie theater bottle.
It can be a piggy bank or a drink
holder.
I bought a lot of different bottles.
I'm a fan of Mitsui.
I talked to my brother and went to see
the movie.
I talked to him about which one would be
good.
I bought a 11-year-old bottle.
It's really interesting.
Please watch it.
I recently watched a movie.
I watched the movie Kotonoha no Miwa.
It's shorter than I thought.
Please let me know if you have any
recommendations.
See you.
I wonder who will eat this.
It's cute.
It's really cute.
I want to eat this donut.
You can bring it home.
I took a video of eating this, so I can
bring it home.
I'm not good at it.
I didn't think I was the best at it, so
I was surprised.
I want to be a little more cheerful.
I'm not good at it.
Cute.
It's a cute picture.
It's a picture of a cat.
It's the most American picture.
Is this the picture?
What?
It's a picture of a person's name.
I see.
I'm going to put it on.
It's cute.
This is amazing.
It's amazing.
I threw a lot.
It's floating.
It's fine.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I'm not sure if I can do this action.
I've been doing it for a while.
But I'm not sure if I can do the sword
dance.
Oh, it's cute.
It's written on the back.
Did you take this?
I'm not sure if I can do this.
Please watch it.
Good evening, everyone.
I think you're watching Tokiwara.
I'm in front of my work right now.
It's a secret, but...
I'm hungry, so I can't fight.
I just bought salad chicken, so I'm
going to do a munch time.
Please join us for the munch time.
I bought a chicken from a convenience
store.
I will eat it.
I recently posted a lot of things on
TikTok.
I ate rice omelet.
I washed my hands.
I will eat it.
It's delicious.
Did you have dinner?
It's around 10 o'clock in the morning.
I'm sorry for those who ate breakfast
early.
HAI
I'm going to eat chocolate cake this
year.
I'm not having a physical phenomenon,
but I'm putting my phone on a tissue and
putting it on a PET bottle.
I said it with a loud voice.
It's hard to talk about it.
I had a Christmas party with Kanami the
other day.
I won't tell you the details, but I'll
let you know.
It's a secret to KANAMIN.
It's a secret to KANAMIN, but I'll show
you some pictures.
What should I do?
I'm going to show you this photo.
Ta-da!
Oh, the battery is out.
The battery has been charging so fast
lately.
Ta-da!
I'm wearing Santa hat.
It's like Christmas, isn't it?
This Santa hat is what Kanami bought me.
The color is so cute.
It's the same color as Kanami.
I'm wearing Santa hat.
I'll upload it on Instagram.
Please check it out.
This is a video.
I prepared it two days before because I
thought Kanon would come to play on
Christmas.
I'm going to put on a shirrin makeup.
Bye bye.
Isn't it amazing?
I did it in earnest.
I'll post it on Instagram and TikTok
later.
Please check it out.
Thank you.
Bye bye.
Today's fashion point is...
This one piece camisole.
My mom told me that I have a lot of new
clothes.
This is definitely a little new.
I don't buy a lot of clothes just
because I'm changing my clothes.
I've gotten better at changing clothes
than I used to.
That's all.
So I don't buy a lot of clothes.
I wore a scarf and gloves because it was
cold today.
I bought a cute glove because it was
cute.
You know, gloves are a problem.
You have a problem that you can't touch
your smartphone.
I bought gloves because I was more
interested in luxury than smartphones.
I found my fingertips were open.
I was surprised.
I wondered why I didn't see it.
My fingertips were open.
I think I made gloves that have open
fingertips for smartphones.
My fingertips were open.
But when I saw my gloves in spring, I
thought they were separated.
I bought gloves that I could take off my
fingertips and gloves that were
separated.
But my fingertips were open.
So my fingertips are cold.
After this, I told Kanami that my
fingertips were cold.
I thought I'd hold hands casually.
I hope you all stay warm.
Bye bye!
and see you on spring YouTube!
Hello everyone!
It's been a while since I've done a
promotion video.
I used to do it in the dressing room,
but I haven't done a promotion video in
a long time.
Are you enjoying Tokiwawa?
It's been a long time since I've seen
you.
In November, I couldn't see or talk to
any of you.
Please look forward to December Toki
Cream!
I'm looking forward to seeing you in
December.
Don't fall down because you're not
excited.
Bye bye!
Today, I'm going to do no makeup plus...
Really?
No makeup?
I'm not going to do it.
I have eyelashes up, so I'm not going to
do it.
My eyes are swollen when I do no makeup
plus.
I'm in trouble.
I'm going to stop it today.
My makeup is bad.
You have a very bad look.
I couldn't put on makeup because my eyes
were swollen.
No, no, no.
This is just right.
White is not good.
It's true.
It's a season when white is in.
It's cold today.
It's really cold.
I got a circuit from Piyo yesterday.
I got a lot of circuit from Piyo.
I used a circuit.
It's not a pocket.
I'm going to burn my hands.
It's so hot.
It was a very warm circuit.
It's a normal circuit.
It's different.
I usually use it.
I see.
It's a lot of circuit.
I can't stand the circuit for about a
month.
For about a month.
I'm going to burn my hands.
I've been saying this before.
There's a circuit in Kanagawa.
Is that so?
It's at the limit.
There was a lot.
I don't use it this year.
I don't use it today.
I may lose it again.
It's your turn.
Did you hear my voice?
I don't know what you're doing.
You're not dead.
I've been talking a lot.
I have to do it.
Good luck.
I'll do it.
Bye bye.
Goodbye, goodbye, thank you for
yesterday
The city after the rain is colored
I'll draw a fragment of the future on
the canvas of my damaged heart
It will guide me
I can say it now, the reason for my
tears
When I'm lost, I remember it right away
Even if it rains, I'll smile
Come on, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights after the rain are
sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day, I'm happy
My heart is like a sunny day, I'm
playing the mario of the rainbow
I'm playing the rainbow piano
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights after the rain are
sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day, I'm crying
I'm wearing a rainbow dress
Please subscribe to our channel!