21 days after birth.
The weather was very good, so I came to
the park for the first time.
I want to eat it.
What is it?
It's not just a wiener.
It's a crepe.
It looks delicious.
I'm scared of the green jacket.
I can draw anyone.
Everyone is easy to draw.
I can draw a play jacket.
I'm scared.
I'm going to draw Hinata.
I want to draw Ayaka.
What's going on?
Someone said they wanted to draw me.
Then I'll draw you.
I can't help it.
Thank you.
I'm going to draw Amatcha.
Amatcha?
It's really hot.
It's hot.
I'm scared.
Bye.
,
Once upon a time, there was a fisherman
who had no energy, no idea what he was
thinking, and couldn't catch any fish.
Once upon a time, Nakoyama was taken by
a rescue turtle
and he came to the airspace, and he saw
a beauty that he couldn't see.
I wonder if there's anything good today.
Today
You dropped...
This, Famiyen's relax area ticket?
Or
Summer chair ticket?
FAMIYEN!
Ah no, it's a lie
Both of them
Thank you for watching.
You are honest!
Tenku!? Ten... Tenku!?
Um, um, thank you for saving me at that
time!
That's too much! I didn't mean to save
you, but when did I say that?
That's the thing you used on the back of
your head! What did you bring?
What's that? What's that? What's that?
A turtle!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
You guys are an anarchy!
Thank you for watching!
I'm the best, I'm the best, I'm the king
You walk out, you walk out
3, 2, 1, go!
Blue sky in my head
My head is blue sky
My heart is blue sky
I'm waiting for you
I'm going to jump into you
Hey hey hey
Thank you!
Mire!
I want to play a rhythm!
Newlyweds!
Moya moya!
Moya!
I'm going to fix my lip hair
You're going to be so excited
I'm glad you're here
That's the new scientific communication
And, uh, I like you, I hate you, I hate
you, I like you
You can cut everything out
I want to make you so excited that you
can cut everything out
I like you, I hate you, I hate you, I
like you
Let's talk without talking
And then, you're a fool who looks at you
like a fool
I want people who are a little more
excited and want to go higher
I want two people
Yes, Takami-chan, two people
Dance, fool, look, fool
I want you to say
One, two, three, four, five
Dance, fool, look, fool
I want to dance with everyone.
One more time.
I'm going to close it now.
I'm scared.
psycho
It's like purple
BIBO
B restoration
Anyway
Re-chod Meow
Hey!
I'm a little nervous about the opening.
Oh, yeah.
It's space.
Space.
It's not space.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Let's make it space.
There are some songs that are not in the
game.
I'm going to sing a song.
Singalong.
Singalong after your part.
It's a strange movement.
And you should enter the room before I
go in.
Please enter properly.
I'll change the position.
Yes.
Pong.
Let's go.
My throat hurts.
Where are we?
Space.
We are A-Teen.
Let's fight.
She shows what kind of song CHOI WON
groß has...
Chazan, who was her number onefont in
then and...
Chochika makes those American shows into
a giant hit song...
and shows how familiar with it what b ml
».
NAKA also takes on the Late Night
Show았습니다
They're working on a version withнимely
longer short parts
They took the short part from new
project at the place where there wasn't
an OST
and made it into music
Fold your hands to the air.
The must do diet before worry about
health.
Thank you for watching!
Hello.
My wife is coming today.
Mire-chan?
I'm the winner.
You're the winner.
Yuichi's Mire-chan.
Our performance.
My wife.
I'm glad I made Yuichi come.
Let's do our best.
For Yuichi.
Where are we?
Gushimaru.
We are the one and only.
Yuichi.
I'm so happy.
What is this?
It's Mame-chan's.
It's good.
It's so good.
I wanted to eat it.
I'm glad I made it.
I want to eat it.
It's good.
Please say hello.
I don't want to eat something this good.
It's okay.
I'll eat it.
Goya-chan is coming.
Can I eat this?
Yes.
I don't know if I can wear this.
Who will do it?
One, two, three.
What is it?
You can't wear it.
No.
You know it.
I know.
You can't wear it.
One, two, three.
Eight.
One.
Four.
Eleven.
I'm sorry!
This is the only thing I can do!
I'm the main character!
If it's a number, I'll take it to the
bottom.
I said it!
From 1 to 10, right?
You can't say it properly.
It's important.
One, two, three!
Who won?
The person who got 4 points!
The person who got 2 points!
The person who got 5 points!
Thank you for watching!
Let's start!
Spring, summer, fall, winter. Which is
the longest summer?
Summer, summer, fall, winter?
If you say all of them, it's going to be
Aki.
Spring, summer, fall, winter. Which is
the longest summer?
Summer?
Winter, winter.
Let's read it again.
Spring, summer, fall, winter. Which is
the longest summer?
Summer?
Summer.
What about the number?
Winter?
Fall.
Autumn, fall.
It's there.
Summer, summer, summer. Which is the
longest summer?
It's so hard!
I'm so glad!
I have no idea.
Summer, fall, winter. Which is the
longest summer?
Is it 72?
That's correct.
The choices are spring, summer, fall,
winter. Which is the longest summer?
That's so cute!
Let's start.
How much is the fish you bought for 100
yen?
It's not here.
What?
If you can only give 100 yen.
Correct.
How much?
You used 100 yen coins, so you don't
have fish.
Oh, I see.
Let's read the next question.
The first letter of the alphabet in
English is A.
A is in front of B.
What is the last letter?
Wrong.
Oh.
What is the second letter?
It's the alphabet.
What is the third letter?
The alphabet.
I love alphabet.
I don't know.
What is the second letter of the
alphabet in English?
It's the second letter.
The alphabet is the same as the north of
the Great Plate Oil.
That's a strange name.
Correct.
Oh, I see.
I'm so frustrated.
You can drink alcohol from 20 years old.
You can ride a bicycle from 18 years
old.
How old is your car?
16 years old.
Oh, I'm 0 years old.
You are so young.
You are a trainee.
I'm a trainee.
Thank you for your hard work.
I won the Okinawa Aigyo Show.
I was able to win the show today.
I learned a lot.
Thank you very much.
We are the C-CHANNEL.
Thank you.
Cute.
If you like, let's take a picture
together.
I'm not alone.
Mayama-san is here.
I'm here.
I'm going.
Cheese.
I'm going again.
Thank you.
Cheese.
Can I take a picture with you?
Sure.
What are you doing?
Stop it.
Draw a card.
Carrot.
Your neck is straight.
Are you done?
I'm not going up.
Aya-chan.
I don't like that room.
Let's go upstairs.
Thank you for watching.
This is my idea.
What are you doing?
Are you going to do this?
No.
Thank you.
I want to change it from the middle.
I'm so happy.
But I want to see the whole thing in the
factory.
When I was told that I would definitely
do it,
I saw Hina's reaction.
I felt that there was a minute after
this.
Hina also became stronger and changed.
I thought I would definitely convey my
feelings.
I thought there was something.
This time, there was a lot of reflection
on the previous time.
After the last fan meeting, I thought I
would do it.
I thought I would do it.
I thought I would do it for a year.
I've been thinking about it since the
last fan meeting.
Sometimes I'm wrong.
I've been doing it for a while now.
This time, as a finalist for the first
year,
I'll do it just a little bit.
Just a little bit.
I'll do the unison part after the part
where I was off.
I'll sing with a really loud voice.
I'll do my own thing.
I'll do my own personal job.
Thank you for watching.
As long as I'm in Ebichu, I'm connected
to Ebichu.
I have a lot of things to do after I'm
in Ebichu.
No matter how much I say I'm me, as long
as I get the name of Shuiichi Ebichu,
I think the last stop is the work that
comes back to Ebichu.
As long as I'm in Ebichu, I'm not
Yasumoto Ayaka.
I'm not Yasumoto Ayaka.
I'm not sure if I'm a new weapon.
I think it's difficult.
I'm doing it because I want to improve
myself.
But the conclusion is that I'm a
beginner.
I don't know.
I don't know which one is which.
It's too early.
But I know it.
I know it.
It's similar.
It's just right for the real show.
It's too early.
I don't know.
I cut my hair. No one notices.
I cut my hair, but no one notices.
I cut my hair a little.
In the song called Beat the Omedama,
we're all doing the same thing,
like the same melody we did in the
second half of the song.
We're looking at each other's eyes,
and our movements, and our movements in
our mouths.
We're looking at each other's faces, and
we're singing together.
I think those songs are also helping us
grow.
So, I think we were able to show our
power after the spring tour with these
six members.
I think each of us has our own unique
and unique atmosphere.
I think we are becoming a part of
ourselves.
I think that even if we have two days,
we can show something completely
different.
I think that even if we have three days
in the university, we can change
everything.
But we can do a lot of things, and we
can do new things.
For example, we have all the new things,
like the new car. So, we can do
something completely different for three
days.
But we don't get so excited.
So, I think that there are people who
are watching us every day.
I think it's fun to know what the next
song is, but I wonder what's coming
next.
I hope people will watch us every day
with new feelings.
We want to reach the limit of our body
weight.
We have high calories, and we're having
a hard time.
But I think everyone is looking for
that.
It's hard, but we've done it.
I like the sense of accomplishment that
we've done it all.
It's like this for everything.
Thank you for watching.
早い早い。
美宛ちゃん、きゃりーだ?
早い。
美宛ちゃん、きゃりーは?
昨日起きたら2時でね。
インスタの記事を作ってて起きたら2時で。
I was going to do my best this year, but
I couldn't.
Shock, Zekamaru.
I don't want to be a part of it.
Let's run together, Zekamaru.
I want to eat a lot of udon.
Are you sure?
I don't have a camera.
I'm glad. I haven't eaten it recently.
I'm glad.
I'll eat only the cashew.
Is this beef?
It tastes like chicken.
Tomorrow?
The day after tomorrow?
I'm hungry. I'm hungry. I'm hungry.
je h iPad
a
me
Pieces
Please tell how good stray cats you were
in buildings on the old Tokio-Kabukicho
I have moments when I really feel like
I'm done, but I feel like I've been
organized.
I feel refreshed.
I don't feel like I've done enough, but
I don't think it's a bad thing.
I'm looking forward to seeing what kind
of decorations I'm going to put on next
time.
I'm not a woman.
I see.
Your eyes are narrow.
I have my eyes here.
I can see my eyes here.
I can see that you look like me.
You look cute.
I can see my eyes.
Your eyes are big.
I'm a vegetable.
You're a vegetable.
You're small.
You have a cute face.
I often go to Kyoto alone.
Really?
I like to travel alone.
I like to travel by myself.
Wow, that's nice.
I like to travel alone.
It's comfortable.
It's a lie.
It's not good without people.
I was surprised that I was playing with
my friends since morning.
I wanted to go home because it was too
late.
I think we are all dreaming of going to
the country of dreams.
Let's go from afternoon.
I thought I was going to be tired.
I thought it was a moment to go home.
Then I went up again from the evening.
It's annoying.
I understand.
Let's go from the morning to the
evening.
I will take a walk.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Salad.
I'm sorry.
English translation by C VERY
Yes.
Thank you.
Look at this.
It's cute.
If you grow the green onion, will it be
a normal cabbage?
Like this.
So, the green onion...
What's wrong?
If I leave it for a while, it will be a
normal cabbage.
Is it a real cabbage?
I don't know if it was a long or short
tour.
I think I'm having more fun than before.
I think I'm getting better.
I'm saying that it's the first time that
I eat shaved ice for free.
It's a festival, so it costs more than
300 yen.
That's free.
I'm scared.
It's too big.
It's round.
It's like a real room.
It's like an illustration.
What do you think?
I don't feel anything in my ears.
You don't feel anything?
I feel the snare and the instruments.
I feel the sound of my body.
What about your voice?
My voice is good to hear, but I don't
feel like I'm listening to it.
I feel like I'm listening to the music
in the back.
All over?
I can hear only the instruments.
Your voice?
My voice and my voice.
I thought it was amazing that the
teacher was always there even though it
was hard.
I know a lot of patterns, so I want to
make it look like a different song.
I don't think there's anything like
this.
This song is really difficult, but it's
a difficult song.
I'm glad I could do it and put it in for
everyone.
I'm glad everyone's having fun.
I couldn't help it because I wanted to
go home.
I was worried that I couldn't go home.
I'm sorry.
I'm really busy.
The theme of the song is fun and busy.
I thought I'd be busy with the theme,
but I couldn't remember myself.
I'm only good at formation.
I was asked to fix it, but it was too
different.
I learned that it was so hard.
This is my room.
I can't make it too small.
You guys...
I'm cool
The field is like this
Hmm, is it a push-pull?
It's a push-pull, isn't it?
The field is like this
But, how do you say push-pull?
Push-pull is a person who throws
I see
Aoki-san runs as it is
The moment you hit it
You understand, don't you?
It's easy to do it one by one.
Ballet is here.
Swing is too full.
When you come to the home run, you have
to use one hand to come here.
My shoulders are soft.
Then you stand up and throw it like
this.
My shoulders are soft.
Te-chan's one time is faster.
Really?
Anyone can do it.
You can do it too.
Can I do it?
No, a little bit diagonally.
I'm sorry.
codes is also in the description
But today, the live house...
I didn't think Okinawa would be the live
house.
So, today is the last live house.
It's the semi-final.
I'll try to get to the last one.
Live house and all-star.
All-star means an all-star game.
In my head.
Baseball.
Seba.
It's an all-star game.
I lost to Valentin.
I'll get tired if I play twice in a row.
But I was so determined in the last
half.
Sugou-san is amazing.
If you say that, it's Riko.
Riko.
That's good.
I have a big butt.
But I'm a small one.
That's good.
Kao-chan, you're playing twice.
Look at the second time.
It's fun.
You're making me listen to you.
It's fun to play the second time.
It's fun.
It's amazing. It's beautiful.
It's beautiful.
I'm tired.
Huh?
It's different.
It's a real family.
It's not a family.
It's peaceful.
In the morning, the kids...
I said the kids, but there were two of
them.
The wife was running around.
Are you still going home?
This is it.
Come on.
Riko.
This way.
I'm tired.
I'm not good at stairs.
You're not good at stairs?
The stairs of life are still left.
Three times?
It's coming out from here.
It's close.
It's cute.
I'm tired.
I took a picture a while ago.
I'm going to take a picture of you.
I'm scared.
Wait a minute.
I'm not sure if I can use it or not.
I think you can use it.
You're cute.
Take a picture of me.
I'm going to take a picture of you.
I'm scared.
Riko's hair is good these days.
Is it red now?
You finally got used to me.
Riko.
Everyone says that.
I feel like I'm in trouble.
I feel like everyone has seen the part
that Aya showed.
That's what Aika said.
Riko's impression.
When Aika hears this story,
I get that impression.
I get this feeling.
I didn't know that.
That's why I said that.
Please subscribe to our channel.
わー!
マイニーマイ!
ウェルー!
OK!
あ〜、元気できた。
元気できた。
元気で始めるよ今。
あ〜
お〜
よっしゃー!
せーの、ぐるぐるぐるぐるぐるぐるぐる
反対、ぐるぐるぐるぐるぐる
待ってて!
あ〜!
Jump!
Ready, set, go!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10!
Okay!
Okay, let's start!
I'm tired
I'm nervous
Don't make it too bright
Okay!
I'm sorry!
And don't fall down.
Okay.
And don't fall into the water.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
Are you going to the toilet?
I'm going to the toilet.
Okay.
Everyone, please.
Don't get too wet.
Okay.
I think it's because during the day and
night...
During the night, I think...
I don't know.
I think it's because during the night,
the sky was really beautiful.
During the day,
it's always...
It's always from dawn to night.
Every year, it's held five times.
This is the first time this year
that I'm going to end this year's FAMILY
ENT.
I'm so happy.
When it's bright outside,
I'm like...
I'm like,
I feel like I'm bright.
It was a completely different two days.
It was fun.
I'm not crying because I'm injured.
I'm glad I'm strong.
I've decided to hold a 3-day university
concert.
I want to do what I can do with six
people.
I'm looking forward to the concert and
what I can show at the concert.
I got something on the table.
Since the girl passed
Does not even blink
Why don't you dance here
Speaking continue
Everyone is over when a super star
But I remember
Wow!
Let's go back get it.
No, no, no.
No talking.
Just this?
Dance, dance, dance.
Yes, yes.
Tell me.
What?
Rhyme?
Oh, really?
One more, one more, one more.
Dance, dance, dance.
What?
This is...
Super star!
Oh, and...
And...
A super star who can deliver the things
that need to be emergency.
A super star who aims for the most
powerful monster.
Why are you doing that?
I can't get there.
And...
Dance, dance, dance.
This frequency is great.
This was Mr.
No.
Mr.
Thank you for watching!
It's cold.
July.
No, it's not July.
What does July mean?
July.
January.
Let's go!
I want to be the one who plays the white
car
Baby, it was a long time
Everybody, is the dream a dream?
I'm screaming, I'm going to the sky
today
I want to be the one who dances
I'm screaming, I'm going to the sky
today I want to be the one who dances
Here we go now!
I'm a child who is a child who is a
child
A new science communication
I like it, but I don't like it
I'm a child who is a child who is a
child
Do you estão pursuing nothing now?
I'm going to spank you
Do you still want me to go to something
now?
And in the end why did you come?
mais
Thank you for watching.
I want to be the best
I want to believe strongly
I-i'm
I'm sorry, but I'm not going to let you
go.
I'm going to be a good friend of the
king.
I'm sorry, but I'm not going to let you
go.
I think it's better to come to Akitade
than to Tokyo.
I feel like I became a superstar when I
came to Akitade.
Because we are a lot.
It's not easy to have such a good look.
Thank you.
Thank you for watching!
Now, Tami, could you do it once?
Tami's part is okay.
Oh, thank you.
B-melody of the B-album is
People who are just getting tired
Ah, it's okay if you can do it
Ah, Akita Bench
Ah, do ma
Do ma
Leave it to me
I can do it
Yes, I will practice
Thank you
I'm sorry for the preparation
I'm sorry
Thank you
Excuse me
I'm a little worried, but I'm here.
Thank you
Thank you, I'm really sorry
Ah, good
I'm tired
Ready, go!
Round and round, round and round
Ah, it's a rhythm
Ready, go!
It's a rhythm
2, 3, 4, 5
It's over!
Kaho-chan, please
I'm the president
Are you the president?
Yes
I'm so nervous
I'm nervous too
President
We're going to enjoy the Akita branch
Where are we?
Akita!
We are M2!
Fighting!
Why do you say we are?
We are M2!
Is this okay, myoco?
Even if the world becomes dark, can you
save it?
Inuu Akiti speaking,
We are Wear it down, generation to
generation
I'm a lonely person who doesn't know
what to do
I don't know what to do someday
I'm a lonely person who doesn't know
what to do
I wonder who I'm singing for
Let's go!
It's not noticeable if you don't change,
right?
Come on, don't do that!
Let's go!
Raise your hands!
Don't put your hands down!
It's a dream!
It's a reality!
Everyone, ready?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
I'm so tired of it
I'm sick of it
Uchiha-san, Tohoku-san, Tohoku-san
Let's go!
I'll call your name with my love
The starry sky is sparkling, this love
is seven
I'll tell you how I feel, I can't stop
I think there was an announcement on the
official website
Milla Hoshina got injured during
rehearsal
and she couldn't sleep today
Today, let's all have fun with Milla's
fan!
Thank you for watching!
I'm the 12th Shizuku BANBO of Sassolita,
Nakayama Riku!
Yesterday was a lovely wibbly day, so
today I'm going to be a biter biter...
I don't like this!
I'm going to be a biter biter!
Thank you for watching!
Thank you very much.
Everyone loves Mire-chan, right?
Mire-chan, everyone loves you.
You've met me in the middle of the year,
right?
Yes!
Let's do it more than usual,
with love!
Next is Mire-chan!
Are you having fun?
Thank you!
Isn't everyone's voice too small?
It's too small!
Everyone, let's go!
Are you going to enjoy the last
performance?
Thank you!
Is it over already?
This year?
What happened?
I wonder what happened.
I really enjoyed every single one of
them.
Like the live performance during the
Ebitu concert.
It was really fun.
But I didn't really enjoy the part where
I could shout out like,
BAM! BAM!
I didn't really enjoy the live
performance.
So I'm really looking forward to next
year.
I don't know.
During the Ebitu concert, it wasn't a
world tour.
But it was a little bit...
I don't know.
What is it?
I don't know if it's big or not.
I think I'm talking about something I
have.
Well...
It's an old...
It's a single from ABiTU.
It's a music video.
I want to try to reproduce that.
Oh, with the members now?
If I were Kofu-chan,
I'd like to do a cute music video with
Butterfly Effect and Hight Tech.
I want to do it with the members who
have grown up this 10th anniversary.
I think so.
Then, if you say, I'll make you three
songs, what will you do?
If you say, I can make three songs...
Three songs? Three songs?
I don't know.
I want to do a high-end song.
What else is there?
High-end.
You said you could make a music video
you haven't made before.
There are songs that haven't been made
yet.
Oh, it's difficult.
What is it?
It's my favorite song.
What is it? I like the song that goes
well with the song.
What is it?
Recently, I often shoot outside for
EriChannel MVs.
So I want to shoot a music video with
cute sets inside the room.
I don't know the song.
Thank you.
I'm hungry.
What are you doing in front of the
house?
I'm keeping my phone right in front of
the house.
I want to eat a pot.
My family came with me.
I felt a sense of unity for three days.
I'm sorry that Mirei got hurt.
I'm sorry that the last one-man show
didn't have six people.
But this time,
I was able to express my feelings.
I think I was able to express my
feelings little by little.
I think it was a good Christmas.
The feelings I have for this year's 3
DAYS are stronger than usual.
Especially, when I was in the lesson, I
felt the same as Mirei.
She told me many things, and she gave me
lots of suggestions.
She also gave me a set list, and she
told me what I should do and what I
should do.
She told me what I should do and what I
I could feel that she really cared about
me.
It's a shame that Mirei wasn't there,
but I felt that Mirei's soul was in the
curtain.
I think there were 6 people standing
there.
I could feel that she cared about me.
There were 5 people, but there were 6
people inside.
I felt like we were connected for a
year.
I always forget what we started this
I thought it didn't matter.
But this time, I remembered a lot about
my head and butt.
I hope I can change in a good way.
I have a lot of things that I think have
changed.
I hope I can do my best to make this
10th anniversary.
I hope I can bring my best to the 10th
anniversary.
I have a lot of things that I think have
changed.
I like the fact that I'm with my family.
I got a message from Mie-chan.
We all replied to her voice message.
We were joking.
We were like, I love you, I don't love
you.
We were joking.
I'm happy to see her.
She is soight as I can.
I'm so excited!
My fingers and you are in my heart!
Hey, you!
Don't disturb me!
Haa!
Thank you for watching!
Ha! Ha!
Okay, thank you.
Please.
Please use the star microphone.
Ha! Ha! Ha!
Hi! Hi! Hi!
Ha! Ha!
Okay, thank you.
Okay, let's start with monitor check.
I hope you will澄 base mercilessly
Thank you for watching!
I'm so sad.
I was surprised.
I'm glad that we can perform in front of
our families.
Our families would be happy.
Mie-chan wanted to perform, so we can
perform.
I'm happy as a member and as a family.
Mie-chan.
It's frustrating that Mie-chan can't
perform.
I want to perform with all of us.
I'm afraid that I'll make you do it.
I'm holding back.
I want to perform with all of us.
I'm not good at this part.
I'll introduce the participants one by
one.
Some of the costumes are the costumes of
your favorite people.
The 10 years of Ebichu are the history
of this person.
This year, he will jump with his small
body.
The third participant is Rika Marama.
Finally, I'm a quick rocker. I'll do my
best!
The song of the number one,
There was a lyrics like Vocaloid in the
Eri,
Now and in the past, the emotion is a
big explosion,
Full of humans,
The number five, Yasumoto Ayaka, who
blows life into the doll.
Yes, let's all get excited.
Go! Go!
From the beginning of the school year,
we have always been in the midst of a
revolution.
In 2019, we will travel and make a smile
on our family.
No. 7, Hoshino Mirei.
Long time no see.
I'm so happy that I'm about to cry.
I'll do my best! Thank you!
The entrance student is a shrimp-chewed
baby.
He is almost 20 years old.
He is still growing.
How far will he go this year?
Together with Swarovski, he is aiming
for the No.1 in Japan.
No.10, Hiroto Kashiwagi.
I will do my best to be the No.1 in
Japan!
Eyes of being unique and warm gesture
Over-the-市
Providing strange face, fair facial
Interview No. 51, Kawayashi Kaho
Hi! Everyone, let's open it!
The only one without a name, the most
arrogant, the most selfless, the most
unambiguous, the number 12, Riko
Nakayama.
Hello! Hello, hello, hello!
I'm the one with the water!
Hello! Hello! Hello!
Now, let's have a word from Mirei-chan
who was looking forward to meeting
everyone at today's event.
Are you crying?
It's been a while, everyone!
It's been a while since I've seen
everyone.
I got injured at the rehearsal last
December at the Christmas live.
I was taking a break from the Christmas
event and the Ebi Negi live.
I'm really happy that I'm recovering
from the injury and standing in front of
everyone.
Thank you.
It's still a little difficult to sing
and dance, but as you can see, I'm very
energetic.
I'm talking to everyone.
I'm doing a little bit of work every
day.
But I'm really getting more and more
things to do, and I'm really happy to
hear that every day.
I'm thinking of getting better soon.
It's been a long time since I've seen
everyone. I'm really nervous.
I was so nervous before the show.
It's been a long time since I've seen
the light of the siren.
I want to do my best to perform with
everyone as soon as possible.
I'm still in good shape every day.
I can do it today, but I think there
will be a little tomorrow.
I want to do my best from what I can do.
Today, I want to talk with everyone and
sing a song.
I hope you can see me singing and
dancing after a long time.
I look forward to working with you.
There was a place where I could see the
stage from above.
It was like a room.
I thought that everyone was moving well.
It was really fun.
Of course, I know all the songs.
It was the most fun live performance
I've ever seen.
It's important to know the songs.
Thank you.
Thank you to you
It's different from the first part, it's
surprisingly good
It's a pleasant place
How is it, Hinata-san?
It's that song
Thank you to you
Thank you to rice
OK
Let's say thank you to you
I'm sure I'm looking at you, Ireh-chan
She's looking
There she is!
Ireh-chan!
Where?
She's in the room
Oh, really?
Wow
She's gone
Ireh-chan!
I'm going to sing this!
Oh, you took a picture of me?
You're a genius.
It's like a stage performance.
Mirei-chan took a picture of you, so
sing.
Please sing a song that's as good as
Mirei-chan.
Thank you for your hard work.
I don't want to meet you anytime, but I
don't want to be honest with you
I want to tell you now, thank you!
You always make me smile
I can do my best because I have someone
important
Even if I'm strong, I'm actually a
crybaby
You know that, right?
I know it well
Look straight into my eyes
I'm holding you in my heart
The one who can convey my precious
feelings is
istas to me
No matter what song comes out,
the way everyone is singing and dancing
gives me a lot of energy.
I think it's YouTube that gives me
energy while watching it.
I feel like I'm more energetic today.
I feel like I'm more energetic in part
two.
And I think it's fun to be together with
everyone.
Even when I watch the family members,
I think I like the space.
I really liked the atmosphere in the
room.
In the evening sun, we hug each other on
the sofa
When the lights go out, the window frame
suddenly turns into a world of hope
My dreams are waking up
When I touch your back, it's like the
sky of today
The invisible clouds are over there
I was looking at you
I can't see myself
I was trying to keep you away from me
I want to believe that person who is the
same as Kiserasen
Our fingers that were connected and
broken have been cut off
Kiserasen, I love you
On my equivalent Kendama
I knew everything about pure and boring
movies
I felt like I could give them to you
It was the kindest place in the world,
everyone
I want to believe in that person who is
a
Kisera Sera's Maginot
Don't lock me up in youth, the first me
Kiss her Br getting closer
I tried to spread the words that were
still in my pocket
But I already realized that it was a
fake and threw it away in the trash can
I want to believe that person who is the
same as the one who erased me
But you are not reflected in me
The other side of the sky is...
I love you
Shabada Shabalubida Shabada
Shabalubida Shabalubida
I'm training my neck.
Seiko is training her neck.
It's a V-shape.
It looks like a normal body.
Next time, we'll come here with the
interview.
I was surprised.
Ouch!
Let's go.
Seiko spilled it.
Please subscribe to our channel.
It's terrible.
It's like a shrimp ball.
It's cute.
I hope you enjoyed this video.
If you have any questions, please leave
a comment.
Thank you for watching.
With attitude you have to think that
this time of shooting will be cut
Because I was using the camera from
rearrop
So, I have to take the reality that this
time is a serious job
However, this time is so fun that I
don't want to take the reality
I'm not reallyitéable to drink
alcohol...
I working to beitéable
But the reality is getting wild
So I want to ask my friend to drag me to
that
You are in Akita right now
I really want to eat the kidney
I'm a little nervous.
I want to be in a relaxed atmosphere.
I want to be with Mr. Nakayama.
I'm in Akita now.
I want to eat a lot of
If I swallow this, I won't be able to
drink the Kiri-tampou.
I can't swallow the Kiri-tampou.
Kiri-tampou is to be swallowed.
There is a reality that you can't accept
if you don't swallow it.
I'm going to do that.
Did you finish?
I'm a little drunk.
I'm not in a good mood today.
I can't drink our reality.
Why?
I'm sure this is a little...
I'm a little tired of it.
I'm tired of it.
If you get tired of it, you won't be
able to use it.
I can't drink that reality.
I'm sorry.
I don't know how to drink it.
I didn't mean to say this.
He's back.
I'm sorry.
I'm really emotional.
I'm a little sad.
I can't drink it.
What is it that you say?
I'm trying hard.
You don't have to work hard.
I can drink it.
Can I talk to you?
I'm talking.
How do you end this?
I'm not sure if I can do it.
There's a lot of it.
This is a reality that is cut in the
making.
I'm talking so hard.
There's nothing else.
I'm rooting for everyone.
Really?
From the bottom of my heart.
I'm going to eat hormones.
What did you say?
I'm going to put hormones in my mouth.
I'm sorry.
Don't cry.
I'm rooting for hormones.
Hormones are there every time you eat
them.
I can't drink it.
I'm sorry.
If you drink it, you'll get a burn.
By cooking the meat,
I was able to swallow it for the first
time.
That's good.
The reality that I can't swallow
will hit the wall.
I thought I had to beat it.
I also eat my favorite food.
I can't swallow it.
I put it in my mouth and take it home.
I'm sorry.
I can't swallow it.
It's too expensive.
I eat it a lot.
It's delicious.
I'm brave enough to put it in my mouth.
I'm sorry.
I can't say anything.
Hang in there, Rika-chan.
It's like hormones.
It's delicious.