Ebichu's video!
1, 2, 3!
It's over!
Let's switch!
We finished 3 songs in a flash.
We'll go to the next concert tomorrow.
Let's do it!
Do you want to go to Sendai tomorrow?
We have to prepare for the concert.
We have to wear masks.
But the live performance is crazy.
How do you do it?
Self-pronunciation!
I'm not sure what I'm saying.
I think you'll be like, what the hell?
The stage moves in this move.
We did different choreography and danced
together.
We did various moves.
I can't say anything.
I couldn't stop dancing.
I'm tired.
At first, I was wondering if everyone
would do it.
Everyone danced, so I was wondering if
they would do it.
At the first concert, I was surprised.
Everyone clapped.
That moment was the best.
It was a combination of family and work.
I didn't think I could see that scene
when I was an idol.
I was happy.
The sound is not good.
It's not good.
It was the first time for six people.
It was the first song.
It was the song of Ebichu Pride.
I remembered that.
I was really sad.
Everyone was sad.
I was sad.
Miyuki, you were angry.
It's your fault.
This performance was produced by Yuki-
sensei.
It's different from usual.
It was Ebichu from the angle.
and produced the performance.
The last nine-color members'
performances
were very important to me.
I'm very grateful.
Thank you.
I want to make it a DVD.
Me too!
I want to make it a DVD!
If you make it a DVD...
Well, 1000 years later.
I want to see this kind of performance
and make it a DVD.
I'll do my best.
So, Moe and I
have a lot of feelings for you.
We'll do our best to make this kind of
performance.
Thank you for your continued support!
Thank you.
Today is the 11th...
Yes!
Thank you.
Moe, Moe, the last one!
The last one!
Is it wrong?
I don't know.
Thank you.
The last two performances are...
We're filming!
We're shooting about 1500 videos.
We'll shoot one more.
Good morning.
We're SHIN-CHAN and MISHIRO.
Thank you for your continued support!
Thank you.
1, 2, 3, 4.
We're done.
I'm nervous.
I'm happy.
The performance of the five of us...
Today is the last day.
I'm so happy.
We'll be back tomorrow!
I'm sorry.
Let's do it.
5 push-ups.
7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15.
Junko.
Safety first, health first.
We.
We've been working hard.
We're Nagoya.
I'm lonely.
Today's Rinko is the most.
Recently, it's been hard.
I'm going to cry.
Let's start from the end.
Let's do it.
Where are we?
Nagoya!
We are Japan!
Let's do it!
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
My tears are falling.
I'm so sorry.
Are you filming me in the dark?
No.
You're not filming me in the dark, are
you?
I'm not filming you.
It's over.
What is the next stage?
We will be performing at the musical,
the musical of the musical opening
night,
Sakurazaki High School.
I will be performing at the musical.
It's my first musical!
In this musical, I will be playing the
role of Mai-chan, a high school
freshman.
I will be the center of the students and
I will work hard to make a musical.
I will fight against various enemies and
I will try to make a musical.
There are many things that I can do with
Mai-chan.
I can connect with her character.
I can feel her actions and I can
understand her feelings.
She is easy to play and she is a good
role.
I will be the center of the students and
I will be in many scenes.
I was told that I was in charge of Mai-
chan from the beginning.
I thought about what I needed as a role
to be the center.
I will be able to express my feelings
and power.
I will learn a lot from her.
I will be able to express my feelings
and power.
I have only done singing before.
I think singing in the play is the most
important task.
I will be able to express my feelings
and power.
They practiced my part together,
regardless of whether it was my part or
not.
And the voice actor, Daisuke Yokoyama,
said,
I'm glad I was in this scene.
Today's Mai is really good.
They praised me a lot and extended it.
I'm really grateful that I was able to
make this work while being helped by the
kindness of the teachers around me.
The live show is coming soon, so this
time it's Team Blue and Team Red.
The cast is the same, but the content is
different.
I think it's hard to deliver a different
cast with the same work.
That's the highlight.
I think each of them has its own
strengths.
I think it's a moment that only Red can
show.
I hope that the girls will have their
own sparkles and moments that will make
them feel cute.
I think there are a lot of people who
decide to bring their feet to the venue
during this time.
I'm glad I saw that kind of person.
It's been a year or two.
I think it's a musical full of things I
want to do, goals, and dreams.
I want to make this stage shine in a
bright way.
I hope many people will laugh at me and
be moved by the passion of everyone.
I'll do my best.
I'm really nervous.
I'm nervous about the investment
training.
I'm wearing a uniform, so it's been a
while.
I'm wearing a school uniform.
I'm a JK.
I don't think I can see that star.
Please come and play with me.
I'm waiting for you.