When you think of Ibaraki, you think of Sakuragi!
Cocona Sakuragi, the navel mermaid of EBICHU born in Ibaraki, will make her triumphant return to Ibaraki on her spring tour! To commemorate this, on the day of the tour, we will have Ms. Sakuragi give a talk to the other EBICHU members about her overflowing love for Ibaraki and recommended spots!
Today
Ibaraki
I'm from Ibaraki! Who says so?
Today...
Cocona's hometown
It's a triumphant return live!
That's why
Today
"If you come to Mito, you must go here!
If you come to Mito, you must go here!
Can I introduce you to some of the places you should definitely visit when you come to Mito?
I'm sure everyone would love to have that information!
Do you have any pictures today?
We have pictures!
Thank you very much!
Okay, then...
Cocona's Favorite
Photos of the Mito spot.
What's this? Looks delicious!
Does anyone know this?
This is
Stamina Ramen Matsugoro's
Stamina Ramen Matsugoro's "Stamina Chilled Bean Sprouts"!
Is this cold?
First, there is a hot bean paste.
Then, there's the hot bean paste.
And there, at the bottom
There are noodles that have been cooled down.
And these noodles are really hot.
And these noodles really go well together.
Sweet and spicy.
It's really good!
Okay, hot! Cold, hot! Cold?
No, no, it's, uh...
You know, when you put it on hot.
It's getting colder and colder, isn't it?
And look at these ingredients!
What do you think it is?
Cabbage, carrots.
You mean like sweet-and-sour pork?
Chives, chives, chives!
Chives!
This thing that looks like sweet-and-sour pork...
It's liver!
It's really good here, but...
But today
We're temporarily closed.
Just for today!
I'm so sorry.
I told them I wanted them to go.
Please go check it out...!
Cocona's.
"I've eaten here before."
"I've eaten here before"!
Please go see them!
Please, next time you come to Mito...
next time you come to Mito.
If you want to see it today
Please go see it!
Please go see it today!
As for the feeling I've had so far
I've been to Tokyo, Chiba, Kanagawa, Saitama, etc.
I've had so many chances to go
I'm so excited to be back! Yay!"
It's not like that.
Because we all live in Kanto area.
I mean Kanto...
We live in the Kanto region, which is a pretty big part of Japan.
So it's kind of like a local thing.
Isn't this your first time?
This kind of triumphant return?
It's my first time!
I'm going to do my best in "Mind Ibaraki"!
By the way, what's "Mind Ibaraki"?
What's it like?
I wonder if it's "mind yankee"? Yankee?
Yankee?
You're a Yankee?
He's from Ibaraki.
He's from Ibaraki, and he used to be a Yankee.
Don't be violent!
Don't be rowdy here!
Absolutely not!
Let me out! Let me out!
Let your mind run wild!
Is there an Ibaraki dialect?
Yes!
It's "pe"!
"What's that?
Does it go up at the end?
It sounds a little bit...
It sounds a little bit intimidating.
It sounds a little bit yankee.
Yankee-ish.
Is that so?
Really?
I don't know.
Let's just say that...
Let's just leave it at that...
After the show...
I heard that they ate natto (fermented soybeans) from Ibaraki.
Ibaraki is Sakuragi.
What was that?
Just after the show in Ibaraki! What do you think now?
Today is just after the Ibaraki concert
Just after the show in Ibaraki, my hometown...
How did you feel?
Well, anyway...
From the beginning to the end
Cocona looked so happy!
Every time our eyes met.
She was smiling so much every time we made eye contact!
It's great to be in your hometown, isn't it?
It's where we held the choir competition.
It's a place that holds a lot of memories for me.
I don't know...
It brought back those memories.
It was so much fun!
Choir competition there...
It's pretty nerve-wracking, isn't it?
I was so nervous!
It's pretty big, isn't it?
There are a lot of people there.
I'll never forget how nervous I was at the chorus contest.
I'll never forget how nervous I was at the choir competition.
It was fun!
We sang dozens more songs today than we did then!
But the tension
I think the tension was a little higher
Choir competition
It's true that at a school competition like that
It's so quiet at school.
Today, the fans...
The fans were so excited.
It was a lot of fun!
How was it? Let's do it.
From the very first song.
Every time I looked at her...
She was smiling so much...
I told you earlier...
She was smiling the whole time!
Anyway...
She seemed to be having fun!
Really? So much!
Unico couldn't contain himself.
Uncontrollable?
Her love for her hometown...
I'm sure Yuno will do the same when she gets to Aichi.
It was my first time at a live concert in my hometown.
It was so much fun!
Besides natto, did you eat any other Ibaraki specialties?
Cocona's dad brought me some pudding.
The pudding...
It was so good!
You ate it?
It was delicious!
I ate the normal one.
The brown one...?
Matcha, soy sauce and miso.
Oh, yes, yes! That's it!
Aren't those sweet and savory?
How did you like the Umaibo?
I'm addicted to Umaibo.
I ate four of them before the show.
They are so good!
Are they a local staple?
You can find them at train stations.
You can even find them at train stations in the souvenir section.
They're a local staple.
And it's sticky, too!
Natto (fermented soybeans), try it!
I'll try it later!
You recommended "Stamina Chilled Bean Curd" during the MC at the concert. Is there anything else you think I should try when I come to Ibaraki?
The traditional dried sweet potatoes made by the Sakuragi family!
They are really delicious!
I got it at the school arts and crafts festival!
You fans can't eat it...
They can't eat it...
I want you to eat it...
If you can't eat it...
Kemon-soba.
It's really famous for its kenchin-soba.
Ibaraki Prefecture is famous for its kenchin soba.
The soba is a little thicker.
with a higher percentage of buckwheat flour.
It has a lot of ingredients.
It's really delicious!
It's been featured on TV a lot.
It's a famous soba that's even been featured on TV.
Please try it!
The udon noodles from today's meal
Is it related to the udon noodles?
I was so surprised...
It's not soba...
It's not even kenten...
For a local...
"Why that udon?"
It was good. It was good, but...
Was it green onion and ginger?
I thought it was famous, but...
Regardless...
I got all warm before rehearsal.
It was hot!
It was delicious, really!
But I want to try that too!
Please let me know the recommended sightseeing spots in Ibaraki!
Ibaraki is a seaside park!
It's in Hitachinaka City.
The amusement park there is amazing!
It has a lot of things to do.
On the other side of the park
There is a flower garden on the other side of the park.
It's called Nemophilab.
The flower garden looks really nice.
There are so many colorful flowers
There are so many colorful flowers.
I highly recommend it!
I want to go there!
I wish we could all go together for a photo shoot!
The amusement park is so much fun!
I want to go there!
Surprisingly, when people ask me about local spots
It's not always easy, is it?
Well, there is one.
There's Kairakuen, for example.
I'm sorry, I've never been there.
It's true that when you're a local...
You don't go out of your way to visit such tourist spots.
When you are a local, you don't go out of your way to visit such tourist spots.
Nemophila is really famous...
Green curry?
Green?
Nemophila curry!
Blue!
Blueish greenish...
Vivid color
It tastes like a normal curry...
Oh yeah!!!
It's so delicious.
It's a beautiful spot!
Fields full of blue nemophilas.
The kind that Instagrammers often post.
There's blue and red, too.
There are so many different colors.
I want to go there!
There are roller coasters and amusement parks
Amusement parks are a lot of fun.
That roller coaster...
Are they hard?
Or are they gentle?
Some of them are really intense.
Oh, yeah!
I'd love to go on that one!
(Are you one of those people who can go?
Instagrammers often post their pictures.
I can go! I want to go!
You know this kind of thing?
It spins!
It goes like this while spinning!
That's awesome!
I've never been on one of those.
I've never been on one of those!
(You can't go on that one?
Yes, I can't go on that one!
I can't go on a regular roller coaster.
I'll have to grow up...
I didn't grow up...
I've grown up and I can ride them!
This type.
Is that one of the big ones?
Yes, that one too!
What's so great about Ibaraki?
First of all, the people are hot!
Hot!!!!
It was so hot today!
That's for sure!
There are so many friendly personalities.
There were so many friendly personalities.
But like I said before.
I feel intimidated by their dialect...
I think that dialect makes them intimidating.
I feel intimidated by their dialect, so I feel like a yankee.
They are really kind!
It's just a mind yankee.
Yankees are passionate
Yankees are passionate, passionate and kind.
There are gentle Yankees too!
That's me.
a Yankee with a tender heart.
I'm kind, right?
Gal!
Gal?
She's got guts.
People in Ibaraki are really passionate!
It's wonderful!
When You say "guts," you're right.
You have a lot of guts.
I wonder if it's because You're from Ibaraki.
I wonder if they inherit it?
What do you think of Sakuragi's story?
Well, Kanto is...
It's hard to go sightseeing in Kanto.
If I'm going to go on a trip
I'd like to get away from the city.
But...
But you know what?
I've been asking Cocona about various sightseeing spots
and good food.
I'd like to go somewhere close by.
And if I can get tomorrow off...
I'd like to go to Ibaraki.
That's when she introduced me.
What was it, ramen?
Oh! That!
Stamina Ramen!
I want to go eat that too!
I want to go eat there!
They're temporarily closed today...
No way!
No way! I was going to introduce you.
I'll see you later.
I'd love to go there! I'd love to!
From now on...
Ibaraki and Cocona Sakuragi
Ibaraki and Sakuragi Cocona!