Ebichu's video
So today
Ibaraki, the local
I came to say that it is the local
Oh!
Thank you
Hey, something like that
Today, in Kokona
Isn't it a day in the
Gwaisen Live?
Gwaisen Live
Thank you
So
If you come to Mito today
I want you to come here
I'm a little
I'm sorry
I want you to come here
I'm a little
I want to know that information
I want to know
Was there a photo today?
I have a photo
Kokona's special
Mito spot photo
Don!
What is this?
Does anyone know this?
Oh!
This is
Stamina Ramen Matsugoro
Stamina cold
Is this cold?
First, there is a hot an
An
There is a cold noodles
An and
Hot An and
The noodles are really mixed
It's really delicious
Hot, cold
It's getting cold
Hot
Please look at this material
What do you think?
What is it?
Cabbage
It's like a
It's a lever
Really
It's really delicious here
Today is a temporary break
It's a temporary break
I want everyone to go
Please go and see
Please go to see
If you want to see it today
As far as I know
Tokyo Chiba Kanagawa Saitama
There was
There was a lot of time
It's not like a real train
Yeah, that's right
Everyone is in Kanto
I agree
Kanto is a very close Kanto
It's like a local Kanto
It's the first time
It's a hot weather
Certainly the first time
I want to choose the mind
Mind Yankee
I'm not sure
Yankee
It was a yaki
It's a yaki
After all, it's rampaging
I'm not sure
No way
Is there a Korak прек bikes event?
Oh.....
Somehow or Naa
Will be spiffy
Will be perturbed
It sounds like something desired
I might be able to hear it
Oh erstmal
Is it so,,?
That
Like that
It sounds like that
I'm super tired...
We ate the natto of Ibaraki.
We ate natto of Ibaraki.
What is it?
What is the special phrase that ended
Ibaraki Park?
Today is the special phrase that ended
Ibaraki Park.
How was it?
It was fun from beginning to end.
I was happy to sing in the countryside.
I had a concert in Gashokonkuru.
I was happy to remember the memories.
I was nervous at the Gashokonkuru.
I was very nervous.
It was a big concert.
There were many people. I couldn't
forget the tension of the Gashokonkuru.
I sang many songs today.
I was more nervous than I was at that
time.
I was nervous between the concerts.
But today, the fans were excited.
I was nervous from the first song.
I was nervous because I couldn't control
my emotions.
It was my first time to sing in my
hometown.
I had a lot of fun.
What was the most delicious food you
ate?
I ate my mother's fish cake.
I ate fish cake.
I ate matcha.
I ate matcha, soy sauce, and miso.
I ate fish cake, soy sauce, and miso.
How good is good?
I ate fish cake and it was delicious.
I ate four fish cakes before the
appearance, so it was delicious.
It does not use the red wine because it
was delicious.
It was delicious.
Is it a small town?
It is a small town.
With the
It's a good snack.
It's delicious.
It's good to eat in the store.
What is the best food in the store?
It's the best sushi made by Sakuragi.
It's really delicious.
It's a good restaurant.
Fans can eat it.
It's delicious to eat it.
It's delicious.
It's famous for the noodle.
The noodles are thick.
It's delicious.
It's a good noodle.
What is the udon that came out of
today's meal?
It's a good udon.
I was surprised.
It's not soba.
It's not keichin.
I was surprised when I ate it.
It was delicious.
I ate it with green onions and ginger.
I thought it was a good noodle.
It doesn't matter.
I was hot because my body was hot.
It was delicious.
I want to eat it.
What is Sakuragi?
Sakuragi is a place that is in the north
of the Kaihin Park.
The amusement park is full of
attractions.
There are many flower fields on the
other side.
There are many flower fields.
There are many colorful things.
I recommend it.
I want to go there.
I want to go to the amusement park.
I want to go to the local area.
There is a place called TAIWANKAI.
I haven't been there.
I want to go to the local area.
I don't go there.
I want to eat green curry.
Green curry.
It's blue.
It's a taste that is similar to green
curry.
It's delicious.
There are many blue amusement parks.
There are many red and blue amusement
parks.
I want to go to the amusement park.
The roller coaster is very intense.
I want to ride it.
Can you ride it?
There is a roller coaster like this.
It's a roller coaster.
I've never ridden it.
You can't ride it.
I can't ride it.
I grew up and became a normal jet
coaster.
That's amazing.
What is your favorite thing about being
a jet coaster?
First of all, people are hot.
Hot?
It was always hot.
There are many people who are hot.
But I think people are hot.
So people are like a hot guy.
They are all kind.
They are just wild guys.
I think hot guys are passionate and
kind.
I'm a hot guy.
That's right.
You are a hot guy.
I'm a hot guy.
There are many people who are hot.
That's great.
I'm a hot guy.
That's right.
What is your favorite thing about Kanto?
It's hard to go to Kanto because it's a
tourist destination.
I want to go there if I go on a trip.
I want to eat delicious food here.
I want to go to Ibaraki if I can take a
break.
I want to eat ramen that Coco introduced
to me.
I want to eat ramen.
I want to go there.
The restaurant is closed today.
I'm looking forward to it.
I hope we can go there again.
I'm looking forward to going to Ibaraki
and Sakura.
Thank you for watching my channel.
Thank you for watching.