Ebi-chu's video!
Ebi-chu's video
What did you do when you joined Ebi-chu?
I joined the drama of Nemoto-san's
script as soon as I joined Ebi-chu.
I knew Nemoto-san from there.
If I had another chance, I wanted to
work with Nemoto-san.
Then I called Nemoto-san and asked him
to appear on the drama.
I was very happy, but I was worried
about the musical after that.
I was worried that I couldn't sing on
the stage except for Ebi-chu.
What is your impression of Ebi-chu?
I'm a writer, so I'm very similar to
him.
When I first joined the drama, I was
very strong.
I asked the makeup artist if I could
apply body cream.
I asked if I was okay.
I thought I was totally different from
him.
But when I thought about it, I started
to think that I was similar to him.
When I was reading the script for the
first day of the training, I thought I
was a villain.
I was inspired by him.
He thought I was like this.
What was the most fun day of the
training?
It was a very fun day.
I was always in a bright state.
I was complimenting Akko Gorilla and
Momo before the performance.
I was excited because it was before the
performance.
I thought it was amazing that I was
doing that.
Everyone was very kind.
It was a happy atmosphere.
What is your goal for the next stage?
I want to do more.
I want to perform on stage for a month.
Thank you for watching.
I think so.
What is your goal this year?
I want to play various roles this year.
I have a lot of roles that I have to
play on stage.
That's a lot of fun, too.
I want to play various roles.
I may end up playing a lot of roles.
I'm very angry.
I want to play various roles.
What is your impression of the
character?
This time, I was in a very bad
condition.
I want to play a role.
I want to emphasize my character more
than usual.
I was told that I should play a little
more.
I was very angry.
What is your favorite part of the
character?
I've been talking to my mother.
I want to go to the school.
I want to go out while I'm wearing my
school uniform.
I love to cooperate with other people.
I want to go to the school.
What is your favorite scene?
Good morning.
I can't see anything because I haven't
contacted you.
Look, I brought it recently.
It's the one behind my feet.
I'm sorry I can't see anything.
I'm going to the rehearsal.
This is my real costume.
I'm going to have the rehearsal from
here.
I'm cute.
I'm going to the rehearsal.
I'm Shiritani Shihara.
I'm NAKAYAMA RIKO, number 52.
I'm looking forward to your rehearsal.
Thank you for your cooperation.
The world is always in the way
I'm sorry that I can't see the rhythm
Rhythm?
But now I'm going to have to play the
rhythm again
I'm sorry that I can't see the rhythm
Yes
Let's dance, Let's dance
Let's dance, let's dance
This song is really the last
Everyone, lower your body
Make up, make up, make up, make up
Let's make a face of ideals
Let's dance, let's dance
I'll see you tomorrow!
Thank you!
I'm tired.
I'm going to bed.
Bye-bye!
I came to see the second anniversary of
the birthday of Rika Mikami.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to seeing the songs
of NAKAYAMA NICO and GYAKO GYAKO RIRI.
I'm really sorry to say that I'm looking
forward to this month.
I'm waiting for you to come to the
event.
Where are we?
NAKAYAMA NICO's birthday party!
We are NAKAYAMA!
One song! NAKAYAMA!
NAKAYAMA FIGHT!
Thank you for your cooperation.
Thank you for your hard work.
I said bye bye too early.
Thank you very much.
I wonder what happened to the stage.
I'm looking forward to this video.
This was the NAKAYAMA RICO's Youth
Festival.
This is what the NAKAYAMA RICO Youth
Festival looks like.
If you think it looks fun, I look
forward to next year.
Thank you. Bye bye.
Thank you.
Hold me close
Hide it, hide it, hide it
Peek-a-boo, peek-a-boo
My stomach, my heart, my...
I finished the birthday party safely.
My birthday is on October 28th, so I
have about two weeks left.
I went to a lot of stages, but it didn't
feel like a birthday solo live.
I felt like I was really doing a solo
live.
The costumes were made very cute this
year.
I had a lot of fun.
I had fun with the last song, but I
thought I'd sing it tomorrow.
I think you saw a different birthday
party.
I was surprised that I had one more seat
left.
I was very happy that I had one more
seat left for last year's birthday
party.
I always think about it after I decide
to do a birthday party.
I decided to do it this year at a pretty
early stage, when I didn't know if there
was a birthday party.
I really like to take pictures and
videos.
I wanted to do that kind of video at
work.
I decided to make a video for the
birthday party.
I didn't feel the summer very much.
I had a lot of fun with the music video.
I hope you all enjoy it.
I'll think about what to do next year.
Thank you very much.
Please look forward to the birthday
party of the 20th anniversary on October
28.
Bye bye.