Ebichu and Momoclo's idol discussion
I'm so nervous!
It rang.
(Caller) Hello?
Hello?
Hello
（Caller) Hello?
What?
Hello
(Caller)Aya?
Is this Kanako?
Yes, I'm Momota
Aya, how are you?
I'm fine.
How are you these days?
Lately? I'm doing well and having fun.
Fine and happy?
We've been know each other for a long time.
Since our debut?
We hasn't changed much since then.
We're so close.
But we haven't really talked much, have we?
That's right. It's not easy.
We don't even had a chance to go on the same set.
Only at the end of the year.
It's only once or twice a year.
That's true.
Also I'm so nervous and shy.
so it's hard for me to talk.
I don't really talked to anyone on the set also.
Somehow I'm nervous too.
I'm so happy.
I've always wanted to talk to you face to face
Or at least with your voice.
I've always wanted to, so I'm very happy.
Some of our staff and make-up artist are the same.
I've heard from them that you wanted to talk to to me.
They've told me a lot about it.
I had heard that somehow.
So it's true?
That's right.
What? Why? Why?
You're just like that.
I just want to talk to you, like that.
It's been about five years.
Five years? Longer than I thought.
What? Why?
I wonder...
What is it?
After all Your presence...
Of course, everyone who works as an idol in Stardust...
I'm sure everyone thinks the same.
You're so big.
Like the leader of Stardust.
That's what I really think of you.
As the leader of all the groups.
I don't know.
When you say "just right",
Feel like something from above
I'm so happy.
I wonder...
But I'm not doing anything, though.
This year, few months ago.
You asked me for my contact info right?.
I was so happy.
Really?
It's not often that I get to meet the junior groups.
But Ebichu isn't a junior either.
And Ebichu too.
You always say that you're our junior, but...
We've been working together since we started around the same time.
From my point of view, we're the same generation.
That's how it is.
But I wonder...
Maybe it's because of Momoclo...
The image of Stardust idols that Momoclo created for us.
The fans, even our fans, at first...
they are the ones who liked Momoclo.
and came to see us.
We had a lot of them.
That's why Ebichu was able to be so relaxed.
That's why We were able to start as an idol group.
Momoclo really gave us the foundation.
That's not true, we built it together.
Is that how you put it?
Live performance for Ayaka Yasumoto
Lately, We've been able to do a lot of live performances.
We've been able to do a lot of things.
Little by little.
After all it's nice to have live performances.
I thought about it the other day when We had a live together.
What's a live show for you?
Yes, live for me...
The moment when I can be myself the most.
Isn't that so wonderful?
Really?
It's the best.
I'm sure the fans are really happy about that.
I wonder.
I see. It's the moment You can be yourself.
Then what do you think?
What do you think is the hardest part of your job?
What kind of moment is that in your work?
It's ...
I think it's very difficult to control myself.
In this job, I think that.
There's a switch, isn't there?
It doesn't have to be inside out.
It's a switch that you can understand.
what your true self is like.
There are moments when I do.
And it's in those moments...
When I stand on stage at a live performance.
I can look at myself in a new light.
I realize that I love to sing.
I like to express myself this way.
I feel like I can really feel myself as I am.
I feel like I can feel my true self.
I always feel like I can switch off
That's where I can switch off the switch that I'm really here,
I see.
I see...
When you're on stage.
You're really cool.
Of course everyone know, it goes without saying.
I don't think so.
(Momoda) On the contrary, I wonder if this is the case.
In many ways.
In the midst of so many difficult things like this
I wonder...
I wonder what...
I wonder.
The girls who quit idols...
I mean, there are a lot of girls who are graduating.
Did you ever have a moment when you thought about that?
Well...
Like when I'm standing on stage.
When I'm working.
I've never thought like that.
But when I had a serious illness.
I felt like...
I wondered if it was really okay for me to be here.
More than anything, I felt like I was causing trouble for everyone.
I hated it so much.
So I wondered if I should quit.
But then I realized that Member made me think again.
They made me think again.
They're always thinking about me as if I were their own.
They're always thinking about me.
I talked to the members.
I remembered the conversations I had with Member.
I don't know.
They don't want me to quit because I feel like I'm causing trouble.
It's not right.
It's not.
And if I really want to keep stay.
Then I should work hard to heal and continue.
I made up my mind.
And that's how I ended up here.
I love being an idol!
That's right, I'm sure no one had thought that you give them any trouble
But for Aya...
I'm sure you want to be careful.
I can imagine what it's like to be absent.
When I'm absent...
I wonder how the members will fill in the gaps
That's why I can imagine various things.
I'm sure that's why you felt like you might cause trouble.
But I was so happy to see you back and perform with Ebichu the other day.
I was really happy.
I thought you were really cool.
I thought you were coming back even more powerful.
I'm sure.
There's a lot of effort behind the scenes that we can't see.
There's a lot of hard work behind the scenes that we can't see.
inside of you.
I'm sure there are many things
I'm sure you've made a lot of preparations.
The courage to stand on the stage again
Your strength.
The strength that got you through so many things.
It's really all really shines through in Aya's heart.
I thought it was so cool.
I'm glad.
I really felt that.
That made me think I have to work harder too.
Standing on stage again...
With a new feeling...
I remember the feeling I had when I started as an idol.
It was a fresh feeling from the bottom of my heart.
Standing on stage like this...
Performing, with all the fans watching me.
to be in this warm atmosphere.
I felt so happy.
Idol is the best! I think.
Right! Idols are the best!
A miracle on a hot day.
What you say makes me happy.
I'm sure it makes your fans very happy.
There's a lot to being an idol.
It's not all about fun.
That's why being able to truly enjoy something like this
It makes me happy to hear that you can enjoy yourself.
Well, something about your ideal
Is there anything that you want to be like, what kind of idol you want to be like?
Is there something you want to be?
Well...
I wonder...
After all the special part of the idol
I think it's the sparkle.
I can really cheer myself up watching them.
They give me a sparkling bright future
I think idols give me a bright future.
That's what I really think.
I want to keep that in mind while
I'm trying to be myself.
I want to be able to be close to the people who are watching me.
I'd like to be able to empathize with them.
I'd like to be that kind of person.
How wonderful.
The color of the group you're in, Ebichu...
The color of the group you're in...
It's unique.
Ebichu's unique way of delivering messages...
I'm sure it's there are something that we
There are things that Momoclo can't do.
It's not like that...
It's always raining when you guys performing.
It's hard to find a group like that.
That's true.
Every time.
It's the same festival.
Even when we do...
Only during Ebichu's time.
It's like it's always pouring rain.
I've seen so many miracles.
Yeah, that's right.
We've witnessed a lot.
Many preparation on the backstage like your make up.
I've seen it all.
All of that work went down in an instant.
I've witnessed the moment when all those hard work is torn apart by the rain.
.
But it's also really cool to see you keep singing in such a situation.
It's really cool.
The moment I saw that...
I can't help but think, "Wow, this is Ebichu!"
I hope they'll be fine.
I know it's a lot of work with broken microphone (due to the rain).
I wonder how it even feels like it's on your side
It's true, it's better if it rains.
It turns me on.
That's for sure.
When it rains that much...
A cool idol with makeup removed.
When i work so hard at everything.
All those energy
I've been influenced by what Momoclo has been doing for so long.
You've been working really hard since You were little.
I've always thought of idols
as being cute
Yeah, I was the same way.
When I saw Momoclo the first time
You all drenched in sweat. so sweaty that makeup comes off.
Seeing idols working so hard...
I realized there were idols this cool.
I was really impressed.
I always thought this wasn't the idol I had imagined to be.
Oh, really?
I always drenched in sweat, no matter what I looked like.
No matter what I'm in, even if I'm on DVD, I'm not pretty.
But all those full power.
made you both so cute and cool.
I'm really happy to hear you say that.
Discussions and fights
In Ebichu, do you have serious talks among the members?
Like talk about the future.
Is there a moment when you do this?
In the past, we didn't really discuss things.
We're a group of caring girls.
That's the image I have of everyone.
It's hard for me to express myself well.
There are a lot of girls who are a little clumsy at expressing themselves.
It's a bit of reading an atmosphere.
That's how it is now.
During the episodes, or when all the members are feeling this way...
I interpreted it on my own.
Then was moving forward.
But after we becoming 6 member
We started talking to each other a lot.
I see.
There are things you don't understand unless we talk about them.
But when we've been together for a long time.
I think I can tell by the atmosphere.
But still, there are many things we can only understand after talking.
I realized that there's a lot we can learn only by talking.
I'm still not very good at it, but I started talking to everyone.
I see.
How about Momoclo
Have you been having discussions since you were little?
Yes, we do.
We don't usually have serious discussions.
But if it is an important moment.
The moments that we all need to talk about...
I've always tried to talk with everyone.
Yes, everyone's thoughts.
After listening to everyone's thoughts and feelings, we finally come to a decision together.
I try to give an answer as much as possible.
I try to come up with an answer.
There are times when the answer doesn't come out right away.
Sometimes it doesn't come out right away, but sometimes it does.
How can we get closer to that ideal?
Do we talk about everything and make decisions like this?
We always decide when it's important.
Have you ever fight?
No, we don't really have fights.
Oh, that's right. When we discuss things like that ...
I'm afraid of getting into a fight.
That's why I can't do it most of the time.
I don't think we've ever had a fight.
There are so many different opinions that come out.
Everyone has to accept that.
You have to be open to it.
And the whole group thinks about what to do.
We think about it as a group.
I don't think we get into fights.
We exchange opinions, of course.
Like "I think this one is better than that"
Or, "I think this is better.
That kind of thing.
But...
But Reni and Arin fight every day for fun.
Not like playful fights, but like sibling rivalry.
Something like, "Didn't you eat this? Didn't you eat my portion?
Yes, They do that all the time.
I don't know what that was.
Something like a hairstyle
When they're deciding on a hairstyle like, "don't do it because i'm doing it"
"Why not? Like, you can wear your hair however you want."
Really like sisters.
Yeah, like sisters.
It's nice to be so close
(Yeah, it's best if we're close.
But as we age...
there are parts that don't change for the better, and parts that do.
And There's a lot that changes.
But in the end, yeah.
We're a group.
It's really nice to be able to get along with everyone.
That's true.
Yakiniku...
We've talked so much
Thank you so much for calling.
It's my pleasure.
If there's any other time...
Of course, just call me.
Really is it okay?
Of course
I'm so happy.
I'm waiting. I don't think it's ever rung.
I'm messing around with my mobile phone
I'll call you when things settle down.
I'd like to go out to dinner with you.
After all Yakiniku
Let's eat yakiniku
Let's go out for yakiniku
Please be careful about your physical condition and do your best.
Thanks, You too. Take care.
Thank you
It was really nice talking to you today.
I'll call you later.
You've got it, I'll call you too
I'll call you too.
I'll see you later.