Wow
What a lonely child
The onslaught isn't over yet!
I'm nervous and Linni is getting
appears.
Hello?
What?
Aya-chan?
Is this Kanako-chan?
This is Momota.
Really?
Aya-chan, how are you?
I'm fine.
How are you recently?
Recently? I'm doing well and having fun.
You're doing well and having fun?
Yeah.
We've been together for a long time.
It's been a while since our debut,
right?
Yeah.
Our debut is close, right?
But we haven't talked much, right?
That's right.
It's hard to be together on the spot.
At the end of the year,
I'm on the first or second floor of the
building.
That's right.
And I'm really nervous.
I'm a little shy, so I can't talk much.
There's no good or bad person for me
like me.
I don't think I've talked much on the
spot.
That's right.
I'm nervous, too.
I'm so happy.
I've always wanted to talk to you in
person.
I'm sorry.
I've heard from other staff members and
makeup artists that Aya-chan wanted to
talk to me.
字幕提供者の提供者の方々にお願いいたします。
That's right.
Why?
It's been about five years since I said
I wanted to talk to Kanako-chan like
that.
Five years?
That's a long time.
Why?
I wonder why.
I think everyone who is an idol of
STARDUST will think that Kanako-chan is
a real idol.
I think she is a big leader of STAPLA.
As a leader who brings the group
together,
I feel like I'm just right for her.
I'm happy. Really?
I haven't done anything.
This year? You contacted me a few months
ago, right?
Yes, yes.
I was very happy about that.
Really?
Yes.
I haven't met my juniors that much.
But Ebichu-chan is not my junior.
Ebichu-chan always says that she is my
junior.
We've been doing it together since the
same time.
No, no.
We have the feeling that we are
colleagues.
But I wonder what it is.
I think it's the idol image of Star Dust
that Momokuro-chan created.
Our fans, at first, said they liked
Momokuro-chan.
But fans came to see us.
There were many things like that.
Em изучie la WWE 3rd cereal by
Konobinobi.
Momokura-chan made the foundation for us
to start our career as idols.
No, it's not like that. We made it
together.
Really? You're saying that?
Lately, we've been able to do a lot of
things, even for live performances.
I think it's great to have live
performances.
We did live performances together the
other day.
What do you think about live
performances?
Live performances?
The moment I feel like I'm myself.
Isn't it amazing?
Really?
It's the best.
I think the fans will be very happy.
Really?
Hmm. I see. It's the moment when you
become who you are.
So, what do you think is the hardest
part?
When you're working?
I think it's really hard to control
yourself.
I think it's hard to control myself.
There's a switch, right?
Yeah.
It's not like holding the back.
It's like switching the switch.
I wonder what my true self is like.
I get worried and tired.
I feel like that.
But when I'm on stage, I feel like I'm
on stage.
I can look back at myself.
I can feel that I like singing.
I like to express myself like this.
I can feel my true self.
I always use my own switch.
I can switch the switch.
But Ayaka on stage is really cool.
I think everyone knows that.
No, no.
But on the other hand, there are many
things.
There are many hard things.
I wonder what it is.
There are many idols who quit their
idol.
There are many idols who graduated from
the idol.
Did you have a moment to think about
that?
Well, when I was on stage or when I was
working,
I never thought about it,
but when I got sick,
I thought, is it really okay to be here?
I hate that I'm bothering everyone.
So I sometimes think that I should stop.
But at that time, I was reminded of the
existence of the members.
I feel like gotten used to, but somehow
respect too much.
でも、自分のことのように私のことを考えてくれたりしてるメンバーと話したり、メンバ
ーとの会話を思い出したりして、
迷惑かけてるからやめるとか、そういうのは逆にみんなに申し訳ないというか、違うんだ
なって、ちゃんと思い直せて。
それで本当に自分がやりたいって思うなら、頑張って直して絶対続けようって決心して、
今に至るって感じです。
そっか、そうだよね、みんなは絶対迷惑とか、絶対は思ってないけど、あやちゃんとして
はやっぱりこう。
I'm sure you'll use your feelings, and
you can imagine a lot of things about
the period of rest.
When I was resting, the members filled
in the missing positions, and I'm sure
you can imagine a lot of things.
I think it's an euxic process that ruins
everything being epidemic stemning, but
I think it's okay to be hurt.
I was really happy to see Aya-chan on
stage.
I thought she was cool.
I thought she was getting even more
powerful.
Really.
I'm sure it's because I have a lot of
unseeable effort behind me.
I'm sure I've been prepared for a lot of
things.
I'm standing on stage again.
The courage and the strength.
The strength to overcome a lot of
things.
I think you are shining so beautifully.
I think you are so cool.
I'm so happy.
I really think so.
I also think I have to work hard.
I feel like I'm on the stage again.
I remember the feeling.
It's a very fresh feeling.
From the bottom of my heart, I feel like
I'm on stage and performing.
I'm really happy and happy to see the
warm atmosphere of the fans.
I feel like that.
I thought idols were the best.
Idols are the best.
Really.
And I think the fans are really happy
about what Aya-chan says.
Of course, idols are not only fun
things.
That's why I think idols are fun from
the bottom of my heart.
I'm happy to hear that.
Do you have any ideal?
I think idols are fun.
I think the special part is the sparkly
part.
I think idols are idols who can get a
pure energy and a bright future.
I want to aujourday's training be
valuable to old One Пр
I want to be able to understand each
other, to be able to share feelings with
each other.
I think it's good.
Yeah.
It's wonderful.
The color of the group of Ebichu-chan is
unique.
There are many things that we can't do
for Momokuro.
I don't see many groups that are always
on live shows.
You're right.
Every time we go to the same festival,
we see coins that are too loud during
our daily activities.
That's right.
We see a lot of miracles.
We are also...
They are watching us.
Yes.
We are watching from the point that we
are making up.
The moment that we make up so much and
take it off with the rain.
We are already in the middle of it.
But the way she sings in that situation
is also very cool.
The moment I saw that, I thought this
was the ring.
I think she's like, please let me go.
Mike is also very difficult.
I think so, but I feel like I'm even on
her side.
I think so.
I think it's better if it rains, so the
switch turns on.
I think so too. If it rains that much.
I think that Momokuro has been
influenced by the fact that she has been
working hard and doing everything with
all her might.
I've been working really hard since I
was little.
I had a strong image of idols as cute,
but...
I was like that too.
That's right. When I first saw Momokuro,
I was sweating so much that I could take
off my makeup.
I saw idols working so hard and I was
really influenced by them.
I thought that I wasn't the idol that I
imagined.
Really?
I mean, I'm sweating.
I look cute in everything, even in DVDs.
But you're so cute and cool.
I'm so happy that you said that.
Do you have any moments when you talk
about serious things or future things
with the members?
I didn't talk to them in the past.
I think I talked to them in the past.
There are a lot of people who are very
careful.
Yeah, everyone has that kind of image.
There are a lot of people who are not
good at expressing themselves.
They are kind of reading the atmosphere
and thinking,
I wonder if this is how it feels now.
I wonder if the members and Bichua feel
the same way.
I was interpreting it myself and moving
forward.
After I became six,
I started talking to people.
Oh, I see.
There are things that you don't know
unless you talk to them.
I think you can understand it by the
atmosphere if you stay longer.
But I realized that there are many
things that I can understand for the
first time after talking to them.
I'm still not good at it, but I want to
talk to you all.
I see.
Have you been talking to each other
since you were little?
We don't usually talk seriously, but
I've been talking to you all about the
most important moments.
I've been talking to everyone.
I see.
I've been listening to everyone's
thoughts.
After listening to that, I've been
trying to find the answer to the
question,
which is, what should we do?
Sometimes, I can't find the answer
immediately.
But then, what should we do?
thickness, how to get closer to alcohol,
which i wanted to full chrome. Talking
bodying me Oh Yeah. Too squeaky,
I really don't have a fight.
Oh, really?
When you talk to each other,
I'm afraid that you might get into a
fight.
I see.
Yeah, there are a lot of things I can't
do.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But I don't think I've ever had a fight.
I see.
Yeah.
I get a lot of opinions.
I think it's a group that everyone can
accept.
I don't think there's much to argue
about.
Of course, there are opinions that can
be exchanged.
I think it's better to have a different
opinion.
But I think it's better to have a
different opinion.
That's true. But...
Remy and Arin fight every day.
Like siblings.
It's like a brother's fight.
Oh, you ate this. You ate my share.
I've been doing that all the time.
Oh, really?
I've been doing it all the time today.
That's... what was it?
When I decide on a hairstyle, I'm like,
Ah, you're going to do that, so don't do
it.
Why? You can do your favorite hairstyle.
You're really like sisters.
Yeah, like sisters.
Oh, you're close.
Yeah, that's the best thing about being
close.
But as you get older, you have a lot of
things that don't change in a good way.
That's right.
でも結局ね、グループでやってるから、みんなで仲良くできるのが本当一番いいよね。
そうですよね。
そうね。
ってな感じで。
もう、そろそろ。
You've spoken a lot.
Right?
Thank you so much for calling me.
You're welcome.
If you have another chance, can I call
you?
Of course. Call me in private.
Really?
Of course.
I'm happy.
I know. I don't think I'll ever call
you.
I'm always nervous. I'm staring at my
phone.
Call me anytime.
I will. I want to have dinner with you
when I calm down.
What are you going to eat?
I'm going to eat grilled meat.
Oh, grilled meat? OK. Let's eat grilled
meat. Let's go eat grilled meat.
Please. Thank you.
Please take care of yourself and do your
best. Thank you.
Aya-chan, take care of yourself. Thank
you.
I was really happy to talk to you today.
I'll contact you later.
Yeah, contact me again. I'll contact
you.
Thank you. See you later.
See you later.
OK. See you later.
Bye-bye.
indicate a