all rights reserved. copyright © 2018
Kinoshita Yuka
Good evening!
Yeah!
We are in the car.
Thank you for watching!
It's a day trip and...
...a day trip...
No, no, no.
We watched Hinoeri and Hinode on the
same day yesterday.
We are on the way to that day.
Yes.
We are in the car.
We watched it.
How was it?
It was fun.
It was like a normal trip.
We enjoyed it.
Hinode was beautiful.
Yes, she was.
It was impressive.
How was it?
We often shoot with GoPro.
We didn't have it before.
We didn't have it.
We shot a lot of cute scenes.
I know.
Meow.
And...
I love Yamagata prefecture.
It was a good place.
I want to go there again.
I'm glad we could go around.
It's good.
We knew many places.
It was nostalgic.
I love Yamagata.
It was a new year's day.
It's the first military service in the
new year.
It's amazing.
It's a new year's day.
In the new year, we eat different things
at home.
What did you eat?
Mochi, zoni,
How about osechi?
Zoni.
My grandmother makes chawanmushi.
My grandmother's homemade chawanmushi.
What do you have?
I eat matsumaezuke.
I know.
It's amazing.
It's a new year's day.
I feel the new year.
I eat it every year.
I eat ikura in kamaboko.
The one with meat.
I eat edamame and kazunoko.
You make it yourself.
It's amazing.
New year's day.
I feel it.
At the end of last year, we had a lot of
events.
I didn't have much time.
It's the end of the year.
It's over today.
Thank you for watching.
It was a little bit noisy but it was
amazing.
Good job.
I used to do this at home every year.
There was a game in my house.
It was a national ranking.
I couldn't sleep until I got into the
top 10.
What?
It sounds fun.
I did it every year.
Isn't it amazing?
At first, everyone sings the song they
want to sing.
It was too hard to sleep.
I sang a core song.
On the contrary.
That's right.
I didn't do it this year.
Really?
I played a board game called Donjara.
I played that.
I don't know.
It's a good story.
Donjara.
I was addicted to Donjara.
I asked the captain if I could play
Donjara with goods.
I thought it would be fun.
Isn't it too much?
Donjara has a role and a character.
Is that so?
I thought it would be fun to make a role
for each member.
It sounds fun.
I asked if I could play it.
I thought it wouldn't sell.
Did you do it with a message?
It's fun.
Please tell everyone.
If everyone's voice is there.
I thought it was a mahjong-like thing.
Really?
It's like mahjong.
Please subscribe to the channel.
Yeah, that's right.
Let's do it next time.
I want to do it.
It's really fun.
Really?
It looks fun.
I'll be 20 this year.
Oh, that's right.
Yeah.
Zero-three-nine.
Zero-three.
So I don't want to be an adult.
I want to do a lot of things that can
only be done by minors.
It's the last T.
Teenagers and 20s are totally different.
So, we want to do things that can only
be done by teens.
Like watching the same day as the date
yesterday.
You can't do this without being a
teenager.
It was fun.
First, we came to see the sunrise.
It was cold, wasn't it?
It was cold.
I thought I would freeze.
It was so cold that Karen started
running.
How was it? Did you warm up?
It was cold even when I ran.
The wind was deep.
The weather forecast was very hot.
I was hoping.
I wore three heattechs.
I wore a back kimono.
I wore this in Gunnai.
It was cold.
It was amazing.
There were many young people around us.
I was surprised by that.
Everyone was fine.
I thought everyone was fine.
It was good.
Next is Kokeshi.
Yes.
Sakunami Onsen.
Kokeshi.
It was big.
I was surprised.
I took a video as soon as I woke up.
You were sleeping.
I was sleeping.
I didn't know why I was here.
You were sleeping.
I woke up and took a video of Kokeshi.
Yes.
Based on this story, it may be different
if you watch the video again.
I usually take a video when I'm awake.
I'm sorry.
It seems that Shinju-san woke up while I
was sleeping.
Yes, in one hand.
I see! Thank you!
That's right!
Thank you!
I can't raise my head.
I raised it.
Thank you.
Say anything from now on.
I will respect you.
Really.
I see.
Thank you.
After seeing the sunset, we saw the
waterfall.
It was amazing.
It was so mysterious.
It was more amazing than I thought.
And it's not winter, so you can see it
closer.
There are stars, so you can see it from
there.
I want to come again.
I want to swim.
You said something amazing.
The shop next to it was delicious.
It was really delicious.
It was like a Kyoro-Kyoro.
The texture of the hair.
I understand.
I didn't feel anything.
It was elastic.
Yes, it was.
It was delicious.
I felt the mountain over there.
I felt it.
I like the exterior.
There is a kotatsu inside.
I think we can eat it.
I want to do it again.
I think it's wonderful.
Next, we went to the signboard of Shogi.
It was big.
I like that.
I like miniature.
I like realistic things.
I like it.
It was cute.
There is a big model of Shogi in ION.
I want to go there.
I've never been there.
Please subscribe to this channel.
I wanted to go to a soba restaurant in
Suisha before that.
But the restaurant was too crowded and I
couldn't film there.
I was disappointed.
I wanted to eat there someday.
The exterior was amazing.
I felt Japan.
I felt like I was in a retro TV show in
Suisha.
I like that place.
I want to live there.
I want to see the ninja.
I agree.
I want to do it again.
But the place we ate was delicious.
I can't forget it.
The noodles were great.
It was chewy.
The seasoning was good, and the one he
was saying was a mitsuba.
It's a little embarrassing.
It's a little embarrassing, but it was
delicious.
There were a lot of vegetables.
It's true. Bamboo shoots and shiitake
mushrooms.
There's a lot of volume in the first
place.
The staff said there were a lot of
mountains.
It's definitely Japanese.
It's an interesting culture.
It's true.
There were many.
Everyone can be satisfied.
But it's delicious.
I feel like I can eat it.
I want to eat it right away.
I'm sure it's going to be good.
It was a good time.
See you later.
Oh, I forgot to put it there.
I forgot to put it.
It was a little awkward for us to eat
alternately.
We wanted to eat together and taste
delicious food.
So we put it there and went straight to
the Japan Sea.
We could have left it here.
We were already sleeping.
We arrived at the Japan Sea.
It was raining before we started
shooting.
So we had an umbrella here.
We stopped the rain. That was a good
thing.
It's been a while since we had a sunset.
I think you could see it.
I felt the sunset.
After that, we were going to make a sea
by mixing the sea of Japan and the sea
of Pacific Ocean.
But, we were caught in a big trouble.
I was a little bit excited.
When I noticed, the sea of Pacific Ocean
was gone.
There was only gravel.
I'm sorry that you were shy while we
were going out.
I'm sorry that I was sleeping all the
time.
I'm sorry.
I think it's a good thing that you were
able to sleep there.
You're so kind.
Thanks to the staff's help, I was able
to sleep.
It's a good thing.
I'm going to take it to the agency.
Let's decorate it.
I wonder if everyone will drink it by
mistake.
I think I'll drink it.
I think I'll drink it around my right.
I have to write it down.
That's right.
There's a fishing port nearby.
I wanted to go.
I found it when I looked it up.
It's a jellyfish.
It's a beautiful jellyfish aquarium.
I want to go.
The aquarium is nice.
I want to go there again.
I really want to go to Yamagata again.
I want to go to Yamagata.
It's a good place.
Yes.
I think it's a really good place.
I'm glad to know that I can introduce
such a place to people.
There are so many good things.
Where do you want to go next?
I see.
I want to go to Akita.
Me too.
Akita is good.
I want to go there.
I really want to go there.
I think it's a nice place to go.
I think it's hidden more.
I want to go there.
I haven't been to Aomori as a band.
I want to go there as a band.
Thank you for today.
It was fun.
It was a dry battle.
I want to do it again.
Please look forward to it.
We'll do our best.
See you later.
Bye.