Ebi-chu's video!
Rikonoheya, the third!
How are you?
This time, the third, no, the third,
Today's guest is
Today, March 29, 22 years old?
22 years old?
I think it's 23 years old.
It's 22 years old.
Hina-to Kashiwagi-san came.
I'm Hina-to Kashiwagi.
I'm 22 years old.
On the day, you're doing a live solo.
It's almost noon.
Just after watching this.
That's right. From 15 o'clock.
From 15 o'clock?
I'm sorry.
I thought it was a little earlier.
So, on your birthday, there's one thing
I'd like to ask you first.
What is it?
What's your goal this year?
My goal this year?
That's right.
Even if I set a goal every year,
I don't want to be considered.
I'm the type to think a little.
I want to be healthy and smile this
year.
Health is important.
I think it's important.
How are you today?
I'm fine today.
Imagine yourself on the 29th.
What do you think it's like now?
You're rehearsing for the SETAN solo
live.
I think so.
Is the content of the performance
different?
That's right. The set list is different.
Where did you start?
Nagoya.
On the 15th.
Osaka was on the 16th.
Or is the Tokyo performance a little
different?
It's really a little different.
The composition is a little different.
I'm looking forward to it.
Everyone, please celebrate the 22-year-
old Kashiwaki today.
Please celebrate.
Kashiwaki is a little...
I'm sorry.
The members say that you have a good
personal life.
If you take a day off, you often go to
karaoke.
What would you do if you had a week off?
I'm not sure.
Next time, I'll ask you what you'd do if
you had a year off.
So, a week.
Can you tell me the previous question?
You actually had a week off, didn't you?
You didn't have a job, but you had a
whole week off.
I went on a family trip that week.
What if you had a week off?
I see.
I'd been going to karaoke every week for
the past week.
I couldn't waste any time on that.
But when I was thinking about what to do
for the next three days,
I'd watch a lot of videos on the
internet.
What do you watch?
You don't watch Korean dramas, do you?
No, I don't.
What do you watch?
I watch documentaries.
I can laugh at them over and over again.
I want to be in the show.
You're drawn into the show.
I watch those.
I watch funny videos.
I watch the ones I like.
I don't watch dramas.
I think I watch Hildora.
I love Hildora.
I've been watching it since I met you.
I watch it again.
If you had a year off, would you go out?
If you had a year off, would you go
around Japan?
It's a moment.
Really?
Yes, I would go around Japan.
I want to go to Hokkaido, Okinawa,
and...
I want to go to the island.
I don't have the ability to speak
English yet.
It's a little difficult to go abroad
alone.
But if I could go around Japan in a
year,
I would take someone to go abroad.
I would go on a trip.
I understand.
I often go to the toilet of the store.
I often travel around the world.
I will be in Japan when I graduate from
MC.
I promised my mom that I would go to the
gym.
That's right.
The poster is different depending on the
company, so I always compare where is
cheaper.
It seems that it is faster to go to the
gym online.
You always have a toilet.
Yes, I have a toilet.
I'm looking forward to it.
My current hairstyle is short.
It's changed a lot.
Does it suddenly change?
When I suddenly got short from twin
tails in 2013, I suddenly wanted to cut
it.
I cut it, but it didn't continue after
all.
But now I can't arrange it for short
hair.
Now I can do various things.
I don't want to grow it now.
You enjoy short hair now.
Do you really want to have a long hair?
I really want to have a long hair.
I want to have a long hair.
Is it okay to have a long hair?
I want to have a long hair once.
I want to have an orange sherbet.
Is it a sherbet?
Isn't it cute?
I don't know.
I think it's a little different if you
look good on you.
It's a cute color.
It's cute.
It's like the color of ice cream.
Is that why it's sherbet?
Yes, it's like an orange sherbet.
I think it's cute.
I think I'll make an orange sherbet
someday.
Someday?
It's really embarrassing.
I think some of Hinata's fans will also
do it.
Orange is amazing.
It's easy to find.
I think it's coming from my head.
I think I'll have it.
Please look forward to it.
I think I'll do it someday.
Next is the third question.
Who came first?
Rika came first.
You forgot.
Next is Hina.
I'm asking the cast's name every time.
I don't know the left and right names.
Zayu no mei?
Yeah.
Eh?
It sounds like a gag.
It's not Zayu no mei.
It just came out.
Y.
Y.M.
Wait.
A? Is it A? Is it E?
Y.M.A.
You are my angel.
What?
I want to be your angel.
Oh!
You want to be your angel?
But it's not my character.
I want to be your angel.
It's embarrassing.
Yui-tsu-mu-ni.
Oh, there is.
I didn't say that.
Yui-tsu-mu-ni.
I'm not serious.
I'm so stupid.
I'm embarrassed.
I didn't get A or E.
I forgot.
There is.
Yui-tsu-mu-ni.
Everyone is Yui-tsu-mu-ni.
There is no other person.
You can't be the only one.
You can only be yourself.
Everyone is Yui-tsu-mu-ni.
You are my angel.
You are Y-M-N.
It's funny.
I want you to put all the time you've
been thinking about.
It's going to be long.
Yui-tsu-mu-ni.
No.
I'm sorry.
You're the only one.
You're wearing a pair of earrings.
I'm wearing earrings.
That's also a change of heart.
I've been saying this for a long time.
I've been dancing since I was in
elementary school.
I was going to open it at that time.
I was going to open it when I was in
elementary school.
I decided to enter the shrimp
At that stage, I decided to enter the
shrimp.
I can't open it at the right time.
I thought.
I couldn't open it.
I've always wanted to open it.
I was wondering when I'd do it.
I think I'll do it all.
I started dyeing my hair, and I did it
when I was over 20 years old.
I thought it would be nice if I could do
it when I was over 20 years old.
I asked if it was okay.
I think there are probably two or three
types of people.
Next, here.
Really?
It's a lie.
Here?
No.
I'm sorry.
If you open it, make a costume that
suits me.
You're a cow.
Cow?
It's not this year, it's the year of the
cow.
Do you want to do it?
Me?
Do you do this before you open your
ears?
Riku, sorry.
Who?
Mire is a cow woman.
Because I'm a cow woman.
Mire.
It means the year of the cow.
Cow.
Old woman.
Mire.
Please do it to Mire.
Cow woman.
That's right.
That's all.
Is there anything you want to try?
I'm serious.
What I want to try is...
I want to do a band formation for the
first time.
I think it's good to see the
instruments.
I think so.
I'm going to lose.
I got a job application.
The amount of work I've done so far
hasn't changed much.
But I've been getting more and more days
off.
I want to do it.
I want to play drums.
Did you buy it?
I didn't buy it.
Do you have a drum set?
I didn't go that far.
I bought a drum stick and a practice
pad.
I looked it up and thought it would be
good for beginners to practice like
this.
I'm not good at it.
I'm not good at it, but I'm practicing
alone.
I'm doing this.
I don't know how many years it will take
me to play the drums.
I'm looking forward to playing the
instrument.
I want to study the rhythm of music.
It's the best.
I've never heard of this before.
Thank you for the introduction.
Thank you.
This is a secret.
I've already released it.
This is not a secret.
I don't know when it will be real.
I don't know how many years it will be.
I've been doing it well.
I hope I can perform in front of you
someday.
I hope I can sing the song of AB-CHU.
If you can go to a candy locker, it's
cool.
Today's guest was Hinata Kashiwagi.
Thank you very much.
It was fun.
Who will come next time?
Please look forward to it.