The end
That's all for today.
We were the sweet potato girls.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
Aki-chan,
today's sweet potato girls were also
fun.
Yes.
I'm really happy that we can
work for the sweet potato tonight.
I was just talking about the sweet
potato,
but I'm hungry.
By the way,
there was a gift for the sweet potato
that I thought I'd eat after the show.
That's right.
I want to eat it quickly.
Let's go.
Sweet potato.
There's only one sweet potato.
What?
There were six, right?
There were six members, right?
There was definitely six.
Tell me you're lying.
Julia-chan.
You're lying, right? Julia-chan.
Aki-chan, calm down.
Why is there only one sweet potato?
There were definitely six when I first
saw it, right?
That's definitely strange.
Did someone eat two?
That's not true, is it?
I don't think everyone would do that.
But there's no sweet potato.
There's no sweet potato that should have
been there.
What should I do?
Why are you speaking in Kansai dialect?
Anyway, I don't want to doubt it,
but let's start with Haru-chan, who's in
the room now.
We're the famous detective,
Julia Aki.
Let's go.
I know.
I'm sad, but I can't help it.
Let's ask Haru-chan.
I'm going to ask her.
This ramen looks delicious.
Soy sauce or pork cutlet?
Maybe it's not.
Aki-chan, Haru-chan is easy.
She's a little messy.
Let's go ask her.
Good job, Haru-chan.
Good job.
She's a sweet potato girl.
She's cute.
Haru-chan, did you eat today?
I ate.
I also ate baked sweet potatoes.
It was so sweet and delicious.
One baked sweet potato?
One.
It's obvious.
I like to eat, but I don't like it that
much.
That's right.
Let's find out what she likes.
I got it.
I'm Suda Aki.
Two sweet people like sweet potatoes
came.
How cute they are.
They are really cute.
These boiled eggs are cute.
I'm wearing a new T-shirt again.
This time, I'm wearing a T-shirt that
aims for the stars.
I'm looking at such a cute girl.
I'm becoming a star.
This time, all seven colors.
The design is glittering.
It's wonderful.
I want this T-shirt soon.
What are these two people?
Sweet potato girl is cute.
Purple and lemon.
I like the color of the sweet potato.
I want to eat another sweet potato when
I see them.
But there were only six.
I can't eat all of them.
Everyone, I like to eat.
But I can eat them all.
Don't worry.
I'm hungry.
Aki, you're not Oharu.
I think it's different.
Is it different?
Where are Hito and Hiyori?
I ate sweet potatoes with them.
I'm going to shoot now.
I think Hiyori will be back soon.
I'm going to eat ramen.
You like ramen.
I see.
So, Hito and Kanamin only eat one.
Chiriya, Hiyori is back.
Let's eat.
Hiyori, have you eaten sweet potatoes?
Sweet potatoes?
It was very delicious.
Have you eaten sweet potatoes?
No, I'm going to eat sweet potatoes.
Aki, now.
Leave it to me.
Suda Suda Suda Suda
Don't imitate Hiyori.
Suda Aki
Warabi Mochi Mochi
I can't.
No, it's not.
It's okay.
Suda Aki
I didn't know.
I know.
It seems that no one has eaten two.
The truth is still a mystery.
But after all,
That sweet potato looked delicious.
That's right.
The sweet potato is delicious.
It's delicious.
It's a sweet potato.
Sweet potato
Sweet potatoes in the corner.
Hello.
Can't you hear me?
What is this?
What time is it?
Why are you singing while looking at me?
It's horror.
It's too scary.
Staff, it's too scary.
Please stop.
I can't sleep.
But if you look closely,
Your eyes are sparkling and cute.
What?
I don't think my heart is broken.
No, it's not broken.
Maybe I'm just singing naturally.
I'm just looking at you.
I don't know.
What should I do?
There is only one sweet potato.
Is it okay for such a sad thing to
happen?
We love sweet potatoes so much.
Don't you love us?
What should I do?
Please tell me.
What should we do?
What?
What is this?
That's right.
Didn't you eat it in about 3 seconds?
I ate it.
Please.
Let's share our feelings.
T-shirt for the new year.