Yakan and Idol
I love carbohydrates.
I didn't realize that I loved rice.
When I ate lunch with my members, I
realized that I ate more rice than
others.
I see.
I eat rice in my lunch box.
I eat rice as a side dish.
This is a story that fans can't stand.
I'm a fan of men.
Why do you like men?
I love men.
I want to have rice.
I'm glad.
I like salt rice balls.
There are rice balls shops in
convenience stores.
I see.
There are salt rice balls in convenience
stores.
I will definitely buy salt rice balls.
What kind of salt rice ball do you like?
I like rice.
You like rice.
I've heard that you like cooking.
You like cooking.
You like rice.
I like rice.
I love rice.
Do you have a particular taste in
cooking?
I like all kinds of rice.
All kinds of rice?
I think you have a particular taste in
cooking.
I think all kinds of rice are delicious.
I like cold rice.
I like freshly cooked rice.
I see.
I don't have a particular taste in rice.
I like rice.
Really?
I have a particular taste in rice.
I see.
I like Gifu-ken's rice.
It's very delicious.
What is that?
I see.
It's called Gifu-ken's Mikazuki.
It's a cool name.
It's a good rice.
I think you like rice.
What?
I noticed it later.
I noticed it when I grew up.
When did you notice it?
I used to eat a high-quality meal at
work.
It's a good job to eat a high-quality
meal.
I ate a high-quality meal with my
colleagues.
Did you eat a high-quality meal at a
meal party?
I ate a high-quality meal at a meal
party.
It was a restaurant in Aichi Prefecture.
I ate a high-quality meal with a rice
cooked in a kiln.
It was called Gifu-ken's Mikazuki.
I thought it was delicious.
I searched for it and told my mother.
I found it on the floor of my kitchen.
Really?
I found it when I got home.
I thought I was particular about it.
You are particular about it.
Yes.
What is your secret technique?
I'm a type of person who sleeps with a
bad mood.
I have a secret technique.
This program is brought to you by
Pyonkichi,
Azuma,
Slave,
Isshii,
and Otomo.
Today, I feel like eating hot pot.
Bye bye!