I'm going to challenge the 10 spiciest
ones
I'm here to eat curry
I'm going to challenge the 10 spiciest
ones
Are you going to eat them?
I'm not sure if I can eat spicy food
I think you can eat normal food
I'm not good at eating spicy food
I'm going to challenge it
I'm scared
Please subscribe!
Itadakimasu
I've never tried Hachi before
Hachi is in the middle of recording
There is a place near the recording
place
I've been there twice
I've been eating Hachi Kara at that time
It looks delicious
What did you put on top?
I put cheese
I don't know where the cheese is
It's already melted
It smells good
Sausage and spinach
You are a senior
I didn't know that
I didn't know that there was this
I didn't know
Itadakimasu
The color is different
I want to taste it
It's delicious
The color of curry is different
I don't want to show it
Itadakimasu
I'll start with Roo
It's spicy as usual!
It's not 10 spicy!
What?
Why?
You're kidding!
It's gonna be spicy later.
It's normal.
It's 10 spicy.
Is it more spicy if we eat it in a
restaurant?
It's hot.
It's easy to get hot.
Can you eat it?
I can't.
It's delicious.
When I eat it, I feel like I'm being
attacked.
You're kidding.
Can you eat it?
To be continued.
wait,
This is not a joke.
This is extremely spicy.
I put spinach in it, so it became mild.
It's spicy.
I'm sorry.
This is a little sweet.
It's a little spicy.
Isn't it great?
It's delicious.
Is it okay?
It's 10 spicy.
It was written on the receipt.
I was surprised.
I was practicing.
I thought it was spicy.
I think it's sweet.
I think it's like this.
It's cheese.
Thank you for watching.
I think it's getting spicy.
I think it's getting hot.
It's getting spicy.
Oh, is it?
It's the opposite.
This is spicy.
Let's warm it up.
What?
Do you want to try?
It's hot.
It's hot because it's freshly made.
It's different.
It's getting spicy after I ate this.
It's hot.
It's getting spicy.
It's different after I ate this.
It's like this.
It's getting spicy.
Is the spiciness of the spice okay?
The spiciness of ramen is okay.
I see.
I've eaten Mocotan before.
I can't remember.
It's still spicy.
It's getting spicy after I ate this.
Really?
Is it a prank?
It's actually spicy.
I can't believe I ate curry.
It's a mystery.
If you know any curry restaurants,
please let me know.
Please let me know.
If you know any curry restaurants,
please let me know.
I want to challenge it.
It looks thick.
It's very hot.
It's been a while since I ate curry.
It's very delicious.
It's a meal time.
It's hot.
Is it coming later?
No, it's not.
It's coming. I thought I ate it.
It's hot.
Did it explode?
It's too hot.
The sausage is broken.
The sausage is gone.
Where did it go?
That's right.
Is it okay?
It's hot.
It's coming.
I'm getting nervous.
I want to challenge it.
It's hot.
Is it hot?
Yes!
It's hot and spicy!
Is the temperature important?
Yes.
Are you okay?
What?
It's amazing.
It's hot!
Is it different from hot?
Do you want to try it?
No, I'm fine.
I drank all the tea here.
I'll try the Japanese tea.
It's very hot.
but the fact is that blaze mortal
japanese dub will be still on youtube
I can't eat this!
I'm so sorry.
I can't eat this.
I can't eat spicy food.
It's spicy.
I can't eat this.
Thank you.
Is it so different?
You can eat this with your normal face.
I'm fine.
I can't eat this.
Next week review
What are you doing?
It's spicy, isn't it?
What is this?
It's normal
It's 10 times spicier than I thought
It's getting better, but it's still
spicy
But it's still spicy
That's right
It's still spicy
It's hot
It's not because of the hair
It's amazing
If you keep eating it, your mouth will
be burning
It's amazing, isn't it?
I haven't eaten rice at all
It's amazing
I'm trying not to get carbohydrates
I can eat that spicy food
You are strong in spicy food
It's hot
Please subscribe to my channel!
It's hot!
I can't eat it
I'm not sure if it's hot or not
It's hot
Do you want to eat it?
Can I have it?
How is it?
Can I?
It's good
Really?
It's tender
Thank you
I can't eat it because it's hot
I know
It's hot!
Please subscribe!
I can't remember, but last year's
Ikebukuro festival was really spicy
So you can't swallow spicy food?
That's right
This is hell
It's spicy
We finished eating
Thank you for the meal
I'm going to finish eating all of this
You're going to eat it all?
I'm going to eat the sausage as well
This comes later
But when it's spicy, it gets spicier if
you eat it with water
Oh, I see
Do you know?
No, I don't know
I don't know
It's spicy
Is it?
I feel the spiciness
Oh
Is it spicier than the one you ate last
time?
I don't know about the one I ate last
time
But I can eat it from the beginning
I went there alone
I didn't have time to talk
I ate it all at once
So I didn't feel the spiciness
But now, it's spicy
Riko, you ate it all by yourself?
Yes, I did
I can't eat it because it's spicy
You can't eat it all by yourself?
I'm glad
You ate it silently
I always ask you to make it 8
Is it really 8?
Please check
It's okay
I can't eat it
Oh, it's almost done
It's almost done
It's spicy
It's spicy enough
What's wrong, Riko?
It's spicy
Riko, you're sweating
Bra intersection
It's hot.
She can't stop laughing.
Is it hot?
It's hot and spicy.
I can't stop laughing.
I can't stop laughing because it's
spicy.
You shouldn't drink water.
Really?
If you drink water, it will be more
spicy.
So, don't drink water and keep doing
your best.
How spicy is it?
Zero?
It's not spicy at all.
It's relatively spicy.
You shouldn't drink water.
She keeps drinking water.
I'm getting stronger because I took a
break.
I'm getting spicy because I ate a lot.
I'm getting hungry.
I'll give you one more.
Are you serious?
I can eat it.
You're kind.
I did it just now.
It's hot.
You started laughing.
I can't stop laughing.
Is there a theory that you can cool down
spicy food?
I can't cool it down.
I think there are many hot foods.
I think so.
Do you feel hot when you eat spicy food?
Wait a minute.
Do you feel hot when you eat hot food?
I think it's hot when I eat spicy food.
I think so.
My stomach is burning.
You are amazing.
I ate it.
This is amazing.
It's not painful.
It's hot.
Isn't it hot?
I'm eating it.
It's hot and spicy.
Curry which I haven't eaten for a long
time was delicious.
Don't you eat curry often?
I don't eat curry often.
I didn't like curry much.
I noticed the deliciousness of curry
recently.
It was delicious because I ate curry
which I haven't eaten for a long time.
It means that this curry is the most
delicious.
That's what it means.
It's spicy.
It's hot.
I finished eating.
I will eat the rest later.
Chanyu, you should eat something.
I'm sorry.
It was delicious.
Thank you for the meal.
It was delicious and spicy.
I was fine at first, but it was spicy.
I was fine.
I was sweating.
It was hot.
It was delicious.
I'm glad that you followed me.
I will make a series.
What should I name it?
I will name it...
Don't you want to name it?
I'm not a person who can eat spicy food.
I don't like spicy food.
This is a video of Riko Nakayama eating
spicy food.
Bye bye.
This is a video of Riko Nakayama eating
spicy food.
That's all.
Thank you for watching.
Bye bye.
Next time, we will try to eat it with a
spoon.
Wow, can you eat it like this?
What's going on?
It's scary.
Can you eat it with a spoon?
What?
Next time, we will try to eat it with a
spoon.
Please subscribe to our channel.