Ebitune's videos
It's been a month since we announced the
new member audition.
We haven't had a chance to talk about
the new member audition like this.
We would like to share the news about
the new member audition.
It's been a month since we announced the
new member audition.
We don't know how many members are in
the audition.
We don't know yet.
I'm so excited.
Mayama was in the audition before the
Ebitune.
It's the first time for someone to be in
the audition.
We were in the same group as the
previous members.
We didn't think we could grow as a
group.
What is Stardust?
We are at home.
We didn't have a chance to work together
before.
But we have been working together
several times a year.
We are at home.
I don't feel like the president of the
company.
But we have been working together since
we met.
We have never met before.
We are all friendly.
We are young and we can talk to each
other.
When I was in the audition, I thought
everything was strict.
But I was wrong.
We can talk to each other.
We don't have a rule.
We have our own opinions.
We are a flexible company.
We have many tours.
We are happy to meet our fans.
We have different atmosphere depending
on the place.
We have different way of meeting.
We have many fans who are waiting for
us.
We are happy to meet our fans.
We had a lot of fun on the plane.
We were happy when we went to Osaka for
the first time.
We were happy because we could eat ice
cream on the Shinkansen.
We went to many places for the first
time.
We bought a guitar.
We bought a deck brush.
We bought a black tire.
We were asked what it was.
I want to go.
I hope we can go around the country
again soon.
I want to conquer the 47 prefectures.
That's a dream.
I want to go around with the new
members.
Our voice trainer, Emiko, is always
thinking about the training we need.
There are many patterns.
We don't always do the same thing.
We do what we need to do.
We have two days of live performances.
We do it on the first day.
On the second day, we do it to get rid
of the tiredness.
We check our condition.
We also talk about our training.
We talk about our training.
It's fun.
We take care of our body and mind.
We also do voice training.
We do our best.
It's not limited to voice training.
We are blessed by the teachers.
We only had a manager at first.
We couldn't talk to the girls in junior
high school.
It was difficult to talk to adults.
But the teacher listened to us.
She did her hair for us.
She was like a mother.
She was like a big sister.
The teachers are like that.
We do hard things, but we don't feel
that way.
We have that kind of personality.
It's fun.
We are blessed by the teachers.
We get praised a lot when we sing.
But since Emi came, it changed.
We used to sing together.
But since Emi came, we have been able to
create our own strength.
We don't have to force ourselves to fit
in with others.
We have our own personality.
But we are a group.
We have our own voice.
It's a big change.
We are very grateful.
We are very grateful to the teachers.
Thank you.
I think we are relieved.
We have a lot of support.
Even if we are worried, we are here.
We don't have to rush.
We are raised well.
Please be assured.
I think that there is no one who can
relate to this age.
I think it's amazing.
I'm still 20 years old, but I've only
lived for 20 years.
I think it's fun to be involved with
thousands of people.
It's fun to be involved with a lot of
people.
I'm not good at it, but I think it's
fun.
I'm grateful that there are people who
think it's good.
I'm surprised that tens of thousands of
people know me.
I'm grateful.
Idols are not limited to singing and
dancing.
I think it's a job that allows you to do
a lot of things.
Everyone is good at acting and appearing
in magazines.
I think I can do it because I'm in a
group.
I'm worried about being alone in a
I'm glad that I'm in a group.
I spend time with idols.
I'm always motivated by various people.
I want to show my new self to my fans.
I'm glad that many idols support me.
I wouldn't have been able to find it if
I didn't have it.
I'm glad that there are many people who
support me.
didn't dare to meet me if I didn't have
a job.
I'm glad that I'm in a group that can
continue to grow.