Watch the next one!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Stop it! Stop it!
What's wrong?
How old are you?
I'm...
I'm eating so much that I could be a
commentator.
I ate curry the day before yesterday and
yesterday.
What?
I eat curry every day.
I have a dream.
I hope it comes true someday.
Someday...
That's good.
I'm looking forward to it.
Yakan Idol
Happy New Year!
Thank you for your support.
I'm Yakan.
I look forward to working with you this
year.
Please decorate the top banner for 2023.
The winner is this idol!
Once again, happy new year!
Momoiro Clover Dance!
I'm Takagi Reni, the lead dancer. Nice
to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
I'm Kotoyaro.
Thank you.
Finally, Takagi Reni is here.
Thank you for the happy day.
Congratulations.
It's 2023.
Finally, Takagi-san is turning 30.
Oh, my God.
It's the best end of the year.
What year is it this year?
It's the year of the rabbit.
It's the first New Year's Day.
Last year was a big year for you, too.
But it's the New Year's Day.
What year do you want to spend this
year?
This year?
It's the 15th anniversary of Momokuro.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
15th anniversary!
It's our 15th anniversary. We were in
middle school.
We've devoted half of our lives to
Momokuro.
It's a year to remember.
I hope we can do a lot of live
performances.
I want to celebrate as much as possible.
That's great.
15 years is a great thing.
Isn't it?
By the way, the night view...
Yes!
It's great.
How many nightstands?
There are 7 nightstands.
I'm sorry. I'm not sure about the age.
You've been doing this show for a long
time.
It's been 3 months.
You haven't decided yet?
I haven't decided yet, and I have to do
it.
I'm aware of it now.
I'm thinking about the age and setting.
We're going to have an event this year.
How many nightstands should I do for
that?
But 7 nightstands are cute.
It's obviously your voice.
This is different.
If you look at the O-MAYOR, you'll know.
You talked about it before.
What you see is not everything.
That's right.
I don't care about myself.
It hurts! Stop it!
Stop it!
That's a bad place!
You can't do that!
Stop it!
You're supposed to be a man, right?
You should be careful.
That's right.
We're going to start the main segment
from tomorrow.
Starting tomorrow, we're going to have a
special version of the show.
We're going to have a talk show with
Hoshina Mirei.
Please look forward to it!
Mirei, do you have any plans to talk to
me?
No!
I heard you say you like me when we were
in the same agency.
But I didn't say it at all.
I'm sure the agency told you that.
You shouldn't say that.
I want to hear the truth.
I want to hear it, but I want to eat it
with you.
Ouch!
See you tomorrow!
Look forward to it!