Ebichu Tastas has started!
This week's Ebichu Tastas is Ebichu
Tastas University!
The answer to the miracle of the test
cannot be stopped! Ebichu Tastas starts!
This is the first time I've ever seen a
video of a girl being attacked by a
monster.
It was a little scary, but I was happy
to see it.
This is the first time I've ever seen a
girl being attacked by a monster.
It was a little scary, but I was happy
to see it.
I tried to get a lot of stuff out of
private Ebisu Middle School.
This program is brought to you by the
following sponsors.
Bichuu Tastas has started!
If we don't do it properly, the staff
will get mad at us.
Let's do our best together!
What? They got mad at you?
Really?
They said that I was too free during the
BBQ and it was boring.
They said that?
Really?
When the principal said that, I was
pretty mad.
The principal got mad at you?
They said that I should do it properly
from now on.
I see.
Sorry, we are late.
Hello, we are Takiwe and Chue from
Nagareboshi.
It's summer, it's summer, it's summer,
I'm sorry.
Thank you for watching!
Please subscribe to our channel!
Chuu-san went to our live show and
bought it by herself
Takiyama-san?
Everyone is like that
No, no, no, that's fine
It's weird that I bought it
It's like an open-air hell
If you don't buy it, it's like this
I was surprised to see the live show
Mayama's jump was amazing
Jumping
Show me that
Now?
Of course
1,2,3
I haven't done it yet
I'll do it
Let's see Takiyama's
I want to see
You should do it yourself
I'm really hard
1,2,3
It was beyond my imagination
How much did I fall behind?
Please tell us about today's theme
Today's theme is university
We will show you the real university
This time, we will visit the real
university and add university to the
shrimp
Why do you go to university today?
Because I am a junior high school
student forever, I don't have a chance
to be a university student
That's right, you are a junior high
school student forever
So I want to experience university only
today
So, the eternal junior high school
student Ebichu experienced university
only for a day
She went to the classroom immediately
Everyone is a real classroom, how is it?
It's different from what I imagined
It's like a classroom of a school bus
The floor and the environment are
different
The wall is also different
It's a mess
It's time, everyone, get in line
Why?
Get in line
Get in line, we will start the class
The class is about to start
So, we will have the entrance exam of
the Ebisu University
No way
This time, the theme is university
So, everyone, please answer the question
I can't
Don't stand up with your hands up
By the way, 5 of 8 students passed the
exam
What?
Please stand up
And the one who passed the exam is this
The special student, the university
student, Sakai
The class is about to start, 5 students
passed the exam
Everyone loves the celebration of
passing the exam
There is a punishment game
I thought there was no punishment game
If you move Tastas a little bit, it will
be a little bit
No, I don't know
I said it randomly and she came back
unexpectedly
By the way, who is the most intelligent
one in Ebichu?
Hoshino
Everyone is Hoshino
Really?
I know difficult words in daily life
If you can't read in the script, Mirei
can read
By the way, who is the most stupid one
in here?
Even though you have bad grades
She raised her hand
That's amazing
She is the most rampaging in the street
This is the most popular
If you study, you can do it, but if you
don't want to do it
You can't study
because there is a limit to what you can
do and can only be done by the
individual who陽レ 깜 Unlike google, thevet
in this car is selected as Well done
Wow!
Wait a minute, me?
Are you here for the test of Shiri-su
Ebisu University?
Yes
No, no
Do you want to take the test?
No, not here
No, no
I studied all night yesterday
That's why your eyes are so red
I have a bloodshot eye
I see
For some reason, Kaichi Ogata, who was
the first to have a school disaster,
also participated in the entrance exam
for the Ebi University
So, we will now have the entrance exam
for Shiri-su Ebisu University
Yes
The first subject of the entrance exam
is Japanese
The first question
Please
Go
Fill in the blank and complete the word
What is the word for cute girl?
It's cute girl
This is a good question
Yes, it's a good question
I want to go wild
What is the word for cute girl?
What was the word for sender?
Sender?
Takayama, Kageda
What?
What does that mean?
There is only one answer
Now, let's announce the answer
First, Kaichi
This is
I will let the cute girl go on a trip
Oh, you will let her go on a trip
I will go from Hirota
Yes
Please
I will let the cute girl go on a trip
I see
Next, Mayama, Hoshina, Yasumoto are
correct
Then, Matsuno's answer who was worried
about the last question
Matsuno is
What?
Oh, that's what it is
I see, I see
It's like whether B will be included or
not
And, Kashiwagi's answer who declared
himself as a fool is
Yes, Kashiwagi
Let's go on a trip
That's good
That's right, let's go to Kyoto
That's right, let's go on a trip
Let's go to Nakayama
Nakayama, to a cute girl, a good girl, a
good girl
To a cute girl, a good girl, a good girl
That's right
You will do it to a cute girl, right?
I will do it, but I thought there was no
answer
It's under the line
It's under the line?
The answer is under the line
Nakayama's answer, to a cute girl, a
good girl, a good girl
It's the truth
I see, and Kobayashi, the last one,
please
To a cute girl, bungee jump
What does it mean?
I don't know
It's a question that has been around for
a long time, why is it a katakana
answer?
That's right
Bungee jump to a cute girl
The second question
Next is also a question of this
technique
Jump
O-nyarara is sleeping and waiting
I've heard of it
What is it?
It's like a fantasy
What does it mean?
Now, the answer announcement
Okada-san, please
Yes
Kaho is sleeping and waiting
Okada-san is correct
Hoshina just screamed
Let's see Hoshina
Please
Negoto is sleeping and waiting
That's right
It's not a sleep talk
As expected, Negoto is the smartest one
I'm done
What are you waiting for?
I'm writing an A
Curry rice
Please calm down
What does it mean?
Curry rice is better to put it in the
fridge than the first one
It's better to let it sleep
That's what it means
It's better to let curry rice sleep
As expected
I'm done
So let's see Hirota's
Pickled vegetables
I think it's good
It's good to have a special combination
It's good to have pickled vegetables
It's good because the taste is soaked
I can eat oden
Oden is also delicious
It's not like that
It's completely a food thing
Kobayashi
Let's go to Kobayashi
Kobayashi, please
It's not Seino
I heard Kobayashi
It's in order
What?
Santa
Santa is sleeping
And
It's not correct with Yasumoto
Next is the science question
This one
Of course drawing a frog is correct
But what is the member's drawing?
It's disgusting
Who drew it?
Can I draw bad?
Please be quiet
Everyone, did you draw it?
Let's see
I was surprised
Kobayashi
Please show us
You are good at drawing
Frog
You have a good sense
Ogata, Mayama, Nakayama
Hirota is good at drawing
And what do these two people think of
their drawings?
Yes, yes, yes, the legs are growing
And the next one
What, what, what?
What is this?
What is that?
That is a living thing
It grows, right?
Because it says ゲロゲロ
I thought I didn't understand it, so I
wrote ゲロゲロ
And I was wondering what to draw on the
body
It's a little gross
It's super gross
It's like a push and pull
Yasumoto
After this, Yasumoto's painting is
revealed
And there is an unbelievable living
thing
The members are drawing the picture of
the frog at the entrance exam that
started suddenly
Next is Yasumoto's answer
I have a frog
What is this?
This is Otama-Jakushi
Otama-Jakushi
First of all, the frog's head
It's like a frog's skin
I think it's a frog's body
Otama-Jakushi's legs are growing
It's a frog's body
It's like a film
I've never seen the frog's body in the
middle of the picture
I've never seen it
Next is Kashiwagi
Please show us
Is this a parasite?
It's so scary
What is this?
What's going on?
I still don't know what a cat-boy's eyes
and mouth are
What is this?
It's like a tail
I don't know. I think it's better to
grow up
I don't know if it's better to grow up
There is no frog
The score so far is here
The blue member is not qualified
Will it be a reversal?
The last subject is society
The famous phrase that Gagarin said when
he went to the space flight for the
first time in the world
The earth is ________
You like Nakayama, don't you?
I like it. There are two
There are two
I got it
There is one
Now, let's announce the answer
How about Kaichi?
It was wrong
It's correct
Mayama and Hoshina were a bit close, but
these 4 were correct
I got it
And Hirota who was confused with 2
answers
Marui and Kaito
Both were incorrect
While everyone was wondering whether the
Earth is round or blue, what was
Kobayashi's answer?
The Earth moves
It moves?
It's like a song by Laputa
Furthermore
Yasumoto
The Earth is everyone's mother
That's good
It's a famous saying
The second question from the society
Here is the question
She is Napoleon, Napoleon's wife, what
did he say?
He said 〇〇
Is this a little cool?
Cool
A little cool?
I think it's cool
Then the answer announcement
Hoshina
Hoshina's easy answer
It's a famous famous phrase
So these 5 people also got the correct
answer
Kashiwagi and Nakayama also got the
wrong answer
But it's a very close answer
Meanwhile, Yasumoto has a shocking
answer
Yasumoto
Really?
Cool
It's a temple
A, you are handsome
It's a real temple
It's very cool
It's not written in any dictionary
Cool
Finally, the final question
The answer is...
The third question is from Edison
It's in the lyrics of the song
Really?
Is it?
It is
Let's see
Let's see the answer
Let's start with Hiroto. What is it?
Effort
I see. Mayama, go
Let's see the answer
Ability
99% ability
And Ogata is correct too
Yasumoto Kobayashi is unfortunately
incorrect
Nakayama, go. 1% of Tenzara, and 99% of
Hirameki
Thank you for watching
Cute cute
It's like a girl manga's textbook
It's cute
It's sparkling and throbbing
It's true
The shrimp university entrance exam is
over
Who passed the exam?
But before that
Shrimp Chuu Game Quest
The game project is currently in
progress
The members who tested the demo version
of the game last time
This time, we decided to think about the
characters that appear in the game
I like this one
What should I do?
Okay, I'm done
Are you okay?
Yes
What is the character that Mayama
thought of?
This is the character that I thought of
It's a middle school student who is
active
What is this?
This is the background
The background is that Yasumoto-san
wanted an old man
So, he is standing in front of the door
to make an old man appear
This little one is an old man
It's good
Next, what is the character that
Yasumoto thought of?
The name of this character is
Crispy Fried Potato
It's a potato
There are a fried potato and a potato's
face
One by one
Among them, the first member is the
shrimp-chew member
It's fun to be with everyone
It's like a popping EDC
Next, what is the character that
Kobayashi thought of?
This is the character
It's cute
This is the principal
He is wearing a shrimp
What should I call him?
What about Ebi-sensei?
Then, Ebi-sensei
Next, what is the character that Matsuno
thought of?
Please announce it
The name is Ebi-maru-chan
When does it appear?
It's a person who helps you when you are
in danger
It depends on the level
The top one is the shrimp
Shrimp has a great skill
It has a rank
I see
This is good
I will take the idea I received to the
company
and consider it
Will the members' opinions be accepted?
Ebi-chew Game Project
Please look forward to the next
development
The interesting answer is the end of the
shrimp university entrance exam
Who is the pass?
Now, I'd like to announce the pass
The first one is
Congratulations, Ogata-san
I knew it
By the way, Ogata-san got all the
questions right
The campus life you've been longing for
Congratulations
Next, the 2nd place in the same class
Who is the pass?
Hoshina
Congratulations
The winner is Mayama
Yay
The next winner is
The winner is Hirota
Congratulations
There is one more person left
By the way, who do you think is going to
win?
Everyone is raising their hands
You don't have to raise your hands
Masuno and Nakayama are raising their
hands twice
What will happen?
I will announce the winner
Who will be the last one to slip?
Matsuho, congratulations!
We are now in the private Ebisu
University!
And so...
Hello everyone!
Hello!
It's the morning time and we are in the
private Ebisu University!
There's a lot of people here!
We are all here!
The five people who pass will receive a
prize of a university potato!
On the other hand, the four people who
failed were these four people
The most stupid among the four is
Yasumoto, Nakayama, Kashiwagi, or
Kobayashi
The one who was the loser was Kashiwagi!
Yay!
How is it, Kashiwagi?
I'm very frustrated
So, Kashiwagi at the bottom will have a
smart-looking face to say something
Then, please say something smart with a
stupid face
Can you do it? I can't
Thank you very much
You have a good face
So, what is Ebichu plus University?
Can you do it?
I can't do it
Kashiyagi was a junior high school
student with a long history of studying
Next time, Ebichu plus University's
second half
I'm so nervous, I'm going to have an
interview
The interviewer is too scary, Nakayama
Wait a minute
I don't want to do it anymore
Here is the announcement
Kashiyagi Hinata's main movie, No Show,
is going to be released from July 25th
It's so colorful
Don't miss it
In addition, Kashiyagi Hinata's first
photo book will be released
And if you missed Ebichu plus
University, you will get a notice
The movie will be released on the movie
streaming site Stardust Channel
You can watch the movie at any time
And there will be a lot of unsealed
videos
Search for the movie on Stardust Channel
This program was sponsored by the
sponsor.
Welcome to Geki Odoika Cafe!
Welcome to Tokimeki Cafe!
Oh!
I'm the owner, so I'll take off my
clothes when I wear them.