Ebichu's videos!
Mayuma!
Hoshina!
How much do you know about each other?
Oh!
Ebichu has a lot of goods, right?
There are many.
Well, here's what we want to do.
Hoshina!
I want to do this.
Is it a Mayama-like thing?
Mayama-like?
I don't know if you say it's Mayama-
like.
I opened the common things that come to
mind in Ebichu's goods.
I wonder if this is common.
Isn't it good?
It's common in normal goods.
It's not common in Ebichu.
It's not common.
It's common.
It's common in general goods.
Smartphone case.
T-shirt.
Correct!
My answer is...
It's a tote bag.
I think I've seen it before.
It's a tote bag that was released as a
special offer for Singalong Singasong.
It's a special offer, but it's not a
good deal.
I saw it a while ago, so I wanted to
make it.
I want to make it.
I have a t-shirt, too.
I've made a t-shirt before, so I'm
thinking about making it.
So, the result is...
Well, there were some things that
changed a little bit, but there were
only two questions right.
Oh, that's too bad.
I know a little too much.
That's right.
There are some things that came out.
We've known each other for about nine or
ten years.
It's too hard to guess.
I wanted to eat the same thing as the
cake.
We have similar tastes in food.
Unfortunately, the question was the
result of the game.
I'm going to eat a large amount of
peyoung to deepen our friendship.
From now on?
We are going to eat a large amount of
peyoung because we like to eat.
It's important to have a friendship that
shares the same cup.
That's the large-scale Peyoung.
We will eat large-scale Peyoung.
Peyoung
Are you so excited?
You said, why Peyoung?
But it smells delicious in front of you.
Now, because of the influence of Corona,
we have prepared a large-scale Peyoung
for each person.
Let's eat.
Let's say it together.
Itadakimasu.
Do you put this in?
You can put it in or you can't.
First, taste the ingredients.
Ingredients?
Can I eat this all?
I feel like I can eat this.
This is amazing.
It's because the size is similar to the
face.
There are two faces.
Mirei, is this your first time eating
cup yakisoba?
Yes, it's my first time.
I usually eat only cup ramen with
shrimp.
That's right.
This is my first time eating yakisoba.
I'm looking forward to it.
We have prepared a lot of different
flavors.
Let's eat.
It's good!
Peyoung is good!
Let's enjoy it with this.
Let's eat it without furikake for a
while.
It's a project to eat it all the time,
right?
Yes.
I feel like I can eat it all.
It's delicious.
It's a strong taste.
I don't think I can eat this.
I'll sprinkle the furikake.
I'll eat this for a while until I get
tired of it.
This looks delicious enough to make you
want to sprinkle it.
It's a furikake.
It's delicious.
Is it delicious?
I've never seen a girl eat cup yakisoba
so deliciously.
It's really delicious.
It's delicious as a normal food, so you
don't have to taste it.
It's fresh.
I'm addicted to this.
That's good.
Can I eat it all?
Is it twice as much as a normal Peyoung?
I don't know.
Let's put something on it.
Like a donut.
Which one?
Powdered cheese, chili oil.
I'm excited.
I can't wait to taste it.
I'll taste it.
Mayonnaise.
I'm impressed.
It's rare.
Each person has a different purpose.
I'm going to eat the first cup yakisoba.
I'm singing a song about cup yakisoba.
Cup yakisoba, cup yakisoba.
I was dancing with a torch that time,
but it was very heavy.
At that time, you said you had never
eaten cup yakisoba.
I don't know if it's baked or not.
I don't know why I'm not saying it.
It's because you're making it soft with
hot water.
I thought it wasn't yakisoba.
It's like a noodle.
I'll put some cheese on it.
There's so much, I can't decide how much
to put in.
I think it'll make you full if you put
cheese on it.
I'll put cheese on this part.
It's fun.
Hoshino, do you like cup noodles?
I'm already getting full.
I've never been here before. It's hard
to eat alone, so I'm going to eat with
two people.
Do you want to talk about when you went
to play?
Memories talk
When was the first time you two played
together?
I haven't talked to Mire-chan much when
I joined.
I felt like a senior.
I didn't feel like that, but there was a
first-time meeting.
I felt like that, so I didn't feel like
I was close to the same group.
I felt like a senior.
I felt like that.
I think so.
Mirei, you've been in the group for four
years. I thought you were the most
outstanding one.
I didn't know much about it. I was
wondering what dancing was.
I remember when I was in high school, I
used to crush the time between school
and work.
I remember.
Disneyland with Mirei.
I said it from a great place.
Disneyland.
We went to Disneyland a lot.
We went together.
We also did a twin costume.
I originally had matching denim.
The day before, I went to MaruQ and
bought a T-shirt with Mickey.
It's a hat.
I also bought an aloha shirt.
I still have it.
I'm full.
I know you are full because you started
eating with me.
When I'm full, I tend to eat rice with
chopsticks.
I eat white rice with chopsticks.
So I eat rice with chopsticks.
You eat rice with chopsticks like
onigiri.
They force Sushi and onigiri together
Then I'm gonna eat.
Now it looks like this.
not much less?
Miria! You are too thin.
Eh? Why?
Strawberry more porn!
I want to eat it with tabasco.
I want to eat it with kake-yo.
Mayama took a picture of the 23rd summer
night's Kojima V.
Really?
And she said that a little taller person
is more likely to be taken by a man.
Mayama was a little taller and raised
his hand.
So, I was taken by him.
I asked him if I was in the picture.
He said, I think I'm in the picture.
I was taken by him and asked him to use
it.
I put too much tabasco.
Is it spicy?
Yes.
I remember that we were addicted to
spicy food.
We were.
We were addicted to spicy hot pot.
It was a big hit.
Yes.
The other day, in Osaka...
It was a year ago.
It was during the autumn tour.
We went to Nara Park.
We went to Kyoto with Nara.
We stayed in Kyoto.
But we didn't do anything the day
before.
We just went to Osaka, Kyoto and Nara.
We spent 3 days.
We did it.
Osaka was so fun.
It was fun.
We decided not to drink alcohol the day
before the tour.
We went to a local restaurant because we
were going to the day before the tour.
We enjoyed drinking together.
Do you mean a food stall where all the
members go?
I think it's a food stall.
Do you get a discount on food stalls?
Like oden.
Yes, like oden and takoyaki.
It's a restaurant where old men who work
as waiters gather.
We ate together for the third time.
We ate meat, udon, takoyaki, and oden.
It was crazy. We ate a lot at that time.
We ate a lot at that time.
We got on the Shinkansen by mistake.
The ticket says Tokyo, for example, at
16.37.
We got on the Shinagawa train.
It was supposed to be Tokyo time, but
when we got to Shinagawa station...
There was a train that left at 3.7pm, so
we got on it.
But it wasn't Nozomi.
We got on Kodama, but we didn't notice
it.
We passed Shin-Yokohama, and then we saw
Odawara.
Odawara? Did that stop?
It stopped a lot.
Then we saw Nagoya and made an
appointment.
We said, we'll meet Nozomi. We were
like, that's not where we're going.
We looked up the time table a lot.
We looked up if we could change seats
there.
Then we were told that it was the next
home.
We changed seats in Nagoya.
We were free seats.
At first, we were in the designated
seat.
It was open, so we were sitting.
We noticed it in Odawara.
We were like, it's not good to sit here.
We were in the designated seat, and we
were with the lady next to us.
Oh, no. It's over.
No way.
It's really this much.
If it's true, you have to say, like, uh.
I'll take it at that rate.
Oh, it's painful.
It's okay. I'm used to it.
It's painful.
Then I'll enjoy it.
It's tough without changing the taste.
If it wasn't for this situation, I could
eat it every day.
I agree.
I finished eating.
I'm full.
I'll talk to you.
Please talk to me.
I ate this much.
This is the toughest.
You ate a lot.
I ate a lot.
Next, I want to do something with you.
What is it?
I haven't done it with just the two of
us yet.
We haven't done it with just the two of
We want to go somewhere by plane.
I want to go!
I want to go on a deserted island
experience.
I want to go!
You want to go, right?
Do you want to go fishing?
I can go fishing anywhere.
On a deserted island?
We haven't done it with just the two of
us yet.
I want to do it with everyone.
I think I can do it with just Mirei and
the two of us.
You don't cook.
I'm going to go get it.
You're going to go get it?
I'm going to get what Mirei bought.
I can't swim.
You can't swim.
It's almost time for us to go.
I feel like I'm getting better when I
get to this point.
I think you're getting there.
I'm feeling it.
I don't know the lyrics.
I'm done.
We ate it all.
We ate the same food.
We are friends.
We are not the same food.
We are different.
We ate the same noodles.
We are getting along better.
Next time we will go to a deserted
island.
Are we really going?
So, this was Mayama and Hoshina's How
much do you know about each other?
Bye bye!