Night time and idol
Please introduce the title of this
project
My three major elements
Yay
This is a corner to introduce the three
elements that make up yourself
There is a meaning to know more about
the guest idol
Please tell us what the three elements
are
These three elements are the three
elements that make up you
Food, game, anime, and delivery
I thought it was this
I see
I heard a lot of things in the opening
Let's dig deeper
The three elements that make up you
I like to eat a lot
I like to eat a lot of food with my
family
I think I can eat about half of my three
major elements
50% is food?
Yes
You can eat that much?
I am a family that everyone eats
My ramen ramen noodles are three times
So I eat four ramen noodles in total
That's amazing
That means four times
That's right
It's also a big meal
I thought it was normal at first
But then I thought it was different from
everyone
I thought the amount of food was
different
While talking about it on the air
I heard that Seta-san is a big eater
What do you think is the difference
between the members and the taste of
food?
I like strong taste
It's a little bit strong and sweet
It's a little bit strong
Really?
Yes
I like strong taste
When I cook, other people say it's
strong
I want to see Seta cooking
It's like a restaurant
Like a restaurant?
I'm glad I'm an idol
If I'm not an idol, I'll be a fool
I see
You're popular
What do you think of Seta-san?
I thought he was Seta-san
Maybe
Really?
I'm in the game to enjoy the game
I don't want to ask for anything else
That's right
You're serious
I'm serious