Yakan and idol
And the third one is a strange face
I have a strange face during the live
You have a strange face during the live?
I have a strange face during the song
During the song?
Yes
Do you have a strange face?
I would get angry.
Oh, you would get angry?
Yes, I am careful recently
I get angry when singing
I get angry and people laugh at me
I like people to laugh
I see
I sing about 30 songs
That's a lot
But recently, I've been using it for
songs.
I think I've improved my singing skills.
You've improved your singing skills?
I've been praised by the audience.
I'm glad.
But you're not just singing the part
you're singing.
Yes.
You're also doing the part where people
are singing.
I'm doing it.
That's very rude.
That's good.
It's good to be honest.
I understand.
Absolutely.
The audience is not angry at you
anymore.
I can't help but notice it.
I see.
I can't help but do it when I can't see
people.
If you laugh at me, I'll do it.
I have to laugh at you.
That's right.
You're a professional.
Yes.
That's good.
You don't change when you're alone at
home, do you?
I don't.
You're a professional.
I'm sorry.
In recent episodes,
I've been using the app called STACOM.
I've been using the app for three years.
I've been changing too much.
I've got a problem.
Who's the problem?
I don't know.
I've got a problem.
Really?
I was in a hurry and went to the Mars
station.
I took a picture.
You took a picture in a hurry and went
to Mars?
Yes.
I'm changing now.
Who is it?
You can't show me a weird face.
It's a weird face.
Why?
There are a lot of people watching us.
Can you show us a weird face?
It's a mosaic.
If it's bad, it's a mosaic.
Okay.
How weird is it?
I don't know.
It's a weird face.
I don't care.
I was in a hurry and went to the Mars
station.
It's not weird.
It's cute.
You said it.
Why?
I'm sorry.
I put a mosaic on it.
It's okay.
Everyone who drinks tea is surprised.
Thank you very much.