Ebichu's video
Hello, I'm Miru
I'm Kuma Yoshikawa
The dog is barking
Don't bark at the dog
I wonder if it's related to the barking
So, Ebichu's video is a celebration of
the first anniversary
I've been watching it for a while
Who are you?
Kaho
Today, you came here
Great
I was eaten
Today, a friend of mine came
Everyone, you're so great
I'm 4pen
So, here it is
I'm at 4pen cafe
It's on the screen
Cute
I'm looking forward to it
This is 4pen cafe in Soramachi
I'm going to go to 4pen cafe with my
game friend, 2pen
I heard that 4pen cafe is open
I said let's go
So, I'm going to go with Ebichu's video
Let's go together
I'm going to go with Ebichu's video
Let's go
Bye
We went to 4pen cafe
We took a lot of pictures
We will talk about this picture
We will deliver it
Let's go to 4pen cafe
We came to 4pen cafe
This is 4pen cafe in Soramachi
I'm glad I went
Everyone was popular
There are many people
There was a person who was taking
pictures.
The social distance was properly
protected.
It was a draw.
This is KOUPEN.
You are not KOUPEN.
You are talking to yourself.
I'm talking to myself.
You are eating with me.
This is KOUPEN.
This is AISUKI KOUPEN.
This is a great KOUPEN that can be your
partner even if you come alone.
This is a system that can be placed on
the side.
This is a picture that has been posted.
This is cute.
This is a picture taken by MIREPEN.
This is a picture taken by KOUPEN.
There were many MIREPEN.
This is the picture taken by me and
KOUPEN.
I wonder if KOUPEN took this picture.
This is a great picture taken by
MIREPEN.
This is an acrylic plate.
This is a picture taken safely.
This is a picture taken by MIREPEN.
This is a picture taken when choosing
goods.
This was taken when I was very worried
about it.
I was worried about which one to buy
because they were all cute.
There are many AISUKI KOUPEN.
This is a picture taken by KOUPEN.
This is cute.
I found a person who was floating.
This is the appearance of MIREPEN
carrying KOUPEN.
This is also a picture taken with goods.
This is cute.
This person is floating.
This person is holding a picture.
This is a picture taken with a
reversible cushion.
This person is cute.
This person is carrying KOUPEN.
This person is floating.
This is the picture taken by MIREPEN.
This person is holding a picture.
This is a puppet and another one is a
mascot that Ko-Pen-chan is a type of
animal.
cute
Ko-Pen-chan, let me fly alone.
Ko-Pen-chan, Ko-Pen-chan, Ko-Pen-chan,
Ko-Pen-chan, Ko-Pen-chan, Ko-Pen-chan.
Mirepen-chan was the only one who was
blown away.
I'm the pen.
The pen you write is a pen.
This is a magic stick sand set.
cute
Ko-Pen-chan, who became a magician, is
floating in the cup.
What?
Underneath it, I imagined a magic stick.
What was this?
Was it a croquemush?
It was very delicious.
It's like a croquemush.
What does that mean?
It's a stick.
Next, Mirepen ate this.
Heart-pounding, indescribable curry.
It looks delicious.
This is full of vegetables.
There is a spice that has a magic that
makes you feel energetic.
If you eat it together, your heart will
be warm and indescribable.
This curry is a little spicy.
I wondered what this rice was made of
when Ko-Pen-chan was born.
The color was very delicious.
Next, we ate dessert.
Ko-Pen ate this.
Ko-Pen-chan man, the magic of
friendship.
This was an anman.
I felt nostalgic.
It was like a childhood friend.
The anman was very delicious.
I ate it very deliciously.
It was very delicious.
I wondered where to start.
I feel sad.
I started with no pen.
Mirepen ate this.
This is Ko-Pen-chan's birthday cake.
Ko-Pen-chan's birthday was on April 4th.
I ordered this.
This is a muffin coated with white
chocolate.
There is a strawberry on the side.
It looks delicious
What do you think this is made of?
Magic
What a fantasy
The correct answer was black sesame
It was black sesame ice cream
This ice cream is very delicious
I ate the plate of the previous salad
I was on the plate
This black sesame ice cream was
refreshing and delicious
The white chocolate was also crispy
This was a nice birthday cake
Happy birthday
This is pink copen
Magic soda
It's cute
The pink part is jelly
It was sweet and sour and delicious
There is whipped cream on it
Copen is floating on it
It was a cute drink
I ordered the magic soda
The blue one was the color
I was surprised
It was very refreshing
I thought it was a waste to eat the ice
cream
It was sinking
The soda candy was on the bottom
Soda
I went to the cafe
I enjoyed the coffee
It was delicious
I was happy
I ate
I went to the cafe
There is a cute guy floating
Cute
He is good at touching
He praises me
It was a happy world
The food was delicious
We ordered a lot
I was hungry
We ate the drinks, desserts, and main
dishes.
It was delicious.
It was very delicious.
It was very cruel to eat Kopen-chan.
It was sweet.
It was a Kopen-chan Cafe.
Everyone who watched it was great.
I will introduce the purchase date.
First of all,
This is a puppet Kopen-chan.
It's cute.
It can be used as a doll.
I will take Kopen-chan to the store when
I buy a mille-pain.
I will take Kopen-chan to the store.
What did you buy?
I bought a puppet Kopen-chan.
This is interesting.
I bought a puppet that can be attached
to a pen tip.
It's cute.
It's comfortable because the part where
the fingers are inserted is fluffy.
What does this say?
It says,
I'm watching you always working hard.
I thought it was this.
Did you decide?
I decided to buy this.
It's cute.
Next, I bought this Kopen-chan key
holder.
I bought a Kopen-chan wearing a bear
doll and a Kopen-chan wearing a Scottish
Fold.
It's cute.
I bought two because they were cute.
Next, I bought a bigger mascot than the
previous one.
I bought a big one.
I bought a Kopen-chan-like
Kopen-chan-like
It's a large amount.
It's fluffy and comfortable.
I want to put a lot of it on my face.
I'm sure you can see the big one in the
live.
I bought another one.
This is a Kopen-chan's large Gengar hand
towel.
It says Kopen-chan space.
It's a big one.
It's cute.
It's cute that it's a Gengar.
I bought it because I thought it was
cute.
I think it can be used in the kitchen.
It's cute.
There are many things that you can't
see.
This is the blue one that is randomly
included.
It's a Kopenchan Cafe acrylic key
holder.
And the yellow one is a Kopenchan Cafe
acrylic badge.
First of all, I would like to open this
acrylic key holder.
Let's open one by one.
It's cute.
It's a magician.
What kind of Kopenchan is Kao?
Kao has a magic pen.
I have a four-leaf clover.
It's cute.
And it's a key holder.
I would like to open another one.
I will open it.
It's not covered.
What is it?
And it's a cute Kopenchan using magic
soup.
It's cute.
It's a magical power.
I didn't cover the three kinds.
I'm glad.
Next, I would like to open the acrylic
badge in the Kopenchan bag.
This is also a random of six kinds.
I will not cover it.
I'm looking forward to it.
The Kopen got Adelie.
Adelie is using magic.
It's cute.
And the magic pen is a Kopenchan using
magic.
This is cute.
I'm glad I got the badge.
Next, I will open the last one.
Please open it.
What is the last one?
I opened it.
Don't open it so easily.
It's not like we have to keep close.
You are right.
and subscribe!
I went to the Ko-pen-chan cafe and got a
healing.
This time I went to the Ko-pen-chan cafe
and got a healing.
It was a space where I could get healing
with happiness.
It was peaceful.
I think it's good to be able to worship.
I was able to see Ko-pen-chan in real
life.
I got a lot of healing at Ko-pen-chan
cafe.
I'm glad I was able to go.
It was fun.
Ko-pen-chan is Hanamaru.
I got a lot of good things from Ko-pen-
chan.
I will do my best to collaborate with
Ko-pen-chan someday.
I will continue to support Ko-pen-chan.