Night Camp Idol!
The second one is Netflix.
Why did you decide to appear in this
program?
This is...
What is it?
I just said it earlier.
There's one thing I want to do.
I've always had a dream.
I want to appear in a Netflix original
drama.
Oh!
Yes.
That's good.
I hope that dream comes true someday.
I watch Netflix when I have time.
I've been watching it lately.
I'll introduce it to you.
Please recommend this program.
I recently watched a movie called
Revenge Swap.
Revenge Swap?
It's a movie.
It's a movie that crushes a person who
has messed up his student life.
I see.
That's what it's about.
I also watched the Halloween spell
Bridge Hollow is a big deal.
The spirit of Halloween is in the
Halloween kimono.
That's good.
I also like the movie Clueless.
Clueless?
Yes.
The girl who turned into a corpse?
I see, so you're talking about your
private life.
Yes, I'm like a party person.
I've also started watching Jyarinko
Chie.
Jyarinko Chie?
Yes, I've started watching it.
Jyarinko Chie? Is that the old Jyarinko
Chie?
Yes, I've been watching the rerun of
Jyarinko Chie.
The only anime I remember is Jyarinko
Chie.
So I've been watching it recently.
I'd like to introduce the ones on my
playlist.
Is it okay to tell me about them?
The Korean drama called, The Lawyer is a
Genius.
I'd like to start watching it soon.
The strongest running plan.
I'd like to watch the 42nd episode.
The story of a man who changed the
world.
What's that?
Is it about baseball?
Yes, it's about a man who became a major
leaguer.
He changes the history of baseball in
the midst of discrimination.
It was really interesting.
It's a legendary movie about the history
of baseball.
I see.
I think it's really interesting.
I think most baseball fans have watched
it.
But it's a movie that will resonate with
those who don't know much about
baseball.
I've watched this movie many times.
It's Coco Chanel.
I'd like you to watch it.
I was really impressed by the way Chanel
lived.
I went to Chanel and asked the store
clerk what the meaning of the cosmetics
was.
I asked the store clerk how the letters
of the perfume were arranged.
Does the Chanel store clerk know that?
Yes, she knows and tells me everything.
Especially, the perfume has a story and
meaning.
I'm really happy to hear that.
I'm impressed.
I think so, too.
There is a perfume called Boy by Chanel.
If you know the story of Chanel, you
will be more like Chanel.
Please ask the store clerk.
What is the most embarrassing thing
you've ever done?
I'm embarrassed if I say it in Kanagawa
Prefecture.
What is the most embarrassing thing
you've ever done?