Hamamachi Yuka & sozialBoth
So, what's the third one?
The third one is gummy!
I think a lot of fans already know this,
but
I eat gummy every day and post it on my
Instagram story
It's been a hot topic among fans
They were expecting me to eat gummy,
saying it's the gummy challenge tomorrow
I also got a T-shirt from the Japan
Gummy Association
Really?
Yes
That's the real one!
I also found out about the Japan Gummy
Association
I think there are a lot of gummy in it
I brought a lot of gummy today
Show me
My favorite gummy is this one
Your favorite gummy?
Yes, my favorite gummy is Dark Cherry's
Fruity Gummy
I love this one
I love it so much that I bought a lot
Wow, you brought so many!
Calm down, it's not just talking
Sorry
It's pretty good
It's good!
I brought all the gummy that I had at
home
That's amazing
If you like, I can give you one
Thank you! I haven't eaten it at night
Please try it
You already had it at home?
Yes, I love this gummy so much
It's only for a limited time
I bought it because I love it so much
What flavor is it?
It's Dark Cherry
Oh, it's cherry
It's really good
How much do you eat in a day?
I can eat one bag
You eat one bag?
Yes
When I'm hungry, I eat it when I'm at
work
You eat it in a big bite?
I eat it in a big bite
I don't eat it in a big bite
Oh, you don't eat it in a big bite
I eat it
But it's not...
You bite it, right?
I bite it, so it fills my stomach
I see
I eat it a little bit and it fills my
stomach
You get fat as soon as you swallow it
I understand
But it's not like your jaw has developed
because you're biting it
You have to thank your parents
You have a really nice face
Thank you
Do all the members like gummy bears?
I'm not a big fan of gummy bears
I didn't eat a lot of gummy bears
But I have a gummy bear now
That's my favorite
You didn't eat any gummy bears?
I did
You let them eat it?
It's my lulihara
My luliharassment
Luliharassment?
I think it's good
You communicate with them
There are other groups in the sub-plans
Do you meet people who like gummy bears?
I met Yuzuki Mia from Crown Pop
I got this gummy bear for my birthday
Is that a birthday present?
Yes, I got this and this
But I couldn't eat it because it was a
waste
That's a gummy bear from 2 months ago
No
3 months ago
That was in July
But I'm still on my period
It's a snack so it's fine
I'm happy that I can't eat it
That's right
I see
Yuzuki knows that you like gummy bears
And you get a present
Aoi is compatible with a camera
It's made of gummy bears
Please wait for another government open
Sneezing
Hurry up and speak
She is ok after eating
This program is
Hanari-san
Ichine Gumi Drill Sensei-san
Biriyani no Kami-san
Hishimoto Riro-san
Eto-san
I've been providing these.
Today's recommended gummy is...
Mizugumi's Grape Flavor.
Everyone, please try it out.
Thank you very much.