This week's Ebichu Tastas is the end of
Fuyuen 2017.
They split into three teams and relax on
the swan boat.
Or so it should be.
We are the best team.
What is it?
Ebichu Tastas, start!
Bonus
I'm so into you that I can't even
breathe
What should I do with my heart that's
filled with tubulin?
Monotrium, monotrium, monotrium, middle
school students
Try adding all kinds of things to your
private Ebisu middle school!
Ebisu Middle School!
This program is brought to you by these
sponsors.
The members enjoyed the Tokyo Doitsumura
so much in the winter festival, Fuyuen.
The sun is about to set.
We've come to the end of the winter
festival in Tokyo Doitsumura.
The sun is about to set and it's getting
cold.
Everything was cold.
Everything was cold, but no one was
cold.
Lastly, it's time for a boat ride.
You can ride a tour boat and talk about
things you don't usually talk about.
You can talk about anything.
Let's go.
The last part of the winter festival is
a relaxing talk with the members.
The last time, Matsuno was absent, so
the members who are on the boat are
the youngest Nakayama and the oldest
Mayama.
Hirota and Hoshina, who formed a unit at
the end of last year's college game.
The last is the three people who look
lively, Yasumoto, Kobayashi, and
Kashiwagi.
Please go!
Let's go
Let's start our relaxing talk time on
the boat.
It's time to relax on the boat.
What are we talking about?
What did we talk about last time?
Last time?
We talked about the hotel.
A year ago,
on the Ferris wheel talk on the boat.
Yasumoto and Kobayashi are...
Funny Soon
Like this.
LOL
Thank you!
I'm tired again.
I'm tired.
Oh, no.
Meanwhile...
I'm hungry.
We didn't have enough food to cook.
It was delicious.
We should have had more rice.
We didn't have enough time to eat.
I was cooking.
I was grilling the fish.
I'm hungry.
Next, the pair who began the chit-chat
with theداhos,
Pat is saying…
We'll really well in this game!
She clashed the boat of Mayama and
Nakayama.
In addition,
We can move from here
Let's go together
I'll go first
I'm going first
Why are you following me?
What's going on?
I'm going first
Let's do it again
Sorry, I'm so tired
I went the wrong way
Can you do it?
I can
Wait a minute
We are all in the same row
Chuu-en, who was looking at the members
who were too free,
Hi, everyone!
Since we're a pair, please let us go.
What are you doing?
It's like a Mercedes logo.
So the three groups were separated and
reunited.
I'm dancing.
How was it today?
Today?
Which part was the best?
I think Shibasuri was the best
Shibasuri was the best?
It was so hard to ride
At first, I couldn't ride straight
I started to ride in the back
I thought I would fall down, but I was
able to ride fast
I think it's better to ride in the front
I feel like everyone is here
Mayama and Riko's pair is quite
surprising
It's a strange feeling
This pair is a combination that members
think is rare
What if we add Mayama to M2?
What if we do that?
What do you want to do?
What should we do?
What do you want to do with 8 yen?
We will rent a hotel in Naska and make
something
We will make a message from the ground
We will make a huge domino
I want to do it
It's hard
Please subscribe to our channel!
What do you want to add next?
What do you want to add?
They are also talking about what they
want to add.
I want to add a lot.
I don't know what I want to add.
I don't know.
I want to add a job experience.
I want to go back to the beginning.
I think it's good to go back to the
beginning.
But, I want to add a staff experience.
I don't know.
I want to add it, but I don't usually do
it.
I want to make a video with everyone.
I want to add a live performance.
I want to make a plan for a live
performance.
I want to make a live performance.
We can practice together.
Then, we can make a plan.
We have to do the Moratorium of TAKIUE.
We have to learn the Moratorium of
TAKIUE.
What is the Moratorium of TAKIUE?
In the previous trial, TAKIUE was
accused of being affectionate towards
Ebichu.
He was sentenced to life in prison.
As a result...
TAKIUE will be in prison for a month.
So, if Tastas Live is realized,
Takiue's Cancopy Moratorium Junior High
School may be unveiled.
Isn't it good?
It's good.
The universe plus the doggie world.
Yeah, it's decided.
It's decided.
It will be held in the fall of this
year.
year, 2017.
Everyone, look forward to it.
We are waiting for you.
And the one who will take care of the
boat is Tashiwagi.
The driving skill is not good.
I think I will be in trouble if I get in
the car.
Can I get a driver's license?
Yes, you can.
I want to get a driver's license.
I'm worried about the car.
I think it's dangerous.
I will drive.
I have been longing for driving since I
was a child.
You are cool.
I thought that a man should drive.
I have the image of a father.
I thought that it was cool when a woman
drove.
I thought that I would like to drive
when I grow up.
I'm nervous when I get on the boat.
I want to drive with the members.
I want to drive with this camera.
It would be nice if everyone's age
increased.
It may be possible.
Will they be able to drive?
On the other hand...
I'm getting sleepy.
No, you're still working.
You're still working.
What do you want to do?
I want to do something like a
staycation.
That's good.
I went to Eritrea once.
I want to set up a camera in my room and
take a video of us staying there.
That sounds fun.
We can share a house.
I want to stay at someone's house.
That's good.
I want you to stay at my house.
I want to.
I haven't called you yet.
I might be a little late.
I'm not sure.
OK.
I'm going.
That's good.
It's not like we're all together all
day.
We say goodbye halfway.
We go home.
I wonder what it's like to be together
all day.
It must be fun to be with people who are
sick.
It's hard to be sick.
I have a bad sleeping habit.
While they're talking about the
staycation,
they're talking about when Kashiwagi and
Yasumoto shared a room at the hotel.
I had a sexy pose once.
Really?
I was like this.
I think it was the first time we shared
a room.
I was told that I had a bad sleeping
habit.
But we couldn't sleep in the same bed.
I was like, I'm fine.
I didn't have a bad sleeping habit.
Aya and I sleep until the last minute.
I wake up early.
I look at the wall and my legs are up.
I put my hands on my head and it feels
good.
That's amazing.
I want to put my hands under the
macaroon.
I put my hands under the macaroon.
It's warm and comfortable when I put my
hands under the macaroon.
I used to have a bad sleeping habit.
I used to fall down and my bed was torn.
I used to sleep with my face up.
But I've been sleeping with my face down
for about half a year.
I'm sure I'll get sick.
I'm not a sick person.
I don't think I'll get sick when I wake
up.
I sometimes sleep like a crushed frog.
I do.
I do sometimes.
The three are excited about the story of
sleeping habits.
Hoshina and Hirota are talking about the
live performance this month.
It's not me. It's Taekwon Live.
Ebichu has been participating in Taiwan
festivals for two consecutive years.
This year, they will hold their first
one-man live.
I've never been to Taiwan.
It's the first time, and it's warm.
But it's colder than here.
It's warm. It's easy to live.
Ko-chan said she wanted to participate
in Taiwan's Sudden Death.
I said that.
I really like Sudden Death.
I think it's a great song.
I'm glad that we can do another exciting
song like that.
I think it's going to be a great song.
I'm looking forward to the live
performance.
I really like Sudden Death.
I want to do a live performance of the
real-time version of Sudden Death.
At the end, when there are two people
left, I want to revive the loser.
Revival
If I revive, I'll be a loser.
And these two people.
The spring tour was very...
The spring tour last year left a lot of
challenges.
I'm a college student.
So I want to do my best.
There are many places this time, and
there are places for the first time.
I'm glad that Riko-chan talked to me a
lot like this.
Thank you.
In this way, the peaceful time goes by
slowly.
Swan boat time is over.
What are these three talking about?
TASU TASU
What do you want to do?
What about this pair?
TASU TASU
What do you want to add?
The topic is the same
And, Mayama and Takayama
Did you guys fight?
No, we didn't
It's getting cold. Are you ok to talk to
us?
Are you ok?
We want to add something
Really?
We are not all here, but we are all here
This is all on air
Look at this, everyone
The illumination
Let's go home
No, we can't
We can't go home
This episode will end when it gets
beautiful
We will go home
After this
Members are screaming
That episode will be
Bring the ladder
We can't go home
They enjoyed the winter park
While they were enjoying the park, a
member was called to a certain venue
Come in
What are you doing? You're late
You're late
Why are you guys late?
The hellish plan was waiting for them
To be continued
Hashiraya-san, you look a little funny
now
What's wrong?
Don't worry!
Take it!
Thank you for watching!
Bring the money!
What's your name?
When did you start?
I'm not sure...
Who are you?
I'm Hayashi Choichoyamon.
We're going to start the second entrance
exam for Shiritsu University.
We did this before.
Do you remember the goal?
If you get 1% correct, you get 99% of
the prize.
Do you remember this?
What's this stupid thing?
It's you!
It's your answer!
Wait, what?
Let's do it again!
Wow!
The entrance exam season has come again
this year!
So, the entrance exam for Ebi University
is held urgently.
How good are their academic abilities?
A year ago, they took the test for the
exams.
The question that determines the growth
of the frog is...
The pearl has appeared.
The result is 1% of flounder and 99%
of...
...pearl!
They got the same answer twice.
They couldn't measure their academic
abilities properly.
How much have they improved in the past
year?
Let's start the exam!
Everyone, this is the second entrance
exam for Shigetsu Ebisu University.
You have 10 points for each question.
If you get 80 points, you pass.
You have earned a reward.
This is the most popular menu of Madame
Shrimp, a Ginza restaurant specializing
in shrimp dishes.
It's a high-class shrimp cutlet
sandwich.
It's 1,600 yen per piece.
It's a good price.
The person with the lowest score will be
given a special treatment to improve
their brain.
Everyone, do your best.
Is it okay to raise the ladder?
You're going to give a difficult
question, right?
A ladder game.
I'm going to give a difficult question.
What should I do if I want to make this
a dog?
Put a pen on the right.
Yes, genius.
As expected, you are a ladder game.
You can do it if you do it.
The shrimp entrance exam has started
with the switch of the ladder game.
The first question is a national
language.
The first question is this.
No.
Describe a beautiful landscape in four
letters.
Five.
Flower.
Wind.
Please write the letters in between.
I forgot.
If you are Japanese, you know this.
Hurry up.
This is easy.
The first one is a hand-waving game.
The correct answer is a bird and a tree.
What is the answer to the question of
common sense?
Ok, everyone has written down the answer
Yes
Yasumoto
Volcanic Balloon
I see
What does it mean?
It represents nature
Beautiful things, flowers, mountains,
wind, river
Japanese wind
It's good to read the river as a line
It means the line of the dragon
That's right
Next, Nakayama-san, please
The name is like a flower
Flower?
You are a singer song writer
Flower
It means the wind
Flowers
Beautiful
Did you make it up by yourself?
Yasumoto-san explained it for some
reason
Ok, Hoshina-san and Mayama-san
Please give us the answer
This one
Kachou Fugetsu
Correct
Congratulations
Ok, I'll turn it over
Here we go
Kachou Fugetsu
It's like a flower, isn't it?
The remaining three answers are as you
can see
Unfortunately, they are not correct
Next, the second question
Good for you
The feeling of being surprised by
something strange
I'm going to play with my belly button
I don't know
That's good, this is an easy one
I can expect this
That's good
I'm worried about the kanji
I don't know at all
If you cheat, you'll die
I don't know
You'll die, so be careful
This is also a service question
The answer is to boil tea with your
belly button
What does the shrimp do with its belly
button?
Let's start with Hirota.
Hirota, what's the strangest thing you
can't get enough of?
Looking at it with your navel.
I see.
Looking at it with your navel?
You look at it here?
Looking at it with my navel.
When it's really bad, I look up so I
can't see it.
Your answer is bad.
And Mayaba.
Yes.
Looking at it with my navel.
Looking at it with your navel?
What does that mean?
When I do muscle training, I'm often
told to look at it with my navel.
It has nothing to do with muscle
training.
But when you're laughing, you look at it
like this.
Yes.
It's strange.
You can't get enough of it.
I see.
And let's look at Nakayama.
Nakayama, here.
I stop laughing with my navel.
You stop laughing with your navel.
I see.
Kashiwagi, you wrote it first.
It was fast.
Kashiwagi, let's go.
Yes.
I dance with my navel.
You dance with your navel.
I see.
It's strange.
Kobayashi, let's go.
I make tea with my navel.
That's correct.
Yasumoto.
Why?
I make tea with my navel.
Following Kobayashi, Yasumoto is also
correct.
Wait a minute.
Challenge time.
You don't need this, do you?
Is this all you need?
Yes, that's all you need.
Well, there's also a question mark,
which is the lower bracket.
They're all wrong.
It's true.
Challenge time.
It's not a big cut, so Kobayashi is
wrong.
It's a big struggle from the beginning.
Last time, Kashiwagi was also
successfully passed the zero-point test.
Who will pass the test?
Next time, more questions will be added!
Think of a sentence using the word, Todo
no Tsumari.
Todo no Tsumari is the meaning of the
show's opening!
Oh, Todo is clogged.
A shocking test of 1 game!
To be continued...
I wonder what it is.
He's preparing.
I can see it.
What is it?
Is alcohol a person with a bad temper?
I think he changes his hairstyle
depending on the season.