Ebichu Tastas has started!
Ebichu Tastas this week is a project
that Hirotano is planning to introduce.
Ebichu Tastas photography!
The members pick a picture of the
picture
Oh, this is good!
Cool!
The members' unexpected talent is
discovered
Ebichu Tastas, start!
The
Evis中学
Add various things to private Evis中学!
This is it!
Oh, camera!
This program is provided by the sponsor
you see.
This again! In a row!
If you take it a little bit more
slanted...
Thank you for watching!
Today, I, Hiroto, will be singing a song
Thank you
And the star of Nagareboshi, Taki Yuya
and Chuu-e
We will attack each other
Spring break, I will be singing Chuu-e
Today we went to school, what are we
doing today?
This is it
Camera
This time we are going to explore space
with a photo
I see
Why is the photo the theme?
There was a guy talking in the Ferris
wheel
At that time, I talked with Riko-chan
about being into photography
When she was enjoying the Ferris wheel
in the winter, when she was enjoying the
Ferris wheel in the winter,
Kino-tao talked about this
I thought cameras were good recently
I thought I would use it for the train
I thought it would be nice to take
photos of people
Hirota, who was only interested in
trains, wants to take photos of people
Hirota's wish came true and the project
was born
Hirota, is this your camera?
Yes, I bought it myself
What did you take with that camera?
My favorite photo is this one
Ta-da
Wow, it's beautiful
It's quite serious
Where did you take this photo?
I went to Kagawa prefecture
Kagawa?
Kotoden
By the way, what's your favorite point?
My favorite point is
The backlight
The face
The shadow
It's good for the backlight
You call it face?
I thought you said face
I thought it was Thomas
Thank you
This time, I brought a favorite photo of
everyone in your smartphone
It's good, this will show your
personality
I'm looking forward to it
First, check the members' private photos
From the photos in the smartphone, they
chose the most favorite
The big selection, Ebichu smartphone
photo studio
First, this
Who is this?
First, the victim is not a doll
No
Is it different?
This is Yasumoto
It's Yasumoto, right?
The one who took it was?
My father
So this is Yasumoto's photo
Favorite photo
You brought your favorite photo
I don't know, I don't take many photos
I'm grilling shrimp
You're grilling shrimp
I see
I brought shrimp only in Ebichu
That's the point of attention
Then, Matsuno found something
Matsuno, what happened?
Something that I was curious about
What happened?
I was looking for my father
Where?
Here?
Yes
Is this your father?
This is your father
It's like your father is looking at the
front of the room
It's amazing
Everyone is aware of it
It's like a ghost photo
It's really amazing, Matsuno
You noticed it well
Thank you
The next picture is this
This is continuous
Who is this picture?
Kobayashi-san
The student took a picture of the
teacher
At the Shinkansen station
Where do you know that Hirota is from
Shinkansen?
I don't know
I know Shinkansen but it's not Shinagawa
I recommend the angle and the face
The face is a bit cold
I really like this
I want to use it as a stamp in a
conversation with my mom
I'll use it by myself
What kind of stamp do you use?
I don't like the feeling of going home
now
Yasumoto-san, did you know that?
I didn't know
You're a stamp girl
I'm happy
Isn't this the picture of your dad?
No, it's not
It's the green one
I think your dad isn't here
You're a stamp girl
You can use it in a conversation
What do you want for dinner today?
Nothing
You can use this picture again
It's not a snake
Let's take a picture together
The next picture is this
Amazing
Is this a waterfall?
Whose picture is this?
It's mine
Mayama
What is this? Where is this?
This is when I went to Haruhi-zawa with
my family on a trip
There is a white-threaded waterfall
It is in the middle of the white-
threaded waterfall
It's not a white-threaded waterfall?
Oh, I see
It's very confusing
Why do you like this?
I like the sound of water
I've been playing the sound of water at
home
I'm sorry
Wait a minute
I've been playing the sound of water
It's a healing sound
I've been playing that sound
I think I can hear it now
That's true
This is it
But it's a little slanted, isn't it?
If you take it a little slanted, it
looks cool
It's difficult to see
It's a little fashionable
It's fashionable
I wonder if you can make the waterfall
in the middle
That's wrong
That's why it's called a waterfall
I'm sorry
I'm not talking about myself
I know
The next picture is this
This is nice
Cool
This is?
Yes
Matsuno's picture
This is also Matsuno's picture
This is me
When I was in Kawakura and Shonan, this
is a story from last summer
I was taking a picture with my friend
Your friend took it?
Yes
Amazing
It was very beautiful
I thought it was nice to eat
I see
You're eating the sun
I'm eating the sun
You didn't take a picture of the light
coming in the last minute?
I'm eating the sun
The next photo is this
What is this?
This is it!
It's a bedclothes
The color is amazing
It's very cool
It's pastel color
Who is this?
Hoshino
This is a slope along the sea
It's like a stable
Yes
There is a bed there, and I was told to
take a picture
When I was taking a picture of Rina,
Riko was taking a picture from above
I see
I put a filter
It looks fashionable
I don't know what to do because I wear a
normal one
Let's do it again
It's normal
But everyone has their own taste
Yes
Next is this one
It's so beautiful
Wait a minute, who is this?
What is this? Is this Nakayama?
Mizocchi took it for me
It's like a photo book
It's like a photo book, like a shampoo
commercial
It's a very suitable one
There is a catch copy here
Amazing!
I gave the camera to Mizocchi
Mizocchi took it for me
Mizocchi screamed
At the moment?
I was surprised
I was like, I took a great photo
Amazing!
So cute!
Mizocchi took a photo of a miracle
This frame is also good
There is a movement in the photo
The white is also good
Next is this
This is also amazing, who is this?
Hirota
Yes
What is this?
It's a
It's so cool
What is this? This is not a photo that
can be taken aimlessly
Where is this?
This is a photo taken by everyone
I went to Atami
At that time, I got on a boat
Like this
Where the birds come, it's like a bait
It's like a bait
It's amazing composition
It can be sold as a puzzle
That's right
I think this is amazing
I want to see the second best friend
again
No
It's good
It's like a bridge
I want this puzzle too
Next is the last picture
This one
Who is this?
Is this a knife?
It's a knife
What is this?
It's a line
When we were at Saitama
When everyone was taking a break
The line of the shiver was stuck
It's the line of the transceiver
I couldn't move
It's stuck here
It's stuck
It was a big explosion
The moment it went like this
The director was like
It's the face when you move
I was in a big explosion
I couldn't take it
Please let me take a picture first
It's done
This is good
I'm not a robot in charge of charging
I'm just looking at it
I'm confused
I can imagine the expression here
So
Each member showed their favorite
picture
Next
Idol who can always take pictures
They showed each other their favorite
picture
tell me
I'm not sure, but I'm sure I'll get it.
I'm sure I'll get it.
I'll get it.
Is there a mouth?
Muneo-chan, wait a minute
What are you doing?
Muneo-chan is
Something like
Ah
This is the point
I'm doing it
Because
I'm doing it unconsciously
I don't know
Right and left move together
Something is moving
Ah, like this
Like this
I see, what is this star?
If you do this, you do this
It's connected
I see
I also do this
No
It's a moment
It's not the same
It's the same
Next, Kashiwagi shows his face
3, 2, 1, go!
I feel like I've won
Matsu-kun's good
What's wrong?
You two are doing it
Yes, we are
It's a collaboration
Kashiwagi has been chosen as the junior
of the junior high school
He has a very special face
Let's see
Kashiwagi's face is a little different
I'm going to do it seriously
The broadcast is a mosaic
Just look at it
The mosaic is a stardust
But I think Mizuchi has given up
Let's see
The pose of the two of you
3, 2, 1, go!
No
This is the pose I taught yesterday
You taught it
No, no
No more in front of Mizuchi
Mizuchi gave up
Now, it's time for the members' wish
Let's have a photo contest for the photo
contest
After this, the members will take a
photo of each other
What kind of photo will they take?
It's amazing
The photo contest is over
Now, it's a member's wish project
I would like to hold a photo contest for
the pair photo shoot
Everyone said they wanted to do it
This contest is for each member to
choose a camera they like
The pair will be separated and the
photos will be taken together
The stage is school
The winner will be the one who can use
various situations such as classrooms,
roofs, gymnasiums to take the most cute
photos of the members who become models.
The winner will be the one who can use
various situations such as classrooms,
roofs, gymnasiums to take the most cute
photos of the members.
The winner will be the one who can use
various situations such as classrooms,
roofs, gymnasiums to take the most cute
photos of the members.
Hello, are you Mr.Kunitake?
Yes, I am.
Thank you for your evaluation.
Thank you.
First, let's start with the pair of
fate.
The result of the lottery is...
Mayama Matsuno pair.
Kobayashi Nakayama pair.
Yasumoto Kashiwagi pair.
And...
Hirota Hoshina pair.
Let's start!
Finally, the Ebi-chu photo contest
starts!
First, Mayama and Matsunopuya chose a
photo spot for their photo shoot
It's a shoe box
I'll take a photo of you
Good
I like the photo
It's the second photo
I'll take a photo of you
I like the image of Rina in me.
I like the image of a model Rina.
I was eating.
Mayama continues to cut the shutter with
a serious expression.
What kind of photos are taken?
I feel uncomfortable with the coat
I feel uncomfortable with the cloak.
Next, Hirota and Hoshina pair chose a
place to shoot.
Classroom
First, Hoshina produces Hirota.
Take off the cloak.
I'll take it off without permission.
I have to take off the cloak.
It's a atmosphere.
They start shooting without the cloak.
Let's go.
Let's take a picture of the setting.
OK.
Let's take a picture.
Hoshina is already having an image in
her head.
She gives detailed instructions on
setting, pose, and facial expressions.
Oh, you know?
Yes, I know.
The key point is to look from the
shadows.
If you like Aika, you can take a
picture.
I'm scared.
You look like you're looking at Aika.
It's like a peek.
Next, they came to the smoking area
where Mayama and Matsuno were shooting.
It's hard, so I'll do it like this.
Oh, good.
I want to try it.
Good.
Ready, set, go.
Aika is only taking pictures of her
fluttering.
It's dark here.
I'll do it a little brighter.
On the other hand, Kobayashi-Nakayama
pair
Choose the room.
What kind of photo does Kobayashi want
to take here?
I want to put Riko-chan in this.
What is the meaning of putting Nakayama
in?
I don't know Riko-chan.
The question is alsobye...
I don't know what to do.
It's in my face.
Just like this.
This is a little more like this.
Isn't it good?
It's amazing.
Memory is currently working artifacts.
But it's amazing.
It's a good work that makes you think of
it as the best.
Once again, Nakayama goes into the
flask.
Okay, let's go.
Cheese.
It fits.
I think it's better than before.
I want to do this.
What are you laughing at?
Anyway, I'm satisfied with Nakayama.
I can't see his face.
And the place where Yasumoto and
Kashiwagi Pia chose to shoot is...
The gym.
It's very wintery.
What do you want?
Do your best, Riai-chan.
Is it better to do it with both hands?
Yes, both hands.
You're facing up.
It's cute that you're facing up.
Yasumoto is struggling to find the right
angle.
Oh, I did it wrong
Oh, the video has started
Why?
Oh, I did it wrong
Oh, the video has started
Why? I don't need this kind of video
I fixed it
Yasumoto doesn't understand how to use
the camera
Please subscribe to my channel
Please dance here
Dance?
Please spin around
Next, Yasumoto's instruction to
Kashiwaki is dance
It seems difficult to take a video even
for free
Scary
I can do it
I can do it like this
They take a lot of photos that they
can't even recognize
Will they be able to take a cute
Kashiwaki photo?
To be continued
Next episode of Ebichu Tastas
Ebichu Tastas photo
Thank you for watching.
Ready, set, go!
It's not going to work!
The first round is over!