Yakan and idol!
That's it for the ending. Do you have
any news?
Yes, I do. On Sunday, October 23, 2022,
we will be performing at Sanrio
Puroland.
That's a dream country!
We will be performing with Cinnamon Roll
and Pocacko.
I think we will be able to see cute
Kurako.
We want to do a cute performance on this
stage.
Please come to our show.
And the Crown Pop Tour will start in
January.
We will be performing in January and
February.
And one more thing.
We will be releasing an album in this
winter.
We will also be releasing a DVD of the
performance we just did.
That's great.
We want to hear more about Kurako.
I'm very interested.
Thank you.
I don't talk about myself much.
I'm a bit shy.
But we want to hear from you.
I want to talk to you.
That's it for Yakan and idol.
Today, we had Yakan, Kajuta, and Airi.
Bye bye. Thank you.
Thank you.
The end.
In Tokyo, people ask if it's okay to
make a Tokyo branch.
But I'll say no.
You'll say no?
I'm not a good person.
I'm in the batting team.
I'm not like them.
I want to see Seta without the mitt.
I'm told I'm not like Seta.
Yakan and idol.