Yakan and idol!
Now, let's move on to the main event!
Please call the title of the event!
Yes! My three factors!
Oh, you're so cool!
I feel like I'm strong!
Now, let's hear from Yatomori!
Here it is!
Ta-dah!
Can you say the three letters from the
top?
Okay!
Gyal!
Inaka!
Amato!
That's cute!
Thank you!
First up!
Gyaru!
This is Yasumori-san's big name.
Yes, it is.
When it comes to me, it's Gyaru.
Gyaru Mori.
Yes, that's right.
The nickname Gyaru Mori is a necessary
Gyaru for my character.
But when did I become a Gyaru?
I'd like to hear about it.
I was originally scouted and forced to
become an idol.
I think it's a good way to express it.
When you joined the entertainment
agency, you didn't think you were an
idol.
That's right.
I wanted to do anything.
I was interested in anything.
You were interested in entertainment.
That's right.
I didn't expect it to be like this.
But I thought it would be fun.
I was curious.
You were positive.
Yes, I auditioned.
At that time, I was a model-career type.
I see.
I wasn't good at being an idol.
I couldn't do what an idol should do.
I was very reluctant to do cute things.
But I thought, if I couldn't do it, what
kind of character should I be?
I was attracted to cool women.
I was attracted to strong and cool
women.
I thought I'd be a cool woman.
At that time, I was still bare-faced.
That's right.
When I was allowed to wear makeup, I
decided to be strong.
It's hard to say.
I don't know what kind of entertainment
it is.
I don't know because it's too
mysterious.
You were bare-faced.
When I was bare-faced, I was allowed to
wear makeup.
I decided to wear cool makeup and be
strong.
I was in the first year of high school.
I see.
I was in the first year of high school
when I started to wear cool makeup.
I was 16 years old.
I see.
I wasn't aware of cool makeup at that
time.
But a customer told me that there was a
cool girl.
I thought, isn't that a cool girl?
I thought, isn't there a cool girl?
That's strange.
I noticed that the customer was saying
that.
I thought, this is a cool girl.
I decided to be a cool girl.
I see.
I became a cool girl.
That's right.
I became a cool girl because of your
support.
The reason I became a cool girl is
because each of us has a strong
personality.
If I were a cute girl, I wouldn't be
here.
I can be a cool girl because each of us
has a strong personality.
I can do what I want to do.
I'm glad that you recognize me as a cool
girl.
I'm glad.
Thank you.
You're a good person.
See you again.
I'm not a neighbor, but I live near my
house.
I don't have a map.
You don't have a map?
You like it, don't you?
This program is
Neko-san
Kazuma-san
Seiten-san
Yakkuru-san
We have prepared souvenir box.
Thank you! Let's meet at the live!