This time
сообщ
They are very close to each other
Furthermore
We are Shiritse Ebichu Junior High
School
We are the reverse
Ebichu Junior High School
You are very happy
With the cooperation of TV Kanagawa-san
Emma and Yuna's first appearance
Special appearance to all the members of
the country
I can't see the change
I've never seen the change
The members of the country are very
close to each other
I thought
Please look forward to the next episode
She becomes a morning official
Good morning
You have name from a movie
Alright, tell us how it feels
Let's take the theatre
Ok
She's excited
I'm incredible
I'm great
Thank you for watching!
Thank you very much
Good morning
Today is the recording of Kannai Devil
I was thinking why I should do it
I was nervous and I was about to freeze
I will do my best not to freeze
New members have visited
TV Kanagawa where recording of Kannai
Devil is going on
Kannai Devil is a cafe in Yokohama
Music information variety where masters
and guests are giving free talk without
a script
It looks like you are wearing it
The members are also working part-time
jobs
The two new members who are performing
for the first time this time are still
in the process of being selected
This is Yono-chan
Oh, it's Yono-chan
Yes
It's perfect
It's pretty perfect
Yes
O..one is here!
First, we will take a photo using the
program's website
Everyone, what is the meaning of Hido
Aya Raki?
I don't know
Yes, please take a look
Please show us your various poses
I will do it with all my heart
I can't do it myself
Hido Aya Raki's Do
Do is?
Do
Do is
What was your last word?
I understood it
I understand it
Thank you for watching!
Tsuyoshi Watanabe
Srieben by yeti
Cute
Kururu Kofei
I'm not sure if I can do it.
I'm not sure.
He's shaking with his heels.
Isn't it cute?
He's shaking his feet.
Thank you for watching.
At the same time, Emma is creating a
history book that she uses in the
program.
If this is a name, Hikahira Gana, is it
okay to just have the name Furigana?
I've already made all the radio.
But I don't know how to say it on TV.
I usually watch it myself, but I don't
know how to say it.
What should I do if I'm in trouble?
I'll go home for now.
What?
Master
Nice to meet you, I'm Yuma Sakura
Nice to meet you
I'm Yuma Sakura, nice to meet you
I'm Mami Saburo, nice to meet you
Yuma also changes into her costume and
takes pictures
euro
Let's do it with a different feeling.
Change the feeling of the foot.
what's wrong with him?
Thank you for watching!
I don't have a phone, so I don't speak.
If I don't speak, I have nothing.
I want you to say something interesting.
Something interesting is something that
makes you laugh.
Good morning.
I'm going to the TV.
Finally, they are going to try to record
for the first time.
Thank you.
This time, they will deliver the first
broadcast.
New members of Ebichu.
That's right.
Sakurai Emma and Yuna Nakamura from
Shiritu Ebichu Middle School came.
Thank you.
We are Shiritu Ebichu Middle School.
We are Ebichu.
It's delicious.
I'm nervous.
I'm not satisfied that they are a little
off.
Cute.
If we get a little more time, we will
meet.
We only have this moment.
They are professionals.
They are fast.
Thank you.
They are Shiritu Ebichu Middle School.
They will work at this company.
We will give you a release award.
She has a qualification.
What is it?
Amazing.
Sakurai-san, A-ken 3-kyu.
No, Kanken 3-kyu.
A-ken is also 3-kyu.
Kanken A-ken 3-kyu.
Kendama is also 4-kyu.
Is there a Kendama competition?
I'm going to the school.
That's the standard of school.
I'm going to 4-kyu.
Kendama, come here.
Please give me a Kendama.
Thank you.
It's a little difficult to do.
This is the big plate.
There is a big plate.
Please.
Amazing.
Is that so?
There are various things.
She has various hobbies and specialties.
By the way, Nakamura-san.
She plays with a dog that she is
interested in.
Sometimes she goes fishing.
Her special skills are standing bridge.
And hula hoop.
She has a strange face.
I don't think she has a strange face.
I've never seen a strange face.
If you have a strange face, you can
destroy it.
You should do this.
This?
If you put shrimp in it, it's NG.
It doesn't exist.
Let's do it.
Ready, go.
It was more strange than I thought.
I was getting a cold.
This was a special skill.
There is a desire.
We are doing it as a store.
That's right.
I felt the momentum.
I'm already wearing a uniform.
That's strange.
Why are you wearing a uniform before you
put out the certificate?
I'm not a restaurant worker.
You are a person who can't say no.
I thought it was strange when I entered
the store.
That's it.
That's good.
It's a good thing.
It looks good on you.
The show was exciting and ended safely.
That's good.
Thank you.
That's all for the two of you.
They asked EMMA and YUNA about their
impressions.
The wind was refreshing.
It was cute.
I'm not saying that MAYAMAYAMAN is not
refreshing.
I'm sorry.
I thought it wasn't there.
But it was amazing.
They were very cute.
The last time we were together, we were
very cute.
But when I came alone, they were very
cute.
They are very cute.
They were very cute.
I said it many times.
They have a lot of potential.
I think I will lose if I fight.
I think I will lose.
I will not fight.
I think they have a gap.
I'm looking forward to it.
I was the first to appear on the show.
I was hiding.
I didn't have a chance to announce it.
I will enter the shift and show my true
self.
I'm looking forward to being with you.
Yes.
They finished recording.
I was so excited.
I was thinking about what to say, but I
was so excited.
They talked to me a lot and I was happy
to talk to them.
I didn't know about KENDA, but I was
surprised.
I'm glad I was able to talk to them.
I'm still nervous.
I'm nervous because I'm alone.
But I'll do my best.
Next time, the last episode of Zenmashi
MIX.
December 14th, Wednesday night live.