Ebichu's videos.
My name is Ayaka Yasumoto and I'm in the
5th grade of junior high school.
I started to eat a lot when I was young.
I ate a lot of tomatoes and drank a lot
of tomato juice.
I arranged how many tomatoes I could
eat.
That's right.
It was the worst.
It was difficult.
I got about 10 points.
I'm still waiting for 100 points.
That's right. It's important.
I want to give it to him.
I think it's important to convey the
deliciousness.
I often do food reviews of a project
that is a little bit like a story, such
as trying to eat it with a combination
that looks a little bad.
So I haven't done much food reviews of
eating really delicious food.
I think the reaction is big, so I think
I can convey the deliciousness if I can
convey it honestly.
Is it a meal report?
I was ready to eat.
I will do my best to do a meal report.
Yasu eats!
I call people and I'm Yasu of Mekiki.
I will do a meal report.
First of all, I will eat this first cut
beef tongue steak bento.
I will eat this.
I like beef tongue.
I want to eat this as it is because it
has chopsticks.
It smells good.
I'm tired.
Can I eat this?
This is thick.
I have a high image of thick beef
tongue.
I like beef tongue.
It looks expensive.
This rice with chilli miso is delicious.
I know it's delicious.
I'm sorry I can't eat it.
I'll do my best.
I wonder how it tastes.
I think the box is important.
The box?
The box is not that expensive.
It looks soft.
I can tell it's soft and delicious.
I can't stop eating this saltiness and
flavor.
After I finish eating this, I put rice
in this bowl and I can eat the rest of
the rice.
I want to eat it!
How sad...
Hey, Kiki. Is this a food review?
I didn't eat anything.
Udon is almost gone.
I want to eat the・
I'm going to open the next lunch box.
I'm a commoner, so I know that the food
in this box is expensive.
The material of the paper is...
I'm going to open it because I don't
want to be found out.
Open!
It looks delicious!
What is this?
Japanese food is...
It's like a Japanese-style Gozen.
It's a bento box like this.
It's great to have two kinds of rice in
a bento box.
I want to eat it.
Why can't I eat it?
I usually eat like this and taste it.
I can finally tell you how delicious it
is.
But it's not enough.
I can tell you how delicious it is just
by looking at it.
That's what a professional does.
The one with yuba is expensive.
This is yuba, isn't it?
And it's grilled.
Japanese food is carefully colored like
this.
Bento boxes are usually expensive and
delicious.
What is this?
I don't know what this is.
I don't eat this, so I don't know what
it is.
What is this?
I like this kind of bento because it is
elegant to eat a little bit of various
things.
It's good to eat one by one, but I like
to enjoy various flavors like this.
Colorful bento is beautiful, so I think
girls will like it.
Next, I will eat a burger.
This is written Tokyo Ebisu.
I've been to this store many times, but
I've never been there because it looks
expensive.
It looks delicious! I've never seen it
before!
I've been looking at the food samples.
There are always a lot of customers.
It's definitely delicious.
It says 100% hamburger.
It's a set of hamburgers like this.
The potatoes look delicious!
I'll have the main hamburger.
Ta-da!
Well, it's a take-out.
It looks delicious!
Is it tartar sauce?
I really want to eat it!
I want to eat it!
I've come this far and it looks so good!
The meat is thick and the tartar sauce
is also very unique.
I don't know because I haven't eaten it
yet, but it looks like a unique tartar
sauce.
It looks so good.
It looks very simple, so I'm sure it's a
hamburger that you can enjoy the taste
of meat to the fullest.
I don't know what I'm doing.
It looks delicious! I want to eat it!
Look at the potatoes.
I think it's fried.
It looks healthy.
It looks like it's grilled.
It looks like it has a lot of tartar
sauce.
I'm going to open it now.
I can see a little bit.
I'm going to open it.
It smells good!
The smell of the demi-glace sauce is
good.
I think you can tell just by looking at
it.
There's a lot of side dishes.
I love everyone.
Napolitan, hamburger, fried shrimp.
And here's the shogayaki.
It's got meat in it.
It's gorgeous.
It looks delicious.
Is it a macaroni salad?
I can't see it from here, but there's
fish in it.
No, it was a potato. I'm sorry.
It was a potato.
It's gorgeous.
It looks delicious.
When it comes to bento, I want to eat
rice deliciously until the end.
I'm glad that there is a kelp on the
rice.
It's delicious.
I can't eat it because I don't want to
eat it soon.
I can't eat it.
I like this pasta in this bento.
It looks delicious.
I think this is vinegar.
It's good.
I think I want to eat meat and pasta.
I eat vegetables at that time.
This is a very good balance.
It's a lunch box.
I haven't eaten it, so I don't know.
I'm going to open the lunch box that I
was most curious about.
What a surprise!
It's a double-decker.
I have to open this one, too.
Open!
Look at this double-decker lunch box.
I'm excited about the double-decker
lunch box.
I tend to choose fish in my lunch box.
If the fish is delicious, I trust the
lunch box.
I don't know.
This is a Saikyo-yaki lunch box.
This is also very colorful.
It looks delicious.
It's very simple and I think you can
taste the fish.
There are eggs and celery.
I can eat various things.
I think this lunch box is the healthiest
and most balanced.
I can eat this while I'm on a diet.
The rice looks delicious.
I was most curious about this double-
decker lunch box.
I can't eat it.
It looks delicious.
I wanted to say it's delicious.
I wanted to say it's delicious, but it
looks delicious.
It looks very delicious.
Did I think about the ranking?
I did a ranking.
I will do my best.
I will guess the ranking of the lunch
boxes.
I will guess the 5th place.
I think this is the one.
I like beef tongue.
But this is the one that I ate the
least.
So I think this is the cheapest one.
The 4th place is...
This one?
This one has a lot of side dishes.
This one has all the side dishes that
everyone loves.
I think this is a bento that everyone
wants to eat.
And the third place is...
The third place is...
This one?
I thought this was the first place at
first.
I thought so at first.
But when I looked at the whole thing...
I think this is the third one.
But it's pretty luxurious to have two of
these, so I'm not sure.
And then the second one is...
This one.
This is a hamburger.
If you compare it with a lunch box and a
hamburger, I think fast food is more
affordable.
But I'm using 100% black beef, which is
a great meat.
I think it's a good deal.
And the first one is this one.
It's the most colorful Japanese food
lunch box.
After all, this Yuba is a luxury.
There are a lot of side dishes, and I
feel like it's taking a lot of time.
There are two kinds of rice in the
process of making it.
I think this is the first place.
I've been predicting from 5th to 1st
place so far.
I'd like to hear the results.
I didn't know at all.
That's right. It's fast food.
My guess is that it's going to be 1,800
yen.
I was pretty sure it was going to be
expensive.
It's a great deal for 1,500 yen.
1,100 yen
I'm right, right?
Yay!
I think I'm doing well.
I'm in the third place.
I'm in the third place, right?
I'm doing well.
I thought I was in the first place at
first.
I'm glad I changed it here.
I'm in the third place.
I think so.
GYUTA is expensive.
I'm in the fourth place.
This is the third place.
This is a different color.
This is shining alone.
Is this okay?
I did it.
I'm in the fourth place.
I will eat this expensive eel bento as a
reward.
I'm finally eating this.
I eat this.
I open this.
This is warm.
Please look at this.
This is a rich eel.
This has a good scent.
It has a fragrant scent.
I will eat this eel.
Can I eat this eel?
I can't eat this eel.
This is a very luxurious chopstick.
I will eat this eel.
I can finally eat this eel.
This is amazing.
I heard that I would do a food report
while shooting this video.
I slept through the morning and
afternoon.
Then I was exhausted.
So I can finally eat this eel.
This looks delicious.
I eat eel.
This is very soft.
I eat this.
It's delicious.
I'm sorry. I'm a girl, but I can't say
it's delicious.
It's really delicious.
I wonder if it's okay to say that the
eel is soft.
The eel is too soft.
I think it's a balance with the fat.
The eel is very soft.
It melts in my mouth.
It's delicious.
The rice with the sauce is also
delicious.
I'm sorry. I was a little focused on
eating.
It's delicious.
It's delicious as it is.
I love delicious food.
Can I cry?
I'm crying because it's so delicious.
Really?
Can I?
Can I think it's so delicious?
It's delicious until tomorrow morning.
Eating is the best.
Thank you for the meal.
Mmm.
It's good.
But, it's hard to taste it.
It's hard to do a food review, but it's
also hard to express the taste and smell
that I haven't tasted yet.
I'll do my best to do a food review and
a report on the taste of the food.