I love the lyrics.
It's so fresh.
It's like a battle of the flesh.
It's beyond my imagination.
The moment I finished it, I thought,
Is this really the song I made?
Please look forward to it.
Haito Kegai
Mor determining the
Even if it changes
I believe that it is a valuable sadness
that can last forever
So I'll go today as well
Thank you, Yakuza Arena
Last turn, the cry from the heart
The world is made up of only
Even if you try to look forward
There are times when you don't know
which is the front
The faint hope is the one that blocks
that hope
Whether it's happiness or good
Whether the world is wide
I don't try to do that
If you are the protagonist of your drama
It's okay if someone points their finger
and evacuates
Most of the time, that finger is dirty
While we are alive
There is no discrimination, crime, or
war
The song you played this time is called
En.
I was impressed.
The poetry reading was very bold.
There are many songs, but this time I
chose En.
This song was played a long time ago.
No, last year.
Last year?
En.
I played this song.
I've been doing it live all the time,
but it's hard to put the CD in a song
like that.
That's true.
It took me a year to finally release it
at the end of last year.
When I heard you talk,
there was a part that changed while you
were doing it live.
The lyrics change every time you do a
live.
You can change the tempo of the song.
And when you do it live, the lyrics and
the nuance of the lyrics are changing.
It's been changing every live.
And this is the final version of that.
Do you think it's going to change as you
try to convey it?
Yes.
While looking at the faces of the fans,
I think it's about which one is more
suitable for me.
If there's something I want to say
strongly,
I think it's going to be a good song.
There was a slight difference in the way
I put the word kindness in the words of
the same era, but it's changing and now
it's a very ideal form.
Not only artists, but also many people
couldn't continue their activities as
they wanted.
But we continued to release our songs
positively and without stopping our
growth.
We were probably the first to have a
live performance.
We had a live performance.
The president of the agency was really
annoyed.
He was probably going to get angry at
the live performance.
The president of the agency had asked
for more advice.
June 6th was the anniversary of the
We decided to do it on that day.
We didn't stop our pace.
We were moving forward in our whole
body.
There was a live performance in the
axis.
That's when...
When I was trying to convey the message
in words, I wanted to convey it in the
song, not in the music.
So when I was trying to make a song for
the live performance, I started to make
this song, エン.
You didn't want to use the MC, but you
wanted to express yourself in the song.
I like writing lyrics.
I've liked writing poems since a long
time ago.
That's a pretty different school.
It's like a junior high school.
エン
エン ここは書く日っていうのを決めたりしてて エン
ここは書く日っていうのを決めたりしてて その日に友達誘われても エン
アキをちょっとポエム書く日だわつって エン アキをちょっとポエム書く日だわつって
ことあるぐらいちゃんとポエム書く時間を作って書いてたのは中学校ですね。 エン
ここは書く日っていうのを決めたりしてて その日に友達誘われても エン
アキをちょっとポエム書く日だわつって
ことあるぐらいちゃんとポエム書く時間を作って書いてたのは中学校ですね。 エン
15年ぐらい前は歌詞を書
エン アキをちょっとポエム書く日だわつって
ことあるぐらいちゃんとポエム書く時間を作って書いてたのは中学校ですね。 エン
15年ぐらい前は歌詞を書き エン
アキをちょっとポエム書く時間を作って書いてたのは中学校ですね。
I used to write poems with the words I
liked.
Especially the circle, I wrote poems in
the way I liked.
I made two lines that I could stick to.
I was able to write it very quickly.
I wrote it very quickly, but each line
was completed.
I was impressed by the combination of
sentences, or the dense sentences.
What impressed me the most about what
you just said was that I didn't want to
write one line or two lines and extend
it to four minutes.
You have the mindset that you have to do
it in four or five minutes with the
theory, right?
But that's...
For example, if it's settled in two and
a half minutes,
the song that you're finishing in two
and a half minutes is recently being
made.
It's so easy to make your own style like
a softening.
Is it a point to be careful not to be
too trapped?
After all, that's...
There are various types of music that I
want people to listen to.
A-melody, B-melody, chorus, A-melody,
B-melody, chorus.
There are intervals, and I wonder if the
chorus is good.
I wonder if it's easy for everyone to
listen to.
There are formats that are easy to
But it's not that.
Recently, people can easily listen to
music,
various music, and foreign music.
I feel like my ears are overflowing.
That's true.
I think that's why I feel more free.
I enjoy making music.
I don't think about unnecessary things.
How do your fans react to your music?
It's really good. It's better than I
imagined.
You said that the song has poetry
reading in it.
Is it experimental?
I don't think it's a new method.
I think I had to make a few excuses
before I could tell the members.
Thank you for watching.
I thought it would be better if I didn't
sing it like Poitry, and I thought it
would be better if I could sing it more
with a soulful scream.
So I was a little afraid of this song. I
was too afraid to tell everyone. I was
too much of a
I had no choice but to use this method.
I didn't change the lyrics little by
little to match the melody.
I used poetry reading to convey the
words.
But I didn't feel it was new.
But I thought it was a good thing.
I believed that it was good to go beyond
the walls of old and new things.
And I felt that it would still give
whiteness to new things.
表現が 想像以上に良かったです。 僕は一番初めに 懸念したいなことで、
言うお客さんもいるのかなと思ったんですけど、
そんな声は一つも聞こえなかったです。
大西さんでした。
嬉しいですね。 直接届いてるっていう感覚あるんですね、きっとだからね。
I really thought the beginning part of
the song was amazing.
Poetry reading is so raw, and it's
dangerous, isn't it?
It's like talking to the MC.
But it's dangerous, so it's easy to
convey the heat.
It's because of this era that I'm so
into it.
I think there's a reason.
The beginning of the song starts with
that day.
When I made my debut, I asked the record
company,
What day is that day?
That day is weak, isn't it?
I wrote a song 15 years ago.
There are people who say that.
That's pretty much in my heart.
I don't care about that, but
When that day came out in this song,
I was told that everything changed from
that day.
It was a day for everyone.
Now, that day is one and the same for
everyone.
Right.
It's amazing that everyone can share it
in an instant.
In that sense, I think it became a song
that has more power.
I wonder if it's because of that that
it's resonated with people.
I see.
Do you search your name?
I do.
I see.
I do a lot.
I don't really care about it, but I want
to know everyone's opinions, so I'm
trying to know that.
The evaluation of this song is very
good, and thanks to that, I'm even more
motivated to produce it now.
That's great. It's the best.
It's a song that's a turning point for
me.
When I record, I have a strong throat.
I perform in the afternoon and play for
two days.
I can play about 20 songs in full and I
can't go home.
Wait a minute. You have two concerts in
the afternoon and two days in the
evening.
Only half of the people can go home.
I see. I perform four times in the
afternoon and two days in the evening.
I can't go home.
In two days? That's amazing.
Then everyone can see it as usual.
Do you usually get a hangover?
I do, but I'm totally fine.
You sing and the MC part is also shouted
out.
If you do that, do you usually get a
hangover?
I get a hangover from the MC.
I'm screaming at the MC.
I understand. That's right.
On the contrary, there are times like
that.
Well, it seems that the throat is
stronger.
That's amazing.
But...
To be continued...
When I recorded this song, I had to make
excuses like when I let the members hear
it.
I had to say, I think it would be better
to sing this with more soul.
So I tried to make it sound like a CD
without any excuses.
After three days of singing, I couldn't
speak.
Oh, really?
I recorded many takes and I sang without
using my throat.
It's hard to do it technically, but it's
good to be able to sing with damage.
It's not good sound, but it doesn't
sound.
But there's something that sticks to it.
I wanted to do it in the first place, so
I really overworked my throat.
I was so exhausted. I was screaming out
loud outside, even though there were two
doors in the booth.
There are ways to scream without
damaging your throat, but there was no
such thing as that.
I was so exhausted that I couldn't even
say anything.
I think that's why негоff in 最後が怖い
生々しい肉弾戦感が出て 納得できる言い訳なしに 聴いてもらいたい
一枚になりましたね すごいですよな
やっぱりギリギリまでやるってことが繋がっていくっていうの
そういう部分ってありますよね? ありますよね もちろん
やっぱりCDで聴いても レコーディング最中 マイクの前で
すごい大きい声で歌ったんだなって分かる?
I think there are expressions like this.
But without that, I think there are
things that don't come in.
You can do pitch correction very well
now.
So, every artist has a pitch that fits
the song.
So, if there's a lyrics that doesn't
reach you...
if the pitch isn't in from there, the
fish might move to the side...
You have to the details clean and clean
with reels.
Not only that, you have to take that
part on the song.
We will build it this time.
I feel that I have a great chance of
winning this song, but do you think that
this song will change anything?
I've always wondered how many songs I
can write that surpasses my imagination.
Thank you for watching!
I'm sorry, I don't think you know this,
but I'll say the title of the song.
The 7th Decision, The Over, and...
The song you wrote in your dreams.
Oh, that's right.
Isn't it amazing that you can do
everything in your dreams?
There was such a miracle.
The 7th Decision.
And Playin' Ground, All Alone, and in
myself,
I was beyond imagination, and the moment
I finished it, I was like,
is this really a song I made?
There was a song that made me doubt
myself.
I wondered how many more times I could
write this kind of song.
I thought I couldn't write it anymore.
I thought this was the end.
But when I wrote 縁 again, I got used to
it.
I believed that I could feel that way
again in the future.
Until now, I thought this was the end
every time I could.
But when I wrote 縁 again, I thought I
could feel that way again in the future.
I thought I should believe in that and
work hard.
So I think I can make songs that can
inspire me more positively by making
this.
You've made something amazing at that
time.
Thank you.
I really love it.
I'm really happy to hear that you're a
new artist.
That's great.
Thank you.