Thank you for watching.
It's started.
I'm the host of this week's show.
Please give me this!
Hokaia game!
Let's announce today's project, Himura-
san!
Summer
Thank you for watching!
So, today is October.
Really?
Please do it with the feeling of
October.
It's amazing.
The end of the year is coming soon.
This summer, there is a tour.
For members who are not good at
shopping,
A studio auction that has been held for
the first time in 4 years.
We introduce the recommended products
selected by the program according to the
members' wishes.
If you want it, you can buy it for free.
If you want it, you can buy it even if
you don't say it yourself.
You can participate.
This is not a gift, so you can buy it.
This is a gift.
You can buy it if you want it.
I'm crazy about shopping.
I may have already taken it.
HIMURA has bought more than 20 million
items in total.
That's right.
Porsche bought it.
We buy watches, suits, and sandals.
I bought a suit and it's all smaller.
I wonder what that purchase was.
Let's loosen the string of the wallet
and buy it.
The first customer is ENDO.
What do you want from ENDO?
I want a dryer.
You have a beautiful hair.
I think there are many good dryers.
There are many dryers.
This time, the person who explained the
products is the man who was there.
This is the man who was there.
Fujiyama, the home-made writer.
Nice to meet you.
Fujiyama came to the home-made shop
before.
He was lost in the middle of the shop.
He doesn't know where he is.
I understand.
If it's home-made, please leave it to
me.
The first product is this.
This is cool.
This is a product that professionals
use.
This is a mat.
This is a product called NOBI from
TESCOM.
Do you know this product?
I know.
This product is used in 70% of Japanese
beauty salons.
This is what professionals use.
I want to hear the professional
specifications.
Is this a general product?
The product used by professional beauty
salons is a temperature adjustment.
This is a temperature adjustment.
Adjust the temperature?
Yes
Is there such a thing?
Dryers are dryers that dry with wind
speed and wind volume
Is it different?
I'm sorry
I don't know the difference
This is the speed corner
It's dark
So if you have long hair, it won't fall
off
So the drying time will be shorter
Really?
You are the most crazy
You are the dryer
My hair is not dry
It's wet
You are like a
Next
What is this?
Is this a dryer?
Do you know this?
I wanted a stylish one
How did you know?
Where and how to use it?
I think I'll get a nail
Dad
The second recommended product is the
stylish hair dryer
It's very popular in recent years
It's sold out every time you enter the
store
It's very light
It's light
It's only 360g
It's better to use a light one for girls
That's right
It's not only light
It's compact
It's small
You can put it in a small space
You can take it on a trip
When I go on a trip, I take three dryers
You can stretch it and roll it
There are many types
This is a wind-dryer
If you hit it from here, it will reach
It's stronger
That's great
Next
Ta-da
It's already sold out
It's very popular
The third recommended product is the
popular Super Sonic Ionic
But it's not just Daisoan.
What?
It's big?
No, it's not.
It's a vacuum cleaner?
It's going to fall.
Actually, it causes a temperature
difference.
What's the difference?
What changes when you put out a
temperature difference?
The static electricity is not turned on.
The structure is better.
It's good.
It's better to use a comb.
It's the best.
It's shaking.
Daisoan has this.
What's this?
It's an adapter.
It's amazing.
It's like a vacuum cleaner.
It's very convenient to have a lot of
tips.
It's like a vacuum cleaner.
Do you put it on here?
It's a magnet.
It's a magnet?
It's attached.
I don't know.
Anyone can put it on.
Do you use this with a magnet?
It's not a magnet.
You're completely in the direction.
I'll do it.
I'm fine.
ENDO, who wants a dryer, has tried three
products.
ENDO, what is it now?
It's a little old.
It was when I was in the situation.
Four years ago.
The dryer industry has changed in four
years.
It's not four years.
It's been half a year.
That much?
That's right.
It's strong.
It's quite strong.
It's good to go to the bath and go to
the bath.
It's quite strong.
It's very strong.
There are about 78 wings on the side.
Why is there a strong wind?
It's about to fly away.
The price is 24,200 yen.
It's quite expensive if you use a dryer.
Let's use the next one.
This is amazing.
This is also cool.
Hey, old man.
It's light.
It goes well with this uniform.
It's a little old.
It's the strongest one.
It's going up.
It's strong.
It's quite strong.
It's cool.
It's powerful.
I think it will reach the other members.
It's cool.
It's coming.
It's amazing.
It's a dryer, but it's talking.
Why?
It's a super high-speed motor.
The frequency is different.
I listen to the radio and watch TV.
I dry it and watch TV.
While doing something.
This is Kinujo.
It's 33,000 yen.
It's a little higher than the previous
one.
You can buy it now.
You can't get it.
I want to buy it.
It's light.
It's very light.
How light?
Banana.
It's like a normal banana.
Really?
It's very good.
It's amazing.
It's not that noisy.
It's a high-speed motor.
It can talk.
The volume is very good.
It's amazing.
It's good at controlling the
temperature.
It's controlling the temperature 20
times per second.
It's 45,700 yen.
Why is it so expensive?
It's expensive.
I want to buy it.
I think it's better to buy it.
I think it's better to buy everything.
It's good for home, mobile, and music
store.
It's good to buy it.
It's time to buy.
Is there a dryer that you recommend that
you like?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
It's a good one.
Thank you.
What did you decide?
My hair is long.
I get tired when I do it all the time.
I like light hair.
I'm tired of carrying it.
Did you say you wanted a dryer?
I want the same one as SAKU.
Did you want this?
I don't like heavy things.
It's hot after taking a bath.
I'm sweating because I'm carrying heavy
things.
I don't want to carry anything anymore.
I'll change this priority today.
I want it.
Okaiyage!
Also, Higuchi and Tamura bought Kimu-jo
hair dryer
It's expensive but I think it's Daiso-n
Kakiashi bought Daiso-n
You saw Kaki, right?
I wanted to see Ion's hair
But it's expensive but it's light
You can hold it
Please
Don't talk
You just talked
It's very light
This is professional
Cute
It's like Mr.Bing
It's a situation where you can't talk
Cute
Isn't it all the same?
It's not like that
If you pay double with card, you can get
10,000 yen
They don't do that
I got a lot
The economic effect is bad
Stop talking
Me too
Thank you
Akidake's hair dryer
Next, what do you want?
I want Ion
I have it
I started living alone for 8 years
You use it that much?
It's growing but it takes time
I don't think there's anything better
That's why you always wear a messy one
I wore it
Next, Ion's hair dryer
It's here
It's different
This is
I brought a classic
First, I recommend
Irui steamer from Panasonic
I have this
This is really good
Please tell us
This is steam Ion
Just hang it on the hanger
It's just like that
It's growing
I use Ion
I'm living in a house in Jomon
I want to do that
You don't use it now
I use steam
You can use it even if you leave it
Yes
It takes 19 seconds to steam
When you want to use it right away
When you're busy in the morning
That's right
That's fast
Even if you turn it around
Steam comes out at any angle
I see
It doesn't have water
Normally, Ion
It doesn't come out when you turn it
upside down
I understand a little.
It's really coming out.
It's amazing.
There is a time when it is concentrated.
In that case,
Really?
It's amazing.
I see.
It's on the bottom of the pants.
I spilled a little soy sauce.
I spilled a little poop.
That's not true.
There is a surprise.
This is a parasonic. 15400 yen.
This is a good deal.
What is this?
This is good.
I saw this for the first time.
This is a good deal.
The second recommendation is
Yugi of Swiss manufacturer Rollaster.
How do you use it?
I don't know how to use it.
It needs to be warmed up to about 2
minutes.
It's coming out from there.
This is amazing.
It's amazing.
It's really strong.
This is amazing.
You can remove it.
You can also prevent pollen.
Is there anything like a plate?
There is no plate.
This is a plate made for steaming.
This is a plate.
You can also use it.
This is 23000 yen.
This is a good deal.
This time, Aki-moto brought something
amazing.
This is amazing.
This is a good deal.
This is
What is this?
Is this an iron?
This is an iron.
This is a steamer.
This is a closet.
There is a water tank here.
This is an iron.
You can just pour water in it.
Can I explain?
I have this.
You can put water in it.
You can throw this away.
So, these two exclusive hangers for
press
pants, and these st relate to
pilaf gloves, they've brad
a lot
Please subscribe to my channel!
There are various things here.
It's the future.
Refresh, special care,
Salary, dry.
You can dry it.
Steam is coming out of it.
This handkerchief is shaking.
Dirty, wrinkles are growing.
The pollen is fine.
You can also use a knit.
The latest model is also OK.
You can also use leather.
You can hang it.
There are three types, but there are
also five types.
There are five types.
What?
It's a bigger one.
Is that so?
You can also use a pillow.
This is very good.
You can also put a band on the door.
There is also a press for pants.
You can put it here.
You can also put your pants on it.
This is 250,000 yen.
That's a little expensive.
This is the future.
This is a premium machine.
Akimoto also checks the user experience
of the iron.
I'm really curious.
This is very strong.
This is a ball.
You have to think about the space to put
this.
I live in a small house.
I think this is very good.
You can also move.
This is for this.
Can I open it?
This is cute.
You can hang clothes when you don't use
it.
It's a big problem if you buy an iron
couch.
I imagined this.
I'm going to buy an iron.
I'm going to buy this.
This is a very good product.
Will Akimoto buy expensive products?
It's time to buy.
Akimoto chooses from the ones that are
available.
What should I do?
Can I buy this and that?
I want this.
I can't put this.
You can put it.
Akimoto is standing in a room with that
much space.
Akimoto was worried about this.
Akimoto bought an iron.
Who wants the iron?
Ume. Panasonic.
Oh, Uke.
What do you want to do?
It's very attractive.
I don't know what will come out after
this.
I wonder how much money I will spend.
It's a reward for yourself.
I want to see it.
If you go too far, you can't change it.
You decide at this moment?
Everyone is doing it.
I really recommend this.
It's expensive, so you can't buy it.
I don't know if you regret buying this.
I didn't say that.
I don't mind buying it.
I will buy it.
I got it.
Thank you.
This is a very good product.
I bought it because it was a surprise.
Everyone can buy it if you leave it to
me.
I did it.
Next, what does KAKI want to buy?
I want a pillow.
I prepared a special item for you.
It's amazing.
This is an order-made pillow.
You can make it by measuring your own.
This is a pillow for NISHIKAWA.
This is a pillow for pillow.
This is a pillow stand.
This is SHINOMIYA.
I'm glad to meet you.
This is a pillow made with KAKI.
This is a pillow for you to buy.
What should I do?
First, please stand here.
Stand here?
You are old.
I will measure the neck line.
This is a neck measurement machine.
Please stand here.
I will divide your hair.
Why is that?
I'm sorry.
KAKI is strong.
I will measure the neck line.
That's amazing.
It's measured properly.
This is the line on your back.
Is it a little bent?
The back of the back is low.
I see.
Let's start.
Then, I'll buy it.
Not yet.
I don't know the angle of the
I'll try the product called Prime
Premium, which can be adjusted in detail
this time from the result of the actual
counseling,
First of all, I will adjust the height
from the back of the head.
I will put a board of 3 cm on the back
of the head.
It will be pulled out by 1 cm each, so
the height of the soil is the easiest to
breathe.
Interesting.
Please answer while keeping in mind the
height that the weight of the body is
not concentrated in one place.
Then, I will adjust the height by 1 cm
each.
In the case of oysters, it is easy to
set the head low.
Then, adjust the height of the neck by 3
mm.
I will make it about 3 mm high.
3 mm?
Yes.
It's amazing that you've been talking in
that kind of clothes all the time.
I'm sorry.
I'm always like that, so it's okay.
I'm sitting down.
Is the situation where you usually sleep
harder than this?
I wonder.
It's like three layers.
I put a set blanket on the mattress.
I think this is better than this.
I'm thinking about it.
I'm always sleeping in a slightly wet
concrete.
That's a cover.
It's a cover in the backyard.
Then, you get tired of being hard.
He's not tired of being a cover.
I see.
Only one in the world.
The special bedding is complete.
After the counseling, he makes a special
bedding for oysters that has been
adjusted to the height he has just
decided.
When I thought it wouldn't fit, this
type of bedding can be adjusted for
free.
Free?
You can do it for free.
Even if you are 90 years old, you can
change it.
I'm already 90 years old.
I did it.
This is the height adjustment for
oysters.
It's amazing.
Please.
Excuse me.
It's a special bedding.
The neck fits well.
The horizontal direction is lower than
before.
That's true.
This mattress is a little high.
If you sleep at home, your body will be
a little flatter.
Can I buy it now?
Yes.
Is it okay?
It's okay.
What is the price?
38,500 yen.
Thank you.
You've been using this for a long time.
That's right.
I'm glad.
I've been wandering around this pillow
shop for a long time.
Really?
That's good.
Finally.
Thank you.
The clothes are wrinkled, so I should
buy an iron.
The underlive Osaka Park delivery ticket
is on sale.
I think it's okay to have all of them.
Legend has appeared for the first time
in four years.
The members are buying cat fur with
shocking products.
Sexy.
Please subscribe to the channel.
Thank you for your viewing.