Thank you for watching.
Hello?
Who is it?
Wait, hello?
Do you understand?
Hello?
How are you?
Are you watching?
Yes.
Long time no see.
It's amazing.
Where are you now?
Now, my room.
Your room?
My room.
Osaka?
Yes, Osaka.
Long time no see.
I'm so tired.
I haven't been able to contact you.
It's been 4 or 5 years.
I see.
Are you busy recently?
I'm preparing for my next work.
I've been on a break until now.
I've been at home all the time.
Really?
I just finished my summer vacation.
You must be busy.
Yes.
It must be hard.
I finished my internship and now I'm
studying for my exams.
You're late for your homework.
I'll finish my summer vacation with a
break.
Wow, you've grown up.
You're so energetic.
I didn't finish my summer vacation
homework until the last day.
There was a day when I decided to do it
on the last day while doing TV play.
You did that every year.
I'm doing what I can do today when I'm
off work.
I don't know how much I remember myself.
I don't have any friends in Tokyo right
now.
I know.
That's right.
So...
How should I say this?
I don't play with them.
I didn't play with them when I was in
high school.
I see.
I think I was more active when I was
with Miyu when I was in elementary
school.
I was surprised when I went to see you
after I went to Oita.
Really?
I thought you were very active and
running around.
But you were a little naughty.
Don't say naughty.
But I wonder what it is.
Is it a tochigara?
I don't know.
We were both living in Osaka on the
Shinkansen for summer and winter
vacation.
You were so energetic.
At that time, Nana was collecting
friends from Osaka.
Do you remember? I'm so nervous.
I don't remember. Sorry.
I don't remember.
Don't be nervous.
Nana said that friends from Osaka were
coming.
I don't remember.
I was so happy. I think everyone was
proud of many people.
I think I wanted to gather everyone.
I thought it would be nice to be
friends.
Miya is a person-lover.
What?
At that time, she was not a person-
lover.
I'm a person-lover now.
I can't speak at all.
You called your friend?
Yeah, I was happy and thought I should
be friends with him.
You always cried on the last day, right?
You cried and sent him off on the
Shinkansen.
Yeah, Miu always cries first.
He always cries.
I always cried on the Shinkansen.
I was told that I'm sorry for talking to
a man.
I was worried that he was crying so
small.
I was like, I'm sitting in the wrong
seat.
You were sitting in the wrong seat.
I'm sorry.
I was sitting next to him.
You were crying next to him.
Yes.
I was so embarrassed.
When I talk to you, you always laugh at
the memories.
It's so funny that I can't help it.
It's funny.
It's okay to laugh at this.
Let's talk about our real story.
I thought it was a good thing to do.
Really?
I'm sorry.
For example?
But, how can you say that?
If you are wearing special clothes, it's
not okay.
No, it's really cute.
No, how can I say that?
You are straight.
Yes, you are.
You had curly hair with a straight hair.
I was jealous of that.
I see.
I never thought about it.
I didn't know.
When you were not forced to have a perm,
what did you call the one that made your
hair curly?
A perm.
I see.
I told everyone a few weeks ago that I
would get a perm.
Do you remember?
I don't remember.
You said it again.
I like E-Grams.
When I came back, I was so straight and
it didn't take a perm.
I did it, but I was so straight that I
couldn't do it.
Yeah, it didn't take a perm.
I was so depressed and came back.
I was so jealous of Nana.
We didn't have any doubts.
Yeah.
Isn't there a way out?
Wait a minute.
Wow, you remembered.
I'll change it to the one that Miu
finished in four days.
Thursday, April 8th.
The weather is sunny. Today's weather is
7 degrees.
Today, when I'm in the living room, I'm
so excited.
I'm so excited.
Why did you put it in small?
Does it mean you're a
Was it good?
I'm lonely.
Wow.
This is Tetsu.
Your emotions are so messy.
This is so funny.
I miss you.
Let's go to the next page.
Read it.
September 19th, Sunday.
Are you ready?
I'm ready.
The weather is cloudy.
Wait, this is...
10? 11 years?
Is there another page?
What page?
Oh, this is the one from 11 years ago.
Oh, yesterday.
Oh, this is from yesterday.
Oh!
Here you go.
I wrote the rest of the page.
Oh, I see. I see.
Read it.
My name is Miyu.
Sorry for being late for the
lettering.
It says that you finished the second
half of the book in the fourth time.
Now, Miu is going to the nursing school.
The practice is over recently.
Half a year after going to the nursing
school, I got used to the new
environment.
I'm having a hard time, but I smile
while I'm in school.
I'm going to Osaka Station.
I always get off at Osaka Station.
Nana's ad was on the train.
And on the train screen, TV was playing.
Nana's commercial was playing.
I was doing my best every day.
I wanted to say thank you.
But now I want to report that I'm going
to school every day.
I'm writing it.
Nara-chan?
Yeah.
I don't know anything.
There's no one I know at school.
It takes an hour by train.
I didn't know anything at first.
I don't have many friends who have been
with me for about half a year.
I see.
I'm really going every day.
There are days when I cry.
I tried hard with a smile.
I'm so happy in the first place.
I'm really happy.
I see.
Yeah.
It was tough.
Yeah, I didn't have any friends at
first.
And you didn't have any friends.
You didn't know anything at first.
And you didn't know anything.
You didn't ask anyone you knew.
You didn't know anyone.
Yeah, and you didn't have any friends at
all.
I was always thinking of going to see
you.
Really?
Yeah, I was watching.
You're everywhere.
Really?
At that time, there was a drama, a
juice, and a lot of things.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I think I saw it.
Yeah, yeah, there was.
And there was a bookstore, too.
There was a wall in front of the
station, too.
I'm so glad.
I'm glad you smiled.
Really, really.
When I first sang the first song, I was
so nervous.
I was singing with my eyes wide open.
I was so nervous when I saw that and my
mom.
You saw it.
I was so worried.
But with the second song, I was so
excited that I jumped out of the frame
of the camera.
I was so excited that I couldn't see my
stomach.
I was relieved because I was singing.
But I like Yowasobi.
I like it.
What's your favorite song?
I like the song, The Gentle Sail.
Me too.
I like that song.
I can relax.
That's great.
I'm listening to the song.
I'm listening to the new song.
I'm moved and I'm about to cry.
It's a song that someone far away
thinks.
I like the song.
When I was in middle school, I said the
same thing.
Really?
Yeah, I said,
I'm under the same sky, so it's okay to
be apart.
I remember that time when I listened to
the song.
I didn't expect you to listen to it.
I'm always watching you.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
Thank you.
I have a lot of things to do, but I was
happy that MIU was going to change.
MIU is on the one hand, but she's been
watching me all the time.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
I was happy. Me too. Me too.
Let's talk more slowly at home.
That's right.
I'll call you again.
Thank you.
Take care of your body.
Thank you. Bye bye.