Ebichu's videos!
I was so surprised that my mouth didn't
close.
But I'm glad that we were able to appear
on such a famous channel.
I was most happy because everyone
thought that we were the best.
How was it to sing?
I was nervous.
But I was happy to be on the first take.
I was nervous but I had fun singing.
I knew that Ayaka was coming back, so I
was happy and happy.
What is your memory of the 6 of you?
I have a lot of memories of the 6 of us.
I was happy that I could choose one of
the 6 members.
But I don't think there are many people
who have been able to work with 6
people.
But we have been working with 6 people.
We were able to get a lot of power from
everyone.
We were able to deliver the feelings of
the 5 members to the 5 people standing
on this stage.
I think that the 6 of us were able to
help the fans a lot.
We were able to get a lot of power from
the fans.
What was the reaction of the fans?
The reaction was the same.
We were able to feel that the fans were
also taking care of us.
I was able to write a lot of words that
made me happy as a fan and I was really
happy.
I sent it to people.
I want people to see it.
I sent it to many people by pressing the
share button on YouTube.
I was told to watch it because it was
out.
I got a lot of impressions from watching
it.
I was impressed by everyone.
I got a lot of comments that said it was
cool.
I was glad to send it because I thought
I could see it in that way.
I'm sorry to everyone who sent it.
I was singing the last song of 7th day.
I didn't know when it would end.
I was wondering when it would end.
I was nervous.
I was relieved.
What is your first performance?
I'm doing my first performance as a new
member of FAMIEN.
I'm doing my best in the lesson.
We are all doing our best to learn
various formations and change.
I want everyone to see the moment of the
new and changing EBI.
You can enjoy it better if you listen to
the LP released in August 18th.
Please listen to it.
The LP is a new song that has been
reborn with a new voice.
Please listen to it and spend time with
FAMIEN.
Let's have a fun summer.
Please come to the festival.
I was surprised that I could speak so
much.
I'm happy.
I was very nervous.
I'm always nervous.
I was practicing, but I thought about
something different.
I didn't care much and sang.
I was very nervous and I thought I'd
cry.
The members of the Sony staff who I
always support said that I was very
scared.
They said, what's wrong?
I was scared of their faces.
They said I sang like usual.
I'm not good at singing.
I practiced the first take very hard.
I practiced not to sing too much.
I was very nervous.
I was okay.
I was very stoic during the 6-member
period.
I was a student at that time.
I was nervous.
I was nervous about performing after I
became 6.
I practiced dancing and singing.
I was very nervous.
I'm so happy.
I hope we can perform together with 9
people when we're all in good shape.
How do you feel about the performance?
I'm close to the middle of anxiety.
I don't know if the people who have
supported me so far have different views
on me.
I don't know if the people have
different opinions on me.
I'm scared to see the changes in me.
I'm scared that my favorite things will
change.
I want to make the live performance that
changes for everyone to be good.
I'm worried if I'm alone.
I'm trying to get more power up from the
previous live performance.
I'm a little nervous.
I'm looking forward to it, but I'm a
little worried.
How do you feel about the performance?
I'm grateful that the performance is
over.
I'm preparing a lot of music videos.
I hope you enjoy it.
I hope many people will like the new
members' music videos.
What is the first take?
I watched the first take on YouTube
about a year ago.
I imagined that I would appear on the
first take.
I was afraid that I would appear on the
I was told that I would appear on the
first take.
I was nervous from then on.
How do you feel about the performance?
I'm very nervous.
I'm very nervous about the first take.
I was told that I was okay.
I'm a nervous person.
I was told by the staff that I was
scared before the show.
I was told with a smile that I was
happy.
I was told that I was nervous.
What is the reason for the comeback?
I was told that I was going to perform
at 7-IRO on July 16.
I was told that I was waiting for the
first take.
I was glad that Aika's comeback was the
I was surprised.
It's been a while since I've been on
stage.
I'm in a 9-member team now.
I was glad that I was able to perform as
a 6-member team before I became a
9-member team.
How do you feel about the comeback?
I'm 20 years old.
Everyone is getting older.
It was fun.
I was able to do a lot of things.
I'm glad that I was able to release an
album with 6 members.
What is the most important thing for you
now?
It's difficult to teach what I've
learned.
I'm thinking about how to teach.
The center of the group is next to me.
I'm getting closer to the center of the
group.
It's a feeling that I've never felt
before.
How do you feel about performing in a
new member's performance?
It's the first time we've performed in a
new member's performance.
I'm looking forward to seeing the
performance of the five members in a
different way.
I'm looking forward to seeing the fans'
reaction to the new member's
performance.
Please look forward to it.
If you listen to the fan's performance
in advance, you'll enjoy it more.
Please look forward to it.
Bye-bye.
I'll close the video without permission.