Who is the queen of Ebi Chuka karuta?
Self-sufficiency! Who is the Queen of EBICHU Karuta? In 2022, "Ebichu no Video and More" will continue! As a special New Year's event, they will create Karuta (Japanese playing cards) and hold a karuta tournament with them! This time, we will decide the karuta queen of Ebichu with the members' handwriting!
Self-sufficiency! Who will be the Ebichu karuta queen?
Let's start the karuta!
Kirin-san
Here you go~ !!!!
I'm so disappointed!
Because it's after New Year's
It's funny that everyone is so full of fun!
What's after "Kirin-san"?
Kirin-san?
"Kirin-san, grow up, Kirin-san."
What do you mean?
Your neck?
Thank you!
Who wrote this?
Oh, yes!
"I fucked up."
Oh, no! "You fucked up."
"Oh, no."
You're so smug.
What's the next part of "I screwed up"?
"I screwed up." "I screwed up, too."
The taste.
"No matter how much, no matter how much."
There it is!
Congratulations!
I have no idea.
It's complicated!
I looked at you, didn't I?
We look a little alike.
"run♪run♪run♪"
You're so young!
She's so quick.
I know!
Oh, my God.
Boom!
That's strong!
Are you okay?
We definitely don't want to overlap.
Watch out! There's Mirei's leg!"
There it is! !!!!!
Oops, watch out!
Mirei got it!
What? Her foot?
I thought Mirei's legs were the most dangerous in the dressing room.
They're long!
Yay!
Be careful not to get caught.
Mooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo Cow!
I can't find it at all.
Oh, no, no, no.
"Left-handed? No, it's a lefty.
It's gone!
Who is it?
It's me!
I don't understand.
It's Nakayama, isn't it?
"Tokyo Shibuhaku Ebisu
Is this a deliberation?
But Kaho was downstairs.
Then it's Kaho-chan.
Thank you very much.
Who is this, by the way?
Me!
Kashiwagi-sensei's.
I could barely respond.
"Yaki Udon is delicious."
Which one?
Which was it?
At the same time?
Then it's rock, paper, scissors.
Hold on, Riko.
Strong!
I don't want to get stuck under Cocona's hand.
She's so strong.
"Pull yourself together, Riko, you're 21 years old."
I understand~!
(Who wrote this?
Who is it?
I can't find it at all.
Kurumaya-san.
Why can't you find it?
Because Yasu wrote it.
"Mr. Kurumaya, my neighbor's car shop. He gives me tea.
Really? Tea?
"Stretchy thumb.
That's it!
It's suddenly so strong!
What?
"Let's go Ebichu!"
Oh, my God, she's so calm...
Oh no.
I'm the only one who didn't get it.
I haven't taken it yet either.
Yuno hasn't gotten one either? Hang in there~!
Oh no...
I stopped sledding when I was 5 years old.
"Sledding"?
Where?
Here it is!
I finally got one!
Raw oysters are delicious, no doubt about it.
Raw oysters!
Raw oysters! That's what she said.
Cocona's Ibaraki feeling is growing!
It's really coming out!
By the way, I wrote this...
Yes! That was me!
I'm glad you got it!
Raw oysters!
Noooooooo!
I'm so happy for you!
"Nuh-uh-uh.
Nooooooooo!
"Nuh-nuh-nuh."
That's hard!
"N" for "wowon.
No!
Did you write this?
I wrote it myself!
This is hard.
It's hard.
"From the time of the six."
That's the one I touched.
"From the time of the six"?
"I'll show you a more evolved 9 members era!"
絕絕和香和
You're so serious!
You're the one who reads the text!
"Hoshina-san."
Hoshina, you're strong!
So strong~!
Hoshina-san!
"Hoshina-san, you're still cute."
Thank you! Thank you!
Who? Who? Who?
Who?
Who wrote the broad shoulders?
It's me.
You're not so cute!
These broad shoulders!
5 pictures --- Cocona Sakuragi 4 pictures --- Kazuka Kazami 3 pictures --- Ayaka Yasumoto 2 pictures --- Kaho Kobayashi 1 picture --- Kajika Mayama Mirei Hoshina Hinata Kashiwagi Riko Nakayama Yuno Kokubo
KENTARO, THE BOY WHO NEIGHBORED KENTARO
Who? Who is it?
Who are you?
Who are you, KENTARO?
Classmate?
That's funny!
"Woof woof!
Woof!
Woof! That's my dog.
That's my dog.
Oh...
"Hmm, I wonder what it is."
You two don't want to be on top of each other!
Good fight!
"I wonder... I wonder... I wonder..."
I'm Riko Nakayama.
Good, good, good!
That's right.
It's Mr. Me-me-me-me-goat.
Everyone writes such nonsense.
It's really shitty.
It's so stupid.
"Tepid water becomes water."
"Tepid water becomes water"?
You're Mr. Kobayashi, right?
Yes, that's right!
You made it sound like a quote?
"This time, I'm going to win the gold medal."
It was right in front of you!
You want me to move it a little closer to the center?
What? "This time for sure."
"This time for sure."
Isn't that it?
That's it.
Is it right?
Yes!
You're repeating yourself.
What's the rule?
I don't know what to do with the ""、"n""...
I don't know what to do anymore.
It's so hard!
"Muri muri, winter is impossible."
I've got it.
I'm sorry.
You're strong.
Tsubaki.
Tsubaki, what are we going to eat together?
What shall we eat?
Jukuradan Nakayama.
It's me!
Yes!
"Jukurunda Nakayama's nose is swollen."
It's you!
Seikai!
Finally, the second one!
Seikai! You got it all right.
Toothpaste.
"toothpaste. Itchy, itchy stuff on my chin."
It's me!
Oh, shit!
It happened today.
It happened earlier.
Sunbathing.
Sunbathing is important.
That's great!
Sunbathing!
From the sinewy.
Hey!
I came in!
It looked like fun.
Rock, paper, scissors?
Thank you!
Even if you say so!
What do you mean "even if"?
I prefer salmon roe to salmon roe.
Do you know the difference?
I know, right?
You're a salmon roe guy, right?
"Do you watch TV? Or not?
That was fast...
Let's eat something delicious together!
I'm sorry.
I clapped my hands again.
She said yes.
That's fine.
Yurugiai!
Yielding and kindness!
The world is good!
"I wipe my booby trap and I'm a rapper!"
Yay!
Only 10 more to go! What's the progress?
A contender!
I think he's a contender.
I think we're the favorites! We have to turn it around!
Yes, we do!
How many more cards do we need?
Ten more cards.
We just have to get them all.
We'll take them all...
It's gone!
Nai-taaa...
Naitaaaah!
Nai-taaa!
Rika-chan!
I wanted to take it!
Nonoka is catching up.
Right! She's catching up.
Rika-chan, what is it?
"Rika-chan number one"?
"Thank you, Rika-chan, for everything."
Who wrote that?
Who wrote it for you?
Thank you!
You could have given it to me.
Hey!
Don't say that!
"Cat's Mare"
by Mr. Kobayashi
By Kobayashi
Neko no Mure
Karaoke
I'll definitely order a drink at the karaoke bar.
I understand.
I know!
I get it!
(A little closer to the middle...
A little closer to the middle...
You're bad~!
They're kids!
Bad!
"Mugwort glutinous rice cake glutinous rice cake"
Congratulations!
"Mugwort sticky glutinous rice cake." That's good.
"Hey, Suedertaro?
It's Yuno!
Mokka-yaro?
Why?
You won!
I won!
Because you were confusingly perky, weren't you?
"Greetings."
BGM!
Your voice is playing tricks on me.
You scared the shit out of me.
Until just now.
Since there's only one card left, we'll mix in another card and start again! If you make a move, you're eliminated on the spot. If you make a move, you're out.
Sigh...
Deep sigh!
"Ebichu!"
Congratulations!
Wait a minute!
You're blushing!
It's so easy, it's embarrassing!
"So embarrassing!
Congratulations! Congratulations!
That's great!
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
Congratulations!
That's fantastic!
What's this? Sentence.
"Ebichu in the middle of doing their best.
Yeah, that's the one I got.
Oh, this is like 100 points or...
There isn't any...
I don't have it...
What a shame...
You took it so easily!
Let's count!
It was overwhelmingly fast!
That was overwhelmingly fast!
Boom! Boom! Boom!
It was so loud.
We did it!
So...!
The winner is...!
Yes!
It's me!
It's Cocona Sakuragi!
Congratulations!