I took a picture of the night view of
Date-san and the idol of the next year's
broadcast.
It was fun.
I took a picture.
I thought, but this night view is
lonely.
So I'm going to make myself a little
cuter and go home.
I'm going to draw a face on the night
view.
It's hard to get close to him, isn't it?
I'm going to make him more friendly and
cute.
Please look forward to it.
I'm going to draw a face on the night
view.
Night view.
I'm going to draw a face on the night
view.
No, no, no.
I'm going to draw a face on the night
view.
I want to buy it here.
This is this.
It wasn't like this.
It was like this.
I'm going to be a person.
I know you're taking it like this.
I was taking it like this.
I see.
I'm also a big fan of you.
I'll call you Yakan-chan, and you'll
call me Yakan-kun.
Please call me Yakan-chan someday.
I don't know.
I see.
What kind of face do you like?
I think it's a cute face.
Is it fun?
You're bringing it to me.
Really?
I'm happy.
Do you have eyelashes?
I think the night view is hot.
I'll put my face on fire.
It's done.
Bye.
This is Yua Mikami's night view channel!
I didn't think I'd be able to shoot a
video like this.
You can shoot like this, and you can
shoot like this.
Idol's repertory.
Is it okay to be a detective?
I'm a detective.
I'm a detective of YAKANT IDOL.
I'll be back.
Are you okay?
This is a notice.
Oh, my God.
Please continue to support YAKANT IDOL.