Quenna Patty
Good morning.
I'm thinking about what to eat.
I'm not good at it.
Oh, I'm so happy.
Let's eat.
Bye Bye
Good morning.
It's a rice ball.
How is it?
My sister told me to raise my forehead.
But I couldn't because I had decided.
Good morning.
I thought I should put something in the
rice ball before the rehearsal.
I was very sleepy.
I'll do my best.
Good morning.
I'm going to perform here today!
It was so crowded outside.
The video manager sent me the video.
I could see that PABULIN was cheering up
everyone.
PABULIN is doing his best.
Thank you for watching!
Ho! Ho! Na! Na! Ha! Ha! Na! Na!
Ho! Ho! Na! Ha! Ha! Na! Na!
Please!
Let's say hello first!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6!
To the hearts of the staff,
Rock on!
We are Super Excited Senri-P!
Thank you!
I'm ready!
OK!
When the play is over, I'll tell you
that I'm in space.
I'm embarrassed.
Thank you!
Drink water before scratching the skin.
Thank you for watching.
You thought you disappeared.
I don't know where the miracle you told
me appeared.
What you use devils want to sell is
always surprising.
Through the gap of only 4 days,
or weakness,
you go deeper and deeper into it,
without knowing why you filled up the
spaces in awe.
Though there is no longer any reason,
your feelings are yet to reach it.
What a lie.
This place is really nice.
I can see everything.
It's nice.
The center stage is also nice.
I want to go to all of them.
Thank you for performing on live.
Thank you.
Thank you for watching.
We're going to interview.
I wonder what they're going to ask us.
I wonder if they'll answer us.
Hello.
It's like a stage.
It's got a lip.
I wonder if it's okay.
Why are you doing that?
You are so cute.
When I looked at you, your face was like
this.
I don't know.
You are so cute.
You are so confident.
Thank you for coming today.
Let me introduce myself.
We are super excited.
Thank you.
I came to this venue the day before
yesterday.
I was surprised by the size of the
stage.
I felt like I was at my senior's
festival.
I'm glad that we were able to sell out
the stage.
I hope everyone who comes here will come
back smiling.
The stage is big, so I'm nervous.
I'm worried, but I want to enjoy it.
It's a stage that makes us nervous.
I want to enjoy it with the people who
come here.
Thank you.
We are looking forward to it.
The relocation of the students training
center to some concerned looks the site
of the Capri University
Thank you.
Let's go to the audience seat together!
Audience seat!
Let's go to the audience seat!
Before the show starts.
Please subscribe to my channel!
It's hot.
It's so big.
It's amazing that we can enter all of
them.
There is a synchro light this time.
So, it's good for everyone's pen light.
It's sparkling.
And it can control the color.
This side.
It's amazing.
If you don't have a pen light, I hope
you can use this.
I'm glad.
I can enjoy it.
Let's go outside.
Let's go.
I think it's OK to go outside.
Thank you.
Where are you?
It's so big!
I know, right?
Everyone is so small.
I'm home.
Thank you for watching.
We all came here once.
It's totally different from that time.
It was a little crowded.
Hold me so I can't run away!
I can't stop!
I'm so excited!
Look! It's a bicycle stand!
I'll ride this!
I'm back on the stage!
Wow!
It's huge!
I wonder if there are more on the top.
Really?
Everyone puts this on their wrists.
I feel like I'm going to do a rehearsal
after this.
What should I do?
Hito-chan!
Hiyori!
Julia!
Hello!
It's close.
It's like Sunny Star.
I love you!
The other side is...
Kanamin!
Hi!
You're big!
Did you hear that?
You're standing out!
What?
You're standing out?
You're a human after all!
I'm kidding.
I'm really kidding.
I didn't know you were so tall.
You're amazing!
I'll try to get to the top.
I'll try to get to the edge.
I can see quite a bit from here.
I can see quite a bit.
From the top.
It's too bright to see, but I'll try to
open my eyes and find it.
I'll do my best.
I think it's fun to go to any seat.
I'll go to the truck.
I hope you enjoy it.
I don't need to sit in an ugly seat.
I'm hungry.
What time is it now?
2.15? 2.20?
3.20? It starts at 4.20.
3.20?
1 hour and 40 minutes left?
Oh my god! 1 hour and 40 minutes left!
I have to change my clothes.
The staff showed me the outside.
Then, Aki-chan said,
Wow, there are so many PR people.
Everyone is looking at Aki-chan.
Isn't it amazing that there are so many
PR people?
I can't believe it.
There are so many people with heads and
faces.
Everyone is looking at us.
Aki-chan's expression is so sweet.
It's amazing.
If there are two eyes,
if there are 8000 people,
there are 16000 people watching us.
It's amazing.
I can't make a strange movement.
I can see from here.
I can see everything.
I can see your face when you turn
around.
I should be careful.
I should be careful not to do something
strange.
I slipped from the stage during the
rehearsal.
I wasn't injured.
I should be careful not to do something
strange.
Everyone is separated.
Oh, the princess is here.
Prince, there are many people coming
today.
You can choose from them.
I will find the one who is perfect for
you.
I'm the one who is destined for Julia.
I'm the one who is destined for J.
It's her!
We are connected!
We found the one who is destined for J.
We just got on the boat.
I'm sorry, everyone.
We found you.
We found J.
I'm going to take off my shoes.
I have to take off my shoes.
Be careful.
It's hot.
Stop it.
The camera is hot.
Thank you for your viewing.
You're so quick.
How did you do that?
You did this so that we can't see you.
Did you see?
I made the truck stand in front of me,
so it was super round.
The staff did this.
Look at this.
This is the truck on the second floor.
When it gets dark, the edge is so
beautiful.
It's cute.
It's different from the truck on the
first floor.
I'm going to go inside.
Let's go.
It's high.
It's 2 meters high.
2 meters.
It's about 2 meters.
It's about 170 cm.
2 meters and 30 cm.
That's right.
It's 230 cm.
It's not allowed to enter except for
those who are related to it.
We are related to it.
You are related to it.
This is the part where you ride.
I ride it.
Go up the wall!
I don't care how you do it.
It's not like you're going to get wet.
I'm just going to focus on you.
I just realized that.
I'm not that good at this.
I'm like this.
You're going to turn upside down
someday.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm going to turn upside down.
Can you walk normally?
I can't walk normally.
I can't move my legs.
I want you to cover me.
I'll do my best today.
I'll go to change my clothes.
Bye bye.
Thank you for watching!
It's finally starting.
30 minutes before the show starts.
It's crazy.
The staff said that it's going to be a
great show.
I was surprised that the venue was so
big.
I didn't expect that there would be a
lot of people.
I wonder what would happen if there were
a lot of PR people.
I think the audience will cry.
So I suggested that the staff should
watch the show first.
But they said no.
They said it's better not to watch it.
They told me to imagine and cry.
I'm already imagining and crying.
When did you do that?
When I did the rehearsal.
When I was on the train home.
I was a crazy person.
I was crying when I saw people on the
train.
I couldn't do that, so I just laughed.
Are you okay?
I was so happy that I dreamed of the day
I could stand on such a stage.
I didn't expect that I could stand on
such a big stage.
It was a dream.
I'm glad that it's coming true.
We've done a lot to fill the gap of 2000
people.
We did a lot of things like live shows,
and we did a street show.
We did a lot of things, but we couldn't
stop.
I think it's because we've experienced
it.
It's not easy to have people come to us.
It's a lot more than that.
I'm sure there are a lot of people who
want to do a live show on a stage called
Maguari Messe.
I'm glad we can do a live show.
I think it's important for everyone to
enjoy it.
I hope you enjoy it.
Smile until the end.
Smile.
Smiling is the most important.
Are you okay?
I'm nervous and excited.
I hope we can do everything we can to
enjoy this stage.
We'll deliver our feelings to you.
Please take it.
We'll do our best.
We're 29 minutes before stage.
Until that time when we finished one
hour
we were like I'm looking forward to it,
and then as soon as we finishing make-up
we were all excited.
We're done until now because we have
rehearsed so much.
We're not going to make it explode in
the next few minutes.
That time is coming.
It's dangerous.
So I want to take every second
seriously.
I want to be on stage so that I can be
blown away from the beginning.
I'm nervous because I'm big.
But I think there are many people who
say,
I think I'm the first time I've come to
make everyone smile.
I want to do my best to catch the heart
of that person.
What prefectures are there in the
Makuhari Messe this time?
What prefecture is it?
It's my hometown, Chiba Prefecture.
Isn't Chiba Prefecture amazing?
I feel like I'm welcoming everyone to
have a one-man live at a big venue in my
hometown.
When I grow up, I want to be like an
idol in Chiba Prefecture, like Yoshikawa
Hiyori.
I want to be the Chiba Prefecture
ambassador.
I want to be.
I think it's good.
I want to welcome everyone to the
Makuhari Messe.
We might be the first group to do a
three-day event at Makuhari Messe.
But it's the first time.
It's the first time only this time.
It's the first time only once.
That's right.
First live.
I'm nervous.
I can't speak.
I'll do my best!
It's about to start!
It's starting!
I'm so excited!
It's amazing.
It's a past site.
I'm looking at the moment when the
penlight is set on the screen.
I'm looking forward to seeing how I
react at that moment.
I'm holding back my tears.
If someone cries, it's over.
You're the one who cries the most.
Julia is a dry person.
If you don't cry, it's safe.
Julia cries and I'm the one who cries
the most.
If you don't cry when Kanamin gets on
stage, everyone will cry.
Then everything depends on Kanamin.
It's okay if everyone cries.
I'll cry.
I'm sure I'll be moved by the moment.
I can't stop crying.
I heard that the audience was like a big
person.
I can't see that face.
I think the most important thing is to
enjoy.
We've done a lot of rehearsals.
So, we can relax and enjoy.
We'll do our best.
Please wait for us.
It's so light.
Are you ready?
I'm scared.
I'm sure you'll be able to find a new
love.
It's gonna be alright.
I'm going to be a member of the group.
Thank you for your cooperation today.
Please wait for us.
Oh, my god.
It's gonna be fun.
It's gonna be cute.
I'm so excited.
KANAMI!
NINI-YAH!
ROKO!
MARU-CHAN!
AKI!
YUARI!
Let's go!
Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
I'm not afraid of giving up
Don't worry about what you say
It's okay to jump over the wall that
can't be broken
Just prove it, we are the strongest
Those blending of two really became a
little bit of performance
I want to share just a little bit of my
feelings with you
There's still a view I've never seen
before
So let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye
Thank you for yesterday
The city after the rain is colored
On the canvas of my damaged heart
I draw fragments of the future
It will guide me
Now is the night, and the reason for my
tears
When I'm lost, I remember right away
Even if it rains, I'll smile
Look, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights after the rain are
sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day, the sound
of the rain drops
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights after the rain are
sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day, the sound
of the rain drops
I wear a rainbow dress
Translated by Releska