How to use shoulder bags for the new
year!
Shopping!
Look!
Isn't this shoulder bag cute?
It is!
It's a perfect size, so you can put
other special items in it.
This design is also cute.
Yes, and it's a shoulder bag, so you
don't have to worry about your hands
getting stuck when you go to a concert
or shopping.
It's so cute!
I have a lot of luggage.
You have a lot of luggage?
Can you reduce your luggage?
I recommend this.
What's in it?
Can you give me this?
How many do you need?
10.
I can't give you now.
Shopping!
Look!
There are many ways to use this shoulder
bag for the new year.
Really?
What about the luggage you just showed
me?
Look!
Ta-da!
You can put it in this color flat pouch.
Really?
And, there are 6 colors.
Wow!
There are many colors, so it's cute.
It's cute, isn't it?
What color should I use today?
Oh, maybe...
What?
Where is it?
Look behind you.
What?
Here you are.
I got a handkerchief.
You can't wear it, so stop it.
I can't wear it.
You got it?
I got it.
Is there a way to use it?
Bye-bye.
I'm going to go.
Gentai-hen
Look!
You can use this shoulder bag for your
phone.
It's cute.
Can I borrow it?
Sure.
This is for you.
It's red.
Thank you.
Put it on your phone.
I got it.
It's convenient because you can't drop
your phone.
I collected all the colors.
Really?
I'm glad.
Wow!
Can I use it for my phone?
Are you carrying it?
Let's match it together.
The star-shaped shoulder bag and the
star-shaped belt are very convenient.