Now, it has started! Shrimp Chutas Tass!
This week's Shrimp Chutas Tass is Shrimp
Chutas Shrimp!
And then...
Don't resist!
Why is there such a chemical reaction?
Shrimp Chutas Tass, start!
I want to be with you until the end of
time
Let's be together forever and ever
Never Ending CQ
I want to be with you until the end of
time
Add many things to your private Ebisu
junior high school!
Ebisu Justice!
This program is provided by the sponsor
you see.
Rina, it's your first time to
participate in TASTAS, right?
Yes, it's my first time, but I didn't
speak
Oh, that's right
The first recording was a film shooting,
so she was a mannequin
Was she a little short?
Yes, because of her neck
She was wearing a long face mask
Today, I'm the MC of the show
Don't pull my legs
Is it okay for you to do it?
I'm a little worried
Are you sure?
She's so surprised
Who is she?
I'm sorry
I'm the shooting star, Taki Yu and Chue
Please look forward to the next episode!
We are the best!
The second full album, KINPACHI is
currently on sale
So, this is your first time on TATSU
TATSU's location
How do you feel, Tenryu-san?
I'm looking forward to it
What did you say in the beginning?
I didn't know what you said
It's been a while since we met
It's been a while since you did this
Today, you have a deep conversation with
Ebi-Chu, right?
I'm embarrassed to say that
This is different from the TV show
What is this place?
I was also curious
What are you going to add today?
I will announce it today
Today's theme is Ebi-Chu plus shrimp
Ebi-Chu plus shrimp
It's called Ebi-Chu plus shrimp, but
it's shrimp first
This is definitely the first time
It's not a switch
It's not a switch, it's an Indian
Switch, Indian, shrimp
Then Ebi Talk here
Ebi Talk?
Suddenly something started, what is Ebi
Talk?
Everyone likes shrimp
I like it
Shrimp Chuu plus Ebi Talk is
I love shrimp
Delicious
I like it
What happened to you?
This is suspicious, I took a
questionnaire in advance
Do you like shrimp?
Everyone loves shrimp
I like it
Only Kobayashi does not like or hate
Why?
If you say you like it, you have to like
it
If you say you hate it, you have to eat
If you say you like it, you have to like
it
I don't like shrimp
It's not a statement of someone you like
I don't eat shrimp
I have received shrimp from you
In a bento?
I don't need this, so I'll give it to
you
I hate it
I don't need it
There are various shrimp dishes
Let's ask what you like
Do you like sushi or pasta?
I like sushi and pasta
The question is narrow
I like the way you talk
The answer is Ari
If sushi is pasta, I like sushi
Why? Why?
What's the reason?
From the inside of the fish
It's really fresh and plump
It's good
It's good, isn't it?
I eat it
It's good
Why are you laughing?
What is this girl?
Then, Tetsuko Kuroenagi asks everyone
What do you like?
I like avocado shrimp
It's delicious
It's fashionable
What is avocado shrimp?
Avocado and shrimp
Do you eat shrimp?
No
I did it
What is shrimp?
Shrimp?
I didn't know
Why?
I'm watching
You are showing only your face
Who else knows shrimp dish?
Shrimp dish
Shrimp
I ate shrimp yesterday
It's a timely topic
In the middle
I ate a lentil soup
Lentil soup
Oh my god
I don't know how to explain
What is funny?
I tried to talk
But I was excited
I was wondering if I should talk
I laughed
I understood your movement
Why don't you do it?
Shrimp talk
I will talk
Matsuno confesses her feelings
Tetsuko will talk
Let's talk about shrimp
Let's go fishing
Today we go fishing for shrimp
There is no such thing
It's a fast way
Shrimp
Start from the coast
Where do you fish from?
Let's go
They go to find shrimp
But
Kashiwagi
Can you fish shrimp?
I can
There is no shrimp
It's a field
It smells like leek
It doesn't smell
At that time
Hello
They find the first person
There are cows?
Wait, there are cows?
I didn't come to see cows
There are cows!
Today's theme is not cows
It's watermelon!
Nakae doesn't react to watermelon
Here is leek
The sea is 5000m
The fish is really small
Let's go to catch shrimp
They are looking for shrimp again
They are walking around the leek-scented
farm for 10 minutes
There is no shrimp here
Where is it?
We have arrived
Where?
Here?
We have arrived
This is a warehouse
There is no shrimp
Is there shrimp here?
Yes
This is a place that can be used in a
detective drama
This is where the criminal is hiding
It's true!
It's a detective drama
Let's do a detective drama
Let's do it!
Why don't we do a detective drama?
Let's decide it quickly
What is a detective drama?
As a result of the discussion, each
member will be divided into a detective
and a criminal.
Stop resisting!
After this, we will show you the acting
of a white-hearted person.
Crime suspense in the middle of the day
The place where they came for the shrimp
is a building that seems to appear in a
detective drama
So we decided to try a detective drama
with ad-lib
As a result of the discussion, each
member is determined to play such a high
role
Shrimp in a detective drama Tastas Great
Operation
Please enjoy the ad-lib in the hall
Let's go! Wait!
I don't want to!
Give up on your words!
Shut up! Shut up!
Stop resisting!
There's no 2G M that's decided by you!
Shut up! Shut up!
There's no 2G M!
That's close!
What's this?
Is this a drama shoot?
Is this a TV show?
What's this?
That's close!
What are you doing?
Police!
Help me! My daughter!
My daughter!
Help! Help!
I brought the mother of the criminal.
Mom, it's embarrassing to have such a
sound, so stop it!
Stop it, Aika!
Stop it, you too!
Mom, please.
Please persuade me.
How much did you spend to sleep in that
lighthouse?
How much did you spend?
Is it outside the lighthouse?
Mom, there is no date to decide my life.
Let's go home.
Your favorite omelet is waiting for you
at home.
Eat the omelet quickly!
Hey!
Don't be happy!
I can make my own omelet.
You've grown so much.
Mom, I'm happy.
I can't stand it anymore, so help me
quickly!
Please stop it!
Mom!
Mom! Mom!
I have no feelings for this child.
Mom!
Mom! Mom! Mom!
ель
Noon remain on Europe
Here! Let's go!
What did you say?
It was an act of confidence
It was very smart
Shrimp kiss plus Keiji drama is
It was a rather confident act
Keiji drama was amazing
Is there really this descent?
There is
It was fun
I had to go to a useless place
How was it?
I don't think it's funny
Thank you for waiting
Don't wait
Don't shoot
Listen to me
The official character of the shrimp
I didn't hear that
It's a shrimp rock
Don't joke
This is a great drama
Indies band piano vocalist Kaiki Ogata
He appeared in a character that was
never official
Don't be surprised
What is the name of this time?
It's a shrimp rock
Shrimp rock
I'm being hit
There is no such thing
By the way, it's the first time to meet
a Kashiwagi
Nice to meet you
I'm Kashiwagi, the rumored Kashiwagi
I'm a shrimp rock
What is your impression of Kashiwagi?
He is a strange person
I think it's no good
I haven't opened my heart for about half
a year
It's long
Let's go to the shrimp
Ignore me
Let's go
What is this?
It's like this
This building seems to appear in a
detective drama
Actually, it was a very rare fishing
spot where you could fish for shrimp
After this, will you fish for shrimp in
shrimp?
But before that...
Shrimp in shrimp Game Quest
The project to make a game is in
progress!
The members of the shrimp team who will
challenge various games for the game
project that was suddenly announced
Last time, they challenged the Yamanote
line game and successfully advanced to
level 4
What is the quest this time?
The quest is to challenge the game of
the shrimp team
What is the quest?
The quest is to challenge the game of
the shrimp team
Experience the game of the shrimp team
around the world and aim to level up
Today's game is Air Hockey
Sounds fun!
The member who wins the game with the
most points wins, and the member who
loses will have to change their face for
10 seconds!
Because I don't want to
This time, the shrimp team will
challenge Air Hockey
The first round is a combination of the
above
Then, let's start the Air Hockey battle
with a strange face
Mayama vs Matsuno
I'm going to challenge
You can't win
Ah!
The first round of the Air Hockey battle
is over
Hoshina vs Yasumoto
I won
Final match is 3 point match
Who will win?
It's a hit!
Good job, Umeyama!
I feel like I'm not in the game
After that, they decide one point each,
and each gets one point
Who will win?
The winner is Maya
Let's see Mirei's weird face
3, 2, 1
10 seconds!
9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1
It's cute.
Matsuna's smile.
3, 2, 1
Her hand is on it.
She looks like a ghost.
A ghost came.
I thought a ghost came.
I was surprised.
6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1
But Matsuna doesn't have a smile.
Yes, she doesn't.
Ebichu Game Project
The journey of an adventurous game
continues.
Shrimp is a theme, but it is difficult
to reach shrimp.
Finally, they arrive at the fishing spot
where they can catch shrimp.
What is this?
It's like this inside.
Everyone, please try to catch shrimp
here.
This kind of shrimp is coming.
Wow, amazing!
It's black and scary.
Who has seen this before?
Nakayama.
It's a crab.
Mayama.
It's a lobster.
Lobster?
This is a shrimp rock.
It's a shrimp rock.
Kobayashi.
It's not a sweet shrimp.
It's not a small shrimp.
It's a shrimp rock.
Look, it's completely different.
It's completely different.
It seems that there is no time to catch
shrimp.
I will announce it quickly.
The correct answer is a shrimp that
turns around.
Isn't it amazing?
You can catch shrimp that turns around
at this time.
By the way, have you ever caught shrimp?
No.
How to catch shrimp here.
Please tell Sato.
Thank you very much.
Let's ask Sato-san, the fishing staff,
to teach us the tips for shrimp fishing.
Basically, shrimp are creatures that
walk under the water.
If you can't catch them, you can't catch
any.
The key point of shrimp fishing is that
the shrimp are at the bottom of the
tank.
So you have to stretch the line firmly
to catch them.
And the important thing is to choose the
bait.
You need bait to catch shrimp, right?
Yes, we have prepared two kinds of bait.
The first one is the shrimp.
We use shrimp to catch shrimp.
This is shrimp.
It's a small shrimp.
It looks delicious.
And the second one is...
It's a fish that everyone likes.
It's a blue-billed fish.
It looks like a shrimp.
Blue-billed fish is a common fish in
fishing.
It's alive.
It's amazing.
Look at this.
This is a great bait.
It's a cute fish.
It's a big fish.
It's amazing.
Try to touch it.
Okay.
It's strong.
It's twitching.
It's cute.
Try to touch it.
I was going to pull it out.
It's twitching.
I was surprised.
What is it?
It's twitching.
Who is holding it now?
And when everyone got used to it,
the shocking fact was...
Which one do you want to touch?
I want to touch the shrimp.
Which one is easier to catch?
Basically, the shrimp has a stronger
smell.
The shrimp has a stronger force to
approach.
Is that so?
That's right.
It's a shrimp.
Let's use the shrimp.
Okay.
Who wants to use this blue-colored bait?
I don't want to use it.
Because this is more useful.
If that's better, I'd use that.
I don't think so.
It's easy to catch shrimp.
It's not that good.
That's true.
Everyone, let's put your hands together.
M3, start!
As we learned earlier, the members are
going to stretch the fishing rod to the
bottom of the tank.
Then, in just 10 seconds...
Yasumoto, it's coming!
It's coming!
It's coming! It's coming! It's fast!
It's fast!
Yatsumoto is here!
Eh?
Who is it?
What did you catch?
It's not a shrimp!
What is this?
Is it a good one?
It's better than the one we caught
before
It's similar to the one we caught before
It's not a shrimp!
It's not a shrimp
It started 15 seconds ago
It was really fast
I was surprised
Is it heavy?
It's heavy
It's not a genius idea
So, what is a shrimp-chuu plus shrimp?
Even though it is shrimp fishing, Shima-
Aji caught it
I'm coming, I'm coming
Wait a minute, wait a minute, Kashiwagi
is delicious
Wait a minute, Yasumoto, I'm sorry
Ah!
Next time is the second half of shrimp-
chuu plus shrimp
It's standing up
Will the shrimp catch it?
N'mo!
And a mysterious shrimp character
appears!
A shrimp battle with a hot-blooded!
What will the outcome of the battle be?
This program was provided by the sponsor
you are watching.
Oh, Kashio is coming! Kashio is coming!
Wait, this is...
Kashio, hang in there!