Good evening, everyone.
Today, I'm going to introduce my night
routine.
Let's eat.
First, I'm going to eat my shoes.
The black bar on the left is a big tail.
These shoes are delicious.
Next, I will do a recesh.
This is fun, so please try it.
By the way, I made this down, but the
color has fallen, so I asked for it.
I will go to the washbasin and eat.
I don't eat rice.
I'm eating rice now, but I'd like to
wash my hands before that.
I use spring water for this water.
I'm using my pinky finger. I don't like
it.
I'm a little embarrassed.
I'll give this water to the viewers as a
gift, so please write it in the
comments.
I'm back to the mountain.
Next, I'd like to eat rice with my socks
on.
Eating at home is the best.
Welcome back!
I usually eat on a special day, but
today I was able to eat a lot.
This plate was hard, but it was worth
it.
Next, I'll be playing against this dog.
This is not a dog-dog battle.
By the way, this dog was on the street
five years ago.
I lost.
As usual.
I was wondering what was going on.
I'm going to take a bath.
This water is spring water.
This is always a horse, so I took a bath
and became a horse.
If you buy a shisha, you'll be a horse.
I'm going to dry my hair.
I always put gasoline on my hair and
make it shiny.
I forgot.
My skin has been really dry lately, and
my face is turning brown.
After I take a bath, I watch YouTube on
the second floor.
I'm looking forward to watching it while
I'm on the horse.
I'm watching Metahammer by Tawku.
Please watch it, Metahammer.
Metahammer is a good song. I wrote it.
No way.
I was walking on the street recently,
and I was talking to someone.
It looks delicious.
Next is the bedroom.
It's time to sleep.
The nose is good.
I always do my makeup before I go to
bed.
I can't sleep without my eyebrows.
So, please try it.
My next pet is a rabbit.
So, I'll be a rabbit.
I always do this.
On this day...
Happy New Year!
Happy New Year! Thank you!
I'm going to bed now.
It's nice to have my eyebrows connected.
I just said good night and went to bed.
Thank you for watching until the end.
See you next week!