sequel
Good evening everyone, I'm Sakurai Yuma,
16th place
Good evening everyone, I'm Nakamura
Yuna, 17th place
The new members of Ebisu Junior High
School have finally been announced
Sakurai Yuma, 15 years old
Nakamura Yuna, 15 years old, were
announced on the live stream
So this time...
I'm Sakurai Yuma, thank you for your
support
They are close friends on the day of the
announcement
Their first meeting with the seniors is
also a big success
Thank you
I'll eat rice
The first meeting with the seniors is
also a big success
The second meeting with the seniors is
Thank you for your hard work
Thank you
They are going to have an interview with
the two members
It's time to announce your feelings
How do you feel now?
I want to tell them as soon as possible
I'm a little worried
I want to do my best
I'm happy
I'm a little anxious, but I'm trying to
do my best.
How did you hear about your passing?
I got a line, but it was my birthday.
It was a great birthday present.
I couldn't go out because I was
sleeping.
In the end, my mother taught me.
I was told that I was chosen as the
shrimp.
At first, I thought the members had
already been announced.
I was very happy.
But when I heard it, I was chosen as the
shrimp.
They told me about the moment of joy
like this.
Actually, this day is...
Thank you.
After the audition, they had the first
time to meet the members of Ebichu
Please introduce yourself
I'm Yuma Sakura. Nice to meet you
I'm Yuna. Nice to meet you.
From now on, the new member number 16
will be Emma and the new member number
17 will be Yuna.
She is 15 years old, just like Nonoka.
Thank you.
I said I didn't want you to be the
youngest.
I can't help it.
It's August.
I'm the youngest.
I can't help it.
I don't feel like the youngest.
I'm the youngest.
We entered the competition a year ago.
The third prize was started.
In one year.
A new member will join us.
Yes, a year ago.
Nice to meet you, I'm Sakuragi Kokona,
the 4th year junior high school student,
and I'm the 13th student
I'm Kokubo Yuno, the 14th year junior
high school student
I'm the 15th year junior high school
student, and I'm the 2nd year junior
high school student, and my name is
Nonoka Kazami
Kokona, Yuno and Nonoka had the same
experience of making their debut from
the audition
They were waiting for the new members
We are the same age, so we are probably
the same age as the other three
I hope we can be the easiest to talk to
nd the easiest to communicate with
It's only been a year, and I've had a
lot to learn in that time
But it's only been a year, so I just
wanted to get along with everyone
And I wanted to have fun, and I wanted
to do my best
I want to teach them and work hard
together
I'll do my best
And the advice they wanted to give to
the new members
We were so nervous
I'll show you the video
Please look forward to the next episode
They are still regretting their
nervousness
Can they make good use of this advice?
One more person is waiting for this day
Kaho Kobayashi
Actually, I didn't meet him
Because they are in the same dormitory,
this is the first time to meet two new
members
There seems to be a strategy
What is this?
This is a tangerine
The first one is the key
Last time, I made a mistake in the way
to shorten the distance between the
three of us
I was looked down on a lot
So I drew a picture first
I thought this person might not be a bad
person
I want to gradually show myself that I'm
a senior
Let's go
Here you are
Thank you
I'll bring you more later
Bring me more rice
I want to keep on going like this
Yu-chan
Thank you very much
Thank you.
We met her at국電車yama-wa for the first
time.
Why did you want to apply?
because the
I think
I liked him before I met him
I see
I liked him when he was wearing a dress
But I didn't know if I could get a job
from my manager
So I got a job from my manager
Really?
I see, I'm glad
They are talking with their backs to
each other
And
Which do you like more, dancing or
singing?
I like dancing
And the other members also got the
answer quickly
And finally
I changed my clothes
They changed into pure white clothes
Let's go
Are you nervous?
Yes, I am
I'm nervous
They are getting ready in the studio
Are you nervous?
I'm nervous
Can you do it?
I'll try
Good luck!
Although it's a screen-shuttle, it's
their first big stage in front of the
fans
Can they succeed in their first work as
Ebichu?
At 8pm, the live streaming will start
We are Asana-chan and we are the new
J-Wish members
Thank you for your support
The new members are here
The time has come
The first time they met
I'll do my best to make the family think
that it's good that I joined the team
I'm happy that I finally got the feeling
of it, and I'll do my best
Emma and Yuna made their debut
I'm happy
I want to be a member of M2
I will definitely be a member of M2
They have been through many times, but
they have been running towards this day
Finally, they can meet that moment
When I said my name and my attendance
number, I thought, I got into Ebichu
I thought I had to work harder
I think there are many things to do from
now on
I hope I can make Ebichu more fun
I'll do my best
Like this
11 members of the private Ebisu junior
high school have started a new chapter
I'm looking forward to the future of
Ebisu junior high school
I will do my best not to lose
I hope we can be a group with a strong
personality that can bring out the good
in both of us
I didn't think they were so warm
I feel very close to them
I was relieved that I was able to get
along with them
I'm glad that the young girls are here
I'll leave the fresh and energetic
Ebichu to the five of them
The girls are like the girls
I hope everyone does their best!
If we can do that, we'll be the best!
I joined last year.
I was nervous, but I was able to talk to
the girls.
I was able to talk to them.
But I was worried about Emma and Yuna.
I thought that they could make their
dreams come true.
I hope we can work together to make our
I'm a senior, but it's only been a year.
I won't forget how I started.
I'll work hard to get better.
I want to be the most easy-going and
talkative person.
I'll learn from my sister about
performance.
I hope I can teach my sister that.
And this feeling.
As for the impression of the two, it
feels like Ebichu.
It's cute and A.B.C. but a little off.
I felt that it was very much like
Ebichu.
I'm looking forward to working with you
from now on.
And I realized that the time to be with
Hinata from now on is limited.
I think it was such a strange day.
In December this year, Hinata
Kashiwagi's career is decided.
I felt a strange feeling.
Thanks to the two of them, I think I
will grow even more in the future.
I'm looking forward to it.
Maybe, for example, the part I was
singing.
It may come out that two people sing.
I think there are various ways to
advise.
From now on, we will continue to work
closely with the new members and the new
private Ebisu junior high school.
Please look forward to it!