Ebichu's video!
Ebichu's video
This time, I'm going to show you the
concept live move.
I think there is an image of Ebichu
dancing in the live show.
It's a little different from usual.
I'm looking forward to changing the
approach and standing on the stage.
Are you looking forward to it?
It's a live show that doesn't get out of
your mind for a moment.
I'll do my best to keep my concentration
until the end.
I'll do my best.
Please look forward to it.
What I like about Ebichu is that I
haven't seen it in recent years.
It's a completely different feeling from
usual.
I hope you will come to see it.
There is also a live show.
I think you can enjoy it through the
screen.
There are many places where you can copy
the choreography.
We can dance and sing together.
I hope you can enjoy it.
What is the highlight of the concept
live move?
I can't say it.
Anyway, there is a hint in the word
move.
I will try various things for the first
time.
Please enjoy it.
I will also have you come to the venue.
I hope you can dance with me.
Please prepare for it.
I'm looking forward to it.
I can only see the live performance of
move.
We are also looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it.
I will do my best.
I will show Ebichu in performance.
I'm excited to do a lot of things like
this.
Please look forward to it.
Bye bye.
Hello.
So, finally, the concept live is moving.
A little more?
I think it's really surprising.
Certainly, it's a live that has been
collected.
I'm glad to be able to say it with a
brave audience.
Thank you.
Please look forward to it.
It's moving.
Wait a minute.
It's not funny.
It's not funny at all.
It's a natural high.
It's going up.
Please get excited.
Please come to the venue.
Please move a lot at home and have fun.
I'll do my best.
Bye bye.
It's a love star.
It's not funny.
Please stop.
It's embarrassing.
It's a love star.
Thank you.
Aomiyah is here!
Sheikh B maintained the
cafe in the hallway…
Thank you for watching.
I'm sorry, I'm not in a good shape.
Good morning, we are the Sosomu-chan and
the Yama-chan.
We are Shinsen-Kichi Shinkaku. Thank you
for your cooperation.
Thank you.
I'm sorry, I'm not in a good shape.
Thank you for your cooperation.
We are the first group to perform at the
Omiya Park.
We finished the first performance.
We are the first group to perform at the
Omiya Park.
Next is Kansaki.
Happy birthday!
Congratulations!
Kansaki and Nagoya, we are waiting for
you.
Thank you.
We finished the first performance.
It was the first time for me to do this.
I really enjoyed it.
It was new to me.
I realized that the family was enjoying
it.
I was very happy to see everyone smile.
I was hoping that we could perform
together with that song.
I was very happy to be able to perform
with the family.
I had a lot of fun.
Thank you.
Kansaki and Nagoya are in Nagoya.
I will do my best to improve.
Thank you.
We finished the first performance.
It was the first live performance in a
month.
It was a title song that I could move my
body.
I think I was able to move my body and
enjoy dancing.
I had a lot of fun.
I was very excited.
I was very happy to see everyone's
claps.
I was happy to see everyone dancing
together.
I had a lot of fun.
I will do my best.
I'm blue.
We finished the performance.
I have a lot of energy left.
I am very grateful to everyone for the
last performance.
Next is Kawasaki.
I have my own feelings, so I will
deliver good things to everyone and do
my best!
That's it!
Look over there!
Yes, I finished the MUZU performance!
Everyone, I'm sure you were surprised.
We were surprised too.
From the first song, we were surprised.
I'm going to say it!
I was so moved and excited.
I really enjoyed it.
I will continue to improve in Kawasaki
and Nagoya.
I will do my best to show you more
amazing things.
Thank you very much!
I finished the first day of the concept
live MUZU performance in Omiya.
It's been a long time since I've been in
front of everyone.
I had a birthday party, so it's been
about a month and a half.
I was very happy when I went in front of
everyone.
I was surprised to see the stage.
I thought I had gone too far, but I was
able to have a very fun live performance
until the end.
I thought it was because everyone was
watching.
This feeling will never change, no
matter how many people there are.
I felt it again today.
Thank you very much.
I will improve my skills and do my best
in the remaining two performances.
I'm going to the next venue.
I'm back from the concert.
Thank you for watching.
I woke up in the morning and slept for
about 2 hours.
I will do my best.
Hello everyone.
This is a video of a person who appears
in the video.
I'm very happy to be here today.
I hope everyone will have fun.
I'm still in my 20s.
I'm almost 20 years old.
I want to enjoy my life.
I hope everyone will enjoy their 20s
together.
I'm still in time for the entrance
examination.
I'm in time.
If you have time or something, please
come to play.
I'm nervous.
I'm getting ready.
Please look forward to it.
I'm KAHO.
I'm going to buy dumplings.
Good morning.
I'm going to perform.
I'm going to buy dumplings.
I'm KAHO.
I'm going to perform.
Nice to meet you.
I'm NAKAYUMI.
I'm NAKAYUMI MARIKO.
I'm going to talk a little.
Someone is doing a BAM.
It's difficult.
I'm going to buy bamboo dumplings.
I'm going to buy it.
I'm going to buy a bamboo dumpling, a
hula hoop, and a hopping stick.
I don't remember the name of the hopping
stick.
I'm going to buy a bamboo stick.
I'm done with the practice.
I'm going to perform.
The costumes for 4&6 are like this.
This time, I'm going to do a GACHA
GACHA.
I wrote the name of the clothes I like
in the reference photo.
I wrote the clothes that I thought would
suit me.
I was very excited.
I'm very excited.
I don't have a hairpin this time.
I put on a hairpin.
I'm a little bit of an adult.
I'm not a teenager.
I want to look like I'm 20 years old.
I'm hungry.
Next is RIKO.
I have a guest today.
I made this outfit.
I like the color of the shoes and the
belt.
Thank you.
I'm glad you like it.
I'm going to the store.
Anyway, I'll do my best to make you
sleep.
I'm fine.
I'm going to be a blessing.
It was fun.
Thank you. I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you.
Please come.