next case
Yay!
It moved!
We're going to have a team battle!
Riku, you're the winner today!
The winner gets 3 points for the one-on-
one battle.
And if you make a mistake,
you'll get a scratch on your face!
That's not true!
Cheers!
No way!
Red!
Yellow!
No way!
Oh, I see
Yeah
I was wrong
Yeah, I was wrong
Fighting
Isn't that what you say when you cheer?
That's also cheering
We are the soccer sisters
Yeah
Balloon, Hakuichi Championship
First, the first pitch, Maie
Oh
Let's start!
Amari, Amari
5 seconds left
4, 3, 2, 1
Oh no!
Yeah, right, as I had that ambition
You can keep your lips more different
Ah, I got it
You look like a female face liquor
committee
Okay, second attempt
Nina-Nanems turn
Like a stall
I got it
Wow, you're good!
You can do it!
Go, Sarah!
Go!
So close!
You made a masterpiece!
You did it!
2, 1
2, 7
Look back!
What?
You did it!
It's like a mountain.
There is a mountain here, so you can't
draw a mountain.
Masuro, you have one more chance.
What should I do?
Third one, please.
One, two, three.
What?
Where is it?
Can you count the number of our Matsuno?
Sorry.
Kaho, please.
Cool.
This is cool.
Please look back, Rina.
Cool.
It's fashionable.
It's Rina's.
I can see it in your mouth.
I wanted to connect it to my mouth, but
I made a mistake.
It's like a scratch.
The result is Kaho's victory.
Emi-chan.
Next, we will play the game of
kindergarten.
The first game.
Start.
Hoa!
Go for it!
I did it!
You did it!
Rika-chan!
Please look back.
What is it?
Otomo-jyakushi?
Pokoroge.
Oh, I see.
What's this?
This is to express a faceless person
Ah
I want to win next
It's OK
Will it be the last one or what?
What will it be?
This will decide
First
Ah
Yeah
Go
Go ahead
Cute
I don't say I'm cute
After all, it's cute
You say it yourself
Then, the last 5th time, please
Go
It's like a movie
Japanese spirit
I see
It's like a show
Emi-chan
The second round is Mire-chan vs. me
Good
Hurry up and put your head on the table
Go
Mire-chan wins
7, 6, 5
I want to be kissed by someone
I want to write something
I want to write something if I'm doing
this
Wait, we're in the same team
I'm getting excited
The third round is Mire-chan vs. Emi-
chan
To be continued
Alice, the fourth pivotal move
Ah!
Yes!
Yes-ford!
Thank you for watching!
Nose!
I'm not!
I see.
Go!
It looks like she's walking.
It looks like it.
It's not walking, is it?
It's not walking, but...
Look at the ball!
It's really scary.
I don't care if I fall.
I don't care if I lose.
Go!
What?
Which one is winning?
I imagined it like this, but the order
of the hearts was different.
The winner is the Miura team!
Eri-chan!
The last match!
Go!
Her face is still beautiful.
Get ready!
Go!
The game is still going on!
Ayaka-chan!
It looks like a mustache is growing from
her mouth.
Please watch the next video!
One, two, three
Oh!
Yeah!
Three, two, one
Wow!
It suits you!
It's like a kaiun
It's like a kameyari
It suits you!
That's what I wanted to say!
We're not friends at all.
We're not fighting at all.
Here we go.
Yeah!
That's embarrassing.
Ta-da!
Did you call me?
Why are you looking at me?
Different Heirs
If Yuka here says something, Tre mesa
team wins
Play
Wow
Poem
What is this?
It's a lucky girl, so I wanted to make
it shiny
Like a god
Then, ready, start
Oh, yes, it's a boy
Really?
It's a boy
Chanyu, stand up like this
It's a long face
It's 2 vs 2
It's sudden
It's sudden, so it's the last battle
Do your best
Then, start
3,2,1, start
Oh my god!
I did it!
So, we won the game!
Yeah!
Bye!
It's a design face pack from Shindou
Hope!
Do you want to try it?
Yes, I do!
The two who put on the face pack,
please!
Did you call me?
It's cute!
It's a panda!
Were the two of you touched?