Ebichu Tastas has started
Ebichu Tastas is going to be a trial for
Ebichu Tastas
Then...
It's a trial
What kind of trial is this?
All the crimes of Ebichu are being
punished
Is it guilty or innocent?
Tonight's verdict will be given
What's more, Matsuno is in tears
I'm very negative about the criminal
Ebichu Tastas has started
It's a trial
Ebichu Tastas has finished
The 4th discussion
Available in all the roasted seaweed
stores
etc.
The Privacy M intolerance
Sponsored by the following sponsors
It's an unexpected development
What is this development?
Ebichu Tastas has begun
I will be the host today
This time Hoshina
Is it the second time?
Next time after college
I was told that at college
I am the star of the shooting star,
Takiue
I am Chuue
It's long
I don't know the ending
Hoshina, what is the theme this time?
This time, we will be in Ebichu
It's a trial
But when it comes to trials
Everyone will be accused
Was there an incident?
Hoshina, do you have anything to say?
Just now
Just now?
That's good
I called my mom
We all go to the hotel
I asked her what to do with the bag
Riku said it was dangerous
I said something different is good
She was really angry
What?
Nothing interesting
I don't know what it is
I don't know if it's dangerous
Before that, everyone will explain
Let's start
It's a trial
Everyone, it's a trial
I'm scared
It's in the middle of the show
It's a trial
Even so, you should have come in earlier
Would you use the kind of way to
surprise them?
Sorry, more like violence.
now we like to proceed with the тоже-
Land Viewet
okay, Everyone
now that I've become a Lawyer
that you're going to listen to all of me
i'll prove that you are not an article
okay, then
i'll bemann you if yourying me
one more thing
you should check your curriculum
I'm not.
In this TASTAS trial, the prosecutor is
the prosecutor and the defendant is the
defendant.
The members are divided into multiple
groups and the defendant is the
defendant.
The judge's
Then, TASTAS trial, start!
First, this!
An impersonation of a character that
doesn't look like her.
I know who it is.
You know?
I know.
Who is this?
Hiroto? Who do you think it is? Tell me.
It's Hoshina-san.
Is it Hoshina-san?
Isn't it because she's been called
similar recently?
I understand that she's been called
similar recently.
First, the defendant, Hoshina Mirei,
please come forward.
Why?
Bye-bye.
I think it's already this way.
I'm sorry.
Hoshina's impression of the impersonator
is judged
Then, Kenji Takeue, please read the
basic information
Hoshina Mirei is not like the
impersonator at all, but she is full of
confidence and shows her impersonation
She confuses the people around her
So she is based on impersonator that is
not like the impersonator
By the way, there are also some
merchants
Among 7 of the shrimp, 4 people are
impersonators
I want to be the first one
Kenji Takeu
Let's do the trial of that hair later
Kenji Takeue's trial is a bit later
Matsuno is trying to prove that she is
confused by Hoshina's impersonation
Mirei often does impersonations of crows
and Rola
She is not like the impersonator at all,
so I don't know how to react
I see, you don't know
Mirei, what are you doing?
Is there any meaning in this statement?
I don't want to be the impersonator that
is like the impersonator
Please listen to me
I will listen to you
I always hear that you are like the
impersonator
I think it is necessary to be like the
That's right
impersonator
Let's do the impersonation
Kenji Takeu is trying to prove that she
is confused by Hoshina's impersonation
Rola, please do the impersonation of
Rola
Rola, I want your hairstyle today too
Thank you
Like this
I thought it was similar
Do you come to this place?
Please sit down
How was it, Kenji?
I thought it was not similar at all, but
it was a bit similar
It was similar
Just a little bit.
But I think this is too average.
By the way, this average imitation is
the most difficult to watch.
That's right.
Then I'll do something very similar.
Another one?
Park!
Park? Then please show me that.
The judge is a star with a high voice.
Did you really study watching YouTube?
Did you study watching YouTube?
There should be other witnesses.
Certainly.
Another person who suffered damage.
Yasumoto-san.
Next, Yasumoto Ayaka's testimony.
Hoshira-san, isn't this very average?
When I first imitated Rola-san, I
honestly thought it wasn't similar.
Please sit down!
What are you doing?
The witness is still talking.
I thought it wasn't similar.
But I thought if I said it, I would hurt
her.
The people around me haven't said it
yet.
So I thought I shouldn't say it's not
similar.
I thought it was okay to say it.
This is frustrating.
I was beaten by Hoshira-san.
I see.
The witness is in a panic.
She can't speak Japanese.
But I think she can feel it.
I see.
I was so surprised.
I didn't know if I should say it or not.
Please go back to the witness.
Have you seen any other impersonation?
Hoshira-san?
No.
How can you do it?
She can do anything.
But she can't be Hoshira-san.
I see.
I love you.
Hoshina says she can do anything.
She tried to hit Sazae-san.
Sazae-san.
I'm Sazae.
Isn't it Hoshina-san?
It's not just Hoshina-san.
Where is Sazae-san?
This is a mental pain.
What is the line you just said?
The line is Hoshina.
It's okay.
Next, she imitates.
Please say, Carrie Pamyu Pamyu.
I'm Carrie Pamyu Pamyu.
Thank you.
I'm Tenpatsu.
Did you hear that?
Carrie Tenpatsu is so terrible.
This is terrible.
I just said I like you and shake hands
with you.
I don't know.
What are you saying?
And then, she imitates Takeshi B and
Takeshi.
What are you doing, Nahata?
Oh, not you.
That's a new pattern, Takeshi-san
Now, the final decision
Is Hoshina Hikoku guilty or innocent?
Please show us your answers
Go!
It's the same
Guilty 7, innocent 0
So Hoshina Hikoku will be guilty
Hoshina Hikoku will be
Only be considered as a good role model
for Takeshi Beat
Takeshi Beat, how do you feel now?
I'm happy that I can do it
The next basic case is
Lose and avoid
After this, Matsuno will appear in the
Takiue Kenji's strict pursuit
I'm quite negative
Will he confess his innocence with
tears?
Before that
We'll show you the unreleased footage of
the last episode
Inside the car heading to Niigata
We're also with Ebichu
Ebichu and Aru Aru are having a talk
Mayama is not high tension
Ebichu and Aru Aru
Mayama used to be high tension
But now he's a big sister
He's serious
The most exciting part is Mayama's catch
phrase
Furthermore
I think Mayama has a better catch phrase
We'll think about it
Mayama's catch phrase
First, Mayama's catch phrase
Go to the center
Queen of the royal road
Mayama's catch phrase
Go somewhere!
A roadside village!
It doesn't sound like an idol at all, it
sounds like a roadside village
Next, what is Mayama's new catchphrase
that Ju-e thought of?
Do you like anime?
Yes, that's right, Mayama
Kama-yama-ya!
What do you mean?
I liked Dragon Ball
It's not like the first half of the
anime
It's still there
The youngest
You're being a little bit
The last one is Takiyue Koan
Mayama's new catchphrase
I think it's pretty good
I'll go
I said it before but I like anime
This one
I like Nijigen
Animation girl in Ebichu
How is it?
I like Nijigen
I like Ebichu's animation
Mayama is a third dimension
Isn't it?
I like anime
I know
I'm glad you said that
It's true
So the three of them thought of Mayama's
new catchphrase is
After that, the three of them met Ebichu
They suggested to Mayama
Mayama is not a high tension girl
I know
This is my high tension
It's low now
It's low
I have many experiences of why I became
like this
I used to be like Kobayashi
You can be like this
I'm not like that
Don't say like a grandma
Mayama is busy with live show
She gave her new catchphrase
I'll go
Don't be high tension
Ka ma ya ma ya
So fast
I don't know what it means
That's right
Then
I'll write it down
I'll write this
Go to the center
Queen of the royal road
What does it mean?
Let's go next
It was good
Next
And the last one is Takiue who is full
of confidence
I like anime
I'll go
I like 2D anime
Ebichu's animation girl
How is it?
Yasumoto's face
I didn't get it
I should have said it first
I think I like this one
I like Asaka
I'll use it later
Okay
They will use the new catchphrase they
like
And the opening
Ebichu's animation girl
Maimo
I'll introduce myself
Finally it's time to introduce yourself
I'm going to do it
Which one?
The three people who have high
expectations
Let's go
Ready
Will they?
From the top
Maimo
The number 3, Mayama Nika, who has high
tension in the game
Then, the last is the third
It is better not to think calmly and do
not do it
It is Mayama-sama
After this, Matsuno will be judged by
the TASTAS trial
Will the TASTAS trial be completed?
The next basic case is here
The temptation to avoid losing
Who?
I do not know
Then, the defendant, Matsuno Rina,
please go to the defendant's seat
Me?
I'm scared
What does that mean?
Hurry up
I do not know at all
Everyone, open the way
What is the temptation to avoid losing?
Then, the defendant, Takiya Kenji
Please read the basic case
I do not know
I will explain because everyone is not
paying attention
The defendant, Matsuno Rina, in this
program
Lose, that is, drawing
When the members are reflected
I tend to avoid
When other members are talking
I have an expression that my heart is
not here
The staff is very difficult to use
It is difficult to use the drawing of
the draw
I am very confused
Therefore, the defendant, Matsuno Rina
I will compete with others for not being
too interested
Of course, there is a testimony, but I
have a confession
First, I will show you the evidence
No way
I want to see the evidence
Please
Is it true that Matsuno is avoiding the
drawing?
Test with VTR
Please look at everyone
Please
It's familiar
What is the shrimp?
I like sweet shrimp
The members are talking
This is the drawing
Please pay attention
No
Hirota is talking
Look down
What is the truth?
I did my best
Thank you very much
I see.
So, as you can see, while everyone is
talking, only one person is facing down.
No, no.
The grass is like this, the grass at the
bottom is like this.
Kenji, Kenji, for example, if there is a
child like that, it becomes unusable.
That's right, it becomes very difficult
to use.
I see.
The viewers will look at that.
No, no.
What is that?
Just thinking.
If you don't stay still, it becomes very
difficult to use the drawing because of
you.
I think there are many people who are
bored.
I would like to ask them.
Is Matsuno actually bored?
First, Shogun Hoshinaga.
Matsuno-san is very energetic in the
morning and afternoon.
He is definitely very excited.
In the afternoon, he is hungry, he wants
to eat quickly, he wants to sleep
quickly.
He is always on the table.
When he is waiting for the bullet train,
he is also on the table.
When he is bored again, he is like,
I was thinking about shrimp.
He is thinking about shrimp.
He is running away a lot recently.
It's not about shrimp.
I'm sorry.
I'm thinking about a lot of things
because I'm negative.
I'm thinking about whether I was okay or
if I should say something.
It's a development that you can't
imagine.
What is this development?
You're crying or laughing.
I'm thinking about it.
I'm sorry.
This is the thing.
Kenji Takiue is crying.
I understand.
This is a defense.
I often watch the opening talk of TASTAZ
from the position.
When Kenji Takiue is angry, I often look
up at the sky.
But this is because Kenji Takiue's talk
is boring.
Hey, wait a minute.
EGR.
Please step back.
Kenji Takiue's talk is either
interesting or boring.
It's boring.
EGR.
Please step back.
My girlfriend is angry.
You are the one who is angry.
The trial is over.
Then, I will explain the flow of the
story.
The reason why the TASTAZ is angry is
because Kenji Takiue's talk is boring.
The verdict is that Kenji Takiue is
innocent if he thinks it's interesting.
If you think it's not interesting, you
are guilty.
What is that?
Isn't that strange?
It's strange.
Then, the verdict is that Kenji Takiue
is guilty or innocent.
Then, I will explain the flow of the
story.
Let's start.
EGR.
This is strange.
What did you think, Hirota?
It's interesting that it's not
interesting.
That's it.
Kenji Takiue is guilty because he is
guilty.
Why?
What is that?
It's not a slap.
Then, I will explain the story of Kenji
Takiue to the defendant.
EGR.
Great.
Then, the verdict is that Kenji Takiue
is innocent.
Kenji Takiue was not interesting, so it
looked like that.
Then, I will add the trial to EGR.
Hoshina's impersonation was too novel.
Next time, we will talk about the second
round of EGR plus trial.
Who will be the next defendant?
Kenji Takiue.
Next, Nakayama.
Next, TASTAS trial.
What is the trial?
This program was provided by the sponsor
you are watching.
Don't give yourself that chance.
What is this?
I don't want to hear that.