Ebitune's videos!
I'm the 10th, GINATO KASHIWA.
Today, I'm going to show you my Rubik's
Cube!
It's been a while since I've done this.
I did this at home last time, around
June.
But I was too excited to turn it around,
so I couldn't get it right.
So I haven't touched it in a while.
This is the normal one.
I want to try it.
I don't know if I can do it.
Let's see.
I'll have Su-yu mess it up.
I'm scared.
I wonder if I can do it.
It's hard.
There were many ways to do it.
I messed up the colors.
I had all the six faces.
I'll try it now.
First, I have to make a flower.
I don't remember this part.
I'll put it there.
What should I do from here?
What?
It's not right?
Wait wait wait
I have to put it back
I want to put this here
Down.
What?
llegend good
Good
That's good
yun هي
Somehow
I remember now.
What?
I can't remember.
Wait.
Everything is different.
What is this?
Why?
What?
Look!
They are all different.
I've just encountered a new one.
Anyway, let's fix it.
Why?
It should be okay.
I've never seen four sides so
beautifully different even when I did it
in June.
I've broken it more.
Wait a minute.
Why is this happening?
I've already broken a beautiful surface.
I'll fix it as soon as possible.
I want to go back to myself.
I wanted to do it quickly.
This is strange.
What's wrong?
Why are you doing this?
Why?
I did it.
I'm kidding.
Wait a minute.
I'm going to get my mind back.
I'm going to have fun.
I'm asking you why.
You hate me.
I'm doing that.
I can do it.
I did that much.
I did that much and I was able to do it
that quickly.
I can do it.
It's already done.
It's fast, isn't it?
Okay, it's done.
The problem starts from here.
What's wrong?
I'm back!
What did I do?
I'm back
I got them all
They all came out
I wonder if I used magic
I wonder why
Why did I get them all?
I thought I could do it if I did
something in the middle of the video
I thought it was over
I can do it! I can do it! I can do it!
I can do it!
I'm glad I believed in you!
I did it!
I finally did it!
I'm going to cry because I'm so moved.
I'm not going to cry, but I'm happy.
I'm tired.
This is the main subject.
There's a new RUIKU cube.
I haven't seen it yet, so I don't know
what's coming.
I'm going to look around.
Open!
What?
What is this?
Four?
I've never seen this before.
It's cute.
It's easy to shake.
How do you do this?
I did it.
I got the color.
But...
From November 12th to 22nd,
I was invited to the Elf the Musical.
I touched the green.
I finished it safely.
Thank you for coming.
It's a story of early Christmas.
Because of the corona,
there were live performances with
guests.
There was a mid-tone and a birthday
party.
The musical and the play...
I don't know the current situation.
It was just around the corner.
I filled up the space.
I sat in a full seat.
Since the February fan club event,
I didn't have enough seats.
I filled up the whole space.
I saw that scene for the first time in a
long time.
I almost cried on the first day.
I was moved.
Just by that.
It was hard.
It was so much fun and it was so
fulfilling.
But...
There was no manager at the set.
I was really alone.
I've been on stage and in dramas before.
I've done it alone a few times.
But...
There was someone I knew.
I've done it with my co-star.
I don't know anyone.
I've been nervous all the time.
Everyone thought I was a quiet girl.
I'm a quiet girl.
But I'm not a quiet girl.
You're all grown-ups.
If I suddenly start something weird in
front of you,
you'll be like, what's wrong with you?
You're not the type to joke around.
I was like, what am I supposed to do?
And then I kept feeling nervous.
I was like, I have to do this properly.
I was pushing myself.
I couldn't stand the pressure from
myself.
I had a huge explosion in my head.
I couldn't sing at all.
I was like, what should I do?
I was able to sing a little bit, but I
couldn't sing in my usual voice.
I was like, what should I do?
When I finished my practice that day, I
had a huge explosion.
Koji Tatsuki, the former top star of
Takarazuka,
from the practice room,
he was sitting next to me
and he was talking to me.
He was giving me advice on what to do.
He was so kind and wonderful.
If you don't know how to do it, just be
confident and you'll be able to do it.
I was told that I should work hard
together.
But he said, there's no way.
But he still said that to me.
I was very grateful for the words, let's
work hard together.
I heard it was a musical.
I thought I shouldn't sing like I always
do.
I thought I should sing like a woman.
I had my own thoughts.
That's why I was told that.
But he told me that.
He wanted to do that.
So, I got this one too.
Look at this.
How many are there?
There are 4 rows.
I was like, I did it.
I did it.
I'll try it.
It's hard.
I was like, I did it.
I was supposed to do it like that.
But I talked too much about Elf.
So, I don't have much time left.
Next time.
Next time?
I'll try my best.
Thank you for listening to Elf's story.