Ebi-chew video
Mayama Kashiwari's Christmas party talk
I was wondering how to say it, so I
thought Mayama Kashiwari would come.
I was wondering if I could do it
together.
I was alone.
I think the members' personalities are
different from the Ebi-chew live.
Is there?
I think that the common thing is that
there is a Kobayashi family in the back.
When I was a kid, I didn't have anyone
who was doing lessons.
I think I've been there a few times.
I don't have anyone who does that.
I think it will come this year.
It's April this year.
Maybe everyone is in the back.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Please go home.
I see.
There is a soup of your favorite.
I was catering for the first time.
I didn't have soup.
I don't remember.
I like soup.
I'm excited.
I don't remember anyone.
I was singing Ebi-chew live.
I sing Ebi-chew live alone.
I'm sorry.
It's true.
It's not there.
It's a strange feeling.
This part is difficult.
In that sense, I was surprised by the
difference in the sound pressure of the
Ebi Chiru song.
As much as the voice is low, if there is
only one, it's thin.
I'm a little worried about whether it's
okay.
I don't have many songs to cover.
I think it's okay to have one or two
songs in the Christmas festival.
It's a song that I like and it's a song
that I remember deeply.
It's a song that gave me energy until
the next Christmas festival.
I want to share this with everyone.
I often choose songs that are similar to
making a playlist.
I often choose songs that cover songs in
the form of a new challenge that simply
fits the voice teacher.
Hinata has a lot of songs.
I have a lot of songs and the width of
the song is wide.
The song I like is not my age.
I agree.
When the Christmas festival in October
last year, I thought it was a very
mature song.
So, there are songs that fans of the
same age listen to for the first time.
On the contrary, those in their 30s and
40s often feel nostalgic.
But I don't listen to such songs unless
someone sings it in my young age.
I want everyone to know that.
I also like myself.
I don't know what I'm thinking or
listening to.
Hinata is a mysterious character.
I don't usually say this song.
I sometimes find it a little mysterious.
I usually wear a lot of pants.
I wear a lot of pants.
I want to wear something that I can't
wear with a shrimp.
I think it's the opposite of what you
like and what you think is a shrimp.
So I make and produce what I want to do
at the Christmas festival.
I don't like it very much.
I see.
Shrimp has direction.
So I want to do what I can do.
I think I have a lot of pants.
I also wear shorts.
Mai has legs.
I think I have a lot.
The first time I wore shorts was at the
Mayama festival.
I was 20 years old.
I wanted to wear a shirt that looked
like a frisbee.
I thought about making shorts next year.
I was new to shorts.
I thought about what kind of shorts I
should wear next year.
I suggested it to the designer.
I feel like I want to wear a skirt.
I sometimes decide on a set list every
year.
I sometimes decide on a set list.
I want people to accept me in that way.
I'm not particular about it.
I'm just feeling it.
Please look forward to it.
I want to make a song that I can sing at
the Christmas festival.
This is my prediction.
I'm going to make a band.
I'm going to make a band song.
I want to make a band song.
The band sound is really cool.
And I'm the one who sings.
So I feel like I'm singing a song that's
not my type.
I'm looking forward to seeing if my
impression will change if I sing this
song.
I think I'm looking forward to it.
In that sense, I want to sing the song
called Blue.
I didn't sing the song called Love
rental last year.
So I thought I could sing Love rental.
I'm going to start with the drum sound.
I thought that would be a part of the
band.
I sang the song called Hot Up a few
years ago.
I sang it last year.
I think it's cool.
I think I'll sing if I'm going to do it
again.
I think I'll sing.
The answer is to sing at KASHIAKI's
birthday live.
My prediction is this.
Please expect it and bring it to the
live.
Mayama is my favorite song.
But it's a single album.
Love rental, I'll be here.
It's different.
Love rental is Mayama's feature song.
Mayama wants me to sing.
I'll be also in Mayama's atmosphere.
I think there will be a lot of love
rental around here.
I think I'll sing love rental.
I've been singing love rental all the
time.
I like love rental.
I thought I'd sing because I liked love
rental.
But I love you doesn't suit me.
I want you to have a different feeling.
A little?
I sang a different song.
You sang?
Yes, I sang a different song.
You sang, so I wonder if it will come in
again.
I wonder if it will come in.
I wonder.
I think that kind of song will come in a
little more than 3 or 4 years ago.
I think it will come in.
Will something come in?
What?
On the contrary?
I wonder if it will come in.
I think it will come in.
I see.
But I tried to sing the latest song.
I think this song will also be seen in
the live video.
Please check it with your eyes.
The song that HINATA KASHIAGI will cover
in the SETA solo live.
Yes.
This song.
I think it will definitely come in.
I think it will come in.
I sang this song last year.
This song was also played at the SETA
solo live that was opened to us
personally.
I danced a lot at that time.
I'm looking forward to seeing this.
Everyone is looking at this and saying
that they like this.
I like this song.
I would like to dance with this song.
I want you to dance with this song.
What else is there?
I wonder if HINATA will cover this song.
I think it will come in.
I was surprised that Hamada's song came
in last year.
I wonder if the same entertainer is
singing.
The same entertainer?
I'm sorry, I said it wrong.
The same entertainer.
I wonder if the same entertainer is
singing the same song.
I think it will be a song that may be.
I wonder if it will come in with
DOBROCK.
Your guitar is cool.
Isn't it a little cool?
I wonder if it will come in with a band.
The drums came in from the middle and it
was like this.
And the chorus.
I thought maybe it would come in.
The song that Mayama is going to sing is
really difficult.
I think it's difficult.
I was worried about whether it would be
a male song or a female song.
Including the desire.
Aiko's STORM.
It's a good song.
I like it.
It's a really good song.
Mayama likes Aiko.
I was worried about whether it would be
a male song or a female song.
If it was a male song, I was worried
about whether it would be a female song
or a male song.
Including the desire.
It's a good song.
It's a cute song.
I wonder if I can listen to it.
We have been expecting it.
We are currently holding a spring tour.
I said tour so that everyone can
understand it.
We are touring the country in the form
of a series.
We will hold the same thing on March
15th.
We will hold the Diamond Hall in Nagoya
on the 16th.
We will hold the Osaka No. 8 and the
26th on the day of the birthday.
We will hold the ZEP Diver City.
We will hold the transparent spring
tour.
May is in Tokyo on April 15th.
I'm Nibusei.
Please look forward to it.
We are waiting for you at the venue.
We are looking forward to seeing you.
Please look forward to it.