Hello, I'm Ayame Tsutsui.
This is the second episode of the cafe.
Last time, I went to a cafe in Nagoya.
Today, I'm going to Tokyo.
I'm going to a cafe called Coffee Save
in Nishi-Shinjuku.
Thank you for watching.
I'm alone today, so I'm a little
nervous.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Welcome.
One person?
Yes, one person.
Please take your seat.
Thank you.
Wow, it's nice.
This glass is nice.
What should I do?
Here?
Excuse me.
It's like a cafe.
There are so many.
I like this.
It looks delicious.
What should I do?
I often see this, omurice.
It's nice.
Like this?
I don't know.
I was always curious about parfaits, so
I'm going to order one.
I can drink black coffee now.
I'll take it.
I've decided.
Thank you.
I'll take it.
I'll have a parfait and a drink.
American coffee.
Hot coffee?
Yes, hot coffee.
Thank you.
I'll bring you a drink first.
I searched this cafe and cafeteria in
Tokyo
and I watched a lot of videos.
I watched a lot of cafes and cafes,
so I was finally able to come here.
I'm so happy.
I brought my camera, so I'm going to
take a lot of pictures.
I'll see you in the next video.
Thank you for watching.
I'm going to take a picture.
What did you do during the New Year's
holiday?
I went to a one-night onsen with my
family.
We had a barbecue and went to a shrine.
We got lucky and got to go to Chukichi.
Last year, we went to Kyoto.
This year, we're going to Chukichi.
It's the best place.
I'm worried that I'm too good if I'm
alone.
Chukichi is the best line.
I'm not going to leave today.
Here you go.
Thank you.
I'll have the Americano first.
Wow.
Ta-da.
I'll eat it right away.
It looks delicious.
It's delicious.
I'm happy.
I wonder if it's recording?
The photo I took at the cafe in Naoya
last time was too dark
I can use a flash but I'm not sure
I'll try this
Did it work?
Yes
It's hot.
I'll put it on top.
It's a little...
It's hot.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I usually stay at a cafe and just sit
there.
But I try not to touch my phone.
I like to play with my grandmother and
stuff.
I watch my grandmother and grandfather.
I often watch them.
It's healing.
I remember now.
I often go to my hometown.
Oh, my God.
Thank you for waiting.
Here's the soup.
I'll go to the bathroom.
It's big!
Ta-da!
Wow, it's like ice cream on top of a
parfait.
It's bigger than I imagined.
It looks delicious!
Let's take a picture.
I'll take a picture.
Thank you.
Itadakimasu!
Where should I start?
It's morning, so I'll eat some fruit.
Bananas?
Let's start with the banana.
Here I go.
Mmm.
It's so good.
Wow.
There's a lot of cream.
It's so good.
Please click Subscribe and LIKE.
Do they all eat by themselves?
There is ice cream inside.
Wow.
Ice cream. Ice cream.
This is ice cream.
It's delicious.
It's vanilla ice cream.
Wow.
Delicious.
delicious
I'm turning 23 this year.
I'm graduating from high school this
year.
I was surprised that I was not a student
when I was a high school student.
I wanted to do it when I was in high
school.
I went to Disneyland last year with Rei
Seimiya,
so I can graduate without any regrets.
I was told that I was not a high school
student,
so I was rejected because I was not good
at it.
But I finally got an OK and went to
Disneyland.
I went to the store to borrow a uniform
in the morning.
It was a great day.
I met Rika Sato and Eno-san at
Disneyland.
I was surprised to meet them among tens
of thousands of people.
What is your goal for this year?
This year,
I want to travel alone.
I want to travel around Japan by myself.
It's okay if I don't travel alone.
I like traveling alone, so I want to
travel around.
I want to know what you live in and what
you recommend.
I want to go to a popular shop on the
internet,
but I also want to go to a shop that
people in my hometown know.
I want to go to a shop that people in my
hometown know and recommend.
I don't know what she says..
I want to take pictures of the food I'm
about to eat.
I like ice cream.
How do you dive into sea?
I think I can do this for about an hour.
The last bite.
Itadakimasu.
I ate it.
It was so big.
It's amazing.
Please subscribe to my channel.
It's so good.
I love coffee.
I drink it every morning.
I'm an adult.
It was delicious.
I'm happy.
I decided a good start of the day.
It was delicious.
I'm going to go home.
Gochisousamadesita.
Please take care of me.
Thank you for the meal.
I felt happy with a wonderful atmosphere
this time as well.
I hope I can come again next time.
I hope someone like Rei-chan will come
with me next time.
Please look forward to the next time.
If you haven't subscribed to my channel
yet, please do it.
Thank you for watching. Bye bye.