Nogizaka, let's continue!
Don!
We are Nogizaka Kojichi and I'm the
host, Bananama.
Thank you for having us.
Thank you for watching!
That sounds cool
I'm leaving.
what?
This is a different place than usual.
This is a secret store.
This is a two-night series.
This is not a two-night series.
Please announce the project you will do
today.
This is a white-and-white reunion.
The style of the last video was changed
again.
I want to do it with a different frame.
The famous narrative is that shoguness
is good at theurgy.
There has been word in the toilet where
this person has attained shoguness.
There was an opening act here.
Oh, what is it?
It's an opening act, so everyone, please
get excited.
The audience, please get excited too.
Let's go. Opening act, please!
Oh!
Asuka, this is a good opening act.
I wanted to bring this to my mind.
It's good to start with YAMAKEN Samba.
I like it.
The kimono is better than last year.
It was cheaper.
The kimono is cheap, but the kimono is
good.
This program is the same as the FNS
Festival.
Yesterday, MATSUKEN was in front of
NUGIZAKA.
I thought I wasn't losing.
You are losing.
You don't appear after the fake kimono.
Did YAMAKEN give you instructions?
She is a new member.
She went abroad to study.
Did she go abroad to study?
I told her to do her best.
Did she say that?
When she came out, she was smaller than
I imagined.
Why?
I saw the real kimono last night.
That's all.
Everyone is here.
Let's toast.
Asuka is not here.
I want Asuka to toast.
I'm sorry.
This year, the game will be held in a
meeting between SHITARA and HIBURA.
This year, Asuka will be more powerful.
Please watch again.
Let's start the first game.
What's in the mask?
First, it's a game where you guess what
kind of mouth they have in the mask.
This time, you choose one of the four,
which is Shakure, Peko-chan, Maeba-
dashi, and Hyottoko.
You make a mouth in the mask so that the
other person can't see it.
Read the other person's expression
through the mask and get 3 points if you
can make the same mouth.
This is done by switching the front and
back.
If you can make the same mouth, you can
get 3 points.
First, Shitara vs Iwamoto vs Hibura vs
Kaki
Iwamoto is the first
Ok, I'll start
Iwamoto, please show us your face
Have you done it?
Are you doing it?
You are doing it a little bit.
Do you know the moment when you changed?
I don't know at all.
No way.
Now, please decide the face and make it
yourself.
Now, please take off your masks at the
same time.
3, 2, 1, go!
It's Teko-chan!
That's not good!
Why did you drink water?
Nice, Megu-chan!
I just wanted to see it.
Why did you see it?
Next, Kaki's attack.
Kaki, you don't have a front teeth,
right?
I have a front teeth.
I thought you have a front teeth.
It's not a lie.
Please activate the card you chose.
Please.
He's back.
He's moving a little.
Now, now, do you understand?
Isn't it difficult?
It's difficult.
He turned his face once.
Now, please make the same face as I did.
I'll take it.
3, 2, 1, go.
It's a chin.
Yes.
It's not a chin?
Why is it not a chin?
You said it's not a chin.
No, it's not a chin.
No, you put a fake at first.
You bent it.
I don't know which side is the chin.
At first, you were like this.
I thought you were a man.
Yes.
6 points.
You got 6 points again.
It's amazing.
Next is the one-on-one battle.
Akimoto won the rock-paper-scissors.
Let's see the face.
Please do it.
Go ahead.
Are you doing it?
It moved.
The mask moved a lot.
What is it?
You moved like this once.
Yes.
Is it a chakre, peko-chan, or hyottoko?
You were doing it for a long time, and
it got wet.
You were doing it for a long time.
What?
I didn't know.
Asuka, you don't know?
Please make the same face.
I'll take off the mask.
3, 2, 1.
Please take it off.
It's a chakre.
It was a foreshadowing.
It was shown.
It's like Pekun-chan is doing this.
Really?
It was a foreshadowing.
Awesome.
You got a good point.
You are strong.
Can they get revenge?
I want to keep it a little wider.
She's losing.
She's really hiding it.
Wow, that's amazing.
It's small.
I don't think Asuka will do it.
There's a psychological battle.
It's the last time Asuka does this.
That's right.
I have to make her feel lonely.
Asuka's shakure, hyottoko, peko-chan,
and maiba-dashi are the last.
I've never seen it.
I've never seen it, either.
The last one.
Asuka, please activate the face you
chose.
She's putting in a lot of fake.
Oh, she's done it.
At the end, she had a face like a
dafunda.
She's done it.
Wait a minute. I was really thinking
about it.
You put in a lot of fake, Asuka.
Well, then, Akimoto.
Yes.
Please make the same face.
Then, please take off your mask.
3, 2, 1, go ahead.
Go ahead.
Take off.
You did it.
You did it, Peko-chan.
She did it.
I was busy. I did a lot of work as an
actress.
You didn't have time to change your
clothes.
I couldn't go to the studio because of
Asuka's hit song.
You're a bad guy.
Next game, Himura-san, please!
Slipper Near Pin Challenge
As usual, we'll play the Near Pin
Challenge
Each team will challenge 3 people
The team that can fly the pin closest to
the pin wins 10 points
First, Shitara team Suzuki and Kimura
team Kubo will challenge
Can't we see the exhibition by Himura-
san?
We can't show the exhibition but we can
give Himura-san a lecture
He is called the Himura of the shoe-
kicking
Himura-san, can you teach us the trick?
Yes, well, it's not that high
It's better to kick the ball with a low
line
If you swing it, it's over
Many people kick the ball high
I want you to kick the ball loosely
I'll tell you the point
Think this is a clock
This is 12 o'clock
What time is it?
3 o'clock
9 o'clock
What?
Are you watching from the other side?
Yes, I'm watching from here
This is 12 o'clock
6 o'clock
This is 3 o'clock
This is 5 o'clock
Yes, this is 4 o'clock
4 o'clock and a half?
Yes, 4 o'clock and a half
Remember this
4 o'clock and a half, 7 o'clock and a
half
It's too early
4 o'clock and a half, 7 o'clock and a
half
Why? Isn't it 4 o'clock and 7 o'clock?
If it's 4 o'clock and 7 o'clock, it's
weak
4 o'clock and a half, 7 o'clock and a
half
Did you see the ankle?
I'm holding here
To kick the ball straight, I want to
kick the ball here
Next, Slipper Near Pin
I don't know how much power I should use
Please
Oh, no!
You did it!
I told you!
The one that went into the tempura.
5m 10cm
Next, Kubo's challenge
Go for it, Kubo!
You heard what Kubo said, right?
Yes, 4.30 and 7.30
I did
Kubo, I think 4.30 and 10.30 is fine
10.30?
I raised it quite a lot
She's a woman without strength
Golf is not about strength
It's not golf
It's similar
It's a slipper
Let's go
Slipper Near Pin Challenge
Go for it
4.30 and 7.30
Oh, no!
What's this?
She's weak
She's weaker than us
I tried to put strength into it
But it didn't stop
Slipper is light
It's light
You have to put strength into it and go
like this
Next, Yoda and Hayakawa's challenge
First, Hayakawa from Himura
Actually, I have a special skill that
I've been hiding
My toes move freely
Like this
Can you do this?
Yes
Can you do rock-paper-scissors with your
toes?
I can do rock-paper-scissors
I can grab anything
Really?
You can do that, too, Naoko?
Her toes are like this
Since Ken
I can open my toes, stop them, and close
them when I put strength into it
It's like this
It's a good theory
You can do it with slipper
I can do it with slipper
If you can do it with slipper, it's a
record
Oh, you did it
I did it
I want that
Hayakawa, let's go
Slipper near pin challenge
Go
It's a good distance
Lucky
It's quite strong
She did it with 5.38m
It's the closest so far
Hayakawa's record is 5.00m
Yoda of Chitara
Yoda, please
Yes
Everyone is leaning this way
I'll aim this way
Right side?
I have to do this
It's like this
No, not now
Hey, measure it
It's here
Choro came out, the choro
No, it's not
But you said it before
No, no, it's this
No, no, it's not
It's not
What is it?
Sorry, what you said just now
It's not
There's no excuse
You really can't
You should do it before you spit it out
If you say it like that
You're so scary
Wait, how much are you going to do?
A little
It's amazing
I'm shaking
Your face is also a scary face
Well then, the tripper Miyapin challenge
Please
Why?
You said it
I expected it
You're in a good position
I'm sorry
I knew it, you said it
Will Kimura-kun keep the lead?
The third person is Tamura
You have it
Look, this
It's a good sound
Well then, Miyapin tripper challenge
Please
Ahhhhhhh!
Ah, sorry.
I thought it was a pro-wrestler.
It's the ceiling.
You have a chance.
I have.
Can Kanagawa, the lower-ranked team,
turn the tables?
Please.
Be careful of the ceiling.
It's the best if you ride on the chest.
I'll do it.
I'm counting on you.
I'm scared.
I have hope.
Now, the Slipper Near Pin Challenge.
Go ahead.
It's a one-flare.
It's a distance.
How far is Hayato?
It's not bad.
Is it far?
Is that so?
She won.
Thank you.
And the second match is a showdown
between the two captains.
What kind of high-level battle will it
be?
I want to see it.
This is it.
Please watch Genki, Kimget, and
Shigenoka.
First, Himura's challenge!
I'm counting on you.
You can do it!
He's going to be crazy!
Himura's Near Pin Slipper Challenge!
I wanted to go further!
Rider, Rider!
She's going straight!
2.2m?
She's fast!
1st place?
Will the miracle happen?
She's a bit overconfident.
Let's see the result!
Wow, you got it!
That was so close!
Thank you for watching! Please subscribe
to our channel!
I did it! I did it!
It's so close!
I did it!
Amazing!
So, the winner of this match is
Shitanakata!
I didn't know that slippers would be so
exciting.
It's so fun!
I didn't know that slippers would be so
exciting.
I want to do this in 18th.
Next, Himura-san, please.
It's the 4-kyo corner!
I did it!
Good job!
Asuka-chan will be the judge.
She said she wanted to do this.
Each of us will be the judge.
I'm looking forward to it.
First, the first group.
Let's start!
This is good.
So cute.
Asuka.
I really didn't know who she was.
I didn't know who she was.
She looks great.
Is she a persimmon?
Yes, she is.
Persimmon?
You are doing that with your teeth.
I can see it.
That's amazing.
Fox dance is this year.
Yes, it is.
So I left footprints.
Footprints?
It's okay to leave footprints.
But I left it for foxes.
I see.
She was cute.
You did this in many places this year.
Yes, I did.
You did this in many places.
But this is the most interesting.
It's really interesting.
I didn't know.
Who is the most excited?
The quality is really good.
It's like a DJ booth.
What?
Next person, please!
This is a lie!
I see it!
Why?
TRF!
Why is this?
Asuka-chan, a request for TRF!
It's so high in perfection!
Amazing!
First of all, there are people who still
don't understand DJ Kou-san.
Is it a finger-pick?
This is a lie!
It's a little different.
It's a lie.
This is a lie!
DJ Ryujin!
Why is it a lie?
And it's interesting that Shibata is
doing this.
Because she's good at singing.
But it suits her.
That's right.
She's like a fairy.
It suits her to have a gal-like look.
I understand.
And the South American soccer player.
Sam-san.
Sam-san was doing it.
He can do anything.
Sam-san doesn't have that image.
I understand.
He's a bit shabby.
It's like his mother is doing a garbage-
steak.
I understand.
It's interesting.
How was it when you got this offer?
I was happy.
DJ Kou-san?
Easy-do-it-yeah!
He's crazy.
He thought it would be funny.
I'm lowering my chin.
You're lowering your chin.
Don't do that.
It's interesting.
I met 3 people in my uniform before the
show.
They were doing a rehearsal.
I didn't expect that.
I was doing a rehearsal.
It's interesting.
It's really interesting.
It's really good.
It's the best.
Next time on Saito Masuka.
The last episode of tears.
This.
Ta-da!
Catchphrase?
It's a catchphrase that IKOMO-san used
in the first season of the show.
I'm RENO NAKAMURA, the Nogizaka of
Uruwasu.
Please subscribe to my channel.