This week's Ebichu Tastasu is back again
this year
Winter excursion, or winter expedition
Everyone is going on an excursion
My butt hurts
They are excited in the middle of winter
in Tokyo
Ebichu Tastasu, start!
What is the secret of Ebichu's dance?
The secret of Ebichu's dance
Add various things to the private Ebisu
Middle School!
Ebichu Tastasu
This program is brought to you by these
sponsors.
Ebichu Tastasu has started!
Today, I'll be your guide
I'll announce the theme of this trip
Speaking of the cold season in the
middle of winter
It's a trip to Emitsu, a winter holiday,
or winter
Winter!
Can you call me quickly?
He is a tour guide
Thank you for your visit to Nagariboshi
City Tour
Matsuno is not here
He is not here
He caught a cold
He caught a cold?
It's better not to come here, because
it's 6 degrees Celsius now
It's strange
It's because of the cold
That's right
The other members boarded the bus
without catching a cold and started
their winter trip
What is their destination?
This time we are going to this place
Tokyo Deutsmura
Tokyo Deutsmura is a theme park in
Sodegaura City, Chiba Prefecture
Winter illumination is also recognized
as one of the three best illuminations
in Kanto
We are going to enjoy the trip here
Have you been here before?
Yes
Oh, I see. These three
What about you, Kashiwagi?
We go here every year
You are a Chiba resident
You go here a lot
So, you usually go to Chiba for winter
entertainment
You go to the place of heavy users of
Kashiwagi
Yes, heavy users
What about you, Kobayashi?
I've been there
When did you go there?
I think I went there in the afternoon of
the 6th grade
You went there only once?
Yes, only once
I think I went there twice
You are so funny
You have a very thin memory
What about you, Hoshino?
I went there with my family in the
spring when I was in elementary school
You want to go there in the spring,
don't you?
I want to go there in this season
Why?
By the way, what do you want to do when
you go there?
I want to eat a sausage
A sausage?
Is it famous?
I want to go there, but I don't know
what it is
It's a normal sausage
But it's long, so it's swirling
It's very big
Is it like a Katatsumori?
It's like a Kamponette
Why do you judge my Katatsumori as weak
and make it stronger?
to enjoy the members feel in Tokyo
Doritsumura
This time, we will have two teams to
enjoy the game
We have prepared something for the team
What is it?
This is a huge Amida lottery
It's very complicated
It's a huge Amida lottery
This is a huge Amida lottery
This is the first time I've seen it
I think this Amida lottery will be used
by many people
It's a long Amida lottery
Please be careful
While fighting against the fear of car
drunkenness, the Amida lottery for all
members has ended
Amida!
The results are...
Team A is Yasumoto, Hirota, Kobayashi,
Nakayama.
Team B is Mayama, Hoshina, Matsuno, and
Kashiwagi.
The team names are...
Team Kosoa and Team Kosoa and Team Kosoa
and Team Kosoa
Team Kosoa and Team Kosoa
While they were running, the Ebi-Chu-Go
family arrived at Tokyo Doitsumura.
It's warm!
It's warm, isn't it?
Let's go!
We're at Tokyo Doitsumura!
Here is the tour plan that Nagareboshi
prepared for you.
Enjoy the popular attractions of Tokyo
Doitsumura in a draw format for two
teams.
The team that wins the draw gets points.
The team that gets the most points will
receive a luxurious prize.
Now, let's enjoy the popular attractions
in Tokyo!
Please enjoy it to the fullest!
I'm already excited!
The first popular attraction is...
Everyone, please look over there!
It's here!
Cute!
With me, Guten Morgen!
Tokyo Doitsumura!
Thank you, everyone!
So, this is the famous Tokyo
Doitsumura's interesting bicycle!
There are many interesting bicycles like
this!
About 20 kinds of interesting bicycles
can be ridden in this popular
attraction!
The game to play here is...
It's called, the funny bicycle race!
It's just like that
Who said it's just like that?
It's fine, right? It's just like that
It's simple, right?
That's right
You two will ride on one bike, and start
at the same time
You will go around the course 3 times
Ride on the funny bicycle with one group
of two
Start at once!
Go through three special courses and get
points by ranking
Here is the funny bicycle that
determines the winner
So, here are some funny bicycles
They are cute, aren't they?
I think they are dolphins
They are pandas
Hirota's favorite, pandas
They are in a strange shape
They are in a shape of a teacup
So, now, you have to choose a bicycle
Let's point at the bicycle
If you wear it, you can play rock-paper-
scissors
Let's go
One, two, three
Which one?
This one
Who won?
Rock-paper-scissors
As a result of rock-paper-scissors,
Hoshina decided to ride a teacup-shaped
bicycle
Hirota, you said, you like pandas
No, I don't
Because they are different
That's right
But, it looks heavy
The head looks heavy
Really?
Buy a teacup-shaped bicycle at Family
Car
100 points!
Kobayashi-Nakayama pair got the dolphin
bike
In the end, Yasumoto-Hirota pair got the
panda bike which doesn't seem to have
any speed
Which team will win?
Everyone, please get on the bike
It's cool
Wait
That handle looks good on you
I see
And Hoshina
I'm going to hit my knee
Where are you going to pilot?
There
There?
There is a brake
Why is it slanted?
I don't know
The distance between you and the GoPro
is very close
What happened to the person who made it?
It's amazing
Panda-chan
How is it?
It looks fine
Only Hirota is in the camera
There is no camera
And there is no place to lean
I'm just riding
Fuyuen 2017
The interesting bicycle Tokyo Doitsumura
Grand Prix
It's finally starting!
Ready, set, go!
I'm scared!
Help me!
My butt hurts!
I'm scared!
Help me!
Ouch!
I'm stuck!
What's wrong?
She's going to get a cramp.
I'm scared!
I'm stuck!
Pull her from the inside!
Ouch!
The last lap!
She's fast!
What's wrong?
Ouch!
I'm sorry!
I'm stuck!
I'm scared!
Her legs are spinning.
My butt hurts!
I'm stuck!
The last lap!
She's stuck!
She's fast!
The interesting bicycle race is
about to start!
After this, the race of 2nd place will
not be particularly dead heat, but
please continue to watch
I'm not going to fall
Have you ever been this close?
Hoshino is winning
Hirota is starting to fall with his legs
One more lap
I want to stop
The wheels are so small
You can't get on
You can't get on?
One more lap
Are you ok?
Let's do it this way
This is the end
Be careful
It's coming from behind
Are you ok?
It's weird
Go this way
I'm going to fall
The wheels are so small that they can't
get on
I'm going to fall
Don't make me fall
I'm almost there
Wait, this way is dangerous
I'm going
Look this way
You're standing
You can't get on
One more lap
They got on
Let's announce the result
It was a close race
Bayama Kashiwagi Pair
Congratulations on winning
It was a close race
It was overwhelming
And the second place is
Hoshinata
Thank you
It was so slow
I was riding with Matsuno's spirit
The wheels were spinning but
I couldn't get on
I was trying so hard
The result of an interesting race
The team that finished 1st and 2nd
got 5 points in total
and got a big lead
The next race is
The next attraction is
This way
I'm scared
Which Germany called me?
Germany?
I'm scared
So, we can do Shiba-Sori
Let's go to Shiba-Sori relay competition
The next competition is Shiba-Sori race
If you slide down, you run up the slope
of 60m and touch the next member
If you relay Sori, you can win the team
who finish earlier
The team who finish earlier is the
winner
The team who win gets 5 points
Which team will win by relaying Sori?
Team Hosowa Germany, please announce the
order
No.1 is?
No.2
No.3
No.4
I see
Like this
And team Menten, No.1
No.2
And No.3
No.4
You can't complain
So we have to do it twice
We don't have time to give help, so it's
advantageous
I see
After this, the fierce Shibasori relay
competition starts
Fuyuen 2017 Shibasori Relay
The winner of this competition will get
a luxury item
The heated battle starts now
This is the final battle
I'm scared
Shibasori battle, ready
Riko, go
Riko
I can't do it
Kashiwagi
Which one is faster?
Hirota is fast
He's so fast
Kashiwagi is going to explode
It's here
I can't do it
Go go go
It's a bit cold
Hirota
Go go go
Mayama is cute
Mayama, one more lap
Go go go
Mayama, go
I'm going to cry
You're good
Ayano!
Good luck!
Wait a moment
They have one enemy left
They battle It's a deadly war
Got a bite.
Where is it?
Which is it?
It's here!
Team Upi Upi wins!
It's a big comeback
We've done the Shibasori competition
How fast can you climb a hill?
It's a hill climbing competition
At the end, Mayama was walking on the
hill
I saw it at Hakone station
It was good
The winner is the maintenance team
We'll wait for you
The maintenance team won the Shibasori
relay
The maintenance team won 10 to 1
So, lastly, please do the winning slide
Wait, wait, wait
What is it?
You're going to climb up?
You can't do that
I'm glad I won
You're going to win, right?
Hurry up and win
Hurry up
I won!
Go, go
I won
Why?
Why am I walking again?
So, the winning slide by the maintenance
team
So, the winning slide
Please
1, 2, 3
The sea is coming
This way
They are scattered
1, 2, 3
Matsuda, come on!
Tokyo, Germany
Good
Now, it's time for lunch time
This way please
The lunch that the members have been
waiting for is BBQ
But
The thing I'm worried about is that
Every time we have BBQ
We don't get to take a lot of pictures
Every time we have BBQ, we eat without
thinking
Why do we have to eat BBQ so much?
We got a comment from the production
team
The price is that, so please eat
normally this time
Don't worry about the camera
You already threw away the BBQ?
I threw it away
I cut all the camera
Just eat normally
Like you're at home
And the reward for the winning team is
This is it
The famous German sausage
This is the one you ate in Kashiwagi,
isn't it?
This is the round sausage
It's rounder than you imagine
Let's eat a lot without caring about the
camera
Let's eat
This is the reward for the winning team
It's big
It's a good sound
It's cold
It's good
It's different from the other side
It's like a local food
This is beautiful
It's good
Hirota, is it good?
The round sausage is done
How can we eat this?
Cut it from there?
How can we cut it?
It's going to be separated
I think so
You have a new idea of roundness
You are going to stretch it
Is this right?
It's like this
What is this?
Let's eat this together
I see
The person who stretched it is surprised
It's cut easily
How is the taste?
It's good
It's not round
It's just a normal sausage
It's good
Let's eat this sausage and do a winning
report
Eat this and say something to the camera
The winning team will do a winning
report
The sausage is big
Please do a winning report
It's good
The hot reaction is good
It's hot, isn't it?
Next time, the photo contest will be
held in Fuyuen
Thank you for watching. Please subscribe
to our channel.
This program was brought to you by the
following sponsors.
Ready, set, go!
Thank you!
Tokyo is delicious!