Next time, we'll be back with the fourth
episode of Uchiwa Ukemono!
I'm the master of imitating
It's the first time in 2 years that they
are having a party with their members
Will the new queen of imitating be born?
Tonight, we will start the imitating
party
First, please enjoy the song
The world's most curious about Apple
Watch news, Saito Asuka
I'm looking at you. I'm looking at you a
little.
I'm looking at you a lot.
I saw you. I saw you completely.
I'm looking at you in this way.
I'm looking at you when I can.
Let's continue.
I'm going to the one who is too cute to
be a
six-year-old.
Good morning.
You're cute today, too.
The one who is too cute to be a six-
year-old.
I woke up alone this morning.
You're amazing. You're great. You're
cute.
And I ate three tomatoes this morning.
You ate three? You're amazing. You're
great. You're cute.
You're a good girl.
It's good. It's cute, but I ate three
tomatoes.
Three tomatoes is pretty amazing, isn't
it?
If it was three big ones, it would be
amazing.
It's an animal.
That's amazing.
Let's continue. Please continue.
The part where the song ends with the
head shaking, the part where B and
Takeshi appear, Sugawara Satsuki.
I've never seen this before.
The one that's jiggly.
This one?
This?
No, the last one.
The last one is that.
The jiggly one is the same.
It's interesting.
Next one, please.
Yuru Tsutagawa, living in a different
time zone.
Tsutagawa, dancing?
That's true.
It's so different.
I was wondering how to dance.
Everyone is different.
Only one person does a lot.
I understand.
Asuka, do you watch Apple Watch?
I've been watching Apple Watch all the
time.
Even if I say, hey, Asuka.
I can't listen to the story.
Asuka, you were imitated.
I'm aware of that.
I think Apple Watch is good.
If you get a notification.
I'm worried about breathing other than
communication.
Asuka, don't you have an idea to remove
the approach?
No.
It's stuck to my arm.
It's because of the position.
It may be worse.
It's like this.
I can't see my face.
I don't know which is better.
You're in a mess.
I like the smell of Ichinose.
Did you smell Ichinose at that time?
I can smell it.
I'm holding it tight.
I'm scared.
Ichinose is scary since a while ago.
I was worried about only you.
I'm curious if Ogawa ate three tomatoes
today.
Please tell me that.
It's a big tomato.
Really?
It's an animal.
I cut it into small pieces.
OKAMOTO.
Is this a tomato that is soft?
I do it.
Does everyone nod?
I'm aware of it.
I was shaking when I was taught the
choreography.
I was in the middle of a tour.
I thought it was a shaking choreography.
I see.
What is it?
I do this to make a vibrato.
I do this.
You are a little like TAKISU.
You are not a vibrato.
You are told to hold it.
I have been told about 30 times.
Please fix it.
Hayashi.
I was wondering how Hayashi did it.
This is interesting.
Really?
I understand.
I understand the viewers.
I want Hayashi to get off the car
quickly.
I understand.
When you see a hole in the rock, you
can't help but be curious.
There's a hole in the rock.
What?
Scary.
Too scary.
You are scary.
You put your finger in the hole of your
ear.
Do you do that?
I will choose the hole of my ear.
You can put it in the hole of your ear.
I don't think so.
Please continue.
Makeup is too rough.
Like this.
Oh, you do this.
Too fast.
I'm so smart today.
She said something like that.
Interesting.
I don't know unless I'm a member.
Next.
The second half of the game.
Oh, good job.
Yumeki, good job.
You are beautiful today.
You are like a sculpture.
Yumeki,
Hey!
She is so funny.
I see.
Ichinose, your turn.
I think there are two types of ears.
The one I like and the one I don't like.
I see.
I will be able to eat the food I like
without saying anything.
You will be able to roll it.
I see.
It's not a hole in the ear.
It's called a self-reliance.
I see.
I like this.
Do you want to touch this?
I want to touch it.
I see.
That's why you do this.
What is your favorite ear?
I like this one.
It's like a siren.
Like a siren?
So,
Check out the other videos.
Show me your ears.
Oh, I see. I think I saw the
It's like a high-end store.
How do you touch it?
I want to see it.
Can you eat it?
What's this video?
It's a pretty amazing video.
Next, Shibata.
I was really stupid.
When I finished my makeup, I got all of
them.
I took out all my luggage from the bag.
The clothes on the desk were all messed
up.
I see.
You look like you're doing it right.
But your makeup is like that.
I've been shading like Aoi.
Did you learn how to do it?
When I do shading, I think,
I'm doing it while thinking,
I'm going to make my face smaller.
I'm going to make it smaller.
I'm not gentle.
I'm shaving my face.
That's what you're shaving.
And Kuromi.
This is amazing.
It was interesting.
The next comment.
Have you ever seen it?
I've been beaten.
You've been beaten.
You did it properly.
I'd like to do it with my shoulders.
But I have a problem with my sex.
It's okay.
Do you do it when you're stupid?
I do.
I want to be beaten.
Ayane doesn't like it.
Himura is in a woman's room.
The following entry is for the imitation
competition of the land.
Let's go to the next block.
The usual Kitagawa Yuri
Simple
Hello, I'm Kitagawa Yuri
Similar
My hobby is to look at the sky
I'm a quick talker who can do it
recently
Similar
I said that I was a big roll, red roll,
and small roll
Thank you very much
Similar
Good
Very similar
Let's continue
Let's go
The greeting of Kubo is strange
The greeting of Kubo?
Good morning
Manatsu-san, thank you for your time
today
By the way, I bought a souvenir for Kubo
I'm glad
Thank you very much
Is this serious?
Why do you say eggplant?
I can't say eggplant
I said eggplant
All eggplant
Some people say yes
Let's go
Please continue
Kubo Shiori's voice is louder than usual
when talking about baseball
Good morning Shiori
Good morning
You were on the radio yesterday, right?
Did you sleep well?
No, really, yesterday I was so late
I'm so tired
Shiori, Mogi is back from the army
Oh, really?
He's been on the team for two times and
he's got good grades recently
You're too small
She's the smallest among us
Let's continue
If you make a mistake, you will be a
mentor who has been trained for 8 years.
This is dangerous.
Please watch again.
What is this?
Wow, this is amazing.
Oh, I have to use the
stopwatch.
I have to use the stopwatch.
I don't think I've washed it, but I'm
using it like a line.
Oh, is that so?
It's difficult to go back after it's
like this.
This is pretty amazing.
It's a mistake.
It's like this.
Matsuo.
You're good.
It's a normal Kitagawa.
Thank you.
I started imitating Yuri-chan's voice
about three and a half years ago.
You've been doing it a lot.
My voice has been updated a lot.
Oh, is that so?
It's been quiet.
So, when I imitate it, I'll get a voice.
So, please practice with that.
Otherwise, I won't give you a warning.
I won't give you a warning.
I can't get a warning.
It's okay because it's similar to what
it is now.
Next, Ume.
What's the word for the head?
I just fixed it.
Thank you for your time until about a
year ago.
When I first heard it, I doubted my
ears.
About a year ago, the eggplant was
amazing.
That's right.
I thought I was being pranked.
You changed your name.
I was a masu when I met him.
I became a nasu from some point.
I said that.
I didn't intend to fix it from there.
But UME said to me in a straight face.
He said he had been pranking me for
about three months.
I noticed it.
Does anyone else know nasu?
I shared it with UME.
I said that.
He said nasu.
Then he is a nasu.
I saved it for a year to do it in the
studio.
I was doing it.
I see.
This is a true story.
This is amazing.
The next person was KUBO.
KUBO's voice is small when he is in a
low mood in the morning.
But I can't hear it many times.
I listen to it many times and reply to
it.
I don't know what you're talking about.
But when KOHAZUKI talks about baseball,
I suddenly get excited.
I open my eyes wide.
It's like fried eggs.
Fried eggs.
I don't think I'm low.
You are very low.
I noticed that the third generation
pretended to hear me.
Did you notice?
I pretended to hear it.
I was excited and I was doing it again.
I noticed that I was being ignored.
I didn't notice it because I was doing
it.
I think there is a microphone here.
This is a radio.
If it was a radio, I would have talked
quietly.
I think it's because the sound of the
Japanese language is coming.
I will be careful.
Hello.
That's not it.
I will sing the first song.
I am a nasu.
Why did you say nasu?
Next is SATO KAI.
Did you wear this?
I wore this and the electricity flowed.
Why did the electricity flow?
Did you flow at that time?
I was flowing.
This is the first time in my life.
You don't have to do it.
Did you do it on purpose?
I was wearing it.
You are imitating me.
What kind of imitation is that?
You don't have to hurt yourself.
This is real.
This is not a rehearsal.
This is the real thing.
I usually pretend not to be wrong.
But SAKU-CHAN is cute when she makes a
mistake.
You make a mistake.
You are surprised.
When I am surprised or when I make a
mistake, I feel like I have done it.
I feel like I have done it.
Can you still play the low frequency
treatment?
This is the maximum.
I am wearing this.
Why do you do that?
You can't do that.
I want to reproduce the real thing.
This is not real.
After this, the new generation of
imitations will be active.
There are still many new stories.
Next, the five of them will enter.
Let's go to the next block.
The first one, please.
The answer is too random.
I'm hungry.
Haru, did you have breakfast?
No.
I see.
What's for lunch today?
Haru, what do you feel like?
Beef?
No.
Pork?
Chicken?
No.
税!
What is this?
税 and税?
税 or税?
At first I didn't understand what 税 was.
Let's go.
Next, please.
Nao Tomisa, who is handsome in every
way.
You're tired.
Are you okay?
Thank you.
I'll carry your luggage.
It's cold.
Is that what you do?
Look.
This is surprising.
This is a man's style.
Let's go.
Okamoto Hina, who can play the ball
smoothly.
I see.
I'm hungry.
Don't be a sweet girl.
You can't be a sweet girl forever.
There are sweets here.
Hina will take them.
She is amazing.
Thank you.
We will resume practicing soon.
Yes.
It's fun because it's standing at first.
It's fun.
It's like a Tasuga.
It's like a ballet dancer.
Next, please.
I'm Maya Wada, who can be compared to
the whole Hiroshima.
Good job.
Maya said she'll be here for 4 hours.
4 hours?
If you have 4 hours, you can go back to
Hiroshima.
I bought a bicycle the other day.
It's very heavy.
It's about 14kg.
It's one border collie.
It's heavy.
I see.
I see people who play baseball.
There were a lot of 5th-graders here.
First of all, Ogawa.
Ina.
You're going to answer randomly.
Why do you answer like that?
I've been playing baseball since I was
in elementary school.
There was a time when I was saying Ina.
You don't say it now.
I graduated.
It's strange.
You can tell by listening to that
episode.
It's strange.
There are many things.
Next.
Tomi-san is handsome.
I think everyone knows the 5th-grader.
For example, when I tried to get out of
the car, I was surprised.
Really?
I thought you were surprised.
There are many things.
I'm just walking on a road with nothing.
Be careful of your feet.
Watch carefully.
Oh, I see.
There are some bad impressions, but
there are also some good ones.
There are also some good impressions,
but it feels good to see.
And Ikeda.
It's fun just to stand up.
It's a special thing for ballet dancers.
That's right.
Did you do it?
I've been doing it for 7 years from the
age of 4 to 11.
It was a little bit of a move.
It was completely different.
Ballet has a number on its foot.
Hina Okamoto always has a foot number 2.
2?
This is number 2.
2 is Kasuga.
Kasuga is number 2.
Do it with your fingers.
This is Kasuga.
That's amazing.
I thought this was a Goki block.
I'm sorry to have come out.
You've been imitating the wada that's
always been imitated.
That's right.
This is actually a copy of the one I
borrowed from Hina Higuchi.
Oh, really.
You've been imitated.
I've been told a lot.
I like dogs, so I can understand that.
Hina told me the other day that it was
her 11th anniversary.
It's the life of a golden retriever.
No.
This is the king's new feature.
Let's continue.
The choreographer who has excited
everyone so much that he doesn't know
what he is saying.
The choreographer who has excited
everyone so much that he doesn't know
what he is saying.
This is the last dance scene.
Nice to meet you.
Nice, nice, nice.
I'm a queen.
This is also a joke, but does anyone
know this?
I didn't make any adjustments, but it's
even more amazing.
I see.
So you're trying to liven things up?
That's right.
I'm like, DOSUKOI DOSUKOI DOSUKOI!
What should you do when you're DOSUKOI
DOSUKOI?
I was told not to laugh, and to walk
forward seriously.
I was putting out a fire or something.
But at that time, I was like, DOSUKOI
DOSUKOI DOSUKOI DOSUKOI!
Why DOSUKOI?
What kind of state should I be in?
I do this.
I do this, DOSUKOI DOSUKOI DOSUKOI!
Oh, really?
Now, let's start today's product
introduction.
Thank you for your time.
Good morning.
Well, you're good at this.
This is so funny.
up Panchiisluk
ним
e
No go quoi
Wait a minute.
It's a song for the channel
registration.
Cut!
Please subscribe to Nagisa's channel.
Please subscribe to the channel.