includes movie videos from Ebi!
Now we are going to
take a walk!
Today the second part of today's
introduce
is Naita Visit!
Today I want to take a walk
Last time we were here when I
appeared from the bottom
I think I got a lot of compliments from
the fans.
I thought so, but today I don't have a
single pigeon.
I'm not there.
I came up from the stairs.
I don't know if it's a good thing, but
I'd like to go for a walk right away.
Let's go!
So this is a store near the station.
Actually, there's a music video for the
23rd Summer Night.
There's an individual version.
It's on the fan club.
I used to eat dumplings here.
I took a lot of pictures and used them
on the music video.
I came here and I thought I could
introduce you to the Atachi of the
Summer Night.
As I walked, I passed this road.
I was taking a picture of the music
video.
There's a toy store here.
I was looking at the toy and I went to a
different place.
Last time, I couldn't use this camera.
I was in the picture all the time.
Today I'm going to use this camera.
This is a delicious sandwich shop.
Where did I go?
Did I go this way?
I found the pedestrian bridge.
I'm going to take a picture of the
pedestrian bridge.
It's raining while I'm taking pictures
of the music video.
I didn't have a camera.
I was in a bad mood.
I found it.
I took a picture of the pedestrian
bridge.
It was raining and I was wearing a
umbrella.
I didn't know that I was taking pictures
of the pedestrian bridge.
I was wearing an umbrella.
I'm in the pedestrian bridge.
I was in the picture of the Atachi of
the Summer Night.
I left it.
I went to a place called KAHOSAKE when I
was 20 years old.
Do you remember this place?
This is the place where I went to
KAHOSAKE last time.
Let's go there.
There are people who know this place.
Let's interview them.
Do you remember this place?
This is the place where I went to
KAHOSAKE last time.
Let's go there.
What?
There are people who know this place.
Let's interview them.
I'm sorry.
Who are you?
You know this place, right?
I know you.
I was in Machimura.
I usually drink tea.
Really?
I didn't know that.
I'm Rataima.
You are lying.
I'm wrong.
Did you come to Machimura?
I came to Machimura.
You brought a camera.
What are you drinking?
I'm asking you something.
I'm sorry.
Do you have orange juice?
Yes, I have.
What are you drinking?
I'm drinking tea.
You are drinking tea.
I drink tea.
Can you drink tea?
I'm thirsty.
I'm drinking orange juice.
I drank orange juice.
I'm drinking.
Cheers.
It's dangerous.
I'm walking on the street.
Thank you.
I'm thirsty.
I'm not dehydrated.
I'm walking.
Thank you.
Have you ever been to Machimura?
I haven't.
I've been here for the first time.
I've been here for the second time.
I don't know much about Machimura.
I've been here with you three times.
I went to eat with you.
I haven't been here for the first time.
It was the second time.
I feel like I've been walking with you
all night.
I came to celebrate the 10th
anniversary.
There is a sake stand in Kamazaki.
Let's take a walk.
Please guide me.
I feel like I'm in Okinawa.
I want to go to Okinawa.
I remember.
This is the sake stand.
I ate this two years ago.
That's right.
It's a year ago.
There is a tea here.
I drank tea.
There is a tea shop here.
Hello.
You are kind.
I want to drink.
Let's go.
This is a sake stand.
I was walking with you.
RICO was walking with me.
I noticed that you were walking with me.
We finished walking together.
I think you were already expecting it.
I came alone to Kamazaki.
My friends were walking together.
I want to drink with RICO.
Last time I came alone, I drank with a
sake stand T-shirt.
I want to wear it again.
I will change clothes.
I changed clothes.
This is a sake stand.
This is a winter version.
This is a trainer.
This is red.
I am wearing a full-body jacket.
I can't see my whole body.
My whole body is red.
I think I can drink slowly.
I want to become an adult and say
something.
Adults often ask for a drink.
I want to go to a store and say
something.
I want to ask for a drink.
Please say it.
I will say it.
I will say it for the first time.
I'm sorry.
I will say it in person.
I will say it in two.
I am an adult.
Adults often ask for a drink.
I drink beer for the first time.
I have never drunk beer.
I want to drink with RICO.
I said it on my birthday.
I said it for 4 months.
I am already drinking.
I turned 20 on October 28.
I was born early.
I'm worried.
Thank you.
What happened?
I'm scared.
I'm nervous.
I will drink.
I'm scared.
I can drink.
The glass is cold.
Adults drink beer.
Many people work hard.
Is it because I drink beer at the store?
It's easy to drink.
I thought so.
What did you drink last time?
I drank salmon beer.
Salmon beer?
I want you to order later.
OK.
What's in the sake?
Soy milk in the sake.
What? Soy milk?
Is it broken?
It was really delicious.
I'll order it after I finish drinking
beer.
I'm nervous.
I've never seen it before.
What was it?
Saitan live streaming?
Saitan live streaming.
I've seen it since the countdown.
I know.
I'm excited.
It's delicious.
It's easy to drink.
Do you drink beer?
I don't drink beer.
After the live streaming,
I drank Ebisu beer.
I was curious about it.
I drank it because I was curious.
It was bitter.
It was a little early.
Since then?
It's delicious.
It was bitter.
It was a birthday magic.
It was delicious.
I thought it was delicious.
I drank it after a while.
I was wondering if it was bitter.
It was a birthday magic.
It was a little bitter.
It's amazing.
It's easy to drink.
I like beer that's not that bitter.
I'm drinking it now.
I asked Rika-chan.
What's a beer that's easy to drink?
I asked her.
I'm writing down my phone numbers.
I want to drink it.
It's good.
I'm looking forward to it.
What would you like to order?
I'd like to order a chanjacheep.
I like it.
What should I order?
It's a snack.
I'd like to order a long potato kimchi.
I want to eat it.
The long potato kimchi we ate last time
was delicious.
It was delicious.
I'm not sure what to order.
It looks delicious.
It's a Japanese rice cake.
Rika-chan likes it.
I like it.
I asked her.
I'm not sure what to order.
I'm sorry.
investigatory cheese, ground beef, fried
over feeling longer
eat long experiência
this shop made of sweet potato
Japanese
I like both of them
Do you drink when you
drink, do you eat together Ahetsu
I drank with my friends at home.
Thank you.
I drank with my friends outside.
I drank standing up.
That's fast.
You drank a lot of sopan.
I think it's easy for girls to drink.
I'm glad.
I'm glad I'm your friend.
It's my first time.
It's already fun.
It's really fun.
We drank together on the day of the
trip.
We drank plum wine.
I liked plum wine.
Riko recommended it to me.
I drank Japanese sake a few days ago.
I drank Japanese sake with my friends.
It was fun.
I didn't think it would be such a day.
I felt like I was in the middle of a
relationship.
I thought I was going to be 20 years
old.
I went to eat with my mother after I
turned 20.
I liked oolong tea.
I wanted to order oolong tea.
I asked my mother to order oolong tea.
I didn't think it would be such a day.
I drank tea with my mother.
It's fun.
I'm going to be 20 years old.
I didn't drink much.
I'm still 20 years old.
I saw you as a student.
You have been playing soccer for two
years.
I thought it was two years ago.
I felt strange.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
I'm going to eat chanja.
Can you eat chanja?
I like it.
It's a snack.
I'm going to eat.
Is it delicious?
Is it spicy?
It's a little spicy.
I'm going to eat a lot.
It's delicious.
Is this your first time eating chanja?
It's my first time eating chanja.
What is this?
This is a long-leaved potato.
This is delicious.
I want it to be summer soon.
Everyone is eating in the summer.
I want to drink tea in the terrace.
It's not fashionable.
It's fashionable and mature.
I have the image of an older sister.
Let's do it next year.
I'm interested in hot wine in winter.
It's fashionable.
Hot wine.
I haven't drunk wine yet.
I don't know the type of wine.
I got wine from MAYA.
Champagne?
I often drink alcohol on my 20th
birthday.
I drank a lot of alcohol.
I haven't drunk alcohol yet.
I drink a lot of Japanese sake.
Champagne is fashionable.
I didn't drink champagne.
Everyone drank Japanese sake.
I'm happy.
Let's drink at home again.
Let's do it.
It's delicious.
Thank you.
It looks delicious.
It's hard to find fried potatoes.
There is no fried potatoes.
I like long potatoes.
It's delicious.
Let's eat.
It's crispy.
Is it a kimchi?
It's a long potato.
It's delicious.
I learned that you shouldn't drink sake
with a skipper.
I learned that.
I learned that the way to drink is
different depending on the condition of
the day.
My family likes to drink.
I learned that you should eat a lot of
food before drinking.
That was the best lesson.
We drank at home together.
The lineup of food was fried chicken and
takoyaki.
And gyoza.
I didn't bake gyoza.
I ate three kinds of gyoza.
I ate too much.
I was full.
I ate something refreshing.
I ate a lot of fried food.
Why do you eat?
It's important.
I'm happy.
I feel sorry for other members.
I'm looking forward to drinking with
RICO.
We all said we wanted to eat together.
But we didn't have a schedule.
I haven't had a drink with everyone.
This is the second time.
I'm sorry for other members.
I'm sorry. I'm worried about makgeolli.
I want to eat Korean food.
I'm worried about makgeolli.
Is it similar to amazake?
I've never had this before.
Thank you.
What is this?
This is salmon.
I know the color of salmon.
I think it's salmon.
I'll mix it.
Yes.
Please.
Mix it.
Cute.
It's amazing to have seaweeds in this
color.
I mixed it.
I think it's about this.
Yes.
It's delicious.
I thought it would go well with soy
milk.
It's delicious.
It's sweet.
RIKO, present.
Thank you.
Shoes.
What is it?
Are you ready?
I'm ready.
I ordered mochi.
Both of you are forced to eat.
I can eat this.
I'm sorry.
I'll eat this.
Good job.
RIKO, congratulations.
Thank you.
I drink with you first.
Yes.
I drink with the members.
I drink with everyone.
Yes.
I drink with all the members.
I drink with everyone.