It's started! Eri-chuu Tatsuta-su!
Today, Yasumoto will be the second one.
I can hear the voice.
Can you put the headphones on?
Yes, this is it.
Ah, this is the one.
Hello!
You're still in front of me.
At least change your voice.
This is Hoshina.
Kirari rari rari rari-n!
I'm not doing anything!
Hoshina.
What is this?
It's okay, everyone.
Come out already.
Come out.
Ah, you're going to show your face from
there, right?
What is this panel?
This panel is
a panel that was used in the album's
normal jacket photos.
It was used in the jacket photos.
Ah, but the hair is beautiful.
The hair is very good.
Because this is very
It was pointed out in various ways.
This is difficult, certainly.
You can't see it from the back.
Because the back is very convenient.
You can't see anything.
The picture from behind is amazing.
What is this today?
Yes, today
Ah, I did it.
Ah, it's coming out already.
Do you just take it off normally?
What? What?
What's wrong? What's wrong?
Today, until the album is released,
6 days and
23 hours and 56 minutes and 15 seconds.
No, no, the countdown is fast.
This is just right.
This will change more and more.
Because it's not a live broadcast.
That's the way it is now.
So,
I'm going to talk about the album
release that's coming up next week.
I want to talk about the album.
Raise your hand if you want to talk
about the album.
Raise your hand.
Oh, just the lyrics.
So, today,
The pre-order of the album.
I would like to dig into it.
That's right.
This time is a special edition.
3rd new album of Erichu.
Anarchy, Great Liberation Special.
I'm crazy about you
What should I do with my heart?
Moratorium
Add various things to your private Ebisu
junior high school
Ebisu Justice
This program is provided by the sponsor
you are watching.
So, next week...
Next week...
It's close
You're not reading the kanji
Next week, we'll release the album
You can read the first part
We'll be releasing the album!
MC Yasumoto and Ebichu alone are making
me nervous.
Just like what you saw just now.
We have invited this person who is
involved in the production.
Thank you for coming!
This is the sound director, Seto-san.
Seto-san has been producing sound since
the debut single of Ebichu.
He will be introducing the album with
Ebichu.
Are you nervous just with Ebichu?
I don't think I can give you any wrong
information.
You can't give wrong information, right?
You can't give any good information.
First, we will be introducing the
Anarchy Jacket.
This time, we will be releasing the
limited edition A and B and the regular
edition of the 3 types.
I've been curious about this for a long
time.
You're wearing the crown of your head.
What is this?
It's a celestial bird.
You don't know?
It's not something you can carry around.
You can hold it like this.
You're so mean!
I'm taking it from Seto-san.
You're only a friend of Seto-san.
I'm really thankful.
Why is it a celestial bird?
Because it's a hole tree.
Because it has holes.
I see.
How do you take this?
Trampoline!
Why is your pronunciation so good?
A limited edition A jacket photo created
a sense of movement using trampoline.
I picked up a还 from that photo booth.
When I was little, I used to play with
trampolines.
When I was shooting, I flew really high.
I was really angry when I flew.
Why?
Because you were stuck?
Yes, I was stuck and it was hard to hit
the light.
You flew that high?
I flew a lot.
When you put a blanket on the ceiling,
you were like a fly.
I was like a fly.
You were like a fly.
You played trampoline, right?
Yes, I played with the machine.
Did you really play with the machine?
Yes, I did.
You didn't know anything.
I didn't know.
The recording of the song will begin.
Let's see the contents. All 16 songs are
recorded in the new album アナーキー.
There are 16 songs.
There are many.
Takuya-san, please read each song.
Please read correctly.
It's easy. It's not interesting, but
I'll do it.
I want to fill the blank.
Amazing!
I'm making fun of you, right?
I can read it.
絶対アナーキー.
I want to make fun of you.
This is a song made by Kaiki-san.
春休みモラトリアム中学生.
ポップコントーン.
Next.
What is this?
Just like you think
Anything is fine
I think it's anarchy
Omoppa
Omoppa?
No
I can't read this
I'm a juice can and a cotton swab
This is close. Not a cotton swab
A mole
Close!
It's hard
I don't like it. It hurts
A ghost
I don't like it
It's common in our time
Ah!
I see
Together
1,2
A pimple
You got it right
Let's listen to the songs of each member
From the songs that are full of energy
Please listen while imagining the song
First, Mayama
This is my recommended song
Please Jesus
What kind of song is this?
This is a song that everyone thought
once
It's a song that looks painful just by
looking at the lyrics
But when you listen to the song, you can
feel warm and happy. I want to listen to
this song after I grow up
So you can listen to it later and it
will come to you?
I'm still 19 years old, so I think
adults will think that young people
don't understand
But it's a song that came to me and I
cried in the train
I cried
So I think that if adults listen to it,
they will think more about it
I want to hear
Next is Yasumoto's recommended song
I'm Ren
The fourth is Popcorn tone
What kind of song is this?
This is a song that makes you feel like
popcorn
I don't know if it's a love song or a
friend's story
It's a song that expresses a girl's sad
feelings and wants to move forward
The sound is cool
Is it a bright song?
It's a song that feels like a song, but
the lyrics are a little sad and cute
Next is Hirota's recommended song
My recommended song is Zettai Anarchy
When I heard this song, I was so stupid
So I thought I was very normal
It's a song that teaches me that I can
be more free
It's a perfect song to take me to the
world of Ebichu
So I like it the most
Zettai, how was the present?
300 points
Hirota, this is Zettai Anarchy
Do you remember who made it?
Unicorn's Abe-don
Abe-don made it
We have a message from Abe-don
I'm so excited
Abe-don has already released a song
called Zettai Anarchy
He has released many hit songs as the
leader of the legendary band Unicorn
What a surprise! The members got a
message
Thank you.
I'm Don Abe.
Thank you for your hard work on the song
of Zette Anarchy.
I hope you can play with this song.
I'll make it again if it breaks down.
Please play freely.
Let's do our best and play together
again.
I'm glad to hear that.
We are also from the Unicorn generation.
We want to play the song.
We want to play together.
Next is the song of the Oshi-na.
I am the third song of the last song.
What kind of song is this?
The atmosphere of the song is completely
different.
Just listening to the song makes me feel
good.
Especially, I like the song A-melody.
I feel like I'm in the water.
You feel like you're in the water?
I feel like I'm really vibrating.
Your voice?
Yes, my voice is like this.
When I recorded the song, I thought of
Wakame in the deep sea.
I thought it was Kurione.
It was a shiwakame.
I thought it was a shiwakame.
It's a strange atmosphere.
The chorus is powerful.
Mayamada-san made the song. He is the
one who has been with us since the first
song.
He is the one who supports us.
The chorus is powerful.
I see.
After this, Matsuno talks too much.
Matsuno-san is a good person.
To celebrate the release of the new
album, Anarchy, the members will explain
their favorite songs.
What is Matsuno's favorite song?
Please come in.
Oh, it's the All-Powerful Runner.
I love this song.
Oh, really?
What kind of song is this?
It's a song about a girl's one-sided
love.
Matsuno talks so much about Ryucho.
You like him.
I love him.
I have a favorite song.
It's number 2.
Don't say it's bad.
I'm trying my best.
You're trying your best.
But now you're saying you like him.
That's good.
Thank you.
I'll do it.
What kind of song is number 2?
It's a song about a girl's one-sided
love.
It's a long song.
I was going to sing it, but it's too
long.
Please sing it.
I like this part.
That part?
Yes.
If I buy milk tea at a vending machine,
I can't buy it as a treasure.
You can't.
But if you buy it, I can't buy it as a
treasure.
That's cute.
You're going to leave it in your room
without drinking it, right?
I don't know.
I'm not saying anything weird.
That's not what I'm saying.
You're going to keep it in your room
even if you drink it.
It's a good lyrics.
It's cute.
It's really cute.
I'm glad I could tell that you really
like this song.
We're about halfway through, but we
haven't heard any of your songs yet.
That's a weird story.
Everyone was waiting for you to
graduate.
Everyone's making a face that they can't
say anything.
Heer's 5th generation member, Kai-ki,
was a member of the rock band.
The song that started the show,
It's also in the album of the spring
vacation moratorium junior high school
students.
But we're halfway through.
I think so.
I think this is the song for everyone.
Three cards.
I see.
What is the song that Kashiwagi likes?
Let's go.
Next, Kashiwagi.
Yes.
Right?
Let's go.
The 9th mission survival.
I'm sorry. I didn't say anything about
the song.
This is a great song.
It's a great song.
What kind of song is this?
It's like a festival.
I'm very excited.
What kind of song is this?
The sound is cool, but the lyrics are a
little messy.
The title doesn't feel like a festival,
but it's like a festival.
It's a festival inside.
Oh, so the song title doesn't feel like
a festival?
It's like a young festival.
It's like a popping sound.
Paripi.
It's a party.
It's a party night.
I see.
That kind of thing.
I'm looking forward to it.
I see.
Next, what is the favorite song of
Kobayashi?
My favorite song is...
Ta-da!
It's a pimple.
It's not a pimple.
I was curious about this song called
pimple.
I couldn't read this title.
I can't imagine what kind of song it is.
According to Kobayashi's explanation,
The song title is...
I think the mother generation is
nostalgic.
Nostalgic?
Is it a song like that?
What kind of story is it?
There's a girl and a boy.
That girl has a pimple.
If the pimple heals, will you go on a
date with me?
I asked him.
You don't have to heal your pimples.
That's not what girls do.
Girls don't have pimples.
You can be more confident with girls.
I don't have pimples.
What are you talking about?
I don't know what you mean.
Wait a minute.
I have a pimple in my puberty.
I want to feel the moment of a girl.
I want to feel a different feeling when
I grow up.
You want to be a
I see.
I really understood.
And the last one is Nakayama.
What is the favorite song?
Please tell us what song Nakayama chose.
I'm very curious.
Finally it's out!
Kaeki-san, I'm glad you watched till the
end!
Yay!
I'm watching!
But this is a bit...
It's a bit forced, isn't it?
That's right.
Didn't the staff tell you to write it?
Right, Nakayama?
Eh?
Really?
Really? I wrote it.
I wrote it.
Nakayama, really?
I wrote it in the second one.
That's too bad.
No, no.
Everyone wrote it in the second one.
Yes.
I see.
Everyone wrote it in the second one.
That's too bad.
Everyone's favorite song.
I see.
Everyone's best 2 is amazing.
It's amazing.
It's obvious that everyone likes it.
I see.
Nakayama-san, why did you write this?
Ogata-san...
Ogata Kaeki-san wrote it.
Other than that?
I didn't say anything.
It's okay.
It's correct.
Other than that?
Among the songs I like,
in the song...
How do I say it?
There's a guitar solo.
I really like that part.
Hia-san plays it.
So, Nakayama-san.
Yes.
Who wrote the song for Moratorium Junior
High School?
Ogata Kaeki-san.
Yes.
We have a message from this person.
Oh, Kaeki-chan.
Everyone watching Ebi-chuu Tatsuta-san.
And everyone in Ebi-chuu.
Two shooting stars.
How are you?
Miracle.
Wait.
It's not a miracle.
I...
wrote a song called
Haruesei Moratorium Junior High School.
This song is a rock-like feeling.
The first part, the second part,
using the tencho,
and the beautiful melody line,
I think we were able to express
the core and catchy parts of Ebi-chuu
well.
I'm looking forward to hearing it live
again.
This has been Ogata Kaeki.
Asuna is amazing
For now, I'm fine
Kaiqi-san is fine
That's interesting, Kaiqi-san
Please give Kaiqi-san my message
Ogata-san, I'm waiting for the day when
I can play with Hiei-san and Ebichu
during the live show
I'm waiting for the day when I can play
with Hiei-san and Ebichu during the live
show
Thank you
Bye bye
Lastly, let's see what kind of album the
new album is
Let's ask the sound director Seto-san to
tell us
As the title says, it's an album with
various artists and writers
The album has a variety of sounds
That's what it sounds like
I'm sorry, I just heard Matsuno's
stomach rumbling
I'm sorry
I didn't hear it either
It was quite anarchy
Finally, we will have the album's hit
period
queuing while feeling flustered
This is the first time I do this
This is amazing
Since it's an anarchy, I would like to
make a hole here
I see
That sounds fun
By the way, what is the purpose of this?
To aim for the first place in the Oricon
I see
So, they will aim for the first place in
the anarchy and make a hole
Let's go
Aim for the first place in the Oricon
Ready, set, go
Wait a minute
What is that?
Wait, wait!
There are so many chikuwa
Wait, I want to eat the chikuwa
There are cucumbers in the chikuwa
Can I eat it?
I'm hungry
Let's make a wish and make a toast with
the first chikuwa
chikuwa
Cheers
Amazing
This is the first time we have made a
toast with chikuwa
Delicious
And the national tour starts on the 23rd
of this month
And the Blu-ray of Saitama Super Arena
was released at the same time as the
album
This time, we will show you the first TV
video of the tour
I want to spend another day together
I want to say goodbye
It's still different
Next time
What is necessary for the shrimp stew
now?
Training
What?
Every time the shrimp stew is trained
For me, ramen is a moment of happiness
In addition, the training of laughing
that opens the
mouth is the most important thing
I was waiting
I'm sure you'll say, too.