We are going to visit the holy sites of
anime in Tokyo!
It's called Aragawa Rock Gate.
It's a place that appears in Koichako
several times.
It also appeared in the beginning.
It appeared suddenly.
It also appeared in the second half.
It's a place that becomes a key point.
I see.
It's Sayakana's holy site, Saka.
Yes.
What do you want to do here?
I want to take a lot of pictures.
I think so, too.
I want to take a picture of the place
where the hat falls.
I see.
I understand.
I think so, too.
Please subscribe to our channel and
follow us on Twitter!
I'm here! I'm at the first place I
wanted to go to!
What is this place?
This is the place where Love Come is
shown.
I'm going to buy my favorite anime.
I'm at the place where Love Come is
shown.
Can I say it?
This is the place where the anime is
shown.
I'm happy!
I'm happy to be here. Thank you.
Where should we go?
Let's go down the stairs.
It's an arch-shaped staircase.
This is the scene where Taiga and Ryuji
talk.
I'm happy.
I can see the bridge over there.
That's the sacred place.
It's an arch-shaped staircase.
This is the sacred ground.
This is also a sacred ground.
The characters walking on the stairs are
here.
Can I take a picture?
Let's take a picture!
Please subscribe to this channel!
Can I take a picture of this building?
I can see all the buildings over there.
Where should I take a picture of it?
Maybe from the edge?
This building and that building are the
same.
So, if I take a picture of it from the
edge, it will be exactly the same.
I can see the building over there.
Let's take a picture of it.
Here.
I can see the bridge.
Say cheese!
Thank you.
Which floor is it?
The second floor.
You have long legs.
I have long legs.
Please subscribe to this channel!
I'm going to fly!
Takasu Ryujin, I want to be your foot.
Thank you.
Please subscribe to this channel!
15 minutes have passed.
I'm fine.
Thank you.
I want a picture of me here.
Can I go to the bridge?
Go ahead.
15 minutes left.
It's a great heat wave.
It's hot.
I'm tired.
I was left behind.
Iamped sexually
I'm sorry. I'll go over there.
I see.
Thank you for watching my video.
I'm so happy!
I ran too much.
I'm still lonely.
I'm happy to be able to shoot with the
motion that was a little stiff.
Here you are.
Thank you for the beer!
It's perfect!
I'm so happy to get here.
It's so nice here.
Why?
How was it today?
I always go to the place where I want to
go the most.
But, I was able to go to three places
today.
Thank you very much.
I was able to go to the place where the
master of pilgrimage is.
I was able to understand the nature of
pilgrimage.
Was it fun?
It was fun. I was happy to go with you.
I am happy that I came to the world of
pilgrimage.
It was fun.
Let's go together again.
Is there still a lot of places in Tokyo?
There are many places. There are many
places other than Tokyo.
I hope we can go together again.