Thank you for watching.
Last time, the members came to the
grandmother's house to spend the summer
vacation.
That night, they were able to overcome
the heat with a story of stairs that
burned their hair.
If it was a party, my eyes would pop
out.
At that time.
Please stop for a moment.
Emergency situation occurred. What
happened?
Finally, the shooting stopped. What is
the happening of fear?
The next fear is the scream.
Wait! Wait!
That was aああ
Ebi-Ju Justice
We will add many things to the private
school Ebi-Ju Justice!
Ebi-Ju Justice
This program is brought to you by the
following sponsors.
We are the first one to get married!
The moment I closed my eyes, the floor
started shaking.
The members were scared by the scary
story that Yasumoto and Hoshina had
shown last time.
Furthermore...
Hoshina, this flower...
A big surprise and panic.
They were completely scared by the
situation.
The members' mental state was already at
its limit.
But after this, the members were even
more scared.
We just had three members talk to us.
Today, we're going to read the real
story.
Please read it!
So, we're Kobayashi-san.
Kobayashi Gen-san is scared of the story
and talks about the super story.
Will Ebichu be able to endure the fear?
No, I don't want to be next to you!
This person isn't a ghost.
I'm not scared.
When I talk, you'll feel something
heavy.
You'll feel something.
Be careful.
What is this?
The ghost is coming!
Please watch again.
Hirota cried without crying
It's rare for Hirota to cry
I'm scared
Nakaima also cried
What's wrong, Nakaima?
Let's be friends
The camera is not working
Hirota cried and couldn't stop
This person is not a ghost
Hirota is crying
It's scary
It's impossible
Hirota is not good at scary stories
He is in despair before listening to the
super story
This atmosphere is impossible
It's not necessary to force it
I will be good at it
I can't scare you
Will he be able to endure the fear?
The beginning of the scary story that
Sessuji calls
My friend lives in the countryside
My friend lived in the countryside
She was there
One day, she called me and said she was
going to see me
She got in the car and went to see me
It's a very scary road
The lights of the gas station and
convenience stores are almost dark
There is a road that is most dangerous
That is the bridge
It's called the jumping bridge
Many people die there
I'm very lost when I cross that bridge
I don't like it
I sang and overcame it
I met her and talked about it
I'm going home
She gave me a CD
This is amazing
Thank you
Bye
I have a CD that I got from her
I will listen to it
It comes out right away
It comes out many times
Is it broken?
I put it in
I can hear the sound
Hey
What is this song?
Thank you for your viewing
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
The voice got louder and louder.
I told her to stop.
But she noticed immediately.
I see.
I stopped the car and called her.
I told her to stop playing pranks.
I told her that it was scary on the way
home.
She said it was a bad habit.
I asked her if she had seen the CD.
She said she had seen the CD.
I asked her if she had seen it.
She said she had seen it.
She said she saw a picture of the CD
when she went on a date.
A picture?
What was that voice?
I asked her if she had seen the CD.
I looked at the CD.
The CD was already coming out of the
car.
I asked her if she had seen the CD.
I asked her if she had seen it.
I was scared.
I started the engine and ran.
I noticed that the man's shadow was
running through me.
I noticed later.
I stopped the car and saw a bridge.
I thought it was scary and arrived home.
I thought the CD was a bad habit.
I thought it wasn't music.
I wanted to see the picture.
The file was all black and broken.
I couldn't see anything.
I wondered if something strange had
entered.
I zoomed in.
The file was black and had lines in it.
I looked closely and saw hair.
It was a hair up.
I looked at the file several times.
I saw hair.
This is the CD.
I saw it.
The CD that appeared in the story of the
stairs is in front of us.
The members are surprised by the
unexpected development.
I was surprised.
Why?
This way
I was surprised
No, no, no, I was surprised
This story is actually
This is actually
I was surprised
The old lady was the scariest
The old lady suddenly appears from
behind, afraid of the
What should I do?
Why do you say Chi-chan?
There is a
In the back of the house, there is a
How can you do that?
I'm scared
It's okay
Everyone has a lot of
Let's split into two
I'm okay
Really?
So, the summer vacation experience
during the shrimp
The last one is a trial
The two team members are as you can see
At first, I need courage
Matsuno
I'm not an adult
I'm really scared
I want to be with you
I'm scared
I'm okay
The first thing to do in the house is
A long hallway
There are two dolls
And run to the members alone
In her next room
Even though there was no one there a
Shen Dynamite comes down
And when they split the
fans in two, they have long hair to
block the path
And who would have expected to come to
the abandoned room
Finally, he arrives at the cave.
When he opens the door, he finds a card.
He is relieved that he has reached the
goal.
But his hand is attacked by the lost
person.
Actually, this is the big Kaiki who is
waiting alone in the dark.
He is also in fear.
Will the members of Ebi Chuu reach the
goal?
The team to go first will go first.
Ready?
Let's go.
I will be fine.
Cheer up, cheer up, cheer up.
Yurei, throw something away.
No, no, no, no, no.
There's a mermaid.
So cool.
No, really.
No.
So cool.
No, no, no.
Wait, I haven't heard this girl's name.
Throw away.
No, no, no.
Don't lick me.
Bye bye.
No, no, no.
No, no, don't do it.
It's okay.
Don't do it.
What should I do?
I don't want to.
But there's a mermaid.
No, no, no.
There's a mermaid.
Hello.
I'm a little scared.
I'm not scared.
I'm a mermaid.
Shut up!
I'm a grown-up, a child, a child
I'm a child, a child
I'm back
Where do we start?
There are so many dolls
I'm a grown-up, a child, a child
I can hear her voice
I can hear it from far away
Riko-chan
Is there anything you want to say?
Tell us something interesting
No
Dance, dance, dance
Put your hands up high
The sky is beautiful
Dance, dance, dance
The sun is shining
I'm scared
It's summer
She's going to fall
I'm scared
Ah?
Brother Getan,
What?
Oh, Mr. Haruka,
Let's go over here..
You sound like a liar.
So, let's go over.
Wait, shall we take a deep breath?
Wait a minute.
Well, my system is really fragile.
But, we are getting over here soon.
We did our best.
KAIPE.
Kristina's
I have to take this off. It's so scary.
Are you all right?
I got it! Thank goodness!
What happened?
I lost my strength
My body is out of control
It was amazing
What happened?
The doll!
The doll?
What was scary?
The doll was on the top
And the doll...
Was it scary?
It was scary
The doll was really scary
I thought I was okay
But when I entered, I was really scared
It was the first time I've been in a
doll
I see
If Rina wasn't there, I wouldn't have
been able to go in
You could have come back and left the
doll
That's the worst!
What is this?
Next, the Mayama team will try the
kimono challenge
Kashiwagi and Nakayama, who shed tears
on the stairs, are they okay?
At this goal, the lady, Nakashima, who
has a strong sense of honor, is
attacking in front of the card
Next, the Mayama team
Welcome
I'm glad you came back alive
Are you scared?
It's scary
I'm scared
I'm sorry
I'll be scared
You have to check it
Why?
It's scary
No
What?
Dad!
Next, Nakashima and grand fragrance
Second attempt
Add childish
I'm sorry.
Wait, wait, wait!
It's okay.
Rikuuu!
Why?
Wait!
Wait, you're stillslicking
haha
What? Where are you coming from?
I'm scared!
Sounds of standoff
Who's there?
Nobody's there
Wait, the camera
It's okay
I don't want to
It's like this
Open this
It's open
Open it quickly
Ready, go
What?
Who is it?
Scary
I don't know what it was
I don't know
It's okay
I'm scared of dolls
I'm scared
Wait
Scary
It's okay
I don't want to die
It's raining.
It's okay.
Water!
Water is flowing.
My hands!
It's okay.
Who is it?
It's really dark.
It's coming.
It's behind you.
It's a big one.
Okay.
Wait.
I'll open the door.
I'll open it.
It's a spider.
It's here.
I found it.
Wait.
It's a spider.
Please share with your friends who help
us!
Uh huh.
I am very sorry.
Um how when nice
I get choked but
Hao
The house is seriously
cloud
I guess that good
Ak Daddy
Ah ah ah ah
This earnestly
I heard that Zasuke was scary
I was surprised
The scream was the scariest
She was going through her back
Hina Takashi was in the way
I was scared
What was the scariest?
I didn't see
So we did the kimono test
How was it?
I'm tired
I'm in a state of
Hirota
Yes
Hirota is like a ghost
How was it?
You were the most tired
I was the worst
What was the worst?
Everyone
I shouldn't have been scared
You shouldn't have been scared
You were surprised
Let's end it like a diary
What are we going to do next?
You don't have energy
You're already tired
So
Let's have a summer vacation in Ebichu
You can hear the voice that you can
never hear in live
Sakura Ebis front line
Finally, Sakura Ebis was launched
What a world-class idol festival
Decided to appear at the Tokyo Idol
Festival
Lesson first day
The program staff is specially involved
in the field
Hello
The first lesson of Sakura Ebis
Start from the basics as an idol
But
It's a little bit difficult
It's hard
At that time
This is it!
The basic lesson is harder than I
thought.
This is the basic lesson.
This is too light and my legs are not
straight.
What did the head of Fujii see?
It's better than the first lesson.
Is that so?
Unexpectedly high evaluation.
The main event of the festival is August
1st.
The program will be close to the first
stage of the Sakura Ebis.
Next time on Ebichu Tastas.
The legendary project is again.
New corners are also appearing.
No plan walk recording.
I did that project.
It has begun.
This program was provided by the sponsor
you see.
I wrote Fujii.
I will solve with chopsticks.
I have no time to be lazy.
Thank you for your viewing.