Ebichu!
It was fun, wasn't it?
It was fun!
Hocus Slime!
Invader film.
That was really fun okay?!
What are you?
What did you criterion!?
No no no.
I amenn ready to bring the great culture
of Showa
down to people of Heisei Generation.
Boss.
Did you get it?
kern!
I got it!
Otsukaren!
Where are we?
This time we are going to do
Showa's popular language quiz!
We are going to have Seiyun answer
a quiz about Showa's popular language.
If she gets the correct answer
we will get double the prize money!
No, it's not that.
Everyone, let's get ready!
Let's get ready!
This is difficult.
Answer the meaning of this word and give
me a hint!
Ta-da!
Abekku.
Can I guess?
Do you know?
I will open the answer.
Why did you give me that answer?
Good luck, Abe-kun.
Abe-kun.
The correct answer is
this!
It's a couple.
When I went to Australia with my friend
my mom said
it's Abe-kun.
That's a couple.
Finally,
I will repeat this wonderful word.
Repeat?
Abe-kun.
Oh, Moritsu!
What is this?
Ebichu!
What is the wonderful
popular word in Showa?
Moritsu.
Next question.
What kind of pose
do you make
when you say
Osaki-ni-shitsurei-shimasu?
Everyone,
let's get ready!
Osaki-ni-shitsurei-shimasu.
What?
What's wrong?
The salaryman is doing this.
This is this.
The correct answer is
Osaki-ni-shitsurei-shimasu.
Wow!
It's a date pose
that the Showa salaryman
used to do.
The Showa drawing pose
is good.
Please try using
the chorus of a song.
I see.
But...
I think it's possible.
I'll make a sentence.
Honoji.
I'll open the answer at once.
Yasumoto-san.
Your family is really Honoji.
It's often said that the parents support
the children.
You say to Honoji.
What do you mean?
There is a road called Honoji.
I'm afraid, so please go ahead.
What are you talking about?
You are Honoji to that child, right?
Yes.
Are you a Showa person?
No.
You are Honoji to Mayama, right?
Honoji.
Oh, it's a big line.
Konnichiwa.
Next question.
Draw the next face and bend it.
I got it.
Asima-san is amazing.
I'll open the answer.
Gansu.
I think the sauce is strong.
I'm a little worried about Matsuno-san.
How was it?
I wanted to make it like Takamori-san.
Nakayama-san.
The answer is clear.
The answer is...
Everyone is a bonus.
Well done.
The bonus is...
The face is one of the men's faces that
women in the 80s said.
He has big eyes and deep chest.
He is called the face of a boy from the
West.
By the way, which one do you think is
your principal?
The principal is the salt type.
Salt butter.
Make a sentence using the following
words.
Rotor.
Open the answer.
You are all drunk.
This one.
No, no, it's not a frame like me.
I want to guess it.
Stupid.
No.
Fool.
A person without a gay.
No.
Nothing.
What is the real person?
Alien.
Tatsujin.
Normal person.
No.
What is a rotor?
Old man.
Correct.
Rotor.
Debuchuu!
First question, using the following
words,
make a sentence and give us a hint.
Hakui.
The answer is open!
I'm Hakui, so I rode my bike yesterday.
I'm bad, so...
Debuchuu, Rina and Aya are especially
Hakui.
This is Irojiro.
I'm worse than you.
Nakayama, I'm Hakui.
I'm good.
Hakui is a beautiful word in kanji.
It's a good word.
That's right.
The reward is a snack.
Congratulations.
Finally, Hakui...
Hinata!
I'm really Hakui!
It's a round of applause.
That was fast!
It's so embarrassing!
One, two, three, four...
Look at that face.
I'm sure it's just a matter of taste.
It seems that this spaceship is going to
warp.
Where will it arrive?
But I'm sure this is also necessary to
reach the first star.
Our journey has just begun.
Chiritsue Bishu Chugaku will continue to
grow with everyone.
And I want to appear in front of
everyone someday.
So everyone, until the time we meet
again,
have a good day!