Kangeta-chan shouldn't be an oni.
Ha...
Yakan and...
Idol!
Yakan and Idol
I'm sorry, I've cut the first part of
Shonen Manga quite a bit.
I'm sorry, I'm running out of time.
The second one is Ice Cream.
I love ice cream.
I've always had a crush on ice cream.
My family loves ice cream, so I always
put it in the freezer.
I learned how to swim because I thought,
why do I love ice cream so much?
When I was taking a test for swimming,
I saw a picture of SEVENTEEN ice cream
on the wall of the swimming school.
And I regrettedrament that I couldn't
swim.
I think I like ice cream so much because
it is special once a month.
Why is there a swimming school and ice
cream shop in the swimming school?
It's a set.
It's a memory of that.
I think that's where it started. I love
ice cream so much that I'm doing a
personal YouTube channel called Akihito
Honoka's Ice TV.
I'm doing it, and Denny-chan sometimes
watches it.
Really? Takagi-san?
He told me that he saw it.
I'm doing a new ice cream review.
Ice cream is really fast, so every week,
a new convenience store ice cream comes
out.
There are convenience stores that only
sell FAMIMA, SEVEN, LAWSON, and LAWSON's
UCHI CAFE.
There are new products.
There's also SHIROKUMA.
There are many different stores that
sell ice cream.
My favorite is SEVEN's SHIROKUMA.
There's a lot of condensed milk in it.
We have different tastes, so we
introduce them.
The staff agrees with you.
Do you have a favorite?
I don't think there's anyone who doesn't
like ice cream.
I've never heard of it.
I don't think there's anyone who likes
ice cream the most.
I'm sure everyone likes ice cream.
I don't know.
Akagi-san is amazing.
Akagi-san's playfulness is amazing.
Can I say that?
Akagi-san has a great playfulness even
from Garigari-kun.
I think he is a genius of packaging.
Akagi-san is the one who has the most
packaging in a convenience store.
Wait a minute. The Akagi I know is only
Garigari-kun, but that's how many
products there are.
The number of products is changing more
and more, and new ones are increasing.
Have you ever had a chocolate ice cream
with a gorilla statue?
There are a lot of chocolate chips in
vanilla ice cream, and the chocolate
chips are too big and too much.
Everyone knows that I ate it.
I want to eat it.
There are a lot of that series.
Chocoza Orizo
Yes, there was black tea and bananas.
I'm gone, but I love Akagi's ice cream
called Cho-Go-Go-Go.
I've been talking about this all the
time, and I think it'll be resold again.
You should say it.
It's called Cho-Go-Go-Go, and it's
amazing.
You bite it, and you get a super hard
chocolate,
then you get a chocolate chip, and then
another chocolate.
It's an ice cream you can enjoy in many
ways.
That's amazing.
The ice cream is delicious.
I was just listening to you.
I'm sorry, but I had a jewelry box ice
cream when I was a kid.
Wow!
Do you know what it is?
Is it similar to mine?
What kind of ice cream is it?
It's like vanilla, but it has ice
jewelry in it.
I still want to eat it.
I was able to synchronize with the
feeling of wanting to meet again someday
and accept your story.
Ice makes people's hearts move.
It moves.
It's amazing that you can think about
why it's different.
I agree.
The fans already know that side of you.
Ice TV also has a lot of things to say.
I heard a good story.
I see.
Thank you.
You should watch Ice TV in detail.
Please watch it.
Please subscribe to the channel.
We were excited to say that we could do
a full marathon.
That's a lie.
We are a group that is carrying a super
tough.
I think it was just right.
This program is...
At Fukubaya-san
Otomo-san
Aisu Daisuki Yuuki-chan-san
Amitaro-san
Kagechi-san
I'm sending you this program
Today's program is 10 times of abs