Thank you for watching
Thank you for watching!
In the middle of the summer, the banana
man is entering the Hokkaido park
As the official cameraman, he is
shooting the members' faces
Himura was very excited when he arrived
in trouble
Oh no, the switch is off
He is so painful
Tonight's final episode
Did they get the best shot?
Especially, I want to see the camera
line between the front and the exit
This is good
Who is this?
I'll take this.
No, you can't.
I don't think I can.
But I don't know.
illes
KAMIY Open your eyes wide
Oh, looking cool
You Frankl
Closing your eyes
Awesome
ня
I'd like to shoot here
Aquaria
The Инией
Unlike other white Elementary School
students.
The Korean ship
It's good
Has a dog
Thank you for watching!
Thank you very much.
Summer Memories 1minutes.
Summer 1minutes.
Take a break.
Today, Banana Man is watching us.
He said, all our fans are united.
He is coming out.
Yes, yes, yes.
Normally, something is strange.
It hurts.
I don't know. I just saw the picture.
I wanted to take a picture of the moment
the bug stopped.
I was surprised by that.
And the live performance was a hit at
the Himegaw Grand Prix.
After this, they move to a new place to
find a new structure.
I see.
This is totally different.
This is very beautiful.
Please subscribe to my channel.
And in the 5th edition of Fingers
Crossed, which appeared in the Kimi-Gao
Grand Prix, the two official cameramen
are in full focus mode.
The first photo is of the two main
characters, the main character of the
5th edition of Fingers Crossed.
The second photo is of the main
character of the 5th edition of Fingers
Crossed.
The third photo is of the main character
of the 5th edition of Fingers Crossed.
The fourth photo is of the main
character of the 5th edition of Fingers
Crossed.
The fifth photo is of the main character
of the 5th edition of Fingers Crossed.
The sixth photo is of the main character
The seventh photo is of the main
character of the 5th edition of Fingers
Crossed.
Thank you for watching!
That is a good example
They also play live under giving ad KO
L profile picture
let'sOoh
that's a goodаж
Fish
A lot
It's beautiful.
It's nice.
You can take a picture of Maya.
Please subscribe to our channel.
I'm not sure if I can see it.
I can't see it.
I can't see it at all.
It's good.
T factions Sitions
What is好吃 1 of the members bar
installation?
喜歡
Thank you for watching.
Let's go!
The live show is the climax.
The new song, Banana Man, and Volpheus
have reached their limit.
Volpheus is a Japanese-American singer.
This is a great song.
The song is very good.
This is very good.
I'm impressed.
The first day of the trip was a success!
The second day was a success!
The third day was a success!
The fourth day was a success!
Thank you for watching!
This is amazing!
Let's try to get out of the dark
I'm taking you far away from the sun
The sky is free
I can go
The waves are running
I'm going to the hot season
This is great!
The banana man has gathered for the
first time in a long time for the truck
shooting
It's so close
I can't see anything
Please take a picture of me
The first time I saw this, everyone
said,
I said, and they let me out.
The second half of the second half is
completely
I called you a lot.
I couldn't find it at all.
Seriously, this is super.
Eiga! Eiga!
I'll go this far.
But after all, I'm singing.
I'm screaming a lot.
I didn't know that.
I didn't know how to do it.
I'm getting a head start.
I'm going to go to the microwave.
Next up, in the center, is Asuka Saito's
song…
She's the princess of the land.
Justiver!
It was a good fight.
She is shooting.
She is shooting very well.
I didn't know she was shooting.
If you had told me, I would have taken
it in a hurry.
You and Asuka were shooting together.
I thought you two couldn't shoot it.
But you were able to shoot it.
Look at this.
You were discussing it in advance.
I sometimes discuss it, and sometimes I
don't.
But this time I was discussing it.
So everyone was coming.
I knew that if I did a ball shark, I
would get a perfect score.
That's the way to say it.
I was surprised. I'm glad I got this.
I'm glad I got this.
And the live show finally comes to an
end.
Thank you very much for today.
Thank you very much.
The two men continue shooting without
rest even after entering the encore
oner
Himura also goes to the stairs on the
opposite side.
It wasanish
It's coming
No one has noticed me here
Hey, it's surprising. straight
Here…
It's coming
этого
IsViewing
bounded by the texture of the
by the texture of the
서
My swinging might have been
sprechen
What?
Before IUUM gets here, I'd like to
stopper lovely SupaLY for the amazing
night view of Poland
I can't hear you.
It's going up.
Oh, good.
And everyone else is having fun, too!
Make sure to leave a vote!
I'm atop this silence now...
Water總 mao?
I'm sorry.
Oh my god.
I went to the stage.
I stood on the stage.
Oh my god.
I was a little nervous.
I stood on the stage for sure.
The two of you are standing there?
I was surprised.
I was a little blank.
There are more people than I thought who
know us.
Okura and Miyazaki.
That's amazing.
I'm glad I was able to come here.
I noticed it and I was happy.
I don't know what this means.
That's amazing.
I'm glad I was able to come to Akizaka.
I didn't know that either.
It's hot.
Everyone is grateful.
It's amazing.
I've been singing and dancing for three
hours.
And the encore is the last song.
I wanted to see more.
She's so good!
There are many similar girls in this
group right?
Yoon-gi is so championship.
Oh, that's right.
That's right.
Oh!
Wow, that's so pretty.
And so, the second day of the Hokkaido
concert is over.
Hokkaido was really good.
It was a good venue.
The atmosphere of the local concert is
different from place to place.
Yes, it's different.
Did you change the set-up a little?
Yes, it's a little different.
You did about three songs in the same
song.
It's a new song.
But the members are also hot, aren't
they?
Aren't their costumes pretty hot?
They don't get all wet, do they?
I think it depends on the situation.
How about you, Aki?
I want you to go around with your
seniors.
Many seniors talked to me behind my
back.
I was hit on the back of my back before
I went on stage.
I did it with a man who puts his soul
into it.
I was asked to do it for the first time
by my junior.
That's how it was.
I always do it before Hina and Ayane.
You ask them to do it.
Yes.
Kikuchi's looks painful.
I feel like my power is going to
explode.
I saw everyone was standing in line.
I wanted to line up with them.
You didn't line up?
I didn't line up.
So I asked Kakihaji to do it in the next
performance.
Kikuchi's is better.
Why is Sakurajino better?
He hits me hard.
Kikuchi's is better.
It's a chance to get closer to your
seniors.
You can ask your seniors to do it.
I understand. I ask my seniors to do it.
I ask my seniors to give me makeup.
You are so stupid.
Suddenly makeup tools.
It's not good if I don't have makeup
tools.
It's important.
I have to give it to you when you ask
me.
They are giving her makeup tools.
Thank you for your hard work.
I took it like a fool.
You did.
I was so happy to see the audience.
It was so close.
Everyone's face.
Did you get it?
I got it.
I was so close.
Himura-san was so close.
I got a lot of pores.
I didn't mean that.
I got excited once.
I went up the stage during the encore.
Did anyone see it?
On the Unobore beach.
The tour?
No, I went up the stage.
Oh, really?
I thought I was on the stage.
And I took a lot of pictures.
Himura-san?
I took 526 pictures.
I took almost all of them.
I took about 10 pictures of everyone.
I'm sure there's something good.
新しいありますこれだよねトラダいくす俺がね52006
邪魔いたおれのうんだから多分みんなのキメ顔と抑えてると思う
I shoot it on the train.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
You can also learn percentile
programming of Kee's competitions in
Komeenders softeness.
Yeah, we decided to do it.
More than usual.
We're from the same hometown.
It was fun.
Really?
It was great.
I'd like you to run to the Jingu.
We'll give you a little bit of a gift.
That's right.
We've prepared a number of people.
This is it.
Wow.
Some of you may know this.
This is Uninametake from Kinokon-okoku,
Hokkaido.
This is very delicious when eaten with
rice.
Yay.
I think it's sold at the airport in
Hokkaido.
We eat rice together during the live
broadcast.
I eat rice because I want to eat it.
There is one for each person.
Please, everyone.
Thank you for the best movie so far.
And, sorry, everyone.
There are many Balsharks.
If it's Balshark, it's Kaizo.
It's a great era.
Do you know Zucchin?
No, Zucchin.
Zucchin?
No, it's not Zucchin.
I thought it was Zucchin, so I shot it
and confirmed it later.
You shot it once?
I was also shown something, but it was
Zucchin.
It was definitely Zucchin.
I did this.
That's right.
There's a lot of that.
It's Zucchin.
I did it like a fool.
I made a mistake.
I also shoot.
I'm going to shoot a lot of Valshack, so
I'm going to shoot this much with
Kaname.
I'm going to shoot a lot of Valshack.
I'm not sure if I can do it.
But you did a good job for two days.
Good luck for the rest of the day.
Thank you for your hard work.
U... U...
Uruku Kansha Ego! Uruku Kansha!
Oshin-shi!
Yay!
Uruku Kansha! Yay!
The one that has never been there before
will disappear first.
We ran around and took pictures.
It was fun.
I think everyone was there.
At the end, HIMURA said that he had 526
pictures and I had 5215 pictures.
But when I looked at it again later,
HIMURA also took 1897 pictures.
I took it too.
We took more than 7000 pictures.
Did you think you were good at this
place?
Yes.
Oh, here it is.
Balshark.
Oh, that one.
I was asked to take a very beautiful
picture.
You got that one, right?
I thought I would get it taken.
My girl's room, 01, show me a little.
Look at the beauty.
The beauty is already.
Oh, that's right.
If that's the case, I didn't show up
earlier, but my summer free and easy
number 16.
Oh, this is good.
Yes, like this.
Like a toy box.
I think...
I think Tamura, the 8th member of
Rockdaze, is really cute.
Why are you so angry?
No, no, no.
This is cute.
I think this is cute.
Thank you very much.
This is cute.
I really like the number 04 of G-NOO's
Kanata.
This is the number of the customer.
This is a face that is not a face.
This is good.
I want this.
I will check this for 30 yen.
This is good.
What happened?
Can I recommend one?
This is the number of the customer.
8.
You remember it well.
How do you know that?
I think it's Maya's cool moment.
This?
I said it with my mouth.
You know it.
Maya is good.
And the best shot chosen by Banana Man
after a long time.
Both are good.
I can't get out of the key in the future
live.
I'll give you this.
Thank you.
I'll put it on my mouth.
That's good.
It must be on TV duda puchoma and
NON TOKYO STUDIO
The real 3D mask of Kubo who won the
Kimegawa Grand Prix is completed
So tonight, they will do the mask
removal ceremony
Please take the red mask
Please open
The real 3D mask of Kubo who won the
Kimegawa Grand Prix is completed
It's more like a square than I thought.
This is a spider.
Is this me? really?
Amazing.
This is a very good picture.
This is a spider.
Is this me?
Can you guess this?
This is a spider.
This is similar to Mei.
How about your picture?
I can't help but laugh.
I'm scared.
He suddenly started talking.
I feel like I'm in a department.
I'm a little scared of the daily life.
Hide this side too.
And it's time to make a decision.
I'm a little embarrassed.
Everyone wants it, right?
Under Live's delivery ticket is on sale.
Next week is Bakugai's Okatsu.
I'll take this.
Thank you for watching.
Please support me!
Beep beep beep beep
Please subscribe to my channel!