Hello, everyone!
We just had our birthday party at Nogi
Shrine.
We'd like to talk to you about a year
ahead, and talk a little about
celebrating a Christmas holiday.
Who is it?
I want to introduce her.
She is a senior.
Don't say that.
Ta-da!
It's so nice.
I like the combination of pink and
yellow.
It's like a night cherry blossom.
Night cherry blossom?
There is a night cherry blossom.
Why did you choose this?
To be honest,
I didn't know what to do.
When I was thinking about what to do,
I consulted with my colleagues.
Among them,
I thought the combination of gold and
black was good.
It's blue.
I thought it would be a little bit like
the sea.
So, I chose this.
It's so shiny when you look at it
closely.
This is so cool.
And the hair accessories are also in
good color.
It's like this.
Ta-da!
It's YAKUBO.
I chose the representative.
Red.
I think everyone will choose pink.
When I consulted with my colleagues,
I said pink or light blue.
That's right.
I said that, but it changed a lot.
My mother said that a tight-fitting
dress would be good.
So, I chose red.
It's cute.
The hair accessories and the obi look
like YAKUBO.
It's really good.
I thought it was cute.
It's yellow.
It's my favorite color.
I'll wear it all over my body.
It's cute.
YUNA.
Yes.
Why did you choose red?
I really wanted to wear red.
I asked her to wear red.
So, I chose red.
You chose red among them.
Yes.
It's gorgeous.
It's good.
It's cool.
It's the same red, but I chose it to
differentiate it.
That's right.
I chose it to look cool.
The obi is black.
It's good to be tight.
I chose white and black.
And the shoes are also black.
I chose black shoes.
It's cool.
It's gorgeous.
It's mature.
The obi is really cute.
It's a butterfly.
Look at this.
The manager called it a darts.
White and black.
It looks good on you.
This is also white.
It's really cute.
I chose green.
It's green.
It's cute.
It's really good.
I really like this color.
I wanted to wear a traditional kimono.
I'm happy to wear this kimono.
It's cute.
The orange accent is also cute.
It's blue.
I chose a siren color.
The siren color is originally green and
white.
So I chose green.
And the back is also white.
It's cute.
The face is clear.
So I like dark colors.
I understand.
I'm glad.
It's cute.
I'll look back.
The hairstyle is also cute.
It's a little side hairstyle.
The point is to put this hair on.
Really?
It's a good way to look good.
It's cute.
I'll look back.
I chose red.
It's cute.
It's a color that goes well with both of
you.
It's like a gradation.
I saw the asuka's sleeve at the Nogi
Shrine.
I found the red of the royal road cute.
I didn't want to dress up that much, but
I wanted to wear red, so I chose red.
Cute.
The flowers are the main point.
I think it's cute.
I tried to be a virgin.
You are a virgin.
Thank you.
What is the point of your hair style?
I'm wearing a short hair.
I wanted to raise my hair.
But I asked the makeup artist if I could
raise my hair.
She raised my hair.
It's beautiful.
It's very beautiful.
This is a craftsmanship.
I tried to make a simple and elegant
furisode.
I don't know how to draw a girl.
You draw it small.
I drew it small.
This year's...
I can't tell how excited you are.
When we were doing the interview at Nogi
Shrine,
you seemed to be nervous.
I was nervous.
Let's take it easy.
I drew my year's goal.
I like it.
You like it?
I drew a lot of hearts.
I did a lot of things I like as a job
last year.
I did a lot of things I like as a job.
I will appeal to you more and more this
year.
I will do a lot of work.
I want to do my best to let people know
about Nogizaka.
I will do my best to make my favorite
members, staff and fans happy.
You are a great idol.
Thank you.
My goal is this!
Cute!
I drew this because I like rabbits.
We have the same image.
I often post a picture of a rabbit on my
blog, Instagram, and other social media.
I think it's good to have a picture of a
rabbit.
I want to decorate it.
It's so cute. I think it's a good idea.
I'll post a picture of a rabbit on my
blog.
I'll do my best on the 2nd.
Please subscribe to my channel.
The next day
Here is my goal.
I chose to move on.
Well...
Oh, I got a message.
What?
I got a message.
I'm sorry.
I made it a sum.
I've been a little bit since last year,
but I felt like I've been stuck for a
year.
I want to challenge a new genre of work
this year.
I want to move forward as a group and as
an individual.
That's great.
This is my goal for this year.
That's great!
The brush I used was so thick that I was
out of energy.
It's so sharp.
I'm going to fly. This year is the year
of the rabbit, so the characters are a
little different.
I drew it with the feeling of
fluttering.
It says cute Teresa.
It's too wide.
It's gone.
It's delicious.
The kanji I chose as my goal is this.
Tsunagu.
You are good.
Are you really doing this?
I'm not doing it.
I'm impressed that you can write so many
characters.
The reason I chose this kanji is that
I've been working hard for a year since
I joined Nogizaka46.
There were seniors who graduated after
spending a year last year, and we were
not going to work hard as a new member
of Nogizaka46, but as a member, we chose
the kanji Tsunagu with the feeling that
we would connect Nogizaka46.
I will continue to connect.
The kanji I chose is Hiragana.
I'm not particular about it.
But I heard that Hiragana was good.
My father thought my name was Hiragana
until recently.
Is that so?
I've been doing it for 20 years.
Both are cute.
I will use this opportunity to choose a
woman who will remain alone.
I didn't think I would do this at the
beginning of my work.
This is a joke.
Right or left?
I'm scared.
I'm still scared.
I'm going to start.
I'm really scared.
I'm scared.
I don't want to do this.
I want to finish this quickly.
I told you I don't have luck.
I told you.
I'm lucky.
Isn't it harder to get close to the
second floor?
I'll push it.
What are you trying to do?
I'm trying to endure.
It hurts.
It's like a static electricity.
I should have done it with my right
hand.
You're too long.
I did it.
Thank you for watching.
It's been 3 years!
3 years!
We're so lucky!
It's been 3 years!
You're so lucky!
Thank you!
We did it!
It's a good start!
This is our first time.
I'm not sure if this is really a good
start.
But there are so many good things.
There are.
I hope this year will be a good year.
Please subscribe and like us!