Thank you for watching!
Thank you for waiting.
Did you wait?
Was it okay?
I'm glad.
Then, let's go.
Let's go.
I'm hot.
I've never done a river crossing before.
What should I do?
What's this?
Wait, I can wear a kimono here.
I'm so excited.
Let's go here.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Hello.
Welcome.
Thank you.
Oh my god.
Can I?
It's so beautiful.
What should I do?
It's a gorgeous dress.
I think it suits you very well.
It suits me?
Yay!
It might be good.
It's gorgeous and beautiful.
It's amazing.
Oh, no. From a strange place.
I'm going to put it out here.
How is it? I think it's pretty good.
By the way, it's beautiful, so please
enjoy it with your boyfriend.
Thank you. He's my boyfriend.
Ta-da!
What do you think?
Isn't it nice?
I'm saying this myself.
I got a bag ready for me.
I think it's pretty good.
What do you think?
Let's go out with this.
It's a little nice weather.
I'm glad it didn't rain.
Hey, let's get on the train.
Let's get on the train.
Please subscribe to our channel.
I'm riding for the first time.
Is it your first time?
Yes, it is.
Let's ride together.
Are you OK?
Yes, I'm OK.
It's great.
Please subscribe to our channel.
It's shaking.
It's fast!
It's a car.
The wind is nice.
It feels good to ride.
Wow!
It's nice to ride a car.
This is my ideal date.
It was my dream to ride a human-powered
car in such a beautiful place.
Oh, my god! Sweet potatoes!
I'll go for a walk after this.
We're here.
Watch your step.
Thank you.
I'm done.
That was quick.
Thank you.
Thank you for today.
It was fun.
It was a good trip.
What should I eat?
I'm so into food.
I'm curious about the sweet potato
sticks.
It looks warm.
Sweet potato sticks look delicious.
I'll buy it.
One sweet potato stick, please.
Wow, thank you.
Let's eat.
It's very warm.
It's so good.
It's so warm.
I think my body is getting warm now.
The salt outside is delicious.
The inside is really sweet potato, but
the outside is also salty and delicious.
Let's eat.
This is really delicious.
I've been walking around and I've been
thinking...
I've been told I'm cute.
I heard I'm cute when I was on the
train.
I was praised.
I'm getting carried away.
It looks delicious.
It looks delicious. It's golden.
I want to eat this.
I'm tempted.
I'll eat this.
This looks delicious.
I'll be hungry if I walk for 3 minutes.
I'll have this golden dumpling.
Thank you.
This is big.
This is normal size.
I'll eat this.
This smells good.
Look at this.
I'll eat this.
Oh my god!
Did it get on my mouth?
I think it got on my mouth.
This soy sauce is so good.
The rice cake is warm.
It's very deep. It's different from the
usual soy sauce.
There are a lot of delicious looking
things. Let's take a look.
This looks delicious, doesn't it?
What do you call this? Mini?
Is this a kawayaki?
I'm getting a little full, but I thought
it would be okay, but it looks
delicious, so I'm hungry again.
Thank you.
Thank you for watching.
It smells so good.
I'll eat it.
I really like strong taste, so I'm glad
that they put this much sauce.
Wow, let's eat.
I'm afraid I'll spill the kimono.
Oh, no.
I'll try it.
Delicious.
It's so easy to eat.
It's delicious.
I came here with a low plan,
but it's a good place to eat a lot and
ride a human train.
There's a Gacha-Gacha.
I like this place.
I'm curious.
Here it is.
Wow.
There is ice cream.
There is something here.
Mango juice or lemonade?
Which one?
What do you want?
I'll have mango juice.
I've decided.
Do you want the same?
I'll have mango juice.
I'll have two mango juices.
I'll put it here.
This is good.
I'll have it.
It's delicious.
It's very rich.
It's pretty smooth.
It's smooth.
What? Bear?
Bear shrine?
Bear?
Thank you for watching!
It's written here.
2 bows, 2 bows, 1 bow, 1 bow.
And pray.
Thank you.
I'm going to get a present.
OK, let's go.
What did you wish for?
Me? I...
It's a secret.
I wished for happiness.
But I won't tell you the details.
Guess what it is.
I'll go with fortune.
I wanted to do fortune telling.
There are a lot of fortune telling.
I miss it.
I have a love fortune.
Do you have a love fortune?
I don't have one.
Go!
I'll take a picture from here.
Bye.
Mid-range.
It's mid-range.
The constellation. The Leo is ideal.
The Gemini. The Pisces is also good.
Meeting. You can enjoy shopping.
The town is good.
Oh, isn't it now?
It's good.
Studying.
Is this easy to understand?
You can make an effort.
Don't worry.
It says that a kind person will succeed.
A kind person.
Please subscribe to this channel.
let's start
done
Please.
Time really flew by.
Which way do I go home?
This way?
I see.
I'm going this way, so I'm leaving.
Time really flies.
Well, see you later.
I ate too much today.
I didn't eat much. Are you okay?
Are you okay?
I'm glad. I'm full.
See you later. Thank you.