Let's have fun at Amikiri!
This week's Ebichu Tastas is a new
project
Everyone is on a winter tour
In other words, winter tour
In the middle of winter, get on the bus
and set off for the tour
I'll do my best until here
In addition, the exciting Ebichu Derby
Start the race of the pig
Big Thunder is fast
Big Thunder
In addition
Sakura Ebis fight!
Thank you for watching!
The light is up to 4
High school, high school, high school,
high school, high school
Never ending school
We will add various things to private
Ebisu Middle School
Ebisu Desserts
The first program is...
This program is provided by the sponsor
Desserts are so much fun
Now, now, now
It's good
Tontation
Ebichu Toast has started!
My voice is echoing
This time, I will be my host
I will do my best
Today, we are starting from Ebisu's
hometown, Ebisu
Really
What are we going to do in Ebisu today?
Today's theme is Ebisu plus plus
I'm worried
Ebisu plus plus
Today's theme is Ebisu plus plus winter
speed, and it is winter speed
But it's cold in winter
Really
Every year, summer family speed family
garden is held
It is a special project that wants to
make the speed of the speed in winter a
standard
Ebichu summer customary event, the
outdoor one-man concert family garden
that is held on the theme of speed
In addition to the family garden, Ebichu
plus plus will hold a hot speed winter
garden in the cold season
I called a tour guide for speed
Thank you for your cooperation
Thank you for coming to our tour
Nagareboshi tour Nagareboshi, Takiyu and
Chuu
Chuu and Sayonara
Spring is coming
Hello
Please call me quickly
It's long
I was like this
Today, my mom said nice to you
Don't say that
Why did you say that?
I said nice to you
You said nice to me and now you say Chuu
and Sayonara
We are not friends
We have never met
We don't have
We have prepared various programs for
you to enjoy
Please enjoy the winter
By the way, one person is missing
Where is the
I have another job so I will join later
Let's go
It's cold
I don't want to wait
There is no one
Wait
It's too hot
I'm going to go
Since you are here
We will meet later
Can I go to pick up the cashier?
I want to go too
If you go straight, it's the station
The manager should go to pick you up
I'm busy with management
Please take me
Thank you for your viewing
We will be your guides
Please take care of us
Please leave it to us if you are going
on a day trip
It's not fun to be on a day trip for one
night
But if you are going on a day trip,
please leave it to us
Please leave it to us
Have you ever been on a trip?
No
Do you have any memories of a trip?
Yes
Yasumoto
Let me ask you
When we went to the school for a school
trip, we were told that we are idols
Ayaka told us that we should not hide
our identity
We were exposed to the world
We were very careful
I was also very worried about that
Thank you
I was so worried
It was evening and I was about to go
home
But nobody noticed
I put on a mask
I didn't notice
I was surprised
Do you have any other memories of a
trip?
No
Really?
I don't want to talk about it
I feel like I'm going to get drunk
I'm worried about getting drunk
But I have a story
It's going to be very long
Then it's okay
Let me talk
I was walking in the mountains and I
heard an Ammonite was happening in my
friend's house
I started to touch it and it moved and I
thought what was it?
I grabbed a bug and threw it away
Then it hit a girl in a different class
It was terrible
It was like a reverse manga
It was a good idea
Let's go to the place where we can enjoy
the long trip
It's time to announce the destination
I hope you enjoy the trip
By the way, I'd like to announce the
destination of today
It's Mother Forest!
Have you been to Mother Forest?
Yes!
There are many!
Wait a minute!
There are no Nakaayama and Hirota?
Oh, I see.
When did you all go?
We went with our family.
We went to school.
You went to school.
There are many places.
Nakaayama and Hirota?
No!
You're the first mother, right?
Yes!
First mother.
Do you all have memories of Mother
Forest?
We went to the horse market.
It was dangerous.
The horse was very small.
It was when I was about 5 years old.
When my father gave me a horse,
I ate the food very well.
I thought it was okay.
When I got in the horse, I ate it hard.
It was okay.
You can enjoy anything today.
I enjoy the app.
But I'm not good at animals.
You're not good at it?
I'm not good at it.
I'm not good at animals.
I'm bitten by all the big and small
animals.
Really?
Is it easy to bite?
You can't eat this.
No!
I hate it!
While they were running,
the bus that took the 5th step was
arrived at Mother Forest.
Futsu City, Chiba Prefecture.
A tourist ranch located near the top of
the Kano Mountain.
There are various facilities for animals
in the park.
We arrived.
It's cold.
I can smell the bugs.
Bugs.
Everyone.
Mom.
Good morning.
Bugs.
Did you bring the bugs?
I did my job.
I'm Katsuo Isaru, the manager.
The manager is the hot one.
Thank you very much.
We came all the way here.
Please come to the park.
After meeting Kashiwagi, they went to
the park.
Then, Kashiwagi told her mother's story.
I came here since I was in the 4th
grade.
When I was in the 4th grade,
I went to the upper floor.
There was a big ball in the pool.
There was a ball that could be played in
the ball.
I know that.
It was here.
After the Pasta,
they arrived at the first attraction to
enjoy the park.
The first program is
the
small pig race.
We will have a match with the small pig.
I will explain the rules.
This is a one-man race.
The losing team will have a punishment
game.
If you lose, you will be scared.
The first program of the winter garden
is the small pig race.
The pair will be divided into teams and
compete for the first place.
The little pigs don't go to the goal
easily.
The team members will pat their butts
and lead them to the goal.
The little pigs have a certain
characteristic.
Each of them has a characteristic like
this.
First, the number one, Tonkotsu Taro.
The previous race was a bit of a hint.
The second, Mother Ton Ton.
I love playing with sand.
The third, Pig Thunder.
The previous race was the first place.
The fourth, Great Ton Sok.
When I say, this is it, I say, Great Ton
Sok.
I don't know what you mean.
What does it mean to say Great Ton Sok?
I haven't made much progress so I'll
just write it like that.
I want you to choose the pig.
I want you to choose the pig so that it
doesn't overlap.
This is a good hint.
Which one do you want to go?
When I was told that I was first place
in the previous race, I was tired.
I see.
That's good.
I've decided.
You've decided?
Let's go.
One of the team members will go first.
Ready, go.
It's a pair of
You're a pair of
The pair of
I wonder if I can go on a trip like a
crane while playing with sand together
crane while playing with sand
I wonder if I can go on a trip like a
I see
I thought about it
Then, Yasumoto Hoshina pair chose
Great tonsoku
Why is this?
The name is really cool
Say something good
Great tonsoku is not a name, it's a big
sand
It's not great tonsoku
It's cool
Great tonsoku is not a name
I like the catch copy
I just explained it
I'm curious about this
I want to see it
Show us when you say great tonsoku
Next, Hiroto Nakayama pair chose
Tonkotsu taro
It was a close match
It was close but
Maybe they are standing now
They are using their power
They might use Great's Tonsoku
Yes
Everyone uses Great's Tonsoku
If so, you will use Great's Tonsoku
Stop it
Everyone uses Great's Tonsoku
Finally, Mayama and Kashiaki pair chose
Pig Thunder
My teacher is pushing me
I see
This kid is likely to be the best in the
race
And this kid is the first one I played
in kindergarten
Really?
Why are you a pig?
No, I'm not
I see
You have the same name
I won the race with this kid
Really?
I see
Wait
You mean the name of the race is not
Great's Tonsoku
That's right
Great's Tonsoku is here
So I will use Great's Tonsoku
Let's do it again
Kashiaki, what's up?
I'm asking you what's the name of the
race
Please be quiet
Thank you for watching
, I can play well
The first race of the year, the opening
of Ebichu Tastastarby
Are you ready?
The goal is to go around and control the
lid
Are you ready?
Let's go
Ready, start
It's a start
The first race is over
She's fast
Is she fast?
Number 3
She's fast
Is she fast?
Number 3
It's over
I'm so sorry
Wait a minute
These three are not
Not at all
Oh no, Matsumoto is playing with the
smartphone
They are playing
They are playing a game
Which one is the Tonkotsu Taro?
Tonkotsu Taro
The blue one?
They are looking for food
Kobayashi-san
Kobayashi-san, say more
Masao Ton Ton
What is Masao Ton Ton?
It's the second one
It's good
Kobayashi-san, say Ton Ton
Kobayashi-san
Hoshii Ton Ton
Goal
Masao Ton Ton
What's left?
The rest is
The battle between Ton Taro and Great
Ton Ton
Great Ton Ton
She is getting hit
She is coming
She is going backwards
Masao Ton Ton
She is getting hit
Great Ton Ton
It's good
From behind
The last battle is a good battle
What was that dead heat?
It was amazing
It was close
And the last battle was
Tonkotsu Taro
It was Tonkotsu Taro
It was close
Thank you for watching!
Now, let's announce the results!
The winner is...
...Kashiwagi Mayama!
It was a close call!
I'm sure you were right about the
veteran's name.
information about the Masanaboku Castle.
I'm sure the winner was...
...Anagachi.
That was pretty accurate.
The one who was the last one to win was
the last one.
I'm sure you were right about the
information about the results.
And Mother Ton-ton was really good at
playing with sand.
And Great Ton-sok was also good at
I didn't really get that.
The winner will receive a medal!
This is really something you can get at
the Masanaboku Castle.
Congratulations!
And the last one is Hirota and Nakayama
pair
It was close though
I was trying to find something even
though I didn't find anything
You were angry, weren't you?
I was trying to find something
But it was a good fight
I couldn't take my eyes off of the sign
So Hirota and Nakayama pair decided to
do a punishment game
Next is...
Sakurai Bees
This time, we will show you the Sakurai
Bees' one-man live
Sakurai Bees' first live
There are many people at the venue to
see the first one-man live
The members just before the live show
I can't drink, I don't have the skill to
drink
I cried a lot yesterday, the day before
yesterday
To make the tension a little less, they
check the lyrics
The live show is about to start
Mizuha, Ayame, Rizu, Risa and Sara
Sakura B B's FIGHT!
Good!
After a waiting time of 5 people, here's
their
Finally, the stage leaders, 5 members,
dominate the stage
snap!
Let's open our pockets
SAKURAI umi is all O international
SAKURAI RIZU
Secretary, Secretary
Let's go! All right!
Let's do this!
Everybody, let's go!
Thank you for watching!
And during the live, a sudden big
announcement
We want to introduce our new friends!
I'm 9 years old, Moa Serizawa. Nice to
meet you.
New member of the 4th grade, Serizawa
Moa joined.
5 members have run through the first
live performance of Moridake, such as
the announcement of new members.
And the live performance is also the
ending.
I would like to ask you to sing, dance,
and perform in front of everyone.
Good luck!
We've been given a lot of things.
Everyone is giving us.
Do your best!
Do your best, I'm Rizuha!
We want to show you the good points of
each individual.
Please continue to support Sakura Ebi-
Niz.
Thank you for coming to the first one-
man live.
Thank you very much!
Thank you for your hard work.
Bye bye.
I want to say that we succeeded in our
performance, but I think we did well for
the first time in the excitement of the
audience.
The latest information is that Sakura
Ebis will hold a new member audition.
Next episode of Ebichu Tastas will be
the second episode of the winter
special.
Ebichu will try bungee jumping.
Then Nakayama will cry.
Thank you for your hard work.
This program was provided by the sponsor
you see.
My heart is beating.
I'm going to squat.
5,4,3,2,1
Thank you for your hard work.