Mini Corner Festival
Tonight is a new project, Mini Corner
Festival
That legendary corner has come back
This is the beginning of the small
corner
Everyone, think about it
Also, shrimp-chutas laughing
Your forehead is good
Shrimp-chutas laughing
Shrimp-chutas walking
Thank you for the meal
Gundam
Three highlights
Shrimp-chutas start
3D model
You should add the later half of
the egg white into the white
Goacha
at no
Ebichu Tattotsu
Delicious
This program is provided by the sponsor
It has started! Ebichu Tattotsu!
The first song is YASUMO KAYAKA
Today's song is YASUMO KAYAKA
You went for the second round?
Yes
You did it
We are the lucky ones
I'm Chuya
Be careful, Chuya, you're about to get
on the seat
Everyone, wait
Today is not the time to test your
courage
It's important to be strong
Please hold your breath
This room is...
This is the room where we, the legendary
Kobayashi Yasumoto, and I, the old men,
were very active
Thank you for watching!
Yes
You were so energetic for 3 years
I was more energetic than usual
You were more energetic than usual
But it was fun
I want everyone to feel that feeling
So today
We are going to have a mini corner
festival
What is that? Mini corner festival?
We are going to have a variety show with
different contents
We are going to make a mini corner
This time, 3 teams will be divided into
3 mini corners
What is the content?
I have thought about the team
I am confident
I am looking forward to it
I will announce the winner
The first corner is...
I am Yasumoto and Kobayashi's
G-Dragon 2
You are here
You were waiting for this
I am getting the responsibility
Yasumoto and Kobayashi's G-Dragon
They will decide the winner
I am getting the responsibility
Matsu's Kashiwagi
Takeuei's
Matsu's Kashiwagi walk
What is that?
This is a walk to eat
They are eating
They will walk slowly
Have you ever done this kind of walk?
We often do it
We often do it in Enoshima and Kamakura
We have never done it
We have been to Enoshima and Kamakura
We have eaten Nure-Okaki
We have eaten it
I can't stop
Matsu's and Kashiwagi's walk
Will they make a plan?
The last one
Maaya is from Hirota, Hoshina, Nakayama,
and Chuu
The shrimp is big
Why are we the only ones who are being
pushed up?
Why is it big?
Ayai got the Zabuton
I didn't pick up the good ones
Nakayama-san and other people have a
miracle
I'm looking forward to it
The rest is up to you
Why?
Will these 5 members get the Zabuton?
We'll split into 3 teams and each of us
will do a corner
If it's not interesting, we'll cut it
all
Everyone, let's do our best
If it's not interesting, we'll cut it
all
The pressure is on, so the teams split
up and the shoot begins
First, we'll start with the mini corner
of the shrimp and the walk
It's started
Matsu's Kashiwagi Walk
Today, we're going to walk around the
Togoshi Ginza shopping street
We're going to eat
By the way, we haven't decided anything
this time
You can walk around as you like
It's up to you
Do you want to go in there?
No
We can't imagine what's going to happen
They walk around the Togoshi Ginza
shopping street freely
Where will they go?
What do you want to do first?
I want to eat
You're addicted
But you can walk around and there are
other things besides food
I want to be released from the category
Let's eat first
We're hungry
Wait
Wait, there's a fried chicken!
I want to eat fried chicken!
You want to eat it?
Yes, I want to eat it!
Is it okay?
Please wait a moment
Please calm down, please wait a moment
It's a bit early
Oh my, they don't run away from fried
chicken
It looks delicious
In the central area of Togoshi Ginza
shopping street
There is a store of fried chicken and
ingredients
Tori & Deli
Togoshi Ginza
They are going to enter the store
It looks delicious and smells good
It's a fried chicken shop
There are many fried chicken
I think so
Let's enter the store
Let's go
Hello
Excuse me
Thank you
Do you have any recommended food in the
store?
Yes, in the area
The most popular is the fried chicken
with the young radish
Then, please have it
Thank you
There is also asparagus cheese
Oh, that's right
It's pork roast
Wow
Excuse me
I'd like to have pork asparagus cheese,
please
Oh, they order fried chicken before
tasting it
The first fried chicken has arrived
Fried chicken
It's a live up
Then, please tell us your recipe
I told you that it's a recipe
That's a recipe
Really?
Then, I'll have it
Matsuno-san, please
He's laughing
It's hot
It's cooked
It's like a meat juice
It's melted
Delicious
It's hot and crispy
The meat inside is juicy and delicious
It's delicious
It's surprisingly delicious
Next, Kashiwagi-san
I'm scared
Don't say that you can't wear it
Wait, I'll have it
It's hot
Thank you for watching
Delicious
How is it?
The taste is soaked
It's soaked inside
This is delicious
It's coming
Amazing
Mango salsa sauce
It's a little funny
When I heard about pork belly
I was like
I was like, yay
You like it?
I love pork belly
I'm looking forward to it
How is it?
I can smell cheese
I like it
I'll try
How is the taste?
It's delicious
This is delicious
Is it delicious?
It's soft
But asparagus
Cheese and meat
It's wrapped
Cheese is melted
That's how much cheese is melted
Inside
How is the report?
It was perfect
That's good
Do you know these two?
Well
Yes
You don't know
You should do that
Gundam?
Thank you for the meal
Gundam
She laughed
She's familiar with this
You've never seen it?
The next person
who enjoys fried chicken
is
We can go
Where should we go?
It's the first one
It's so crowded
What is this shop?
I'm curious
I used to make plastic models when I was
in elementary school
Plastic models?
It's a specialty shop
It's amazing
Kashiwagi
Don't look so boring
It's like this
I'm curious
Squid?
No?
They go to the place they want to go
It's like that
Matsuno
He found something
What happened?
What should we do next?
We can only see her eating
while walking
Really?
Yes
So we can hear her talking?
Yes, we can hear her talking
Wait a minute
I want to eat
Where is it?
You just said you can only see her
eating
That's right
Wait a minute
You two
The camera is not following you
Oh no
Oden croquette
What should we do?
I want to eat menchi too
Oh my, are they eating again?
This one too
Fukashi-jyagai
How about eating?
Let them eat
They are eating again
The two who are so eager to eat are
the one who treats the ingredients with
oden
Goto Kamaboko
I want to eat
I'll have oden croquette
I want to eat kashiwagi
I want to eat
Matsuno-san is buying oden croquette
I'll put salt
Please
Salt is good
I did it
It's a kashiwagi
Fukashi-imo is eating kashiwagi
How does it taste?
How is it?
It's good
It's good?
Potato is the best
Potato is the best?
I'll have oden croquette
There is something crushed
It's good
It tastes like radish
It tastes like kelp soup
It's good
It's a new feeling
Kashiwagi is eating potatoes
Simple is the best
Right?
Matsuno is eating kashiwagi
Meanwhile
The team of Gigi-taidan is still
preparing
Please enjoy the big cut by this member
Thank you for waiting. It's the shrimp-
chewing corner.
The next player is Chuu E.
Please say hello to the viewers.
I'm 17 years old. I will do my best to
be a professional middle school student.
I will not overdo it. I'm Mayama.
Please say hello to the viewers.
My hobby is to go to the school by
myself.
I put my phone on and take pictures with
the scenery.
Please say hello to the viewers.
I feel that eating alone is a very happy
time.
Where will you go next?
I don't know.
I'm Hoshina. Please say hello to the
viewers.
I want to speak a lot of Japanese. I'm
Nakayama.
Who will carry the futon?
I will carry the futon with happiness.
I'm Hiratsuka.
Please say hello to the viewers.
I'm Hiratsuka. Please say hello to the
viewers.
Please say hello to the viewers.
Ta-da!
I want you to use two letters of shrimp
and write a sentence to PR Ebi-Chu!
The first question is,
Write a sentence of Ayu-E and PR Ebi-
Chu!
Please start with the person who wrote
the sentence.
Okay!
Oh, Nakayama-san is fast.
Okay, Nakayama!
What?
What are you looking at on a Thursday
night?
I'm surprised! I'm looking at Ebi-Chu-
Tastas!
I see.
You're using the picture in a surprising
way.
This is a new impression.
Hiratsuka-kun, please write a sentence
of Zabuto Ichibayu Nakayama!
Oh!
Okay, Mayama!
Okay!
A, Exotic.
B, Beautiful.
Wow!
How about this?
Zabuto?
Five.
Zabuto, you're good!
You have a good way of writing.
Okay, next is Hoshina!
Chuu-ei-san was chosen.
You're surprised, aren't you?
Ebi-Chu-Tastas' MC!
Okay, Hiratsuka-kun, seven Zabuto!
Wow!
Okay, okay, okay!
Okay, Nakayama!
What? Please!
Beauty Chuu-ei-san!
Nakayama-san!
You're using the picture as a picture,
aren't you?
The next topic is the classic riddle.
Do you know the riddle?
Yes!
For example,
Ebi-Chu-No-Ninki-Takakema...
Wait a minute.
Hoshina-san, what's wrong?
Nakayama is also...
I see.
As expected of the Yutori generation.
Hiratsuka-kun!
Take one picture from everyone.
Okay, then, from the person who floated,
please write the address.
Okay, Hiroto!
I drew the Nakayama record for the first
live performance.
I'll melt the bangs of Hiro and Aika.
What's your heart?
Both are hard!
Hiroto's bangs are hard.
I'm freezing it with a spray.
Thank you for the information you first
learned!
Hiratsuka-kun, please take one picture!
It's hard.
Yes!
I'll stand up.
Ebi-Chu-No-Ninki-Takakema!
I'll solve it with the one I have now.
What about the one you have now?
Both of them are flying.
That's a more than I imagined.
I was surprised.
Let's draw a picture.
Let's give him one.
Is this a riddle?
Please draw.
I'll draw with Mr. Fuji.
I'll solve it with chopsticks.
What about the one you have now?
Both of them are number one in Japan.
I'll give you one if you eat it.
I'll give you one in Japan.
That's great.
Nakayama, please.
I'll draw with gentle water.
I'll solve it with gentle tissue.
What about the one you have now?
Both of them are important.
I'll give you one with gentle water.
I'll give you one with gentle tissue.
It's the opposite of the word.
It's gentle.
Water?
I think it's easy to convey.
What is this?
I don't know.
Hiratsuka, please take one.
This is a normal water and tissue.
Finally, they will try to meet the lord.
Hiratsuka, bring me something.
Yes.
I got it.
Is this a temple?
You are the lord of the temple.
I will be your servant.
The lord is angry because there is a
problem in the temple.
Please answer what I said.
Ayama.
Yes.
Stop it.
What is it?
Takihei is taking pictures again.
This is great.
Give me one.
Are you taking a walk?
Yes.
Hoshina.
Listen.
What is it?
You don't say much, but you drink
alcohol.
It's a normal way to meet the lord.
I can see it.
It's great.
Yes.
Give me one.
Is it okay?
What are you doing?
Ikebana.
Give me one.
Yes.
She ignores the topic, but she seems to
be having fun.
Please follow her for a while.
Mayama.
Chobihige.
Chobihige is too big.
Mayama, take one.
Nakayama.
This is white.
Give me a new camera.
Hoshina.
Hello.
Give me a new camera.
Nakayama.
Your cat is great.
Iratukaku, take one.
She is not a fool.
She uses a wig as a wig.
Hoshina.
She used the most of the camera.
Hoshina, give me one.
What is in your left hand?
A stylish bag.
Nakayama, Hirota, take one from Mayama.
Give it to Hoshina.
Nakayama.
Iratukaku, give Mayama, Hirota, Hoshina
to Nakayama.
Hoshina.
She suddenly became a national student.
The mini corner that will add shrimp
is...
Hoshina Mirei, HITOKAWA MUKERU.
Next time, that legend will be repeated.
It means to put your life on the line.
There are still many people who are
waiting.
What is your name?
I'm a wooden goddess.
This program was provided by the sponsor
you are watching.
There are many people.
Buy it.
Who said that?
It's a design.