Do you have any ideas for a voice actor?
No, I don't have any ideas.
I don't think I have any ideas.
I'm often told that I'm different from
Seta.
I want to see Seta without the glasses.
I want to see her eating a lot.
I like this kind of taste.
Yakan and Idol
One day, Yakan, who was sleeping in the
living room of the Star Dust company,
showed up.
His name is Yakan.
Yakan, who is interested in idols,
asked the people of the Star Dust
company to talk to him.
The people of the Star Dust company who
are kind and like tea are okay.
Yakan, who was born in the dormitory,
was born in the dormitory.
I'm Yakan, who was born and raised in
the dormitory of the Star Dust company.
Today's guest is an idol.
I'm Seta Sakura, president of the Kyushu
Food Culture Association of the Star
Dust company.
Nice to meet you.
Yata!
Thank you for coming.
Can I talk to you for a while?
Nice to meet you.
I want to ask you about the Kyushu Food
Culture Association.
What is the president?
I really love eating.
I've loved food since I was little.
I want to eat more and introduce it to
people.
That's why I'm the president.
You have that association, right?
I made it.
I'm the president alone.
My fans and employees want to join the
association.
Everyone says that.
I'll just say no.
Why do you want to join the association?
I'm thinking of making a Tokyo branch.
I'm not familiar with that yet.
I'm a little bit of a stop.
You're a very good person.
I'm an idol.
Seta's showroom is famous among people
in the industry.
Thank you.
Do you do it yourself?
Yes, I do it myself.
Is it a live studio?
I used to do it at home, but I want to
do it in earnest.
I'm shooting now using the studio.
I've never seen you sitting like a
gaming chair.
I feel like I'm completely subduing the
studio.
Do you have any thoughts?
On the air?
I'm an otaku.
I don't talk to idols and fans.
We talk to each other as if we were
friends.
I see.
I like talking to you.
What is your favorite flavor?
I like the strong taste.
It's a little strong and sweet.
I want to see Seta Cooking.
It's like a restaurant.
I'm easier on brains.
There are things to cheer up.
She's different from the impression she
gives on the first hand.
There are my family.