Ebichu's Fufufu Showroom!
Good evening everyone, we are the
private Ebisu junior high school.
I'm Yuma Sakura, 16th place.
I'm Yuna Nakamura, 17th place.
Thank you for watching the 51st episode
of Ebichu's Fun and Silly Showroom.
Thank you.
The showroom is the showroom of Uka's
sister.
Today, we have two new members.
Yay!
How do you feel?
This is our first time in the showroom,
so we are very nervous.
I didn't expect that we would be the
first two members.
I'm a little nervous, but I'll do my
best.
I'll do my best.
Let's check the user rankings from the
5th place.
Thank you for watching.
5th place, Ganryu-shima, thank you.
4th place, Ju-san, thank you.
3rd place, Den-den, thank you.
2nd place, Mucho, thank you.
1st place, Miyan, thank you.
You can get the original avatar at the
showroom.
You can get it for free or by gifting.
Wow.
There are so many.
Did you make one?
This red one?
Wow, everyone is wearing it.
Wow.
Click the mark below.
You can spread the word on Twitter.
Please help us.
Please.
It's time to spread the word.
To get more people to watch this,
we will tweet on Twitter.
Please retweet.
Please.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
Please introduce yourself.
Yes.
Let's start with a funny...
Yes, sorry.
First, we will do this project.
It's called,
Fun and funny questionnaire.
Thank you for watching.
This is a familiar show in the showroom.
Before we start, we'll take a survey and
decide what to talk about.
Today's topic is...
Can you see it?
This.
Let's vote.
1. More details about yourself.
2. The behind-the-scenes of the
audition.
3. Your first impression of your
seniors.
4. My secret mission.
5. Embarrassing emoji.
6. Dog-like or cat-like.
6. 7.
7. The best side dish for rice.
Let's vote!
Which one will it be?
I'm curious about Enoki.
The Enoki illustration looks like Enoki.
I mean, it's Enoki, but it looks like a
Japanese character.
I'll do my best.
I want to see your illustrations again.
No, no.
We are not good at it.
5 seconds. 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
It's over.
What was the most?
5th, it was embarrassing.
It was embarrassing.
Which story is this?
This is...
I said it.
This is my story.
Don't you get stuck in your teeth after
eating?
I get stuck in my mouth.
The other day, graduation...
The day of the graduation album
shooting,
there was a mushroom soup for lunch.
I liked it, so I was really happy.
After I finished shooting, I looked in
the mirror,
and there was a enoki in the middle of
my front teeth.
I was hanging from the middle of my
front teeth.
In that state,
I took a picture of that.
I realized after I took it.
I went to see the mirror many times,
but I didn't check it.
From here, I was crying.
I was crying when I was eating.
That's the worst.
I cried for a moment.
It was a graduation album.
I didn't realize it.
I forgot to say it.
It was white.
I was crying.
I was thin, so I got stuck in various
places.
That's bad.
I got stuck in many places.
I've been wearing a mask lately, so I
don't really care.
Before I put on a mask,
I've been stuck in various places.
I've been careful lately.
I'm checking it.
You're saying it's okay because you're
increasing the color.
I'm changing it.
The mushroom is stuck in the middle.
Not a mushroom.
The edible tree.
The edible tree that was eaten.
It's moving from here.
That's bad.
I want you to fix it in Photoshop.
Can you do it now?
Now?
I'll ask you next time.
Ema, do you have any embarrassing
things?
Embarrassing things?
I don't have much.
It's a trend to hang up the enoki
mushroom, isn't it?
It's a trend.
It's a trend. That's good.
Let's hang it up from now on.
Let's hang it up together.
It's funny.
The latest trend.
The latest trend?
I'll be the mother of the sea.
The mother of the sea that carries the
enoki.
The mother of the sea that puts the
enoki in the teeth.
Everyone?
Everyone from here?
Then it's not embarrassing.
Then, the next story.
Next?
Then, the next one.
Once again, from the middle.
What I'm curious about.
Then, start voting.
Don't say goodbye energy.
Goodbye Drive.
What's next?
But there are a lot of good songs.
You can choose the same song.
The same song?
I can't choose any more.
It's a solo song of Emma.
I wonder if we can do a lot of live
performances someday.
It's fun.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
It's over.
What's next?
Senpai's first 2 songs
Should we say all of them?
Yes
First, Maimai-san
Before I got the audition for Ebichu,
I've been calling her name for a long
time.
I was Maimai-san's fan.
When I first met her, I was so happy.
I couldn't meet her during the audition.
Yeah, I couldn't come.
I couldn't come.
So when I first met her,
Maimai-san is short, isn't she?
But her face is too small, so she has a
great style.
She has big eyes, and her nose is high.
I thought she was a very beautiful
person.
She was cute.
Her face was small.
Her face is as small as a fist.
I've been saying that.
I like her low voice.
She's cool.
I like her beautiful low voice that only
she can sing.
I like her high notes.
I like that.
Only she can sing that high notes.
Next, Ayako-chan.
Ayako-chan has been smiling at me since
the training camp.
She has been smiling and talking to me.
I was nervous at first, but I was able
to compliment her.
Can I take this off?
It's okay.
I passed the audition for the first time
on the day of the announcement of the
new member.
I was scared and everyone was suddenly
nervous.
When we were in the bathroom, I heard
someone singing a song.
I wondered who was singing.
Ayako-chan was singing a song alone.
She was so cute.
I lost my image of being cute.
Ayako-chan has a big gap.
What about you, Emma?
I'll see you later.
Next is...
What's the name of the song?
It's a song I wrote myself.
What is it?
I don't know.
I didn't know either.
It was cute.
I was writing a song.
It's very rare.
I'm going to the rare place.
Mirei.
Mirei is very attractive.
It was a feeling.
He talked to me very frankly from the
beginning.
He asked me what I like and hate.
I knew at that time.
What I like and hate are similar to
Mirei.
It's very similar.
I was in sync with the atmosphere.
I like spicy food.
I thought Mirei was really good at
comedy.
And her style is really good.
I was surprised.
Her legs were so thin.
They're long.
I think she's the idol.
She's so elegant.
She's the opposite of Yuna.
She talks to me.
Kaho?
What's my image of Kaho?
It's Hinata.
Hinata?
Hinata had big eyes.
Yeah, she had big eyes.
She had big eyes.
She had big eyelashes.
She was really cute.
She has a cool image when she sings.
But she's really cute when she's in
private.
She has a cute face when she sings.
She talks to me gently.
Everyone said she was the boss.
I was scared because I was told that she
was the boss.
But she was kind when she talked to me.
She came to teach me how to dance.
She taught me in detail.
She is very kind.
She told me many times that she didn't
know.
She taught me gently.
She was like a mandarin orange.
When we first met, she brought me a lot
of sweets.
She gave me a mandarin orange.
She said, eat it.
I asked her later, she brought me a
mandarin orange.
And she gave me cookies.
She said, eat it.
She gave me cookies and a lunch box.
She was kind.
She was kind from the beginning.
Riko-chan.
Riko-chan has a strong image of being in
a training camp.
I was a little scared.
That's the first impression.
She has a strong eye power.
She looks serious.
I was a little scared.
When I was in the audition,
She was wearing a black dress.
She was next to Hinata-chan.
I wonder if that's the cause.
That may be the cause.
But when I talked to her,
There was no such thing.
Riko-chan really likes clothes and
fashion.
She is really cute.
She is fashionable.
I don't know if it was yesterday or the
day before.
She was wearing glasses.
She was cute.
She was so cute.
I was watching her all the time.
She was originally Riko-chan's style.
She is cute.
And KOKONA.
I saw her on the screen.
She was just as she was.
She was cute.
She always jokes around, but she is
serious when she is on the stage.
She is good at dancing.
I thought her performance and her gap
were amazing.
KOKONA has a great gap.
Yes, she does.
I like her dance too much.
The double speed dance was amazing.
It was so clean.
I couldn't see what she was doing.
It was clean.
She is cute when she talks.
She has a great gap.
YUNO.
YUNO was so kind.
I could see her around.
She is like a babu babu.
She is so attentive.
She was the first one to share her LINE.
She added me to her group LINE.
She was also the first one to ask me to
eat the catering.
She talked to me a lot.
She talks to me a lot.
She is like a big sister.
She is so kind.
She is kind.
She is cute when she talks.
She is good at talking.
I like her.
I didn't think she was the same age as
me.
I thought she was the oldest.
She is really mature.
She is mature.
She looks mature.
She has a great style.
She has a great face.
She is beautiful.
She is really cute.
I didn't think she was the same age as
me.
That's my first impression of her.
Yes.
My first impression of EMA.
My first impression of EMA was that she
looked smart.
She looked smart?
I thought she was studying every day.
She really studied.
She was like a Newtonian.
Like a past student?
Yes, like a past student.
Was she?
She was.
She was like a student.
That's strange.
I thought YUNA was cute when she spoke.
She has a soothing voice.
But during the audition,
we were in different teams.
We couldn't talk much.
Her voice was cute.
I forgot one thing.
My first impression of EMA was that she
had a smiley face.
When we were on the bus, we were
nervous.
But she was smiling.
What are you talking about?
No, no.
She was smiling even when she was
nervous.
That's amazing.
I thought she was a bright girl.
I'm happy.
I think that's it.
I think so.
Then, one more.
Let's do it.
Please vote. Start!
I can heal Yama-chan's smile.
I know.
I'm so happy.
What is it?
I don't care.
I also heard the first episode of Fujii-
san.
Did you hear the first episode of Fujii-
san?
Fujii-san?
Not the first episode, but the last one,
the one at the end of the show, the one
at Gin-Yama?
Yes, the one at Gin-Yama.
That was so funny!
But I didn't know how much I could
laugh.
It was so funny that I couldn't stop
laughing.
After I got home, the fans were raising
the cut-out part.
I was laughing so hard after watching
that.
At that time, Mirei-chan and Hinata-chan
were...
They were playing around.
2, 1...
The voting is over.
Yes.
I wonder what it is.
No.4
My secret mission
My secret mission is...
Ayaka is here, right?
At first, she was really cute.
And her singing voice was cool. There
was a gap.
My secret mission is...
I have a secret mission to sit on
Ayaka's lap.
But I'm going to say it, so the fans
will say it.
So please don't tell anyone.
I'm not going to tell anyone.
I want to sit on your lap someday.
When Hinata was doing a lesson for us,
Kokona was sitting on your lap.
I thought it was amazing.
But I want to sit on Ayaka's lap.
I want to sit on Ayaka's lap.
Yuna, do you have a secret mission?
I want to hug Riko.
Hug Riko?
You look cool.
You look like you're protecting me.
I'm going to hug Riko.
You look cool.
That's my goal.
I'll do my best.
But...
I'm going to hug Riko.
The last one.
I'll do one more.
Start voting!
Thank you very much.
I'm worried that she'll do it right
away.
I hugged Rika-chan.
I hugged Mayama-san.
No way.
She hugged me from behind.
I was nervous.
She said, do your best.
It started.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
It's over.
What's next?
2nd, behind the scenes of the audition.
We talked about this a lot.
There were two things.
One is...
There were people who noticed it.
I don't know what day it was.
I think it was the second day. Everyone
was practicing.
There was a team called Egg Girls.
The other three people were practicing.
But Emma wasn't there.
Everyone was wondering why Emma wasn't
there.
They were wondering if she was sick.
I don't know why, but I didn't think it
was a good idea.
I thought I'd take a bath first.
Even though you were sweating.
But I danced and sweat a lot.
I thought I'd take a bath again.
I was wondering why I took a bath.
Everyone was saying that I came home
refreshed.
I should have come in later.
Behind the scenes of the barbecue.
I didn't have time to cook.
I couldn't cook when I was cooking.
I cooked for the first time.
Half of the meat was raw.
Everyone was in a hurry.
It was dangerous.
I couldn't eat much.
I was shocked.
Karen's luxurious meat.
Everyone ate a bite.
Everyone was like a staff.
Karen didn't eat much.
Everyone ate a bite.
Karen gave everyone a treat.
It was really delicious.
I didn't have time.
After that, we practiced together.
I can't eat barbecue meat.
Let's eat together next time.
Next is this.
Fun and funny Q&A 100 times!
We will explain the rules. We will ask
you questions in the comments.
We will answer the questions and talk
about them.
The goal is to answer 100 questions.
Please leave your comments.
What do you ask at the end of the video?
What is your favorite sushi?
I'm definitely salmon.
I like tuna and egg.
It's delicious, isn't it?
It's fast.
It's fun because it's the opposite.
Mushroom mountain or bamboo shoot set?
Mushroom mountain.
I met a person who likes mushrooms for
the first time.
Mushroom is more delicious than tuna.
Everyone likes bamboo shoots.
It's good because there's a mushroom
rice cake.
The rice cake is so delicious.
I'll eat it first and eat the cracker.
No, if you put it in between.
I don't know.
Mushrooms are rare.
Thank you for watching.
What do you do first when you wake up?
First of all, I wake up...
I wake up in the morning and...
I go to sleep.
I wash my face.
Oh, I see.
I wonder if it depends on the day.
Yeah, that's true.
I wake up in the morning and...
I turn off the snooze alarm.
Oh, I see.
You turn off the alarm clock.
Yeah, yeah.
I really don't notice the alarm.
I don't turn it off unconsciously.
I can't hear the sound when I'm
sleeping.
I don't know.
I can't hear it unless it's a
smartphone.
Really?
It's really loud.
I'm sorry.
I have to ring it every five minutes.
Otherwise, I'll be in trouble.
Are you okay?
I'm ringing it.
I have a lot of snooze.
I'm going to turn it off.
It's a pain.
But I can't wake up unless I do that.
I wake up every day.
I can't watch it.
Is it dog or cat?
That's a good theme.
I'm a dog.
I'm a dog too.
Because I'm a dog.
I used to be a cat lover.
You said that.
I liked cats.
But after I got a dog, I became a dog
lover.
So you became a dog because you were a
cat?
I think it's cute.
It's so cute.
It's been a while since I've been home.
I want to see you.
I want to see you too.
It's healing.
You don't have to think about anything.
It's so cute when you play with it.
Yuna-chan said she looks like a cat.
I think people say that a lot.
Do you have a favorite comedian?
I think I should answer this as
Nasunaka-san.
I'm Osuwaru.
I'm Nasunaka-san and Osuwaru-san.
I really like Gerardon-san.
I like Chocopla-san and Kaguya-san.
I like them because they are funny.
I like Gerardon-san and watch his
YouTube channel every day.
I see.
I like a lot of things.
I watch the same thing all the time.
I see.
I think it's fun to watch the same
thing.
I think so, too.
Well...
I have a lot of questions.
Ah!
Muzo?
Literature? Science?
I think I can do it!
This one is really popular!
Eva is...
I think she's better at literature.
Better?
I think I'm better at science...
Yeah, Yuna is good at science...
I love the math...
Because
It's more like a brain exam...
She took her test a while ago, and...
What was her score?
92 points.
But...
I didn't study much this time.
I studied a little the other day.
It was the lowest score in the past.
The lowest score in the past?
The lowest score.
How many points did you get?
I don't even know.
I don't even want to calculate.
So...
Emma, I can't read Katakana.
You can read it.
I made a mistake.
Goodbye Drive.
Where do you want to go abroad?
I want to go abroad...
There are a lot of places.
I have a lot too. Where is it?
Have you been abroad?
I haven't been.
Where is it?
I want to go to Hawaii.
I want to go too.
Hawaii is hot.
Isn't Hawaii hot?
South?
Yes.
I want to go to Canada.
Canada?
I don't know why, but I want to go to
Canada.
I want to go to Canada.
There is no particular reason.
There are only Japanese people in
Hawaii.
Is that so?
Hawaii is not Hawaii.
Hawaii is a Hawaiian.
I'm confused.
I don't know why.
Hawaii is not hotter than Japan.
Oh, really? That's great.
Which do you like, cold or hot?
Cold!
Your clothes are cute.
I like the autumn and winter clothes.
It's cute. You can stack them.
It's better than hot.
I know where you are from.
Where?
So, it's Hawaii, right?
But I don't know where it is in Japan.
I don't know.
Please tell me the answer.
Hawaii?
I don't know.
I don't know where Hawaii is.
I don't know either.
I couldn't understand.
I don't know.
Oh, USA. USA.
USA. Korea is good, too.
I want to eat Korean food. Isn't it much
saltier than Korea?
It's salty. It's delicious.
It's not far from the bottom left of
Japan.
That's right.
It's close to the bottom left of Japan.
What do you mean? Because it's Fukuoka?
Yes.
It's the bottom left.
Udon or soba?
Udon.
I like Udon.
I like udon.
Really?
Udon with no ingredients.
I envy you.
Udon is famous in Fukuoka.
I like Udon.
Do you like something?
I like...
I like meat udon.
I like meat goboten udon.
Meat.
Looks delicious.
There is meat udon, but I have never
eaten it.
Really?
Let's go.
I like meat goboten udon.
It looks delicious.
It's delicious.
What's your favorite school lunch?
School lunch?
I don't have school lunch in middle
school.
Really?
I don't know.
Curry?
I like curry.
Is curry sweet?
What is it?
That?
ABC soup.
What is it?
The soup of ABCD.
I don't know.
Is it from Kanagawa?
I think I know.
Do you know ABC soup?
I heard that.
Really?
ABC is really small.
ABCD, ABCD, ABCD.
There are many.
It's a soup.
It's delicious.
It's cut like letters.
It's ABCD.
It's really delicious.
Pasta is ABCD.
I ate it because it looked delicious.
Is it pasta?
It's like pasta.
It's really delicious.
It looks delicious.
I've never been on a school lunch.
There's a different part.
It's like a small pasta.
I see.
Tanabata jelly.
I think I know.
You're terrible.
You can read all the alphabets.
I'll try.
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
I'll put it in.
What's your favorite day of the week?
I have only one.
Friday.
It's the same.
Friday is the best.
I know.
I hate Sunday the most.
Why?
I feel like it's over.
I'm in elementary school.
I'm sad when I watch the show every
Sunday.
I don't watch it.
I don't get sad.
I don't know.
I get sad when the show starts.
I think it's a Friday.
Do you watch TV?
I watch a lot.
I think I said TV more than SNS.
Emma is quite SNS.
It's regrettable.
But I watch TV and SNS.
I have never done Instagram.
Emma taught me when I first did it.
That's right.
Is there anything else?
I can't move.
What time is Yohkashi?
Have you ever been to the all-you-can-
eat restaurant?
Yes, I have.
But everyone goes to the all-you-can-eat
restaurant on their school trip.
I slept at a half-past four in the
afternoon on my school trip.
Really?
I can't wake up, but I'm excited because
it's a school trip.
I know.
I wanted to go to the all-you-can-eat
restaurant.
All?
But I'm going to fall asleep.
I'm going to fall asleep on a day I
don't care.
I was sleeping on the bus.
You sleep on the bus.
I slept on the bus.
I was so embarrassed.
I slept with curtains on my head.
Everyone was tired.
Last question.
What should I ask?
What should I do?
I'm not sure.
What was your childhood dream?
Oh, my childhood dream.
I was a kid, so I had a lot of dreams.
Yeah, I had.
I drew models, pre-cure, patissier, and
flower shop.
That's a lot.
It's a lot.
Everyone... What was it?
I drew Kukurun, Kukurun, pre-cure,
and...
When I was a little older, I wanted to
be a doctor or a nurse.
I've been longing for it.
I'm glad I'm a doctor.
Hmm.
End of training.
Thank you very much. How was it?
I was able to get a lot of things that I
didn't know.
I don't know what I'm doing. I had a lot
of questions that I didn't know.
Thank you very much.
That's all for the fun and funny Q&A
session.
This is the end of the 51st episode of
the showroom.
Thank you for watching.
Riko will be on the showroom of Nekojita
Showroom 5 from 8 p.m. on November 15th.
Please watch it.
One more.
And...
One more...
Wait a minute.
I'll read it.
Here we go.
Kashiwagi Hinata Ebichu...
Is this how you pronounce it?
Jyunifu?
How should I read it?
Twelv...
What should I do?
Wait, wait, wait.
Kashiwa Egi Hinata, Egi-chuu!
12th Anniversary Live Let's Laugh
Together Forever!
Surprised, surprised, surprised,
surprised!
I think there are 10 surprise marks.
Maybe it's because it's the 10th
episode.
Oh, really?
This will be held at Nakano Sun Plaza
Hall from November 28th at 7 p.m.
I'm going to be there at 12 o'clock.
Wait, I want you to do this. Tell me.
Twenties.
Is it wrong?
Is it Twenties?
Huh? Twenties?
Twelfth.
12th?
What's 12th?
12th is 12th.
12th.
I learned.
You learned.
Then, Yume-chan, please.
The graduation ceremony of Hinata
Kashiwagi Smile for You will be held at
the Makuhari Messe Event Hall on Friday,
December 16th.
The ceremony will start at 6pm. Please
check the website for more details.
New Style University Art Festival Run
in...
It's our.
I'm frustrated.
Run in our Ebichu family will be held at
the event hall on Saturday, December
17th.
It starts at 5.30pm.
Please check the website.
I'm nervous.
Here is the announcement.
Let's announce the top 5.
Let's announce.
Amazing.
Thank you, Mura.
Thank you, 13th place.
Thank you, Robin Hoshi Cook.
Cook.
Thank you, Shackleford.
Thank you, Mia from Oita.
I'm happy to be in Ebichu.
The 51st episode of Fufu-na Showroom is
over.
We will announce the next episode later.
This show will be broadcasted after the
show.
Please check it out.
The show will end soon, but we will
resume soon.
Please leave a comment if you have
anything to say.
This is Ebichu Junior High School.
Bye bye.
Please subscribe to my channel.
It was difficult.
I couldn't read the comments because
they were too fast.
But I didn't fail.
I was just humming along.
Thank you for your hard work.
It was your first showroom.
How was it?
It was difficult to read the first half
of the performance.
The comments were fast, so I think I
didn't read as much as I should have.
Was it fun?
It was fun.
It was really fun.
That's good.
How about you, Nakamura?
I couldn't read the comments because I
couldn't catch up with the comments.
You picked up a lot of comments, so it
was very helpful.
I also wanted to study English more.
I'm 12 years old.
It's not a reflection of the program.
I'm not sure if I'm alive.
Was it fun?
It was really fun.
Both of you were cute.
Thank you.
I'm glad to hear that you are already
close friends.
I hug and sleep every day.
It's enough to do this for the first
time.
I'm glad.
I want you to look at the camera a
little more.
I see.
It's difficult to pick up comments, look
at the script, look at the camera, and
look at the members.
You will get used to it.
Yes.
You are amazing at the end.
Thank you.
Okay, let's start over.
Yes, yes.
You can say, like, come on, come on.
It's okay to be so nervous.
Yes.
You can do this much for the first time.
Thank you very much.
I heard that your career is long.
Career?
I wonder.
I...
It's been a long time.
I think it's my sixth year this year.
Six years.
You have a lot of questions.
You have been asked a lot of questions.
The answer is anything.
I think the reason is important as an
idol.
For example, you are a mushroom lover.
You said you were a mushroom lover.
You said you had a way to hold it.
That's interesting.
When you answer the question, you can
say all the reasons.
Then you will understand that you are a
mushroom lover.
I think it's good.
I'm not unsure though.
It's been a while since we've had a real
reflection session.
We don't do that often.
We don't really talk about it.
That's about it.
Also, announcements.
There are things that the show does to
make announcements.
To connect to other activities,
For example, to buy CDs for fans.
Announcements are the most important
thing.
Not only reading information,
What should I do to make you think,
If you think about it a little more,
It will be a good announcement.
At least read it.
It's a little bit that you haven't
written.
I'm looking forward to it.
I think it's okay to do it more freely.
Only 12 minutes.
12 minutes.
Maybe it's more than just reading.
It may leave an impression.
I think it's okay.
I think it's better to read it.
Yes.
It's like that.
I usually do it in a showroom with three
people, and one senior person enters.
It's completely different to do it with
two people.
I think that you will be able to study
by appearing in that area again and
again.
I hope you can learn how to use it in a
variety show.
Yes.
If you think it was fun, that's enough.
I have a question about the avatar.
Avatar?
It's an avatar called Ebibonjin.
Everyone does that.
It's all in the comments.
Everyone.
It's an illustration of Kaho.
That's amazing.
I want to do it regularly.
I think the hardest part is the first
two members.
I think it's usually easier.
But this time it was difficult.
I hope you can do it next time.
Please do it well.
Emma-san.
Yes, Emma-san.
What should I do?
Thank you for watching Emma's show
today.
Thank you.
Compared to the usual live, it may have
become a very loose live.
I will do my best to make the most of my
reflection and make it a more enjoyable
live.
I hope you will watch it again.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye.
Please subscribe to my channel.