The next day, the first day of the
school year.
The first day of the school year.
Solumiro! Kaoriko!
Good evening, everyone.
I'm Shichiebishu-roku, number 11,
Kobayashi Kao.
The first day of the school year.
I'm Riko Nakayama, 52nd year.
Today's guest is a cheerful character,
from old age to a child, Rika Mayama.
Please come in.
Nice to meet you.
You seem to have a good sense of humor.
Thank you for your hard work on the next
week's Produce.
Yes.
I suddenly got the main topic.
How was it?
Please finish it.
I don't know myself.
How was it?
It was fun.
I was excited.
I'm sure it was good.
It's not something you can judge for
yourself.
It's something that people around you
judge.
If people around you say it's good, I
think it's the best.
I'm sorry.
We worked hard for the first time as
reporters.
Thank you.
We hope you will watch it together.
We want to watch it.
Let's watch it together.
Soremi's Kawariko's In-N-Out Report
In Shinagawa Stella Ball
Yay!
I'm so confident
We're preparing for the match
It's amazing, it's like this
Amazing
It's fun
How are you today?
Please tell us how you are today
What did you eat for breakfast?
I ate ham and cheese bread
You ate ham and cheese bread
I have a place I want to go
Let's go to the store today
Let's go
I want a towel
Is it light?
It's not
I want it
I'm happy
I want to buy it
It's cute
It's sold
I'm happy
Thank you
I want to buy it
I got this
I'm happy
This is a poncho with a food
This is cute
I want to eat this
Can't I eat this?
I will open it now
Please get ready
Thank you
Before today's self-study, we have this
person here
So, question
How do you feel about the self-study?
My feeling is
I don't produce anything
So I'm not nervous
I'm very nervous about the self-study
So I think I can have fun
So, if Hinata-chan were to produce
something, what would it be?
What would it be?
I don't think I've ever done something
like this before
It's not a sports day, but I want to
have a little bit of a feeling of being
nervous
I'm always nervous, but I want to make
the audience enjoy watching me
I want to think about that and do my
best
So, what did you eat this morning?
I ate a Yaki Onigiri this morning
It was very delicious
It's very similar
Thank you
So, that's it for the interview
Thank you very much
That's all from Hinata
Bye bye
So we have a guest here today
Mirei-chan
Mirei-chan, here you are
Hello
Hello, it's me, Kaho
It's Mirei
Hello, what do you think we're doing
today?
We're doing a live show
Really?
Who produced today?
Mahama and Mizuki
Right?
Yes
So, we're going to interview Mirei-chan
First, how do you feel right now?
Right now?
Right now...
Last time, I was with Ayaka for the
first and second part
It was the first time for us, so I
didn't know anything
I did a lot of things I wanted to do,
and I gave the script to everyone the
day before
It was really close
It was a live performance but it was
really like a concert
But this time we did a rehearsal
So it was like a real live performance
I'm a little nervous now
But the members produced it
So I feel safe
Thank you for watching
What should I do to give you the Jushin-
Ko?
I don't have it!
You do, right?
You do!
Because I was told I was an old man at
school
You're lying!
Really!
All the members in Ebichu like snacks
So when I entered, I couldn't eat snacks
But everyone ate it, so it was delicious
if I ate it with seaweed
And I like snacks, and I sometimes buy a
snack at school
And I eat it, so I'm called a man on
Twitter
But today I came to Ashida Mana
It's Ashida Mana! Ashida Mana has a
little bit of a sense of achievement
Is it possible? Yes!
Mana is sleeping early to improve her
female ability, but Hoshina Mirei-chan
is not sleeping.
I see.
Mana-chan, how about you?
I'm Ashida Mana. I'm trying to sleep
early, but I can't sleep.
I understand that feeling.
What should I do?
So, it was Ashida Mana.
It was Ashida Mana.
That's right. It was Ashida Mana.
Bye bye!
The rehearsal is over.
How was it?
I think we were like,
We were like,
I have a lot of chicken skin,
I was thinking if I could do it properly
because I was going to do it next time.
I have a lot of chicken skin.
It was amazing.
It was a good night's sleep.
I was so tired that I couldn't sleep.
But I can't sleep.
It was a good night's sleep.
I will do my best to watch the Osaka
Grand Cube.
Thank you.
Let's enjoy the show.
I will do my best.
Today, I have a guest.
The first guest is the producer, Marika
Maaya.
Hello.
Let's start with the question.
What did you make today as a producer?
I made everything that Mayama thinks is
good about Ebichu.
Ebichu is basically a bit of a personal
thing.
Recently, I've been doing live shows.
I want people to understand the depth of
Ebichu.
I made something that is as close to the
core as possible.
What should I do?
What did you have for breakfast today?
I had breakfast early today.
I didn't feel like eating even though I
was in a high-pitched voice.
I woke up in the morning and drank
orange juice.
Then I ate strawberries, drank yogurt,
and drank it.
I ate almost everything.
I didn't feel like eating at all because
my stomach hurt.
Then please eat a lot for lunch.
I will eat a lot.
Rikko, please eat a lot.
Thank you for your viewing.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye.
Wait, you can't say that.
Thank you very much.
So, we have Ayai here with us before the
next show.
Hello.
We're going to have an interview.
First, how do you feel right now?
We have to learn the only position of
the eight of us,
the only position of the Jishu and
Makuhari messengers.
It's totally different from the dance
we've done so far, so everyone is
nervous and checking.
OK, then, it's a question that has
nothing to do with it.
What do you want to eat for dinner
tonight?
I like sashimi, so I want to eat
hamachi.
Hamachi?
It's adult.
Adult?
Hamachi?
What do you like?
I can only eat salmon.
I like salmon too.
Salmon is delicious.
Next time, we will go to eat salmon at
sushi restaurant.
Next question.
What do you do before the show?
What do I do?
I sing and stretch.
But I'm excited. Everyone is jumping
around.
It looks fun.
That's right.
And finally, I have something to ask
you.
Well, is this okay?
Anything is fine.
Well, now...
The music in my room is playing, so I
cut it.
That's all from Aya-san. Thank you very
much.
So, before the next week, we have
Hirono-chan here.
Please come in!
We're going to do an interview right
away.
First, how are you feeling right now?
Rika's hair is the most popular one.
So everyone has a braided hair.
I don't have a twin sister.
I'm embarrassed.
But you look good on you.
I think you're cute.
It's short.
But you're cute.
Thank you.
I'm going to puke.
Next question.
What do you want to eat for dinner
tonight?
Dinner?
Yes.
That's a very sudden question.
I want to eat ramen.
Ramen? What kind of ramen?
Miso ramen.
That sounds delicious!
What do you do before the show?
I don't know.
I check the hand and the position of the
hand.
That's good.
I turn it firmly.
Finally, what do you want to eat most
now?
What should I choose?
I choose the left hand.
Please keep your eyes open.
That's all from Hirono. Thank you very
much.
I had Rina Matsuno come to my house a
few weeks ago.
Yay!
So, let's start with the questions.
What's your mood right now?
I haven't been on a live for a while, so
I'm a little nervous.
But I'll do my best!
So, Aki-chan, what did you eat for
breakfast?
I had toast, sausage, and white rice.
I had 卵焼き.
That's nice.
Do you want to eat dinner?
I want to eat gyoza for dinner.
Gyoza? Oh, Kaohsiung!
You're the same.
Yay!
What would you like to do if you were to
produce?
What would it be?
I think I have less than 10 weeks, but I
want to do something like a different
look or make up.
That sounds fun.
That's it.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye.
We're going to do a report to Mizuki-san
from 10 weeks ago.
Mizuki-san, please come in!
Yes!
Hello.
So, how do you feel right now?
Right now, I'm kind of nervous.
I'm excited.
I'm looking forward to it, but I'm not
sure how the fans will react.
I think they were expecting a lot from
us, so I think we can do it.
Thank you for watching!
I'm looking forward to it. I'm looking
forward to it too.
What kind of image did you produce?
I wanted to show various kinds of
shrimp.
It's a back-up, but from the original
song of the first shrimp-chop diamond,
I was dancing to a song in order for
each single.
I was taking the songs from the
coupling, not the single.
I didn't have any chance to do it, so I
brought the songs from the past.
I also took the costumes apart.
I didn't decide on the free talk part.
Thank you for watching!
I wanted to show you a way to not stop.
I can't explain it well.
I want to see it quickly.
It's a story that has nothing to do with
it.
What do you want to eat for dinner
tonight?
Today's dinner?
I want to eat soba.
Are you a Zaru-Soba fan?
Yes, I am.
Yay!
Normal is the best.
Yes, normal is the best.
Finally,
What do you want to do now?
What do you want to do before the show?
Before the show?
What is it?
I want to move around a lot.
I have a lot of time.
I can't stay still, so I go out with the
staff and do some shopping.
I play with the camera when I have a
making film.
I see.
I want to relax.
Please do your best on the show.
I will do my best.
That's all from Mizuki. Thank you very
much.
Thank you.
You came to Ayaka Yasumoto.
I came.
Tell me about your feeling now.
I'm really looking forward to it.
You were a producer before.
And you did a sports event.
That's right.
Why did you do a sports event?
It's a seasonal event.
Oh, it's summer.
What?
It's autumn.
When was it?
July?
I don't know.
My dad told me.
It looked fun.
Thank you.
Are you watching?
I'm watching.
What should I do?
I'll do a hidden camera.
What's your name?
I'm Riko Nakaiwa.
How old are you?
I'm 13 years old.
You're 13 years old.
What?
I'm sorry.
I'll close the camera.
What?
What's for breakfast today?
Today...
Today... I'm going to eat yogurt.
I don't eat yogurt in the morning, so I
eat it during the day.
What did you eat during the day?
During the day... I ate a little bit of
yogurt.
What do you want to eat at night?
At night...
I don't eat ice cream at night.
You don't eat much.
I eat.
I'm fine with just ice cream at night.
That's tough.
What should I do?
Thank you for watching!
It was a lot of fun, but...
I'm the producer for the second part.
I don't know what you think, but...
Anyway, let me do what I want to do.
Bye bye! Thank you! I'm Kouki!
It's been about two years since we
started.
Yeah, it's been a while.
It's been a while.
Thank you for watching!
Thank you!
Bye bye!
We will be back with another Seventeen!
Wow, that was amazing.
You did your best.
I did my best.
You wrote the notes properly.
There were a lot of things to say.
I wanted to say a lot of things.
But at the end, Yasumoto took
everything.
What's going on?
You wrote the wrong question.
You were like, eeeh?
I was like, eeeh?
What were you talking about?
I don't know.
Really?
They asked me what my favorite color was
and what age I was.
That's amazing.
It's like you.
You were like, eeeh?
That was funny.
That was amazing.
I was really curious about you.
When you were with Mirei.
You were just a voice actor.
But...
Hinata's era is coming.
You lost?
I lost.
I thought it was okay to do it as a
hobby.
You're an actor.
It doesn't matter if it's similar or
not.
I'll keep it in my heart.
I'll ask Hinata to do it.
It's a big success.
I don't think so.
You're like your mom.
Until you imitate Mano Ashida.
3, 2, 1, go.
See you tomorrow.
What are you eating today? What's the
food?
I don't know.
What's this?
What is this?
Cake.
Cake?
It looks delicious.
It looks delicious? You haven't eaten
it?
I have.
It's delicious.
Here you go.
I'm sorry. It's not that good.
It's interesting.
No.
It's okay.
Why?
So...
So?
I'll go into the main topic.
You'll go into it?
Should I go into it?
Go ahead.
I'm just a sub-person.
Is it okay?
It's okay.
I'll go into the main topic.
I've looked at the self-study and
written down my thoughts.
You wrote it earlier.
I wrote this memo to announce it.
I'd like to announce it.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm the producer of the first part,
Mayama-senpai.
I'll announce the second part, Mizuki-
senpai.
You've interviewed me.
That's what it is.
Let's get started.
Is it itchy?
It's itchy.
I just wrote it down.
I thought it was itchy.
I'll announce it.
My voice is a little hoarse.
Get ready.
The first one is the school after
school, getabako, rock'n'roll, M-MAX.
Wait.
MX.
You're going to sing it from now on.
I was thinking.
I'm sorry.
Did you aim for the right answer?
No.
I was thinking.
You were doing MX in the VTR.
You said M-MAX.
I was thinking with you.
I didn't know.
Wait, wait.
Before that, you didn't say M-MAX.
You didn't say A.
You only said M and X.
If you put A in the middle, it becomes a
max.
MX.
We all had fun.
It was fun to watch it like a free-
spirited shrimp.
Thank you.
From the balloon game.
Mizuki's Produce...
Produce?
I'm sorry.
When we were running, we played a
balloon game.
Red and white.
After that, we played MC.
We had a birthday surprise for Mizuki.
We threw a tissue at the time of the
youth that didn't stop.
You threw it.
We didn't notice it.
I thought you were going to say that.
It's okay.
I threw it.
No, no, no.
It was good.
It was fun.
I couldn't reach it because I couldn't
use my arm.
I couldn't reach it.
I couldn't reach it either.
When you throw it,
It's like a ninja.
Throwing a shuriken.
When you throw it, it flies.
I realized that the song was about to
end.
I couldn't reach it.
My teeth almost fell off.
If you want to record it, please
subscribe to this channel.
We got a lot of messages.
You have your autographs, right?
Yes.
I just finished signing the autographs.
When the lights were on,
I saw the sign on your chair.
I was angry.
But...
I think there are three of them.
You wrote five?
I think there is one.
You have one.
You dropped one.
I think you got the other one.
You are kind.
Yes.
What else?
I thought you were Mayama.
I thought so.
I think...
Riko is a little bit brave.
What?
What do you say?
I think...
Mayama is the best.
What should I do?
Thank you.
And...
I love you.
Really?
I will do it.
I think it's enough.
I have a great makeup artist.
I think you can do it.
I just saw it.
You can do it.
I think you can do it.
oh? Can you do it?
You can do it. You can do it.
Really? Is it cute?
I don't know about the recent ones.
I think it's just that you're not good
at it.
I don't know.
I'll try it next time.
But my hair's grown lately.
Try it next time.
I'll try it next time.
I'm looking forward to it. I'm doing it.
Did you get it all together? I'm doing
it personally.
AiAi is good at cleaning.
You said that.
I'm cleaning the desk.
I remembered that AiAi is good at
cleaning.
You're good at cleaning.
I'm good at cleaning.
I wonder if cleaning is a class.
When the teacher comes, I wipe the desk
properly.
Usually, I run from end to end alone.
What are you running?
I'm cleaning up.
I'm cleaning up the
I'm just wiping the desk.
But I've got a few desks.
I wipe it like that.
When the teacher comes, I'm doing it
seriously.
I'm working on it.
I was seen once today.
You were seen today?
Yes, I was laughed at.
And then I entered.
So I'm not good at cleaning.
You're not good at cleaning?
Yes.
I see.
I'm learning.
Let's go to the report of the teacher.
I'm sorry.
It's okay. It's very interesting.
What?
It's okay.
I'm Mizuki's...
I'm going to announce it.
First of all, everyone's costumes are
different.
I like what I like.
I like what I like, and I like the way
people around me choose their voices.
Everyone has their own unique
characteristics.
Everyone was so cute.
Thank you.
I like the rocker's costume.
I like it.
I suddenly became a
repost.
It was cute.
Also, the unit.
I've always wanted to see the unit
personally.
I see. You don't have much chance to do
it.
And then, the stick-on-bomb and
the
fudel
Wait, wait.
Let's do it properly.
Calm down.
Fudel Girl.
Wait, wait.
I was wrong.
Fudel Girl and
Jazz Kissa Rika.
I've been listening to them recently.
I was so happy to listen to them.
I was so excited.
Thank you.
And then, there was a call from Mizuki.
Yes, during the encore.
I was watching from the second floor.
I could see the whole thing.
I was so excited.
And then, the song.
The song is Cinderella.
It's all about Mizuki.
I was so excited.
I got soooo moved.
When the bell bonus again, hidillon will
sing like this.
It's really good.
It's rare to see a new doctor.
It was my first time.
I was happy to see and report.
Thank you.
I saw them on stage.
I thought there was a red
I thought it was a red.
I thought they were doing their best.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Next time,
we'll have everyone have fun.
We'll be on stage.
I think it's going to be okay.
Why? You two are okay.
I'll do my best.
That's what I'm looking forward to.
It's going to be so much fun.
Right.
It's about time.
What?
What's wrong?
It's about time.
It's sudden.
Today, we have something great for
everyone who is watching.
Oh, this is it.
Everyone, please look forward to it.
Oh, that's it.
That's it.
Okay.
So, now we will announce the details of
the spring tour.
Yay!
Woohoo!
Details?
Wow!
Isn't this our first time seeing this?
Oh, oh, oh.
Is this our first time?
Can I say that?
Oh well soldiers are going home early.
Shirito Ebisu中学 Spring Sony Music Labels
Buki Tour 2014
Reborn Choucho Bon and Etocetera
This is the tour title
Cool
This is the logo
April 27th, Sunday
Osaka Orix Theater
Osaka
It's your first time
It's my first time
I'm excited
Osaka
It's a big venue
As I thought
Can I say it?
May 4th, Sunday
Aichi, Zeppu, Nagoya
Oh! Zeppu Nagoya!
Have you done it before?
Yes, I did it during the last Zeppu
Tour.
Zeppu has a different atmosphere.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's been a day since our debut.
Thank you for your viewing.
It's been 2 years since I debuted.
I'm looking forward to it.
Next is May 6th, Saturday.
Tokyo ZEP Diver City.
Diver City?
It's my first time doing it.
I'm doing it alone.
Last time I did it twice.
It's my first time doing it alone.
Tokyo?
Tokyo.
ZEP Diver City.
It's fun!
It's big.
Next.
May 25th, Sunday.
ZEP Fukuoka.
Fukuoka!
We can go to Fukuoka.
We can ride the plane.
We're looking forward to it.
And then...
June 14th, Saturday.
May 21st, Izumi.
Izumiti.
Wow, it's my first time.
Miyagi. I went to Miyagi Sendai once
when I was on Idol Love.
But it's my first time to go alone on
Ebichu.
Wow.
And then?
June 15th, Sunday.
Tour Final.
Tour Final?
Kanagawa.
Pacifico Yokohama National Dive Hall.
Pacifico Yokohama National Dive Hall?
Wow!
Wow! Dive Hall.
Dive Hall!
You're going to do it at a great place.
Thank you.
I hope you all come and enjoy the show.
Please look forward to it.
This tour is about releasing new songs.
Please listen to our new single,
Butterfly Effect, which is the 6th
single of Ebisu.
It's the opening theme song of the TV
anime, Ryuhajo Nana Nana.
What about today?
It's earlier than anywhere.
It's the same song as the anime.
You can listen to it.
Kao, please do the pre-chorus of the new
song.
Good.
Really?
Where should I stand?
Here.
Please stand in front of the camera.
Okay.
Please listen to Butterfly Effect.
Please subscribe to my channel.
The moment I woke up
What is this? I've never seen this
before
I somehow made myself
Next is the adventure
The world is so sweet
It's like seeing something
The stage I thought it was cold
Next is the adventure
Thanks for watching!
Dec intrinsic locations
Butterfly epic
Lare contrast
End and birth
Saint story
Let's get through
My wish comes true
My memories
Thank you for watching!
My heart is spinning, spinning, spinning
I love you, the day we meet again
Wow!
Cool!
I like it!
Wow!
How was it?
It was our first time.
Right? It was your first time.
Me too.
It was our first time.
How was it?
How was it during the recording?
It was our first time.
Right.
We hadn't experienced it before.
So,
At first, I was nervous.
But,
It was pretty interesting.
The recording?
I didn't like it when
I heard my own voice.
I didn't like it.
I didn't like my own voice.
But, it was the same voice
as the song I was playing.
So, I was able to tell that this is the
kind of voice I am.
When I first heard it, my voice was
completely different from the voice I
was talking about.
So, I was quite surprised.
When I heard the song, I was like, I
didn't know I sang like this.
Really?
Yes, I was.
I was the same as the song, but I felt
like I was different.
That's amazing.
What are you going to do?
I'm surprised by a lot of things.
What kind of costumes are there?
I hope they are cute.
I wonder what kind of costumes are
there.
It's already this time. It's already
this time. It's too early.
Then, today we had Marika Maya come.
Thank you for watching Marika Maya.
Thank you.
This was Marika Maya, number 3. Bye bye.
Everyone, 2 days later? 3 days later?
Let's meet at the end of the day. Bye
bye.
Thank you. It was fun. Good luck.
Bye bye.
3 days later.
3 days later. I'm looking forward to it.
It's about time.
Thank you for watching Soremiro Kaho
Riko.
Thank you.
Shiriti Ebisu High School, number 11,
Kobayashi Kaho.
Number 12, Nakayama Riko.
This was Soremiro Kaho Riko. Bye bye.
Are you nervous?
Would you like to open your mouth, it
means tele Israelites
Hope you enjoyed!
They are boxing real sudden
Heading to a
supermarket
Getting off from