I graduated from university,
but I love boy manga,
so I wrote my thesis in Jump.
What?
What's going on?
It's a fast-paced manga,
so I think I'm a genius at packaging.
Akagi-san is the one who comes up with
the packaging for convenience stores.
I was like,
I can do a full marathon, right?
You're lying!
I'm serious!
Niko's Dorm Life
I'm Yakan, born in Miba and raised in
the old school room of Stardust.
And today's guest is this person.
Hello!
I'm Kimoto Honoka, the leader of Team
Shachi,
from Nagoya, where Super Town, Strong
Energy, and Positive Exciting Soul come
from.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
I'm Yakan.
Finally, Team Shachi is here!
Thank you for having me.
Thank you.
It's Team Shachi's 10th anniversary this
year!
That's right.
It's our 10th anniversary.
It's been 10 years since Team Shachi was
formed.
I'm going to keep doing this with a
happy heart.
What kind of position do you have,
Kimoto?
Me?
I've been doing a lot of voice work
since I was a trainee.
I used to think that my voice would ruin
the world view of the song.
But I've been told by everyone that I
should keep my voice alive.
I've been given a lot of voice work over
the past 10 years.
That's right. I've been given a lot of
voice work.
This is an absolute weapon.
It's something that people don't have.
Thank you.
Are you a voice actor?
I'm a voice actor, a character, a
program narration, and a host of the
Tokyo National Museum's escape game.
Are you the one who's going to tell the
story?
That's right. I'm escaping with my
voice.
Are you doing it at the National Museum?
That's right.
That's amazing.
Thank you.
You're a country-wide expert.
I was surprised, too. I'm glad.
The biggest thing for the team was the
acquisition of a dish label.
We've been taking care of Warner Music
Japan for nine years since we were
first.
We've been taking care of them for a
long time.
We've been working on a new dish label
since the time of the 20th anniversary.
It's called Wakuwaku Records.
It hasn't changed much since the
customers. When we decided on a new
song, we asked them to listen to the
compilation.
We talked about which song would be good
and decided on a song.
We have a lot of opinions on the new EP
that will be released on November 23rd.
I just heard the title of the song.
The title is...
When we peak at the top of the world, we
break through all the peaks.
I made a mistake. Please say it again.
I'm not used to saying this. I'll say it
again.
Let's say this properly.
The title of the new EP is...
When we reach the top, we will overcome
all difficulties.
What kind of thoughts are you talking
about?
Are you talking about the members?
That's right.
We've been a band since we were in the
president's time.
We think we're a live band.
The characteristics of a live band are
that we, not only ourselves, but also
the fans, dance together.
When we reach the top, we will overcome
all difficulties.
That's the title of the new EP.
It's like a concept.
I want to know the definition of a manga
that sells well.
I actually went to the publisher to get
an appointment and listen to the story.
This program is
Toshi-san
Mac-san
Saki-san
Nickname Nashi-san
Bakaba Gakure no Sato-san
I sent it with a gift
Today's recommended ice cream is
Mina!