Thank you everyone! We will be waiting
for the second part!
Thank you for your hard work!
Thank you very much!
Thank you!
I'm sorry.
I said it without thinking.
You are 21 years old.
I'm 21 years old.
You are talking a lot.
What?
I thought it would be a good shape if I
worked hard.
I felt the possibility.
Thank you very much.
I felt like I was being punished here.
I was nervous all the time.
But you can share it with the audience
because you can listen to it directly.
Do you have any chance to show it to the
audience?
I had less opportunities to show this.
Thank you very much.
I'm so glad to work with you because
you're serious throughout the process
like thought out responsible speakers
It's good to be able to eat this.
So, Mr. Yoshida,
I'm not sure.
I think it's Mr. Yoshida.
It's the next.
The staff members are a little nervous,
I think.
I'm afraid I'll call you.
I'm sorry.
I heard about the transmission station.
Is it a little earlier?
It's a little earlier.
I'm sorry.
It's Mr. Yoshida.
Let's go to the transmission station.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your patience.
All My Might Nippon
That's all for today.
Thank you so much.
Thank you for your time.
I've been so angry in 2 hours.
But now I'm so excited.
I'm so excited today.
I've been doing what I want to do.
I enjoyed it the most.
I think you'll continue to do it.
I'm so grateful.
I'm so grateful that I can do it.
I'm so happy that many people are moving
because of what I said.
I'm so happy that I can do it again.
This is the last episode of Yakan and
Idol.
Thank you so much.
I'll keep doing it next year.
Please continue to watch the next
episode.