I don't need any of that.
No?
I don't need it. I'm serious.
I'm fine with anyone.
I can't see it. I can see it.
How was it? NARUHA came in.
From the sound of the sound of the
sound.
But it was a year of thinking, wasn't
it?
That's right.
After making a major debut and doing a
whole tour, it seemed like it was going
well, but it seemed that the puzzle was
a little off.
We don't know how to proceed with the
gang parade.
That's right.
I thought it was a time when it felt
like that.
I think it's because it's continued now.
I think it was the best work to continue
the gang parade.
Haruna's disbandment and Saki's
disbandment?
It was a year of separation.
It's a pretty heavy year.
That's why I can't use it.
It's a bit of a hard one, so I'll just
put out the sound.
I'm just going to use the part that I
can use.
I wanted to do it together.
I was pretty strong, but I couldn't do
it anymore.
Haruna's story was fun.
It was a shock.
I don't think it's the most interesting
story.
Can I talk about it?
I don't know.
I wanted to be free.
And the activities of Paradise.
I have to put it out on the screen.
Actually, I was shooting AASA.
I was planning to work with Haruna and
four people in Paradise.
I put out the sound source for a moment.
I put out the sound of G.P.Hatena.
Haruna was in it.
I got in touch with the practice of
Paradise the day before.
I was very angry.
I didn't get in touch with the practice
of G.P.Hatena the next day.
I was worried that I would be really out
of shape if I didn't come here tomorrow.
I didn't know what to do.
It's best to find a place.
It's best to bring Haruna to the stage.
I didn't know if it was best or not.
I struggled a lot that day.
I didn't come to the live show the next
day.
I struggled.
I was wondering where Haruna was.
I will do my best.
Haruna is here.
I will analyze the situation on the
Internet.
Can I talk about this?
I will post everything.
NASA wars everything.
I said I would go, but I said I would
go.
I said I would believe in tomorrow and
wait, but I didn't come.
I was confused as I thought.
I wondered how I should feel about
standing on stage.
After all, I have to laugh at the live
performance.
But I felt like I could laugh.
Haruka and I were very contrasting
people.
We were rivals.
But we were a little behind.
I was thinking, let's do our best
because Haruna was there.
I felt like I had a hole in my heart.
I was the one who had a fight with the
moon.
That's the one, right? The one in
Tawareko, Shibuya?
Yes, the one in Tawakku.
I was also bad at keeping things in my
mouth.
I wasn't as soft as I am now.
Please stop it.
I was really angry once.
I was so angry when I said that.
I sang all the lyrics in four different
ways.
I couldn't remember the lyrics.
I made a mistake several times.
You made a mistake many times.
When the moon appeared, I was like,
Don't sing in the wrong way.
The moon was strange.
I asked the moon, are you okay?
I remember it very well.
I was like, I'm okay.
I was like, I can't concentrate because
I made a mistake.
I kept apologizing.
How was it?
It was difficult because I didn't speak
as I needed to, but I could speak to the
moon.
He spoke unexpectedly.
I can't use it seriously.
I think it's about 3 minutes.
There is a back-up plan.
I wonder how much the interviewer side
can expose it.
I don't think you've ever hidden your
love life.
I think I've hidden it.
No, I haven't.
Who did you like at this time?
I don't have one.
I don't have a favorite one.
I don't know who I liked.
I don't know.
I don't have one.
I've only been hiding and playing tag.
What?
I've only been playing tag.
You're small.
I'm small.
You've been on a lot of taxis.
I've been using it a lot.
I don't have any savings.
I don't know.
You don't know.
You're serious, right?
It's too good.
What should I do?
You can use it.
I don't want to be a
next interviewer.
It's hard to wear makeup.
It's hard for young people.
I don't think I have makeup on.
Thank you for watching.
I pretended not to hear you, even though
I could hear you
I pretended to be stupid and gave up
I can't see the full star