The two people who joined the other day
are 15 years old now, so they're 10
years old.
You were so young when you were 15.
And then I told everyone that I was a
monster.
I'm going to secure a monster car.
You're going to be so active.
It's pretty rough.
I'm going to get a monster car when I'm
16.
I like it, but it's a pain in the ass.
But I like it.
The
I like it, but it's a pain in the ass.
Hello, I'm Viva Form Warre, the cute-
looking Yakan-kun of Stardust.
Today, the most beautiful girl came to
Yakan-kun.
Let's call today's guest.
This is idol.
I'm Mirai Hoshino, the lead role of the
series, and I'm a lucky seven.
Nice to meet you.
Good morning.
I'm nervous.
Mirai-chan came.
I'm not nervous at all.
It's been a while.
I was nervous in the morning.
I'm sorry to say that I'm talking to you
from the morning.
I think it's a job that's not easy.
Thank you.
You're busy with a lot of things, aren't
you?
Yes, it's a time when a lot of things
are changing.
I joined the two members.
Hina Kashiwagi graduated from Matsu this
year.
I've been doing a lot of work.
In the midst of that, Mirai-chan is
already in a position of immorality.
I don't know.
How far are you from the bottom?
I'm 10 steps away.
I didn't think I'd be working with
someone who's 10 steps away.
That's right.
I'm going to do it with you.
I was watching a lot of things on SNS.
But more than that, you've done 10 more.
Yes.
How did you talk?
The first thing that surprised me was
that I joined the three of us last year.
That's right.
In 2021.
Yes, we were doing it alone.
Unfortunately, the first announcement
was during the corona.
I announced it at a live show.
What they did first was not to take
pictures.
They checked if it was in the trend.
They checked if their name was in the
trend.
Aren't you surprised?
I'm surprised.
Normally, I'd be happy to take a picture
when it's over.
I think it's the same for you, but we've
been doing it like that.
I'm surprised.
You were a scout, right?
Yes, I joined the team as a scout.
I joined in November 2009.
I joined in May the following year.
You joined in the middle of the year.
It's been 13 years since you joined the
team.
I've been doing it for 3 or 4 years.
Then you finally wanted to do 10.
The two of us who joined the other day
are 15 years old now.
10 times.
You were 15 years old at the time.
You were a very adult.
You were a senior in the first and
second year of high school.
You were an adult.
That's right.
I think there are many things.
It's very thoughtful.
I'm not going to stop.
I'm going to hold it down because I'm
alone.
I see.
I'm going to live without knowing it.
I'll eat the apple.
I'm a monster.
You're a monster.
You're a monster in many ways.
I'm hiding before the monster comes.
I'm going to secure it before the
monster comes.
This program is Ren-san.
Masa-san
Nanana-san
Osomekko-san
We sent it by the support of Hageon-san.
Thank you everyone!