How did you choose choreography?
Honestly, I've been thinking about
coming,
I never thought I would go to a dance
class or a voice lesson.
But when I passed the second grade, I
wanted to do it seriously.
I got used to being a trainee.
I felt the difference between me and
other trainees.
I cried a little while ago.
I was hated when I was in a dance class.
I was scared.
But I wanted to do it seriously.
I want to do my best to do it properly.
First of all, I want to entertain the
audience.
I want to be an idol who can face
forward with a sad face or a sad face.
I want to be an idol who can push my
back and hold my hands together and face
forward.
I want to be an idol who can be a good
singer.
I think that area is the best.
I think this area is the best.
Sometimes fish jump here.
I usually catch fish here.
But the river is too long to catch fish.
I found a fish.
I will definitely hunt this fish.
Isn't this cute?
I was very active when I was a child.
I love animals.
I like fish, insects, and birds.
I like to catch frogs and fish in the
river.
It's hot in summer, isn't it?
I like to put a fish on my face.
It's cold and feels good.
I like the cute eyes.
My friends always say I'm naughty.
My teacher also said I'm naughty.
I like to perform.
I was in a dance club in junior high
school.
I was often turned to the performance
side.
I enjoyed dancing there.
I liked it since I was a child.
I admired the profession of idol.
I was one of the members of the group.
I was a member who pushed back the
people who were in trouble.
I wanted to be a person who pushed back.
I took the audition.
I'm Shougen Jiyoko, 15 years old from
Hyogo.
I was doing karate.
I'm going to introduce you to Heian Go-
dan.
I'm Shougen Jiyoko, 24 years old.
I've never thought of joining an idol or
entertainment.
I was a little scared of what people
would think.
But I thought it would be better to
chase my dream.
I decided to do my best during the
training.
My father said I was a big girl.
I was happy.
My mother was worried about me.
She was worried about me.
But she congratulated me before I went
to bed.
My sister said she believed I could do
it.
I was happy.
If I had time, I'd like to go home.
My family plays musical instruments.
My father plays the piano.
My sister plays the cello.
My mother sings.
My father plays the violin.
We have a lot of fun eating together.
My family is close to me.
I'm sad that I can't see them often.
My family is always warm.
I'll do my best.
I like miso soup.
I'm worried about my mother.
Is it okay?
It's too early.
I'm worried about my mother.
Don't you have to put this on your lips?
It's slippery.
I'm worried about my mother.
My favorite song.
That's all there is.
My favorite song?
I'll do my best to play better.
I'm after moving.
Please listen.
I'm going to read a letter to my mother.
To my mother.
Thank you for always doing all the
housework.
When I fail, you comfort me.
When I'm having fun and happy, you're
happy with all my efforts.
Thank you.
When I do something wrong, you get
angry.
Thank you.
I'm really grateful.
I love hugging my mother.
Thank you for always holding me.
Thank you for supporting me with all
your might.
I was worried about how I would be seen
by the world, and I cried a lot.
But I was really happy.
Thank you for supporting me.
I'm glad I'm your mother.
Please watch me succeed as a member of
Kinotazaka46.
I love you.
Thank you for always doing this for me.
I'm glad I did it.
I've never seen you cry.
Thank you.
I did it.
I'm 15-year-old Shogun, Jiyoko.