Thank you for watching.
I'm Hyorin.
Can you tell?
I got my hair out today.
I'm sorry.
How is it?
I want to go to the bathroom.
Akita is cute.
Nice!
That was so perfect!
It's a bit dry, right?
I think it's good.
Let's go a bit further.
Hello!
So cute!
Thank you for watching!
Cute!
You're so cute!
I'm showing it to the members now.
Thank you for watching!
Is it too funny to sing Star?
I will become stronger!
Someday...
I will become a star!
I can't touch my cheeks. I have to touch
here.
It's being filmed.
I can't see anything.
Behind me.
Again?
I'm getting stuck.
When I'm filled in.
I'm starting to be in the best
condition.
It's so stable.
I don't know if I can sing.
I can see your chin.
I want to cross the time.
I can see it.
A or B.
That's it?
I'm a player who feels restricted.
I want to love this kind of stuff.
Green!
I don't do it much.
Thank you for watching!
I think you should cut it.
Cutting is not the problem.
I'm really fat.
Are you OK?
I can't cut it.
Where is it?
It's a normal room.
It's small.
There's a ceiling.
If it gets dark, I want you to put it in
front of your face.
It's not right.
It's here, right?
It's here.
It's different.
It's a little big.
I'm not lying.
Aim for the stars, starry starry
The future is in the night sky
Red team
Red
Cute
So cute
I can't
Cute
Thank you for your viewing.
My head is heavy.
Members try to sing together
Am I good?
Hahaha
Bye bye!
This was the worst fall, it was a
disaster!
Thank you!
Please continue to support us!
Please subscribe to our channel!
Hey, I want this to go on my shoulder
bag.
You feel pain åt?
I always think I should have this belt
on.
vou ve em glaze.
fits expertly on my shoulder!
I can't put it on one hand, so stop it.
I can't put it on.
What?
You can't put it on?
I can!
I can't put it on.
You can?
What?
A car accident?
Here we go.
Bye-bye.
A family?
Why are you here?
Yo-ko-san
Those two for sure
Ahh β
Then you will be special
why do you jump and catch up?
Because you can't catch up
You can't?
No, 1,2,3
Thank you, Hyari!
Go, go, go, go!
Romillyw
It's mean!
You are mimick 거의
done
Oh, there you go
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for watching!