Thank you for watching!
The first day of shooting
It's a rare angle.
Where are you today?
I came to Billboard.
I was a fool.
I quit.
I'm going to the Yume chain today.
I want to buy something right now.
I want to buy a photo album.
Let's wrap it up.
The reason why I want to buy from
Billboard is...
I think the pop under the product is
very characteristic.
You all introduce yourself at the live.
I think you've learned something from
pop.
I see.
So I went around the store and saw a
nice pop.
Finally, you wrote a pop of your own
introduction.
I see.
Let's go inside the store.
Let's go!
The first day of shooting
I want to buy it.
Gyo-don.
It's good for illustrations.
It's good to have only illustrations.
I want to buy something and go home.
It's cute.
It's a sauna.
It's a sauna boy.
Sauna girl.
I know this.
I want this.
Sauna girl.
Sauna girl of Doku.
I want this.
It's cute.
It says how to enter the sauna.
I see.
I'm shopping.
I'm having fun.
When I come to the villa, I can't walk.
This is delicious.
I know it's delicious.
I'm hungry.
It's a cute picture that's only been
recently.
It's really cute.
I bought one, but it's a waste.
What's this?
I want a good picture.
I'm opening it.
How much is the price today?
I don't draw a lot of pop.
Easy to understand.
Cute.
What should I do?
Mom.
What did Moe-chan draw?
I'm sure.
Moe-chan, where are you?
Where? Please look.
I'm doing it.
Here it comes.
I want to meet the staff who drew this.
It's a punishment for me.
It's good.
It's like a mirror.
It's like a product introduction.
I want a shark.
It's a shark.
What about the butt?
It's like a looper.
We have to see the pop.
Let's go see the pop.
This is pop, right?
It's like a looper.
I think this is Moni.
Good morning.
This is cute.
This is like, Can you start to push the
dog?
Something like that.
I think this is good too.
It's like a silent horse.
How is it?
Drawing a picture of Hina.
Like a horse.
The picture is really good.
This is cute.
It's like Mon-chan.
It's like Hina is watching while pushing
the dog.
It's good.
Look at this.
It's cute.
I don't know what's in it.
I don't know.
Who put it in?
It's scary.
It's cute how it's close.
It's cute.
Hina's face is like a head.
I think so.
If someone asks me what money is, I'll
answer that it's paper.
I think I know what it is.
It's easy to get it.
It's okay.
Look at this.
It's a doll.
A cup.
Amazing.
Right? Amazing.
It says self-introduction.
I drew a line.
I agree.
It's the same as school.
Yes.
But I failed.
Cute.
I drew a line.
All important.
It's good. It's funny but cute.
Miu.
I called you.
What?
It's simple but cool.
I said it's funny but cute.
You said it's funny but cute.
It's funny but cute.
I don't want it to be cute.
Thank you for watching.
It's amazing.
There are so many pop songs.
Waka-chan!
This is perfect for you.
It's funny.
You're good at it.
I'm the kind of person who says, go!
Yo!
Cool!
You can put it on like this.
I've been trying to be cute since I got
my hair dyed black.
I'm lucky.
I don't know what to do.
I laugh and fool around when I eat.
I'm going.
Good.
Good girl.
I'll make it a daikon.
I'm going to make it a daikon.
I think I should ask you.
I want you to ask me.
You think it's me?
It's a self-introduction pop.
The characteristic of pop is not a pop
that people who know it will see and
eat.
It's a pop that people who don't know
about the pop will see and eat.
I'll make it 30% off.
I agree.
It's a good deal.
I'll make it a good deal.
I'm going to make it a good deal.
I'll make it 5 million yen.
I want to buy it.
I'll make it 300 yen.
I understand.
It's a good deal.
I think I can sell it.
It's a pop-specialized job.
Welcome back.
I was looking for pop.
I found a pop that was interesting.
I've been around.
I found it.
I think I got it.
I'll go and...
I'll go and write pop.
Thank you.
Yay!
We have prepared a set of each pop.
Great!
Amazing!
It's amazing.
There are various sizes of the pop.
There are many.
It's cute.
I was able to explain earlier.
If you sell yourself as a product with a
pop that you introduce yourself,
I want you to write down the price.
I see.
Let's write down one by one.
I will use one.
Can I use it for nothing?
I'm going to fail from the beginning.
I'm going to use two.
Is it okay to use two?
I think it's good.
I want to use my own good point.
Stop it.
It's cute.
It's amazing.
I can work with it.
It's cute.
It's amazing.
Even if I had time in elementary school,
I didn't do it alone.
I was imitating others.
Do-ki-chan is so beautiful!
It's too early.
It's fun.
It's fun?
I don't know.
What was the number of the school?
What?
The number of the elementary school's
communication school.
Ego.
It's not Ego.
It's 2 or 3.
What about Magari?
Ego.
That's right.
I know.
I usually talk to my cat.
Why do you talk to your cat?
It's easy to talk to my cat.
I want you to try it.
If you hear something wrong,
you can hear it.
It sounds like a joke.
I have something to say.
Please try it.
I'm saying it with a lot of effort.
What are you doing?
It's terrible.
It's so funny.
It's a mess.
Your face is so wide.
I'm not trying to be funny.
I'm sorry.
I can see it, but he's making a great
countermeasure.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
I just found out.
Oh my god.
You're amazing.
Wow, it's like a gun.
It's like a gun.
Everyone is paying attention to him.
I'm sorry.
Can I see it?
It's not funny at all.
Read it.
What? Read it.
It's not cold.
All of them are official.
Everyone who passes here, please buy it.
I'll buy it.
I'll take a walk in the morning.
You'll take a walk at 4 a.m.?
I didn't ask you for half of it, but
I'll buy it.
I'm not sure if I'll buy it.
I'm not sure.
Anyway, that's right.
I understand.
I'll buy it.
I've heard it.
Yes.
I think it's better to do it at the end.
I agree.
I'll give you a half-time.
I understand.
This is my pop.
To you who are lonely.
I'll come to you for a thousand yen.
How about Yonawa to my best partner?
Good.
It's a story.
We talk a lot together.
It's like a human.
Why do you say that when you're in the
picture?
It's exciting.
It's like a gya.
It's a wonderful simple.
To you who are lonely.
It's better to talk.
I'll contact you right away.
It's not a joke.
I'm scared.
I'm scared of the dining message.
It's fun.
I'm drawing a face.
Did you draw it with your finger?
No.
I'm scared.
How about Yena?
2000 yen.
It's fun.
I'm curious.
It's good.
I'm a
cashier.
I'm a simple name.
I draw eyes.
I'm a
hat.
The price is infinite.
I'll pay you the money you think you can
pay me.
You're a god.
That's it.
It's over.
This is the most popular item in the
store.
It's like a guitar.
The price is
1030 yen.
It's my birthday.
I don't know the price if I write kanji.
I expect it from Hiragana.
I don't know the kanji.
I'm a little confused.
It's like a guitar.
I'm this.
I wrote a lot of names.
It's a guitar.
It's good.
It's a tibany guitar.
It's a guitar.
The price is
my birthday with Ryua.
It's cheap.
I want it.
I'm sorry.
I'll pay you back.
It's over.
I'm this.
It's cute.
I wanted to invite you in the text.
Hikarun is not here.
I thought what Hikarun would say.
It says,
I'm a god.
It's 0 yen.
It's good.
I'll steal it.
I'll take it.
It's like this.
It's cute.
The big one is
It's easy to understand.
It's like a gift.
As a senior.
I want you to buy it.
It's a little bit of a price.
It's 660 yen.
It's a number of bad things.
It's cute.
It's great.
Thank you.
It's the last one.
This is crazy.
The whole process.
I'll give you the whole process.
But since it's a billboard,
I thought it would be allowed to do
anything.
And I thought it would be better to
write something than my name.
I thought it would be better to write
something than my name.
I'll definitely go to the main event.
I'll definitely go.
Everyone's going to the festival.
I'm scared.
I think it will be there.
It's amazing.
It was fun.
This is a gift.
Really?
I'm just kidding.
Today, we learned how to introduce
ourselves from the billboard.
Thank you.
I'll go home after shopping.
I'll go home.
Thank you.