Next, we will do a 10 second challenge!
You will be given a time limit.
The person who can do it in 10 seconds
will be the winner!
This is hard.
I've seen this on TV.
I'm not confident.
I'm confident.
I'm glad.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm confident.
Let's get started.
I'm looking forward to it.
Let's start the challenge.
I can't see the time.
I'm wearing a mask.
I'll be the one who knows the time
later.
Please start the challenge at the right
timing.
Let's start!
Start!
I'm scared. I don't know what to do.
Please do it.
I'm nervous.
Let's start.
Ready, start!
Start!
I got it.
What?
I don't know.
Maybe this is right.
Next.
One.
Are you ready?
Yes.
I'll do my best.
I chose you.
You are making a serious face.
I wonder how it would be.
I think it was too early.
Everyone was late.
I wonder how it would be.
I will choose you.
Please give us your opinion.
I don't know.
I don't know what it is.
Please tell us when you are in the 10th
grade.
I don't know.
I can't get the feeling of the silver
button.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
I've never felt this time in my life.
Last one?
I'm tired of it.
I'm confident in my ability.
You said you were confident.
I'm not.
How about this?
I'm not confident.
I'm going to start.
I'm a little confused.
I think it's good.
What do you think?
The result is...
I will announce the result.
I don't know the answer at all.
Can I announce it?
Kanamin will announce it in order.
Please announce it.
Kanamin 10.90 seconds.
Wow!
I'm surprised.
Julia 7.9 seconds.
Wow!
Toka 9.65 seconds.
That's close.
Okaru 11.12 seconds.
Aki 12.79 seconds.
That's close.
Aki 11.10 seconds.
So, it's Hito-chan?
It's Hito-chan!
Yay!
Wow!
That was pretty slow.
Wow, you're so confident!
You're so slow!
I thought I was about to get the first
place.
I thought Aki-chan's vote was slow.
Aki-chan's was 12 seconds, so I was
about to get the first place.
No way! I was about the same as Aki-
chan.
I don't know.
You're so slow.
Yay!
You're so fast!
I was the first place when I did it
before.
I thought it was 30 minutes, but it was
15 minutes.
I'm confident.
So, the winner is Hito.
Yay!
The winner is...
Which one?
The last one is Julia.
It's Julia, right?
Isn't it Julia?
Isn't it?
2.1
2.76 is Aki.
Aki?
It's a little early, so I was wondering
if it was funny.
I thought J.A. was really fast.
I thought she was 6 or 7 seconds.
Let's move on to the next task.
Go!
The last task is...
How many times can you do a double jump?
Challenge!
I can do it.
Yes, you can do it.
That's all.
No more retry.
Let's go!
Rock, paper, scissors.
The winner is...
Okay.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Wow!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Oh!
It's the first one!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Oh!
You're the only one who can do it.
You're the only one.
Oh!
Then, I'll go to the last one.
Wait, wait, wait!
Oh!
Rock, paper, scissors!
I'm going to win.
I don't know the principle of double
jump.
I'm going to be the first.
I thought I would be the first.
I'll do it twice.
I'll jump a lot.
I think I'll spread my arms.
I'm scared.
I think it's better to hold your arms.
I'll hold my arms.
The second challenge.
I'll do it.
It's a challenge from Oharu.
I'll do my best.
I'll hold my arms.
I'll turn my wrist.
For now, I'll do it twice.
I'll do it twice.
Yes.
I don't know how to play this game.
I don't know the rules.
You are close.
The first one was close.
Let's play the last one.
The last one.
It's close!
I can't believe it!
You just said once, didn't you?
I didn't say it!
I thought you were going to cry.
I can't watch this episode.
Let's go to the next episode!
Let's start the challenge!
This is scary!
Let's go!
Amazing!
I won!
16!
Wow!
You're really good at jumping!
I had a hard time jumping.
I'm getting goosebumps.
Who is it?
Well...
It's a challenge!
Please!
Oh, it's soft.
Amazing.
You did it.
You have to catch it.
I'm so happy.
I'm going to do it.
Aki-chan, you can do it.
You can do it.
I want you to catch it.
Can you do it?
Okay.
It's Aki-chan's challenge.
Please do your best.
I got it!
You got it!
You got 12 questions right!
Wow!
You guys are amazing.
I'm so happy.
I got a question.
Okay, let's go!
Here we go!
The camera is moving.
You're so fast!
I'm tired.
Let's do one song.
The second song
OK?
I'll challenge you.
Go!
I did it!
It's been 12 times!
12 times!
It's been 12 times since we started
practicing.
It's been 12 times!
I thought I was going to win.
So, the rope skipping is over.
It's over.
The winner is the 16th person!
Yay!
You're strong!
I didn't expect to eat 16 times.
I'm happy.
I was jumping.
How was it?
Well, how was it?
It was close.
The speed of the rope was faster, right?
Yes.
A little more.
You can do it in a little while.
Thank you.
I think you can do it.
I'll do it until I can do the double
jump in the
double jump.
The winner is..
Hitomi!
Nice!
You guys are strong!
She is the best girl.
I thought it was impossible.
I couldn't do it at first.
I'm happy.
It's fun to move your body.
I want to do a one-wheel drive.
I can't do it.
I want to do it upside down.
I want to do it.
Let's do it if we have a chance.
That's all.
This was Tokimeki Mini Sports
Tournament.
Thank you very much.