I introduce songs and sing them myself.
That's it.
All of them are self-made GMA.
Yes.
I want to get involved in it.
I want to be influenced by rock music.
I have a SSD.
Really?
I'm not good at falling asleep.
I want to sleep and concentrate on it.
So...
Yakan and Idol
I'm Akatsuki, the cute one and only in
Stardust!
Today, I'm joined by my senior, Sakura
Nao!
She's the one who came to see me!
Hello everyone!
I'm the super-tall, strong-energy,
positive-exciting soul from Nagoya, Team
Shirt's
Dragon's Blue, Sakura Nao!
Nice to meet you!
I'm Sakura Nao!
This is the second time for Team S MODEL
REEF to meet Akimo-san.
Last year, you had a Christmas event.
Yes, I did.
With the Stellar Ball.
Yes, I did. I played the role of the big
shot of the Chachi in the Stellar Ball.
I don't usually do acoustic or cover
songs.
You're fashionable.
I'm a fashionable woman.
You're a mature woman.
In terms of numbers.
I did the acoustic version of the live
performance in the first half and the
second half was a lot of fun.
You're a double-part.
I did it in a live band, but in the
first half, I did it in a mature style.
I didn't wear a live costume.
In the second half, I did it in a lively
style.
You're a mature woman.
Yes, I am.
Isn't that a good thing for the
audience?
Yes, it is.
It's a good performance.
I was able to see two things, not just
the acoustic version.
You've been working on your career a lot
lately, and you've been thinking about
directing with the members.
Yes, I'm going to have them suggest the
base of the setlist and live costumes.
You're a mature woman.
Yes, I am.
I've decided to add ideas to that.
I dislike stopping at the A-Kart.
I do it every year, but recently I've
been doing it in Tokyo and Nagoya.
That's a long time ago.
But you're doing a radio show?
I did it in two parts.
One part was a live broadcast.
A regular show?
Yes.
I asked people to sing a song and I sang
a request song.
You introduced a song and sang it
yourself?
I did it all by myself.
You did it by yourself?
Yes.
You have more experience.
No, I don't.
I want to tell young people about that.
The way you show your skills is
different.
What do you like about Hide?
I liked Hide from X-Japan when I was in
high school.
I see.
I want to get involved in the rock
scene.
I have a similar image.
I see.
This program was brought to you by
Megumin,
Toshiro,
Inu,
Lisa,
and Sadaaki.
Today's breakfast was onigiri.
Bye bye!