Ebichu's videos
Today is the day of the album jacket
shooting
Jam jam
I'm a little nervous
I'm pretty nervous
I wasn't nervous in the car
I was very nervous when I came here
I was nervous in the car
I'm nervous
This is the first time I've been to a
fan meeting
And it's the first time
This is the first time
This is a huge event
Not only for the L2FAMILY
but also for other idols
There are many fans of other idols
I'm really nervous
I'll do my best
Let's finish
It's hard
One, two, three, four.
Ready, set, go!
One, two, three, four!
Swing!
I'm so excited!
Thank you for watching!
It's been a year since I've been to Art
Jam.
Today is the first stage for these
three.
And Aya-chan's turn.
We're all new students, so we want to do
our best with fresh feelings.
Thank you for your hard work.
We'll do our best!
Thank you for watching.
I'll pass the line, so open this way.
I did it!
The first step is over!
Thank you you guys!
Congrats!
Thank you so much!
It was fun.
I was happy.
How was the educational division?
I know that you are doing your best in
the lesson.
But I thought it was okay to have a
stage.
I thought it was good.
I was glad that I could do what I could
with the three of us.
Next time we will go together.
We will go together.
Including friends.
I want to go with you.
We were so close to each other.
I want to do it with you.
Chinese?
Chinese is the best.
How was it?
How was today's Matera?
Today's Matera is the most difficult.
Matera is the diamond.
Matera is the best.
Wait, you didn't do it in the beginning.
I didn't do it.
I didn't do it from now on.
Thank you for your support!
We were in a state of emergency right
after the live show ended.
I was a little confused because I didn't
know what to do.
But I was glad to see the faces of the
members after the live show ended.
I was glad to see the faces of the
It was a very fun stage.
I was able to have the same power as the
fans.
So I had a lot of fun today.
The first song was Lovely Smiley Baby.
The first song was the flower road.
When I walk on the flower road, I can
see the distance from the audience.
I was able to see the fans jumping and
singing a lot.
I hope you will see me improve.
I want to improve my singing and acting
skills.
I want to perform well.
I want to sing like myself.
I can't sleep.
I can't sleep because I'm tired.
I was very nervous.
When I introduced myself for the first
time, I was surprised by the fans who
were waving the siren.
I was worried that the green light
wouldn't be heard.
But it was very loud.
I was happy to see the fans.
I was nervous and I thought I would
succeed.
I practiced many times and succeeded.
There was a beret behind me.
I saw the faces of the members on the
monitor.
They looked completely different from
the usual faces.
I thought they were really cool.
They were both really cool.
When the seniors came, I thought they
were really cool.
The next live is in the middle of the
show.
I'm really looking forward to the middle
of the show.
I'm going to do my best next time.
I'll do my best.
I'll try to memorize the lyrics so that
I can sing well.
It was a moment.
I was nervous before the show began.
The first school performance was already
starting.
It was a moment of great fun.
I thought it was already over.
But there were a lot of fans.
The fans were cheering for me.
I was really excited.
I was able to feel the adrenaline and my
voice.
The teacher said that the rhythm was
fast.
I was praised for that.
I was surprised.
I drank water while taking a break from
the school performance.
My throat was dirty.
I started singing while lying down.
I was looking forward to the
performance.
It was a moment of great fun.
I will try to learn the lyrics and the
lyrics of the song.
I'm looking forward to the live
performance.
The live performance is just right for
the time being.
I think I can focus on the live
performance.