Yakan and idol
The next one is the third one, sauna
I'm still a beginner, but I've been into
sauna since summer
I used to like salt sauna
I put salt on my body and I'm in this
warm space
Then the salt melts and my skin becomes
very smooth
I'm into it, but I just put it in and
let it flow
I wanted to try sauna, but it was very
hot and I was sweating
I thought I could take a bath in the
water
It was a wet bath at that time
It was a wet bath at first
I was nervous
I wanted to try it from a wet bath, but
it was my first time
You did it
I felt like I could fly
I was very happy
I went to sauna by myself
I went to sauna three or four times a
week
You have a
I have a
I haven't been to the sauna so much
I want to have a sauna with you
I want you to teach me a lot
I want to go to the bath
I was cold at first, but I was told that
I was okay
Who told you the sauna?
My fans
I heard that the entertainer in Fukuoka
liked the sauna
I heard that it was okay to take a bath
in the water
I wanted to try it
I was cold at first, but I was sweating
I felt one-sided
I fell in love with the sauna
I go to sauna three times a week
I think
I will prepare it
Do you go to the sauna at night?
I like the sauna