Ebitune's videos
Kobayashi-O Championship!
There's only one person!
I'm the only one!
I didn't get any applications.
I wanted to do it.
Everyone's here after this.
Thank you for being with me.
Thank you.
Kobayashi-O.
I'll do my best. I'll win the first
I'll do my best.
First one.
What have you been doing lately?
I'm going to win the first Kobayashi-O.
I wonder what it is.
Kaho-chan, what are you doing?
Kaho-chan, is that a hint?
It's okay.
Is it too early?
I'm not kind at all.
Are you doing it at home?
Yes.
I'm stuck.
I'm doing it on top of it.
I think that's all I can do.
I wonder what it is. I roll on the
floor.
Oh, I see.
The answer is something like a team lab.
What is it?
Something like a team lab?
I turned off all the lights in the room.
There's a speaker with a lot of light on
it.
There's a shining one, right?
I put it on in a dark state.
There's only one.
I turn it on, play music, and watch it.
Isn't it chill?
It's a trendy chill.
What's chill?
Relaxing.
I've been doing it alone lately.
Oh, that's cool.
I'm a little bit of a drag.
I thought it would be nice to change my
mood.
It was a team lab.
Next question is this.
When you were in the second grade of
elementary school, who was the comedian
you often imitated?
When I was in the second grade of
elementary school?
It was around 2008.
It was Ebichu's time.
It was popular.
I did it at that time.
Can you stop saying that this is a
generation gap?
It's amazing.
You were imitating Ebichu.
It was in the 8th grade.
I was in the agency for 8 years.
It was 9 years ago.
I did a lesson.
I danced for the first time.
So, the ones that were popular at that
time were Sumiko Nishioka and other
entertainers.
Oh.
I think so.
Enta no Kami-sama.
Desuyo.
I feel like that.
What is it?
What do you choose?
Kaho-chan.
What?
Can I answer?
I don't know the answer.
Can you answer?
The answer is Desuyo.
The answer is Inoki from Antokino.
Why?
When I watch the home video, I see Inoki
from Antokino, and I see Inoki from
Antokino as a shop assistant.
I was doing this video every time I saw
Inoki from Antokino.
Thank you for watching.
The next question is this.
What was the first CD you bought
yourself?
Thank you.
It's a service question.
How many times have you said this?
I want to answer it right away.
Are you sure?
Rika Mayayama's LIAR MASK.
Correct!
I'm glad.
I got a poster because I got the points.
I'm really grateful.
I gave you a sample.
But the CD shop clerk didn't notice.
I was a member.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know that, but I took it with
me.
Thank you.
I'm the happiest person in the world.
I'm really happy.
I'm glad I bought someone's first CD.
I didn't think so.
I'm glad I bought it myself.
Thank you.
I was the only one who came to the game.
I see. It's a service.
Thank you.
It was LIAR MASK.
I'm sure the fans would have known this.
1.5 points.
Thank you.
The next question is Aichiro.
Ta-da!
What made me the happiest?
What made you the happiest?
I asked Santa for a gift.
I was especially happy.
What is it?
Santa?
I've never heard of a story about what
Kobayashi got.
What is it?
I think I got this when I was in
elementary school.
When you were in the first or second
grade?
I see.
I think Santa gives me something trendy.
He said he wanted something.
I wonder what was popular when you were
in elementary school.
I think the fashion witch Love & Berry
was popular.
It was popular.
It's a set that has a lot of cards like
a starter kit.
It's a set that makes you stronger.
Boooo!
The answer is a one-wheeled car.
Thank you for watching!
I got a DS cassette when I was a first
grader.
It was close!
I got the same thing when I was in
elementary school.
It was close!
I got a first-class car.
I was happy because the gift was big.
I'm happy to get it every year.
I'm happy to get a gift, but I'm happy
to get a gift that's big.
I practiced with a first-class car and
went to my friend's house.
It's a little embarrassing, but I went
to my friend's house with a first-class
car.
It was a wonderful and cute first-class
The next question is this.
What is your hobby and specialty that
you have on Wikipedia?
Wikipedia!
What's on your Wikipedia?
It's an official profile.
That's right.
I got an official profile.
What is your hobby and specialty?
I'm not good at anything right now.
You were in junior high school, right?
You were in the first grade of junior
high school, right?
There are two.
There are two?
Yes.
Well, then.
I just entered the field club in the
first grade of junior high school.
I just ran.
And one more thing.
Imitation!
The correct answer is a baton and a
piano.
That's not true at all.
You don't have an image, do you?
No.
I joined the agency in the sixth grade,
but I was almost in the eleventh grade.
I was in a baton club in the elementary
school club activity.
I played the piano from elementary
school to sixth grade.
I could play it.
I didn't have the ability to write, so I
just wrote it.
As a result of writing, I thought there
was no one in the baton club.
Riko was in the real baton club.
Baton touring.
I was playing a real baton, so I thought
I shouldn't go home.
It's not a specialty.
It's not a specialty, so please delete
it from Wikipedia.
It's a robot.
I think I can play the piano as a hobby
now.
I think I can play it as a hobby.
If it's a hobby, I think I can play it.
If it's a specialty, it's a little hard.
It's like a project that can't be done
properly.
I wrote it as a hobby.
I did something stupid.
I asked the producer if I could play the
piano.
I don't want to play it.
I saw it on TV.
There's a piano in the entertainment
world.
I saw it on TV.
I was told like that.
I can't play it.
I was surprised because I got a call.
I was going to recruit you right away.
I can't play it.
I'm fine.
The next question is here.
What club did you join when you were in
junior high school?
There was a club.
There were two clubs that were hotly
welcomed by the teacher.
There are two clubs.
Then you answer two.
That's right.
Kaho was tall since we met.
She was tall, so she was sweating.
So I was sweating a lot.
What is the serious thing that is often
said by the teacher?
This is not it.
Which one is it?
The answer is...
I was worried about it, but I was
worried about it.
I answered both of them.
Jobare is correct!
Jobare and Kendo club.
Kendo club?
The reason I entered the club was
because I wanted to get faster.
I entered the club for about a month and
I didn't meet the club.
I joined the club.
It was a club for martial arts.
It was a club for volleyball and Kendo
club.
I'm glad I got one right.
Only one question.
The next question is this.
What was the first drink you drank at
Kaho sake?
This was before Maya came.
Before I came?
It may be a little difficult.
I asked what you drank.
I drank shake and umeshu.
Did I say umeshu?
Recently, umeshu has become drinkable.
It's a store signboard menu, so shake.
Correct!
I was surprised when I heard the first
drink.
I remember.
It was the first drink.
The last question.
What do you want to do?
It's a simple question.
I want to do something with a project.
What is it?
I wonder.
Maybe in my head.
You haven't told anyone?
It's very difficult.
Hint?
Hint other than the project?
Hint is...
I do it with various YouTubers.
I want to ask you to do it.
I see.
I can't think of anything.
It's difficult.
It's definitely difficult.
I feel it.
Recently,
I have the image of cooking.
Kaho.
I think it's a cooking project.
When I do a cooking project on YouTube,
I eat a lot.
I'm not.
The correct answer is...
I want to do a quiz.
I think.
You did it.
Yes.
I did it on Instagram.
I did it in the question box.
But...
I didn't tell anyone.
I tried it.
It was difficult.
I see.
I want to do it.
I think so.
The correct answer is...
I'm here to ask you about your troubles.
Yay!
I'm Rika Noyama, who is having troubles
in her middle school.
Nice to meet you.
What troubles do you have recently?
I'm addicted to Don Quijote.
There are many products, and they are
all in different categories.
I don't need them anymore.
I don't need lipsticks anymore.
I don't want to buy them for nothing.
How can I not waste them?
Don Quijote is a sloth.
I buy them.
You buy them, right?
I enjoy buying them.
I'm interested in many things.
Mega Don Quijote is amazing.
But...
Please think that it's a hassle to put
out your wallet.
I see.
I thought I'd buy this.
I line up my wallet.
But when I saw a customer who had a long
wallet,
I thought it was a hassle to put out my
wallet.
Really?
Is that true?
Yes, it happens often.
You thought you'd buy it, but you
didn't.
You don't go out anymore.
I thought it was a hassle to put out my
wallet.
I see.
Thank you.
By the way, cashless.
It's a new era.
You can pay with your cell phone.
What would you do if you were cashless?
Cashless doesn't work.
Are you sure?
You can't pay cashless.
So I would use a very thick,
a very thick wallet.
I'd put it in a place that takes a lot
of time.
When I go shopping.
If I have to go through many trials to
get it out,
You put it in a place where you can
easily take it with your cell phone,
right?
And I don't want to put it out.
I see.
If you don't want to put out your wallet
and cell phone,
I think you'll be less likely to use it.
I see.
If you're worried, I'll be here.
I'm not sure if I'm here.
I'll be in trouble if I edit it.
If you go to Instagram,
I'll ask Kobayashi for advice.
I'm on Twitter.
I'll ask for advice on Twitter.
I'll ask Kobayashi to send it to me.
Next time, I'll ask Kobayashi for
advice.
That's great.
Please hold it.
Anything is fine.
Like now.
I'd like to have a serious conversation.
I see.
Somewhere.
Open home.
Twitter, Instagram, YouTube, etc.
The link is in the summary section.
You're making a link?
On purpose?
In the comments section.
I'd like you to write it.
Yes.
Bye.
That's great.
It's simple.