Ebichu's videos!
Next week is the university game
festival!
Ebichu shopping!
What song is it?
Original song!
So, next week is the university game
festival.
I think it will reach everyone.
I was focused on this.
I would like to introduce Ebichu goods
this time!
First of all, Ebichu's color list band!
Each member of the nine of us,
And from the family,
From the
family,
All of them are colorful and cute.
It's a very comfortable band.
But Mayan, this is expensive, right?
This is 900 yen!
I got 1000 yen!
Wait, I have to buy something cheap.
It's too expensive.
We are too expensive.
It's a cute list band, so please take a
look.
Next, I will introduce this!
This is a push-push set!
This is a pen light.
You can put it in the pen light.
And you can use it as a white light.
You can change the light and use it.
You can change it with only one set.
You can also buy other push-push books.
You can use it for Christmas.
It's cute.
It's very shiny.
And this is a key holder.
This key holder has a different design
for each member.
Each member has their own personality.
Each member has their own birth year.
It's a very special key holder.
I show this to my friends on the 20th of
March.
This is a very special key holder.
And this is a key holder that can be
used to hang the pen light from the
neck.
You can hang the pen light and the key
holder.
You can use this set to hang the pen
light.
You can put this in the pen light and
put the key holder on it.
It's amazing.
This is amazing.
It's a happy set.
It's a lucky set.
Please try to get it.
And then,
This is the AirPods case and AirPods
Pro.
We also have AirPods case.
This is the case.
The design is futuristic.
It's cool.
This design was chosen by all the
members of the Ebi-Chu group.
This is the design.
It's a different design from us.
This is the case of the Ebi-Chu group.
Please try to get it.
And then,
Isn't that easy?
I don't have that every time.
I agree.
I don't have that title.
Of course, there are people who notice.
First of all, this is it.
This is the 2021 University Gekkae
Muffler towel.
There is definitely a towel.
The fabric is good.
It's wonderful.
It's fluffy.
It's a good fabric.
It's smooth.
It's a very good fabric and fashionable.
It's a design with a reboot logo.
The T-shirt I'm wearing next to it is
also a reboot.
Please decide the design in a
fashionable way.
This is 1800 yen.
And there is one more thing I want to
show you.
This is what I can't miss when I go to
the event.
2021 University Gekkae Penlight.
It was a paper, but 2021 University
Gekkae Penlight.
Penlight.
This is also a reboot pattern.
And this is also a reboot pattern.
I think I can use it for this.
This is the same as the Ebi-Chu series.
This is not a reboot.
This is a channel that only tells the
truth.
You don't have to say anything.
It's written in the reboot-like design.
It's wrapped in box color.
You can use it as a push-set.
You can also change it to this.
If you have this one, you can customize
it randomly.
This is 3,500 yen.
It is a must for idol live.
And this is the last one.
It's a hoodie.
It's been online since the 27th.
If you couldn't get it on the first day,
please get it.
It's a earphone lion.
This is the color.
There is a member color plus blue.
I hope you can get this in 2021.
See you at the venue.
If you can't get it, please get it.
I will be happy if you get it.
Please support us.
The next day.
I'm nervous because it's the university
concert on the next day.
I practiced hard for the choreography.
I will do my best to make the final
adjustment in two days.
I will do my best to make the audience
smile.
I'm looking forward to the 4th.
I'm nervous about the 6th.
I'm a little nervous.
I have few days left.
I have no time to practice.
I have a few days left.
I will check the rest.
I'll do what I can to relax my throat
and get some physical strength.
But I'll rest and do my best.
I'm nervous and looking forward to the
6th.
The next day is the university limit.
It's the first time for the new members
to go to the university limit.
I'm really nervous now.
Of course, I'm looking forward to it,
but it's my first time on stage.
I'm worried about whether I can do it
because it's my first time as a 9-member
unit.
I'll do my best to make sure that I can
succeed for the first two days.
The important thing is 4 to 6.
I'm looking forward to 4 and I'm 60%
nervous.
I'm nervous and I'm looking forward to
it.
I'll do my best to make you think it was
the best after it's over.