Ebi-chu's video
I've been working in Ebi-chu for about 7
or 8 years.
My favorite food is gyoza.
I've been calling it my favorite food.
Recently, I've been thinking that I like
gyoza too.
I've got something new.
I thought I'd make a new video.
I thought so.
I have to make a video soon.
I can't be filmed in this place.
I'll destroy it.
Ebi-chu gyoza on kippe-sen
I'm number 51, Kobayashi Kaho.
I'm number 55, Kazami Nanaka.
I like gyoza.
I'm number 51, Kobayashi Kaho.
What gyoza do you like the most?
I like grilled gyoza the most.
Do you like cabbage or Chinese cabbage?
I like Chinese cabbage.
In spring, I like Chinese cabbage.
I'll tell you one thing.
I like gyoza.
Do you have any special recipe?
I've been to a restaurant before.
There is a restaurant called Aogen in
Utsunamiya.
I was surprised that the sauce there was
so unusual.
I always eat a little.
The sauce is miso sauce with green
onions.
I ate the sauce in the restaurant.
I ate it at home.
It was very delicious.
I wanted to buy it at home.
I was looking for it.
It's very delicious.
From now on,
I will crush the rice.
What?
I can't be a bad person.
Do you remember?
I remember.
I'm hungry.
I'm planning to eat.
I'm really hungry.
I will eat GYOZA.
Let's go.
I prepared three GYOZAs.
This is OISHIWA.
This is OSAKA OISHIWA.
This is AJI-NO-MOTO.
I will eat.
I ate lunch.
It's delicious.
It's a lot.
I'm eating OSHIWA GYOZA.
It's delicious.
I don't remember when I ate this at a
restaurant.
It's good!
The second one is...
This is a big one.
That's right.
It's good.
Compared to the first one, it's soft and
smooth.
I don't remember this.
The third one is...
Let's eat.
It tastes different when I eat it like
this.
What is this?
It's good.
I don't remember when I ate this.
I remember when I ate it twice and
tasted it.
I don't remember when I ate it.
I ate it.
I'll show you the second one.
I'll show you the third one.
I'll show you the fourth one.
I'll show you the fifth one.
I'll show you the sixth one.
This is a great match.
It's like rice.
It's sweet.
I'm full.
When you ate it, you couldn't eat the
rest.
I'm eating a lot.
I ate a lot.
I'm eating rice.
This is the most delicious dumpling.
It's similar to the dumplings in Japan.
It's delicious.
I'm full.
This is the last dumpling.
I will eat this.
Please look forward to the next.
Oh, cat's tongue.
Wow, it's delicious.
So, did you remember the taste?
I remember.
I was holding my tongue and my tongue
was itchy.
I was about to get a cold.
So, let's eat.
Let's eat.
Which gyoza will come out?
I can't eat this.
So, we ate all the gyoza.
I will eat gyoza from now on.
I will eat gyoza with my hands.
Thank you.
Let's eat.
I don't know what it looks like.
It's delicious.
Let's eat gyoza from the A gyoza.
Are you ready?
I don't know what it tastes like.
Kobayashi, what does it taste like?
Kazami, what does it taste like?
I don't know.
Let's eat.
I will eat gyoza.
I don't know what it tastes like.
I decided.
I will eat.
What is the gyoza?
It's a king gyoza.
I think it's okay.
I will eat gyoza from the C gyoza.
It's delicious.
It's sweet.
I don't know what it tastes like.
It wasn't there.
I don't know.
The true dumpling is...
Hidaka-ya!
I thought it was a 500 yen shop.
I thought so too.
The decoration is Hidaka-ya.
It's sweet.
I've never heard of it.
Next, let's go to D's dumpling.
It's a 500 yen shop.
Wait!
Where is it?
It might be in the middle.
I thought so too.
D's dumpling is...
Oshio!
I'm Oshio.
It's a parallel.
That's Oshio.
I think so.
B is Oshio.
I'll eat Aishinomoto.
If you make a mistake, what did you eat?
I wonder what you ate for 21 years.
Next, let's go to D's dumpling.
This is...
I think it's parallel.
What's the basic of E?
Manshu!
This is...
It's a shape.
Next, let's go to D's dumpling.
Let's go to D's dumpling.
Wait!
It's a parallel.
D's dumpling is...
Kouraku!
Kouraku is in the middle.
Kazami is in the middle.
I thought I changed the song.
I'll eat this.
I'll change the song again.
I'll eat this again.
I'm sorry.
I've heard it on the second floor.
I changed the B Osaka
to F Hidakaya.
Wait!
I changed it to F Hidakaya.
I changed B and F.
Can I change it too?
I changed A and D.
A is Ajinomoto,
D is Osaka Oshou.
I announced the results!
I'm so excited.
First, I'll choose A.
I won!
I will make a request from my mother's
gyoza.
I want to make a request.
I made a request for gyoza this time.
I don't need gyoza in shrimp.
I want to make a request for shrimp
gyoza.
I want to make a request.
I want to make a request for shrimp
gyoza.
I want to eat delicious gyoza with you.
I want to make a request.