This week's shrimp chutas is shrimp
chutas shrimp
Everyone, here I will challenge shrimp
fishing
This is the first time for the same
family to participate in the shrimp
fishing challenge
It's not shrimp!
It's shima-aji
And the third battle with shrimp dishes
The battle is more intense than you
think
So, this week's shrimp show starts again
I want to be the one to make you happy
I want to be the best of both worlds
Add a lot of things to your private
Ebisu junior high school!
Ebisu Jattatsu!
This program is brought to you by these
sponsors.
Everyone, let's put the saury together.
Start shrimp fishing!
Last week, they put shrimp in shrimp.
They will challenge to catch a shrimp.
I got a bite!
It's too fast!
It's not a shrimp!
It's a shima-aji!
They caught a shima-aji in 15 seconds
What will happen this week?
Shrimp Chuu plus Shrimp Fishing is?
What kind of fish is there?
There are many fish.
I'm surprised because they come
suddenly.
Everyone, check if the fish is caught
properly.
I haven't caught it yet.
Yasumoto is coming.
He is pulling a lot.
Yasumoto, do your best.
Do your best.
What is this?
This is also a shima-aji.
Yasumoto is a woman loved by shima-aji.
Yasumoto got a second shima-aji today.
Is there really a shrimp?
I'm coming.
Wait a minute.
I want to eat kashi-yaki.
I'm sorry, Yasumoto.
I'm sorry.
He caught it.
I caught a shrimp.
Where is the shrimp?
I caught it.
You are great.
I didn't catch anything but suddenly it
came.
Something came.
The sound is playing.
Who is it?
I caught a shrimp.
Wait a minute.
I'm not that kind of person.
I'm busy.
Wait a minute.
Eri-chuu plus Eri-tsuri is...
I'm busy.
The scene is panicked.
Wait a minute.
I'm taking you to the river.
Let me introduce the fish.
I will introduce the fish.
Ise shrimp appeared.
This is Ebi Amigo, a local character in
Onjuku, Chiba Prefecture.
This is Ebi Amigo.
I caught a little fish, so Ebi Amigo
came.
Thank you.
If no one caught a fish, did you come?
If no one caught a fish, I waited in the
back and went home.
That's cute.
That's not true.
I'm glad you caught a fish today.
I don't talk.
I caught a little fish.
It's time to bless Ebi Amigo.
Ebi Amigo will give me a gift.
Please.
Congratulations.
Let's go to the shrimp.
Let's go.
Excuse me, can you make a bridge here?
It's hard to pass by.
Last week, Kaiki Odata appeared in a
shrimp costume.
Thank you for waiting.
She also participated in shrimp fishing.
Did you catch it?
Do you have anything to say?
The rod is bent.
Please give it to me.
Please wait a moment.
Is this shrimp?
It's probably the earth.
Is the earth stuck on the ground?
That's right.
What is this?
I'm not going to fall.
I'll fall and wait.
Please enjoy the beautiful scenery of
Ebi Amigo's hometown Honjuku-machi while
you are picking up the
Naka-yama is very angry.
I got it.
Thank you very much.
Congratulations on getting a lobster.
Naka-yama got a lobster in the last 5
minutes.
Naka-yama is dancing with Naka-yama.
Then, again...
Wow, amazing.
Fish again!
Yatsumoto, amazing.
What is that?
It's Shima-Aji again.
Shima-Aji again.
30 seconds left.
Someone, do a miracle.
I want to do a shrimp dance.
It's coming again.
You're kidding, right?
Oh no, it escaped.
It's gone.
It escaped, but it's OK.
It was a fish anyway.
The time limit is closing.
10, 9, oh!
The mat came, the mat came.
It's a miracle.
It's great.
It's from 10 seconds ago.
It's great if it can catch this.
The fishing line is good.
I see.
It just got caught on the ground.
It's a miracle.
It's over.
So, the shrimp fishing is one of the
Koshina and one of the Nakayama.
It doesn't matter, but Yasumoto caught
three Shima-Aji.
Everyone, let's try fishing.
What's wrong with the microphone?
The microphone is the shrimp fishing.
How was everyone fishing?
It was fun.
Two people caught shrimp.
Everyone, do you want to eat this?
I want to eat.
Let's move to eat.
Let's eat the shrimp and Shima-Aji.
Let's move.
After this, they will try to catch the
delicious shrimp and have a fierce
shrimp fishing competition.
And, the latest information of Sakura
Shrimp.
Two beautiful shrimp are fishing and
caught three shrimp.
Who came to ask for shrimp dishes?
Here they come.
It's a big fish.
Wow, amazing.
It sounds like a big fish.
We are fishing.
It's a big fish.
They came.
Yeah.
It's a big fish.
What about the shrimp?
That's right.
I caught it.
There is no shrimp here, right?
Well, not everyone can eat it.
What?
Why?
From now on, we will be divided into two
teams and have a game.
Is that so?
Yes.
So, the shrimp team members, shrimp
friends, and shrimp rock will compete
for shrimp dishes.
Let's divide the teams immediately.
Yes.
Is it a lottery?
Yes, it's a lottery.
This time, it's a lottery.
Everyone, please pick one you like.
No.
There is no one who will be the first to
pick, right?
No.
There is no one who will be the first to
pick, right?
Then, I will pick this one.
There is some left.
I will pick this one.
Good.
Ready, set, go.
Oh, oh, oh.
You picked it all at once.
Why?
The result of the lottery is the team of
the shrimp rock.
And the shrimp rock team is the members
you are looking at.
The first battle is the battle of the
Narmasa Corona.
The Narmasa Corona is Chue-san.
I will judge.
The one who gets closer to Chue and
touches first wins.
Yes.
Please get ready.
Shrimp dish 3rd battle.
The first battle is the Narmasa Corona.
The Narmasa Corona battle.
Ready.
Start.
It's out.
Daruma-san is out.
Out.
Mayama is out.
Look at the power of Ebi-Ryami-Go-kun.
Daruma-san is out.
No, no, no.
You were a bit late.
Both of you are out.
Start line?
Mayama, you too.
Hoshida, you too.
If you turn around, you have to stop.
Ready, go!
Daruma-san is out!
Nakayama is out!
The first round is the winner of the Ebi
Amigo team!
The winner is Nakayama!
Why did you do that?
Shut up!
I don't like your dance
I don't like it
I saw Taiki's face and he danced
seriously
Please stop dancing
The first round was won by the team of
Ebi Amigo
They are one step closer to the shrimp
dish
Next is the battle between the two teams
The challenge is to tell the other
members the topic of the show by just
gestures
The time limit is 1 minute
Of course, you can't speak
The third challenge is the gesture
battle
The gesture game is the first team
The time limit is 1 minute
Ready, start
Sky tree
That's fast
Correct
Good
Switch
Correct
Pineapple
Nice pace
30 seconds passed
I don't know the difference between the
two
Wait a minute
Wait
No
30 seconds passed
Go home
Correct
10 seconds passed
Go home
3 2 1
Time's up!
I didn't know this was the last one
A turtle?
Yes, a turtle
I'm curious about the next one
What is it?
This is hard
By the way, how did you do it if you
were Kaiki?
How did you do the Pashiwagi?
I don't know
Team Ebi Rock, 8 questions correct
Next is the high school Ebi Amigo team
Ebi Amigo is not popular, so Chue-san
will go around
I'm a black kid, it's okay
Let's start
You have 1 minute
Ready, start
Um, pokeball
No, no
Pass it to Tanigawa
columns
that's correct
Who's my grand mother?
Öscu playing?
Trumpets
Hurry up
that's correct
Thirty seconds gone
I'm zero
Really? Ten out of ten?
Forty seconds gone
Three seconds
Five seconds left
No, no!
It's over!
The Ebi Amigo team is the 4-Way World
So the winner is the Ebi Rock team!
Now, the Ebi Rock team
The Ebi Rock team won the second round
Now, the victory is ours!
The final battle is coming up!
Team Taiko vs Team Ebi-Chu, the winner
is Team Rinoe!
I did it! I did it!
Shut up, Pyonpyon!
This is a relay battle!
Amigo can run?
I'm curious about Amigo. Can Amigo run?
Amigo, try running!
It was fast!
Good luck, Amigo!
By the way, can Ebi-Rok run?
Of course!
Ebi-Rok is a normal person.
Hoshina, stop it!
She's not a normal person.
She's Ebi-Rok.
By the way, who is the fastest in this
team?
Kawa-chan.
Kobayashi?
He's a junior high school student.
Everyone is a junior high school
student.
That's right.
How about Kashiwagi?
I'm nervous.
Kashiwagi and Hirota are the slow group.
It looks fast, Choco Maca.
I'm fast at running, but I'm not good at
riding a bike.
Don't talk.
I'm serious.
I'm serious, too.
We were talking about how fast we were.
Don't be serious.
You don't have to be serious.
What's the order?
This one.
Hoshina, you're first.
Two, three, four, five.
Why is it in this order?
Mirei is really fast.
Rika is fast, too.
I'm in the middle.
I'm slow.
The relay race is in this order.
The anchor race is a battle between the
characters of each team.
Let's start!
Chuu-san, look at this.
This is not the attitude of an idol.
This is the attitude of an athlete.
I thought it was like this.
I didn't know you would do this kind of
style.
This is a serious style.
Let's start!
Get into position!
Ready? Go!
Sphinx!
No, no, no, wait a minute!
My stupidity will be shown.
The stupidity of the first generation
will be shown.
Let's do the Sphinx once.
Let's do it once.
Let's start.
Get into position.
Ready? Sphinx!
Why?
Sphinx is not ready yet.
In the end, Sphinx is not decided.
Ready??
I'm sure you can't race alone.
The subject of the video is bad but
please do not worry.
Sphinx, don't Aidio She's fast Integra.
Who is hard Although it is aé
Fast
But
Masumoto is fast
Riria
Riria is fast
Riria go go
Go
Riria
Ebichu No.2 Kobayashi
Fast
She is fast
Now Anzu
Haya is fast too
She is quite behind
Go go
Go
Fast
Ebi Ebi is fast
Amazing
She is really fast
The winner is
Ebi Amigo team
I'm frustrated
Ebi Rock
He was like, are you serious?
How was it?
You lost
I'm frustrated
It's not as fast as you thought
Well
These shoes are quite
Heavy
Kaiki
I'll say it again
Don't say normal things
Ebi Amigo
They did a great job
These 4 people got the prize
They got the food
The winner will get the prize
Now we will start with the shrimp and
shimaji
Please start
Wait
Please
Wow
Looks delicious
This is the one
It's really delicious
I'm hungry
The one who made shrimp dishes is
Chinese restaurant in Tomisato City,
Chiba Prefecture
Emsu Style
Eat the delicious shrimp dishes
These are the two shrimps we caught
earlier
You can make this much with two shrimps?
And in the middle is the fried shrimp
Is this what you did?
Yes, this is my effort
You added shrimps to the dish
Thank you for the meal
she can't cook, she return the fish
balls
there is no need to cannons
end sent
Thank you for the food.
I want to be discriminated by the dog
I'm not going to go
I'm going to be scolded
Hey, Nakayama
Let's go home and eat
It's delicious
Well, please
Delicious?
It's delicious
It's noisy when you eat
The best
How about Hoshina?
The meat is amazing
It's delicious
It's fresh
I'm going to eat shrimp
What are you doing behind?
Me too
Don't argue with reality
I will
I ate delicious shrimp before
So what?
I got a delicious gag
Delicious gag?
What is delicious?
Shrimp
How was it?
Surprised
Shrimp and shrimp
Thank you for the delicious shrimp
itarianism
Yes yes cow
Hypertension I'm going to say something
delicious
That's why birthday
explodes
It was a letter that got many secretік
product from ebi
Apps
In January, the recruitment of the
research group was announced.
The name is also Sakura Ebis.
The audition is already held in various
parts of the country.
Finally, the final screening. The camera
enters the venue.
The final screening is a camera test.
About 10,000 applicants were selected,
and 38 were selected.
How many people will pass the exam?
Let's ask the principal of Fujii High
School, the private Ebisu Middle School
I will announce the exam in June
Announcement in June
Sakura Ebis's big announcement, please
look forward to it
Ebichu Tastas has started
Next time on Ebichu Tastas
A big invasion of mysterious theme park
What will they add to the next episode
of Emi-Chu?
Please look forward to it!
This program was brought to you by the
sponsors you see.
It's the Wonderland of dreams.
Yes, the Wonderland of dreams.
That's right.
I want to go in!
Bye bye!