Are you having fun?
Are you confident?
You won't win!
We got the win!
We are the goddesses!
I think Coco is not in the team.
That's right.
Actually, I'm sorry.
I heard you can talk about anything.
I wonder why Coco is not in the team.
Coco is not in the team.
It's embarrassing, but I was trembling
at the thought of facing you
Everything
What should we listen to?
I'm so excited.
Oh, that one.
Did you watch the audition?
I did.
Did you?
The audition? The one with PPG.
Nice to meet you. We are...
Enjoy Play! We are the playboys! Young
Play Let's!
Nice to meet you!
Young Play Let's
I was a member of Paradise.
I loved Paradise, but I was also a fan
of Young Play Let's.
I see.
I was in the audition with Wag.
Mayuta came in and Tsuki went to Wag.
The atmosphere changed quite a bit.
Non passed, and I worked hard on
Paradise.
Thank you for watching.
I see. I think everyone knows when
Naruha was on leave.
I'd like to hear about that time.
I was on leave because I was going to
focus on my studies.
Did you have a boyfriend?
No
You were in a relationship after
Kyosuke's death, right?
Yes
How long did you date Ryuta?
What?
I think it was in the episode of Aoi
Haruhi
After the broadcast day of Aoi Haruhi, I
was in a relationship with Ryuta
And then I went out to Kyosuke again and
got my second boyfriend
Why didn't you make a boyfriend for the
second time?
I couldn't make a boyfriend
You went back to your normal life
You can't make a boyfriend in that?
I can't
Did you confess?
No, I didn't
Why?
That's strange
Are you interested in that story?
I'm curious
Because I don't know anyone
And I'm back a little more mature
But I'm really not popular
Why?
Why do you think that is?
Students like young people
I'm a hot-tempered person
No one cares about me
I understand
So you don't date during the break?
Then, do you kiss?
No
Who do you kiss?
During the cultural festival
I'm a little bit
Suddenly
How important is love in Narwha?
Love?
Of course, the most important thing is
the gang parade
How many times have you seen it?
It's already 0-100
It's really 0-100
I didn't care about 0-100
If you can love
I don't know, I haven't done it
I feel sorry for you
I think Narwha is popular and cute
I think most people think
I forgive you
But I experienced this gang parade while
working
I can only concentrate on one thing
I see
I'm really focused on work
I'm really lazy
Wait, it's the same
If it's the same
I will definitely do it
Wait, I'm convinced
Do you want to love?
I don't have to do it anymore
Really? Even if you're a very type
person?
I think this is what I want to do
Then tell me only one
If you can't, you'll definitely cut it
Only one
You should definitely say it now
Yes
I don't ask anyone. It's my privacy.
I don't think this part will be used.
Really.
No, it's not good.
How was it? Was it good?
It was pretty good.
Really?
I thought I didn't have a single thing
to use.
Actually, it has nothing to do with
history.
Really?
Yeah.
It was a kind of a
battle of using it.
It was a battle of using it.
Yeah!
Oh yeah! How was it? Did you get
excited?
I was like, the camera is broken.
This guy is a big liar.
I was like, what the hell am I thinking?
I'm glad to hear that.
I was so excited.
I was like, I'm going to do something
amazing with you.
I was so excited.
I was like, what is she going to do?
I was like, what am I going to do?
I was like, I'm going to make Narubo
angry next time.
Thank you for watching.
I pretended not to hear you, even though
I could hear you
I pretended to be stupid and gave up
I pretended not to see you