If there are parts where the air только
is eigenenby, please blow.
Next, the clothes.
Let's start with the cloth.
Handballgear
Originally created farmer participate in
the production of becoming older
clothes.
Hello?
I can hear you.
What?
Who are you?
Actually, it's our first time.
Do you know who we are?
Is it your first time?
Yes.
Wait, you can't understand me.
Wait, what?
Who is it? I don't know.
I'm a director.
What?
I'm a director and I make animations.
What does that mean? Who is it? Please
tell me.
I'm scared.
I'll start over.
I'm Tomoki Isato, the director of the TV
anime Pui Pui Molcar.
Wait, wait.
Wait, I'm scared.
Pui Pui Molcar.
Yes, that's right.
Oh, wow, it's frozen. What should I do?
Wait a minute. I can understand if I say
hello.
Wait, wait, wait.
Oh, no.
You're more surprised than I imagined.
Wow, wait a minute.
I can understand if I say hello.
Yes, I know.
Oh, wow.
Wow.
What?
What should I do? I really like it.
I went to the Morca cafe.
Thank you.
There was a Morca park.
I couldn't buy a ticket.
I was like, why is it 500 yen? It's too
cheap.
That's why it's going to sell.
I'm so happy. What should I do?
I'm so grateful that you're so happy.
What should I do?
There are so many things I want to ask
you.
I have a lot of questions about Molca.
I heard that it takes a day or a few
days to shoot a few seconds.
That's a really precious animation
that's been around for five minutes.
How many days does it take to shoot one
episode?
Well, I guess it depends on the person.
I'm shooting a video called Stop Motion,
which is a one-second 24-pages video.
I think it would be nice if I could
shoot for 4 or 5 seconds a day.
It took about a month to shoot the first
episode of the animation, which was
about 2 minutes and 40 seconds.
No, 40 seconds is a month!
It's been a month!
It's like they're doing something
steamed up and they're doing something
like this.
They went into directly by the hand, and
they're already risking their lives.
It's amazing, amazing.
4 to 5 seconds a day?!
Already.
That's right.
It's disgusting.
Which one is the best?
Which episode was the most difficult?
I thought the reaction of Abby's Itasha
episode was pretty dangerous.
The most difficult was the 8th episode
of the MOLU mission.
MOLU mission! That was crazy!
The action episode.
The adding scene of the helicopter was
especially difficult.
There, you have it. Then again, the
adding scene of Hollywood barrier.
The camera moves one frame at a time,
and the helicopter and the truck move at
the same time.
The explosion and the beam are expressed
only by the
I want to ask you, Nanao-san. What made
you start doing this?
When I was looking at Twitter or
something, I saw the word Puri Puri
Molka in the anime.
I was really impressed and so cute.
In the first episode, Potato-chan was
like,
I have to hurry up.
And then he was like,
I'm ready.
I fell in love with him.
I thought that cute was really saving
the world.
I really thought so.
Because there is not a single line.
I was really impressed just by that.
I was really tired at the time.
I think Japan was seeking for a healing.
But they were too cute.
They were like, this, this!
I was so moved by them.
And the Morkers were so kind.
I was so moved when I first saw them.
I was like, this is what the world
needs!
Thank you.
I was talking to my friend with the same
passion,
and he was like, いや、これなんだよ、ウチらが今欲してるなぁ!
Yeah, because he was a character with a
car,
I focused on his
That's too much!
I didn't think it would spread after the
broadcast, so I was really surprised at
that time.
If it was normal, adults, adults, would
be in the anime of the time of the no
mark.
Originally, it was an anime that was
done from 7.30 in the morning, so I
thought that adults wouldn't see it.
I was surprised and grateful that it
spread so quickly.
It's a huge spread.
It's been spreading for a lifetime.
I recently learned about Akari Nana.
I don't need to know anything.
That's amazing. I've heard some of your
songs.
Before I heard them, I've seen the
thumbnail of the song, like the song, Da
Da Da Tenshi.
There were a lot of parodies of that
song.
That's right. I've seen a lot of them on
the internet.
I think I've seen them before.
I think the fans' desire to produce
music is the secret to their popularity.
No, no, no.
I was really attracted to it when I
listened to it.
I remember that I liked Vocaloid when I
was in high school.
I've heard that a lot, but I felt like
it was very similar to that style.
I felt very nostalgic.
I'm not exaggerating when I say that I
grew up in Vocaloid when I was in middle
school.
I remember that I was in a Nico Nico
video.
I wanted to do that.
I was very interested in that at first.
So I think I will miss the video of the
angel.
I was very happy to see the video of the
vocalist and Nico Nico.
Did you have a chance to meet Miku
Hatsune?
Yes, I did.
Thank you for watching.
Ren, Rin, and so on.
Yes.
It's really good.
It's good.
We're both becoming professionals from
what we like.
You've become a huge hit, and you've
gained more followers and subscribers.
I wonder how you feel about becoming a
professional.
I used to perform at the Shimokitazawa
concert, and there were 30 people in the
audience.
Shimokitazawa?
Yes, Shimokitazawa is a very famous
place.
Thank you for watching!
Shimokitazawa is a city with a lot of
stages.
Yes, there are many small live houses
and theaters.
I started the live show in Nanamo.
I started with about 30 people.
Now, I have a lot of people who
subscribed to the channel and live
shows.
I have a lot of people who are so many
that I can't even think of them.
That's what we say...
I thought, while I'm being supported by
these girls,
I have to go to a better place,
and if I don't keep growing,
I'll feel like I'm being rude.
I never had that kind of feeling when I
was in high school,
when I was in a band.
I think that's where I'm stepping up.
I think that's where I'm growing as a
musician.
I think that's a great way to approach
the audience.
Yeah, I think so too.
But you've become so popular that you
still have to work on your songs.
I'm really scared when I release a song
every time.
When I think about good things and good
things in difficult situations,
I feel like I was left behind by a child
who liked the old 7-O Akari,
who had a very minor world view.
Of course, there are things like that.
I don't want to make Akarin feel lonely
and feel like he's changed.
I want to make everyone feel like
they're all in the net.
But depending on the song I play, there
are things that I can't do.
So I wonder if I can make everyone happy
when I play a song.
How do you feel about the song?
I'm worried about that.
But I'm trying to show people that I'm
happy and that I'm having fun.
I hope everyone enjoys it.
I think that's a lot of work for me.
Thank you for watching.
I was wondering what people would think
of the content of the film.
I think the content is very strong.
I think it's a good idea to make a film
that can only be made in 4-5 seconds a
day.
That's crazy.
Thank you.
I'm sorry, but it's not good to ask you
private questions.
No, not at all.
I'd like to ask you a question about a
popular artist.
Nanao, do you do ego searches on social
media?
I do.
You're quite interested in it, aren't
you?
I am.
Do you want to try?
I thought it was one of the reasons why
the Volca was so popular.
The fan art that the fans drew.
I thought it was one of the reasons.
If I had some free time, I would do a
lot of fan art.
I think that's my hobby recently.
I understand.
I'm really happy.
I have a lot of fans who are good at
drawing.
I often get fans to draw my 7th album.
I'm looking forward to it.
When I found it, I got used to it.
I'm not drawing today.
It's fun, isn't it?
I'm happy to have fun.
Do you want to be a Molcar?
I want to be a Molcar!
I think I've been talking about wanting
to be a Molcar.
I'm so proud of it that I really want to
be a Molcar.
Thank you for watching.
I've seen a lot of tweets like that.
I'm embarrassed.
I've just asked you a question.
Since it's a good opportunity, let's
design a Molcar for Nanao.
Please wait.
This is a personal gift.
Really? Is it a main event today?
No, it's not.
I can send you the illustration later.
Really?
Please let me draw it.
Is it a Nanao Molka?
It's Nanao Molka.
Oh my god! Wait a minute, what's with
this hair style?
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, what
should I do?
Wait a minute, I'll sort out my mind for
a moment.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry, I'm just saying that it's a
bit of a guess, but do you have a desk
in the place where you're sitting right
now?
I'm starting to get it.
Then please open it.
Is this something you can open?
Yes.
What the hell is this?
Zombie white!
What?
It's so cute!
I'm sorry, I'm so loud.
This is actually a zombie white used in
the anime.
Oh my gosh!
Wait, it's so big!
It's so cute!
I'm sorry, I'm so loud.
Ah!
Unfortunately, this time, the zombie-
hiro is for shooting.
I understand, I understand.
It's difficult to put it together, but
the five types of the other stuffed
animals of Molcar will be given to you
this time.
I'm going to die.
Ah!
It's not that.
The information is amazing.
Is this really okay?
What should I do?
I really do a lot of shoe polishing.
I'm really sorry to walk around the
house.
Really?
Thank you for watching.
I hope you continue to write good songs
from now on.
Thank you very much. I hope you continue
to write good songs from now on.
I'm sorry. I think it's time to go.
I'm really sorry. I'm sorry to bother
you. Thank you very much.
I'm glad you were so happy.
Really.
I'm really honored to have a
conversation with you.
Thank you very much. I'm so honored.
I'm sorry for the long time. I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm going to leave now.
Thank you very much.
Yes.
Oh my gosh.