Like Ebichu's videos!
What do you think about the concert?
It's a once-a-year university concert.
This time, the teacher of the practice
is Yusuke.
I think I can see a different live
performance in a different area.
I didn't understand the set at first.
It was amazing.
I think I can see a completely different
view from the stage.
I want to see the live performance in
the audience seat.
I'm looking forward to it.
The set list is very fresh.
I didn't expect this set list in the
concert.
I want to enjoy it with you.
I heard that there were many different
ways to perform.
I have to remember the way to perform.
I'm going to remember it.
I think it will be fun to perform on the
stage.
I'm looking forward to it.
This is the first time I've ever sung in
a concert.
I'm nervous.
I will do my best.
I'm worried about the performance of the
older members and the teacher.
I'm doing a lot of different songs.
I'm worried about the performance of the
older members and the teacher.
I watched the performance of the older
members and the teacher.
I'm going to perform the same way as the
older members.
I'm going to do my best.
I'm looking forward to everything.
I think it will be a live performance
that I've never seen before.
It's my first time performing in a
concert.
I'm going to show you the performance.
I think it will be a live performance
that will leave a great impression on
everyone's hearts.
Thank you for watching.
There are many things to be excited
about with the teacher, such as the set
and the structure of the live.
I hope it will be a live performance
that will not let go of your eyes from
the beginning to the end.
The set designer is Yusuke. I can see
the flow of the set designer.
I like it very much. At the end of the
year, I feel a little lonely.
I was surprised and I wanted to perform
live soon.
It was the first time for nine people to
perform live.
The first and last performances were
very important.
I was very happy to see the original
performance of Yusuke.
I think it's a new feeling for the
audience.
I've been looking forward to the
university performance.
I was working hard this year.
I was very happy to see the performance.
This time, each block is a very
meaningful block.
I can't choose which block to perform.
But I have an important block that I can
connect with my fans.
I hope to share my feelings with the
fans there.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I've been given a set of reasons.
I've been told by Ryusuke-sensei about
the production.
I'm so excited. I can't stop myself from
getting excited.
I'll keep telling you that.
You'll definitely know when you see it.
I'm going to get a headache.
I thought about it when I was shooting
MOVE.
Of course, there are people who always
act.
But they make a stage from a different
angle.
The approach is completely different.
I think I can show you this kind of
performance.
I think I'll be able to see a new
performance this time.
I've been given a lot of reasons.
The director made a really cool
performance.
I want to do my best to meet that.
The school is a big place.
I want to practice so that I can see
various faces.
I don't know yet.
I want to understand.
I want to enjoy it with my eyes.
I want to use it well.
I'm pretty nervous, but I want to do my
best.
I've been to ATEEZ JUMMING, RAP RAP FES,
and Akita Bunco.
I want to make this stage the most
successful.
Reboot 2020 at the Shizue University
Limits.
I was close.
Let's do it again.
I'm going to do it slowly.
Reboot at the Shizue University Limits.
It will be held at Tokyo Derby Theater
on December 27th.
It's my first time performing with nine
people.
I want to do my best.
Please come to play.
See you again.