I want to be an idol who can continue to
work hard and continue to work hard.
Good morning.
How are you?
I'm fine.
I have somewhere to go today.
How do you get there?
I take the Shinkansen.
I'm nervous.
I've never been so far away.
I'm going.
Do you go out alone?
Not really.
How far can you go by yourself?
By myself?
The farthest?
I can go to Shin-Yokohama.
Where is your home?
My home is in Yokohama.
My grandmother's home is in Shin-
Yokohama.
I arrived at Nagoya.
Good job.
Is this your first time in Nagoya?
Yes, it is.
How do you feel about the cityscape?
It doesn't look like Nagoya.
It looks like Tokyo.
How will you go to your destination?
I will drive for about an hour.
I'm almost there.
I'm excited.
I'm going to the hotel.
Bye.
OK.
OK, next.
Is there any place you are particularly
interested in?
In Hinatazaka, of course.
I used to use the Joyful Love area a
lot.
I searched for it, but it was far away,
so I want to go there.
I arrived at Yoro station.
It's like a movie.
How much further?
About 10 minutes, so we'll walk to our
destination.
Then the train may come.
I can see the shooting location over
there.
It's the most joyful place.
I'm getting excited.
I want to go in.
Wow!
Maybe here?
This room?
The second song is...
The lyrics of the second song are...
It's not about being kind to others.
It's about being calm even if you don't
do anything.
I've been used a lot of this part.
I'm a little excited right now.
Wow, I was running like this.
I'm going to start.
Like this?
Yes, like this.
It's pretty close.
I'm so happy!
Wow!
I'm scared.
I'm so nervous.
I'm dying.
I'm scared. Can I get off?
I've been at home all the time.
I don't play outside with my friends.
I'm not good at sports, so I'm afraid of
flying boxes and iron bars.
I'm scared of everything I do, so I
can't do it.
I don't have a lot of people.
I was able to get along with anyone when
I was in elementary school.
I learned a lot of things.
I'm a piano and an electron.
I also played the role of a shrine
maiden.
I started playing the water game because
my brother was playing it.
I also learned how to play the piano and
the electron from my parents.
I've been playing the baton since I was
in the first grade of junior high
school.
I've never seen a baton before.
I thought I would never be able to do it
because I didn't know anything about it.
I was very impressed by the acting of my
seniors, and it was very difficult, but
it was very rewarding.
I've been working hard for the national
tournament.
At first, I was overwhelmed and I didn't
feel like I was one.
I was very impressed by the fact that we
were all working together to create
something together.
I learned to be more cooperative and
considerate.
I want to go to the hill over there.
It's pretty tough.
I'm going to go up.
Amazing!
I feel like I'm in the world of the MV.
How is it?
I did it!
I'm going to the zoo again.
I can't lose.
I'm going to lose.
I want to try lying down.
I want to be a circle.
I'm going to do a scene where I lie
down.
It was so bright that I couldn't open my
eyes.
But in the music video, everyone looked
so happy.
I thought everyone was working hard.
I'm thinking about the other member's
feelings.
I want to experience that feeling.
I'm scared.
I want to go to the white place over
there.
This is the chair where Kato-san, Mirei-
san, Sasaki Mirei-san, and Kyoko Saito
sit when they are in trouble.
Let's do it from here.
It's going to be fun.
I'm tired as much as I can.
You're turning right.
I'm embarrassed.
I danced a lot of the second chorus
here.
At the graduation ceremony, I danced
Nagidaka's dance.
I was the first one to stand on the
stage.
I was nervous, but I had a lot of fun.
That gradually changed my longing for
idols.
I'm looking forward to it.
Like this?
I'm a 4th generation idol who can be
seen by anyone as an idol.
I'm shooting like this because many
seniors from Hiragana, Kiyaki, and
Hinata-zaka are working hard.
We are in such a blessed environment, so
I want to be an idol who can continue to
make an effort that I can't see.
I came to my favorite place.
I want to do what I can do,
and do something that only I can do.
Today, I want to show my baton here.
I can't help but forgive you
Like a shower of rain
I'll become your warm feelings
Joyful love
Is this love?
Wow wow
Joyful love
The first time in the world
Wow wow
The moment I saw you
Suddenly, words become a hindrance
My heart may be communicating with me
It was the first time for me to dance
alone
It was the first time to make a
choreography
I was very anxious
To make the world view of Joyful Love
I danced with the feeling of supple
fingertips
Joyful Love is a memory
I saw the rainbow of the last Joyful
Love at Tokyo Dome
It was one of the reasons I decided to
take the audition
I was very happy to be able to come to
this location and show my skills
Thank you for your viewing
I'm so moved that I can remember all the
scenes and the sound of the place I came
here.
That's where I danced the chorus, and
that's where I did the chorus.
It's like a dream. I'm so happy.
No. 7, Hiyajisu.
I've been watching Hinata Zacon from the
fan's point of view since I was in the
4th grade.
I didn't realize that I was going to be
in the group.
But I came to Yukarinuchi and I got to
dance a song that's very important to
Hinata Zacon and the sun.
I realized that I'm going to be a member
and work hard.
I was prepared.
If I have a chance to sing, I want to
remember this scenery and deliver it to
many people.
I'm Sumire Miyachi, 16 years old, from
Kanagawa prefecture.