Canиях
Nice! Wait, it's close!
Will it go in?
Wow!
Nice shot!
Where did it go?
Wait, you're so good!
Hello! It's been a while!
Were you surprised?
I'm Hina Kiguchi!
I graduated, but I played golf last
time.
I'm doing it again as a continuation.
Today, I'm visiting Aoyama Park 9.
I'm going to try simulation golf for the
first time.
I have a special guest here.
Namiki!
Hello, everyone! I'm Namiki.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
I'm so happy.
I saw you playing golf on the video.
You're so good at it.
I'm so happy.
I was surprised.
I'm so embarrassed because I don't know
anything.
I watched your YouTube.
Thank you.
It's easy for beginners to understand.
I'm going to do my best.
I'm going to do a collaboration.
Thank you.
I'll do my best.
Let's do it!
Let's start the simulation golf.
Let's enjoy it.
Higuchi is very nervous.
I'm not a professional or anything.
I'm just an amateur.
I'm not a professional.
I'm just a beginner.
I'll enjoy it while you help me.
Let's start.
Yes.
Please.
I'm nervous.
The first hole is par 4.
The release is 286 yards.
It says to the pin.
It's straight at first.
I think it's okay if you don't put it in
the pond.
Let's go.
What will she say?
OK! OK!
Nice shot!
Is it good?
First nice shot!
What should I call you?
I was wondering about it.
Well, Hina or Hina-chan.
Anything is fine.
Anything is fine?
Then, Hina-chan.
What should I call you?
Anything is fine.
Namiki-san.
Why is that?
Namiki-chan.
I'll call you Namiki-san.
Or should I call you Namiki-nee-san?
Anything is fine.
I'll call you Namiki-nee-san.
Then, Hina-chan.
I shot a driver for the first time and I
got a scar.
I watched that video.
She is a little bit nervous.
I feel I've learned it so far.
It's just fear.
It's OK. I'll do my best.
I'll do my best.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
It's okay.
Please slip once.
Yes.
No matter how many times you slip.
I'm scared. I'm not going to hit the
bottom.
I'll do my best not to get into the
pond.
Yes.
Wow! Nice hit!
This is totally fine.
See?
Nice!
Hina, you hit 157 yards to the pin.
I don't know how it is at first.
But I think you still have a long way to
go.
Yes, I do.
You can use this to hit a club you are
good at or a club you have practiced.
I use this driver and iron 7.
I only use this.
You have never used this wood or
utility?
I have, but I couldn't hit it at all.
Then, you should use the one you are
confident with.
Yes.
Your swing is really beautiful.
I'm glad.
You are called by my sister.
I'm called by my sister.
Nice! OK OK OK!
If you roll at the beginning, it's OK.
Nice!
I usually hit the 8th iron at 100 yards.
I want to hit the 8th iron.
What will happen?
Don't hit the bunker!
Stop!
She got it!
I can't say, nice!
It's not about flying.
It's difficult.
It's important to be sure.
I see.
Hina's strategy is very good.
Really?
Slowly?
That's the most important.
Hina's strategy
Nice!
She might get it!
This is it!
Nice!
Wait, it's close!
Will she get it?
Yay!
You're good!
Nice!
I might land it!
Roll!
Nice!
Wait, it's close!
Will it go in?
Oh my god!
You're so good!
I'm so happy!
You can just hit it with a putter next
time.
I see.
Just roll it with a putter.
That's difficult.
Nice!
You're at 14.2 yards.
This is difficult.
I'll try 58 degrees.
Wow, it's big! Stop!
Hang in there!
It didn't go in. The green didn't go in.
I'll try again.
It didn't go in.
The ball went to the right in the front,
and to the left in the back.
That's right.
I can't hit the ball because of this.
I'll try again.
Oh, it's weak.
It's weak, but it's rolling slowly.
It's going well, isn't it?
It's going well.
Next.
Oh, it's me again.
That means Hina is close.
Is that so?
I have to do my best.
I'll do my best.
What will happen?
Please enter.
Please.
I couldn't enter.
Amazing!
That's a lot of fun!
We're almost there.
I've got a double bogey.
Hina, if you get this in, you'll be a
par.
I'll do my best.
There's a chance.
You can see the slope.
What do you think, Hina?
This slope...
Which way do you think it's going to
turn?
It's going to turn right.
That's right.
Then, be aware of the right.
Here we go.
Good?
Huh?
Sorry, that was an error.
I didn't react.
Oh, you're right.
Sorry, thank you.
Huh?
What?
The score is higher than the distance.
The one with the higher score is the
winner.
I'm glad.
I'm the winner.
I didn't expect you to be the winner.
I know.
So the distance doesn't matter.
By the way, this is the next part.
So if you score 3 points, you'll get a
point.
The pin is written there, but it's only
127 degrees.
Oh, really.
I'll do my best.
How far can you jump?
I don't know yet.
Let's go.
Please subscribe to this channel.
You can 對 this turn!
Really?
You can go straight.
A three-perfect shot is fine.
It's also short.
Research!
Yes!
My turn is a U-turn in six.
I'll shoot straight.
Amazing!
Straight!
What?
Obrigado!
Nice!
This is really good!
Thank you!
I'm happy!
I showed you a good side of me!
I'm so happy to see you so happy in the
first try!
The second try
OK! OK!
You are moving forward.
I'm glad.
You are doing great.
Thank you.
I thought I was doing well at first.
But, golf is a sport where you make
mistakes.
So, please think that there are few
secrets.
You are so kind.
The third try
OK!
You did it!
Nice!
Stop! Stop!
Stop!
Ah! But if it's this...
How is it? I think you can do it with a
putter.
Really?
I'll have to see.
If you stop a little more in front...
What will you do?
I'll try a putter.
How does this slope look?
It's a little down.
Oh, yes. It's a little downhill.
Downhill, front right, back left.
Oh, that's it.
Oh, great.
Aiming for the straight.
However, there is only downhill, so be
careful.
That's great.
I'll try to be as strong as I can.
Aim for the straight.
I think I went too far.
It's OK. You're doing good.
Go, go, go!
OK.
You're doing good. You're getting
closer.
Thank you.
Please subscribe to my channel!
Close!
But the distance was perfect.
I'm glad.
The next one is a triple bogey.
Yes.
I just did it, so I'm getting used to
it.
I see.
I'm a birdie.
Are you getting used to it?
Yes, I am.
How was your first simulation golf?
It was a different kind of nervousness.
Were you nervous?
Yes, I was.
But I felt I could do it with a relaxed
mind.
You are so kind.
I'm not, but I'm enjoying it.
Thank you.
I've brought something here.
It's an approach competition.
The one who gets the ball in the hole
first wins.
I'll get in the big one.
Nami will get in the small one.
It's so different.
It's not, but I'll do my best.
I'll do my best.
The loser will get a penalty game.
What is it?
I'll drink a very sour liquid.
It's scary.
Have you ever drunk it?
Yes, but I felt like a dog.
I was so thirsty.
It's so sour.
I heard it's more powerful than what
I've ever drunk.
I don't need that power-up.
I have to win.
I'll do my best.
Who will go first?
Rock-paper-scissors?
Rock-paper-scissors.
Please choose.
I'll go first.
Higuchi, good luck.
You're good!
I'm surprised.
You went to the left.
It's hard to control the power.
I don't need much power.
I'll go.
Where did it go?
Look.
It's white.
Is this white?
I'll go.
Where did it go? Where?
You're not red!
Safe!
Lucky!
You're lucky!
But it's amazing!
That was perfect!
A miracle happened!
Amazing!
Just like that!
Wait! You're so good!
She's good at it!
You're too strong!
You did really well!
I should have held my power a little
longer.
You did well!
You're too good!
So close!
This distance is just right.
It's difficult.
The distance is just right.
I was close.
Will this game end today?
It will be a long battle.
The distance is just right.
You are strong.
You are already winning.
The distance is just right.
You are good.
Nice. But I was able to win.
It's difficult.
If the target was bigger, I would have
won.
You are complaining to the target.
It's difficult.
I'm strong.
Please subscribe to my channel.
It's big!
But it's amazing!
But you can roll it in like this, right?
I see.
Hina, you can do that too.
I have that strategy.
You're kind.
You're teaching your opponent.
Hina's strategy
It's going in!
It's big!
Nice!
But it's a little tilted.
It's because of the train in front of
us.
It's not straight.
It's difficult even if it's a little
curvy.
Let's go.
It's white again!
It's not going in.
Red is difficult.
It's difficult.
Go!
Ah, that way.
Acrobatic provinces are difficult!
But I was more into it!
Yeah, if we were more focused...
And with that...
The Lesson premieres on August 26th!!
Come on!
I'm going to lose all the balls here
today.
It's harder than I thought.
The last try!
I got it!
She got it!
You're good!
Nice!
Thank you!
Wow!
It's the biggest one.
But it went in so cleanly.
If I can put this in, I win.
But if you can't, you lose.
The penalty game is...
Let's do our best. I'm so nervous.
Please, God, come in.
No!
To be continued
I won! Is this okay?
It's okay.
I'm sorry. I got a lot of hits.
No, no, no, no, no.
I did it!
Nice!
You were really good.
Thank you.
It's difficult, isn't it?
Strength and slope.
But there weren't many people who could
get the ball up like this from the
beginning.
Is that so?
I was really surprised.
But you're really good.
The penalty game.
That's right. The penalty game.
Please.
Yes.
I'll have a drink.
Is there a penalty game?
I think there is. I'm preparing for it.
Let's do it!
What's the penalty?
The penalty game is to drink a special
drink.
I'll have a special drink.
Look at this.
Sorry.
It's a drink that comes in a bottle.
It looks like water.
How does it smell?
It smells like...
Ramune.
I think I can drink it.
I'll try it.
The color of my eyes changed.
Oh, my God!
I'm glad you have eyelashes.
I want some water.
I won't give you water.
There are about 100 pickled plums.
I'm getting used to it.
I can tell you're going to be a dog.
I'm a dog today.
We played a simulation golf with Namiki.
It was really fun.
Thank you.
I think it's more fun to practice with a
few people than to practice alone.
Let's practice together in the future.
Thank you for teaching me a lot.
I'm not a professional, so I'm not good
at it.
I'm doing a golf competition on Namiki's
YouTube channel.
Please subscribe to the channel and
click the good button.
Please subscribe to the channel.
Please subscribe to the channel!