Ebitune's video
I'm Komae Shikamo, the 51st in the
world.
Yes, that's why.
It's my first time.
I'm the leader of the Terakemono.
Today is the day of preparation.
It's the day of the entry.
Finally, I'm at the venue.
I'm here to prepare for the performance.
I'm going to start right away.
I'm entering the venue.
I'm going to start the performance.
I've been in quarantine for about a
year.
I was at home because of the
coronavirus.
It was really hard.
For me, the quarantine period was just
right.
I've been in quarantine for about a
year.
If it's this size, I can wear it for
half a day.
The big one took me a week.
It took me a long time to make a
different one.
I had a hard time making the draft.
Can it be released?
First, this is a picture called 芋たれ.
This is a picture I took when I was in
the news.
This is a picture of me being carried in
my stomach.
my stomach and a picture of a person
being carried in my stomach.
I drew this picture with my sister.
I've been painting this picture many
times.
I wanted to express the warmth of the
sun, which is like a human.
I've been painting this picture many
times.
This is the most childlike picture.
Thank you for your viewing.
This is a series called Shiki.
It's a series of photos.
It's a series of photos called Shiki.
It's the first time I've heard of it.
It's a series of photos of the seasons.
It's a series of photos of spring,
summer, and autumn.
I wanted to create a seasonal
atmosphere.
The colors of cherry blossoms are
reflected in the photo.
This is a picture of the autumn leaves.
This is a picture of the Christmas tree.
The most beautiful picture is this.
I used a metallic color.
This is a picture of the autumn leaves.
Please look at this.
This is a picture of a mixed animal.
I recommend this picture.
This is a picture of a gorilla and a
fox.
This is the most relaxing animal of the
mixed species.
It's like a scene in an anime.
I want you to see this picture.
This is my profile picture.
I drew my profile picture.
I was born in 2000.
I'm a blood type A.
I'm a Tatsudoshi.
There are two theories.
I drew Tatsu of Dora and Tatsu of Tatsu.
I'm from Saitama Prefecture.
I'm a little timid.
If I were a Tatsudoshi, I would draw a
picture of a person.
I'm a little timid.
I'm weak, so I'm a little timid.
I like dumplings.
I like to eat dumplings.
I wrote a song like this.
This is a picture of me in one piece.
I wanted to introduce everything.
This is a picture called Take Me Home.
This is a dream I saw a lot when I was
in elementary school.
I've been going to the hallway of
elementary school all the time.
I've been looking at it for a long time.
I wrote it.
The pictures around me are painted.
I'm the only one who's painted.
I've been painting this much.
I thought I'd float around like this.
So I'm going to talk about my face.
Okay, the last one is a self-portrait.
Um.
I don't know when this will be released,
but I took a picture with Niko
yesterday.
I was 20 years old at the time, and I
took a picture while looking at my face.
I was not good at drawing self-
portraits.
It took a lot of time.
I tried to express the skin color of the
skin by layering various colors.
I tried to express the skin of a human.
The color has changed now.
I don't know.
I didn't think I'd be able to draw my
face like this.
It's amazing. It's amazing. It's
complete. It's hard.
Do you understand me?
I think you'll understand. I'd like you
to see it.
Yes, that's what I'm going to do.
I'm going to do my first painting this
time.
I'm actually preparing for it today.
I'm still surprised.
I think it'll be over soon.
But I've always liked painting since I
was in kindergarten.
I'm wondering how you'll react to seeing
that picture.
I'm very curious about your reaction.
But I'm drawing all the pictures
carefully.
It's still a difficult situation in the
world.
I hope people will laugh at my painting.
I'm happy that I can do what I like with
my 20th birthday.
I don't know what I can do next.
I hope I can do it again someday.
I want to improve my skills.
Thank you very much for enjoying it.
See you next time.