Ebichu's videos!
Kobayashi, I'm going to ask you some
questions!
Yay!
So, finally, it's my turn.
I actually asked my fans to ask me
questions on Twitter.
I really want to answer all of them, but
I'd like to answer as many as possible,
even though it's related to time.
So, let's get started!
I'm going to ask you some questions!
I also did my homework on the 31st.
So, I think you don't have to do it
until you're motivated.
When you're motivated, the time will
come, so let's wait until then.
So, please do your best!
I'm going to ask you some questions.
Q. What do you think about the fans who
are saying that you're going to get a
lot of comments?
I'm the type of person who says,
I'm going to get a lot of comments.
I feel sorry for them.
So, I think it's better to say it to
them later.
I think it's better to say it.
I don't feel any kind of rejection, so I
think it's faster to say it.
Next question is,
Q. What do you recommend to do if you
have an earring on?
If you drop your earring,
I recommend double-sided tape.
If you put double-sided tape on it and
reinforce it, it won't fall off even if
it shakes.
So, the next question is,
Q. What do you think about the fans who
are saying that you're going to get a
lot of comments?
I'm the type of person who keeps quiet.
I feel sorry for them.
So, I think it's better to say it.
But, I think it's okay to show them a
posture to do something.
Next question is,
Q. What time do you wake up?
I think I have to use more than three
alarm clocks.
My brother is weak in the morning, so he
uses a lot of alarm clocks.
He keeps saying,
I'll wake up with that.
Next question is,
Q. What time do you wake up?
I don't have to worry about it.
I don't have to force myself to match.
I want to be like that.
People who notice will notice.
Please wait until you meet that person.
I'm not a person who is not good at
dating.
I'm a person who is not good at dating.
I was once in a relationship with a
woman.
Everyone is different.
I want to be honest with myself.
I'm also in training.
I want to say what I want to say.
I'm thinking about what I want to say.
I don't see anyone.
I breathe in and out.
I'm alone in this world.
I don't know how old you are.
I want you to be young.
I want you to have a good nerve.
I don't know how old you are.
I made a tofu.
I'll try you this time.
I'm a ponder.
But she said to me that she told me an
original...
I'm happy because I'm full of the
feeling of being a good person.
Thank you for taking the audition.
I think it's natural to be nervous.
I think it's more fun than relaxing.
I'm happy if you can enjoy it as much as
possible.
I'm nervous, but I'm excited.
I would be happy if you could cherish
it.
I'll say that I'll see you at the
audition.
I'm nervous because I'm full of the
feeling of being a good person.
It's hard to get along with people.
But I'm still going to work every day.
I think it's great.
If there is a difficult situation, avoid
reality.
I change my mood.
I like to draw.
I draw and write.
I try not to think too much.
I'm tired.
I don't have to think too much.
I think the person I meet will come to
me.
I don't have to try too hard.
I think it's the minimum way to get
along.
I'm not a person who is good at drawing.
I'm also a person who is not good at
drawing.
I don't have a sense of presence.
I'm glad I don't have a sense of
presence.
I'm sure there are many people who are
good at drawing.
I just want to believe that.
First of all, wear clothes that stand
out by making your voice louder.
I think it's good to start with the
appearance.
I'm not a person who is good at drawing.
I think it's better to finish the day.
I'm the type to think so.
I think it's good to have a day off.
I think it's a good time to sleep all
the time.
I'm tired.
I think it's good to sleep, but eat
properly.
You can take a bath, brush your teeth,
and sleep.
You're having a good time.
I don't have many friends.
I think it's not painful to be with this
person.
I think I can get along with this
I try to find such a person.
It takes time.
I don't care about that.
I try to get along with this person.
I think it's faster to get along with
this person.
I don't have many friends.
I try to find someone who I can get
along with.
I don't want to study.
I don't study this either.
I think it's good.
I can't concentrate on the day I can't
concentrate.
I'm out of focus.
I can't concentrate on the day I can't
concentrate.
I quit.
I spend my days like this.
I don't have any problems with that
method.
I'm not good at the middle school.
I think I'm not good at the middle
school.
I'm not good at the middle school.
I'm the type who can get along with the
other person.
It's difficult to decide.
I can't decide because I'm not good at
studying.
I thought about it.
One day I went to a cafe and was worried
about octopus rice or spaghetti.
I was wondering which one to choose.
The staff told me to hurry up.
I ordered a waffle that had nothing to
do with this.
If you can't decide, you can order
something else.
What is the most difficult thing to do
compared to other people?
I think it's a swamp compared to other
people.
I feel sorry for myself.
I want to sell food and marry my State-
LI
If you're having a hard time, you can
just say,
Yes, people are people, I'm myself.
You are you, I am me.
I think it will be easier if you can
think of yourself as yourself.
What is the most important thing to do
when you are in a relationship?
You don't have to worry about it
anymore.
For example, if you have earphones,
I don't care anymore.
I don't listen anymore.
I don't think it's good to not listen
anymore.
Let's get rid of the concept of right
and left.
LR is like Mario and Luigi.
I don't understand the meaning.
Don't tie it up.
I understand.
That's all for the first time.
Thank you for your concern.
I'm just an individual.
I hope you think your face is like this.
There are things that you can't tell
your close friends.
I think it's easy to talk to people
because of the distance.
If you have any questions, please write
it in the comments.
If you like the video, please write it
in the comments.
I will do my best to solve your
problems.
Thank you very much.