Hello everyone
Everyone is cold
Who are you?
Who?
I am a celebrity, Oshanti Matsuno
Matsuno?
So, Oshanti Matsuno has chosen a hat for
each of you
You chose a hat that suits you
I chose a hat that suits me
It's me
You look cute
Thank you very much
But!
These two are not the same as anyone
else
They are fake hats
This is Riko
This is Kaho
I think this is Kaho
This is the usual one
Kaho seems to choose black
It's time to decide, what do you think?
This is Mirei's and this is Aya's
I have both of these
Let's choose this one
This is the final hat
The correct answer is
Nakayama
Oh
Only one?
Nakayama is the only one
It's not this one?
Nakayama, please do a fashion show
Where are you going?
Wear the costume and come back
It's the birth of Tanko Mars!
Mmm!
Kawaii!
Ebichu!
The remaining 6 people are
again,
a different hat!
Scary!
Hey, Kobayashi-san!
Tomo-chan!
Shut up, Kanshawa!
You're right.
Hoshino-san!
There's only one person!
The best hat for the summer vacation
at the Karuizawa villa
is the best match for the Ebichu's
Karuizawa's
Mie-rin!
How was it?
The hat that flew away
is Hirona's, too!
The prince riding a white horse!
What?
A fairytale?
Yeah!
It's a fantasy!
That's it?
There's only one more time?
Please do your best!
It's not the last time!
The correct answer is...
Kashiwagi-san!
Let's do the final round!
Okay!
A girl who is as fluffy as a white-
haired girl
This is the girl who came from Chiba
and is a girl who doesn't know the
world!
Why did you choose Kaoru Isaka?
She is very pure and honest
She is a toy box in Ebichu
She is a just-watching girl
But she is not doing her homework today
either!
She watches a movie related to her fan
club
and says things that she understands
The culprit is...
Nubai Chimi!
She is a fan of her father
and her black eye-line is very short
She is pretty good!
The only cap type is...
The one that is on her father's head
I'm sorry!
How was it?
How was the serious wearing of the cap?
I'm glad I was able to wear a lot of
different caps!
I'm glad too!
I'll try to use it as a reference next
time!
Thank you!
Ebichu!
No shu shu shu!
Her hair has changed
It has changed, Ebichu
It suits you
She looks like a Japanese
It's a natural thing for a Shariotsu
Seijin
What about you, Ebichu?
I don't have much interest in it
Good timing
I think the front is definitely short
This one
I think this is Maya's
But Riko's is my favorite
I like this one
I think this is Mire's
I think this is mine
I think this is R-medie's
Let's change
Let's go with intuition
We got changed by everyone
I got wrong
Did you get it?
Mom, my daughter is always taking care
of me
So please take care of my daughter
I'm a mother of the family
I'm really here
I'm here
Now, the correct answer is
Mahiyama
Honto-san
Correct
These four people got it right!
Cutie girl outside of court?
If the short hair is popular, I'll go
for the sports hairstyle next!
I think I'm pretty good at long hair
too!
The point is the sense of open hair!
If you have a handkerchief and a face
sandwich in one hand, everyone will turn
around!
But if you let go, it's a boom boom
boom!
It's just like my mom!
Hello!
It was a nice walk for all four of us!
The remaining three, let's Katsuura!
I'm lost.
What is this?
The three of us have changed.
I'm back to my old self.
It suits you.
I'm a little curious.
Please.
I'm a critic.
It's a balloon binicle.
Why did you choose it?
I wanted to go around.
The correct answer is...
I don't have it!
I'm sorry.
It was good for Hiena.
This is the last change.
I'm going to wear it.
How old are you?
I'm nervous.
To be continued.
You were a senpai.
The winner is...
Nakayama-san!
I knew it! It's you!
Anoritan is a long-haired adult who
transforms into a real scorpion with a
great skill!
Scorpion Death Rock! Love & Happy!
Wow! It suits you!
What? What? What? What?
It really suits you!
It's beautiful!
The answer is this!
It's cute!
How was it?
Anyway, Riko-chan looks good in
anything!
That's right!
Thank you! Let's all laugh together!