K ま ま
ек점
de
Ebisu House is a house where eight
members of Ebichu can talk normally
The only thing they have is a nice house
There are no script
Everyone is thinking about their future
I was surprised by the question about
whether they like Ebichu
I'm surprised, but do you like Ebichu?
I don't like her.
Do you want to protect yourself or as a
group?
I think each of them has their own
character.
I think they've given their own answers.
I'm a person who goes to the living
room.
I'm scared.
I feel sorry for them. They're talking
to me, but I'm done.
I think it's amazing that they're being
chased and in a hurry.
What did we do when we were in the 19th
grade?
We were told to take a break from
practice because we were going to go to
the high school.
But we knew that we were going to go to
I was trying to get married in Shimokita
as much as possible.
That's all I know.
Ebichu Tastas is also about to celebrate
its 1st anniversary.
So please tell us your thoughts without
a script.
Thank you for watching!
We all do something together.
Yes, we all make something together.
That's right.
Moreover, school is not like that.
And the concept of Ebichu is connected
to that kind of place.
Ebichu?
It's only been about two years.
So, we still have half of the day left.
You haven't said half of it.
How many years?
I haven't said anything, so I'll say it
from now on.
That's right.
What is this?
It's not a blanket. It's cold.
It's pink.
It's not a pink character.
I'm jealous.
What is this?
It's cold as it is.
I can't let go.
I feel good in the bed.
It's a fire.
I don't want to be in the bed.
I'm sure someone will enter the room.
No way.
I'm sure it's not good.
I'm scared because it's a sea.
What should I talk about?
What? What should I do?
What should I do?
What is your favorite song in Ebichu?
My favorite song?
Simply.
My favorite song.
Simply?
It doesn't have to be the best.
There are many songs.
Songs with memories?
What is it?
A week before the first week of the new
year.
year?
Before the first week of the new year, I
had a lot of lines.
I remember that.
In the old days, I had only six
microphones.
Penlight, heart-shaped.
I had a pair of heart-shaped penlights.
So I was very happy when I had a
microphone during the first week of the
new year.
When I first started, there were no
songs to play.
I only watched the songs with my
sleeves.
That's a little painful.
I remember that.
When I was in Tachikawa, I went in and
out again.
I was repeating that.
That's painful.
I wanted to do something with everyone
soon.
Now that I think about it, I have a lot
of lines.
In 2016, I didn't rely on the negative
parts I've said so far.
If it was like this, it would be easy.
It's hard to say what to change.
Thank you for watching.
How many people will come to the show
for the first time?
This program is brought to you by the
sponsor.
I'm nervous.
Before I go out.
The fight that took my life.
SH countries have been Cette9爱の悪 lado
We talk in the car sometimes.
In the past, we didn't talk about
everything like we do now.
So I think there were a lot of
misunderstandings and thoughts.
I think that was a child.
I'm an elementary school student.
I'm serious. I wasn't in middle school.
I was in a lot of elementary school.
It's a strange feeling when you think
about it.
I think I was the oldest in the last
year.
I'm glad I'm the oldest.
It's not sinking as much as I thought.
This is also the feature of rich people.
We don't know how much we know about the
situation.
I don't know.
We don't know where we are right now.
It's a strange feeling.
There is a hall tour this time.
There are places that I haven't been to
much.
There is a place I'm going for the first
time this time.
I'm curious about how many people will
come for the first time.
I want to ask when I go to the hall.
There is a hall in Okinawa.
I'm a little scared.
I wonder if it will be built.
I don't know how far we are.
I don't know what will happen from now
on.
We have one step left.
I don't know what to do.
I want to break through our teenage
years.
This time, we will release an anarchy.
I'm confident in this album.
This is the third album.
I think everyone is confident in this
album.
What do you think?
If it is like this, it will be
difficult.
It's hard to say what to change.
We are a group that people know.
I think we said too much.
I think we relied on that.
I think so.
I think it's a waste not to be able to
release an anarchy when you are a guest.
In 2016, we relied on the negative
things we said so far.
That's right.
We will face it and fight.
Thank you for watching.
But if you talk like this, there will be
many people who will do this next time.
I thought that everyone was thinking
about it, even these three people.
But I think everyone is thinking about
it.
The other five people are also.
We are clumsy.
I think it's okay to clear it little by
little, not all at once.
You seems to have been talking co
kilometers
But, the age is, as we talked about
before, the age is overlapped
Horikawa will be a high school student,
right?
Everyone is over high school
It's become an age where we can't make
something ourselves
It's become an age where we have to do
something like self-reliance
It's a little bit of a variety
If it's a big stage, there's definitely
a period of time
There is a practice period
It's a little bit of a variety
You said you cheer everyone up with your
smile
I was surprised
I was excited
I think the family was successful
I had a lot of fun
Come on, step on it, step on it, I
understand you
I'm scared
Please do the PPL
Hina Kashiwagi
What's her name?
I feel like I'm a person who falls on
the floor
What's this?
It's an old member's old CD.
I want to see it.
It's so hard.
Let's try it with Rina.
Mayama.
Isn't this a video?
Rina has grown up.
It's a video.
The bass hasn't changed.
She's grown up.
It's nostalgic.
It's the same as Aya.
She's grown up, but she's still Aya.
It's the same as Hina.
She hasn't changed.
She's like a new member.
She's cute.
I imitated her.
I took a picture of her and broke it.
She's cute.
It's the same as Aya.
It's the same.
She's still a kid.
She's working hard.
She's a grown-up.
Why did you close it?
I'm scared.
It's the same as Ghost.
It's nostalgic.
It's the same as the first time we met.
We met.
What do you mean?
We met here.
Mayama said she was scared.
Everyone said that.
I was the kindest.
I was scared.
I don't know.
I wasn't scared.
I thought she was cool.
Rina?
When we first met,
the first day we went to the lesson,
everyone talked to me.
Rina talked to me.
I was surprised.
I was cool at first.
I was told that I was cool and a little
scary.
I was like, is that so?
I was relieved because it was like this.
I changed my personality.
I think I'm open.
I'm a good talker.
What do you think?
I was scared in a different way.
It was the first time we met.
I'm a new character.
I'm a little...
I'm a little loose.
I was like, huh?
I was wondering what to do.
I was scared.
I didn't know what to do.
At first, I was scared.
I was scared.
I was like, that girl.
When I asked her age,
I was 16 years old.
How old are you?
I was scared.
I was like, that girl.
I was 16 years old.
It's a big news.
The next Hina Hina who comes in is
dangerous.
It's dangerous.
When I bought it,
I thought this person would get along
with me.
I was a little worried.
I didn't like this.
But in the end,
I thought I could get along with Rina.
Rina.
I was lonely.
Rina knew it.
But I thought it was okay if I talked.
I thought it was a stranger.
Riko-chan, do you have something?
But the moment I met you, everyone was
like, oh.
Riko-chan is already in the ring.
Because I was playing.
I'm glad that I got 8th place.
But the three of us were out.
We were really good.
We were good.
I and Ayaka were okay to join.
Yes, that's right.
I don't know what kind of two people
are.
I don't know who Kaho and Riko are.
I don't know who they are.
I didn't know how many people might be
in.
That fight was big.
It was scary.
That fight that took my life.
I'm sorry.
When we announced the three of us, they
told us to join.
We were the same.
We were like double-punches.
It was crazy.
When we were in Toyosu, Nagano, they
told us to join.
It was so crazy.
We talked to everyone.
We were like, can we go home like this?
We were late.
It was scary.
It was like a dream.
And the site was big.
The view was bigger than before.
It was different.
It was different when we were in
Saitama.
We were surprised when we were attacked.
We were scared that we would be attacked
from the first.
At least we were six.
We wanted to protect the site.
There were people who met us.
Mirei and Aika were on the other side.
Hina and Rina.
Those four were not at ease at that
time.
Ayaka and I talked a lot.
We thought we could talk together.
We went together and had a fight on
LINE.
We had a fight on LINE with the
recording group.
We had a serious fight.
I don't know why.
I don't know why we had a fight on LINE.
So we made a machine.
It was amazing.
In LINE,
we talked about going to the site
together.
We talked about it.
We talked to the staff.
We talked about it after we met the
members.
We wanted to go together.
But we said no.
The staff said no.
Suddenly, we said no.
We said no.
We didn't know anything about it.
We were surprised.
I said it once.
I thought it was normal.
I thought it was good.
I said it once.
I couldn't say my opinion.
I was afraid if I was told.
I wanted to say it together.
Maya was the most scared.
I couldn't say it.
Maya was the reason for the fight.
At that time,
I was really scared.
These four were the reason.
It was a lie.
I didn't know.
I was also bad.
But I wasn't used to it.
I can say anything because of that.
That fight was big.
We didn't have a fight.
But I was scared.
It was a fight that took a lifetime.
I was very nervous.
I said it because it was big.
I shouldn't have touched it.
I said it for the first time.
It was a fight.
I was scared.
I knew it.
I wanted to do it with six people.
It was the most important thing.
I wanted to do it with this member.
It was natural to come in.
I was in that position.
I thought I was doing the worst thing.
I'm sorry.
That was bad.
But it shouldn't have happened now.
It would have happened before that.
I'm glad.
And the fact that two people came
changed it.
I'm glad.
I'm glad that two people were these two.
Thank you.
I'm happy.
We are spending time together.
I'm not old anymore.
You know that, right?
I'm a baby.
I'm a baby mentally.
It was the first time we talked about
it.
I looked back.
What is your future goal?
You said it with three people.
I said it with three people.
You didn't say it with three people.
I see.
What is my future goal?
I'm talking about negative things.
I have to break the shell.
I always can't take a step.
I'm trying to reach out.
I'm not good at talking.
I have to stop saying negative things.
Pizza is here.
Is it pizza?
Let's talk while eating.
Thank you for watching.
I'm hungry.
I'm hungry because I just finished
eating.
Let's eat together.
Cheers!
What about salad and fries?
Wait a minute.
I want to eat.
Let's eat.
Delicious.
We often think that we don't have to say
anything.
We know that we are all people.
We know a lot from the TV show.
But our awareness is important.
Let's talk more, including MC and the
factory.
I want to make coffee.
Let's go to the cafe.
Let's go for a meal.
I want to go for a walk.
I think these eight are the best
members.
Nattori-Mii.
Thank you for your hard work.
Let's eat.
If I just lay here
Would you lie with me and just forget
the world
Next time, the second year's special
Move to Wednesday and more and more
power up
That famous scene is also a big release
Happy first year
From April, the debut group TASTAS will
move to Wednesday night at midnight
every week
Please watch
This program was brought to you by the
sponsor you see.
Not only do you get to know me, but also
get me to get into it.
And also do what you can do here.
That's amazing. You've already reached
that level at this age.
What did you do when you were 17?
I collected the Kankan of the Pringles.