I think clothes are the most important
thing.
And smiles are the most important.
I got a little order.
Wow, great!
Now, it's my turn.
Komari Mayu.
Komari Mayu?
I'm in trouble.
I think Riko is very fashionable.
She is a senior.
I'm not good at talking.
I know.
Yakan and Idol
Hello, I'm Yakan, a member of Stardust,
born and raised in Biwa.
Today's guest is...
This is the idol!
I'm Ema Sakurai, 16th grader, Shizuoka
University, Shibuya, Shizuoka
Prefecture. Nice to meet you.
Yay! You're a member!
Thank you so much, Ema Sakurai!
Do you have any nicknames you want to be
called by?
I'm just Ema.
I see.
I also like Emaron.
Emaron!
I've never heard of it.
Let's go with Emaron today.
Thank you.
Emaron!
Are you really called Emaron?
Well...
You're so cute.
I'm working as a Love Talkie Girl in
another company.
I'm called Emaron there.
I'm surprised you're so confident.
What about you?
Nothing.
Nothing?
I'm fine with drawing.
Drawing?
Well, I'll just draw a picture of you.
Please.
How about your seniors?
They're kind.
Kind?
Yes.
They raise a tone of voice when they're
laughing.
It's delicious, but it's hard for sour
people.
You're kind.
You're kind. You teach me a lot.
You teach me how to dance and sing.
When I go to work, I have to be able to
hear you when you say hello.
That's why I'm saying that.
Maya taught me how to say hello.
That's right.
How about the others?
KOTONE-senpai,
It's only been a year, but
Yuno-chan is, how should I say this,
She's like a senpai.
There are 5 people who have been doing
anime for a long time,
and there are people who are in a
difficult position.
But from the senpai,
Yuno is like a senpai.
But from Yuna and Emma,
they make a line group,
and if there's something you don't
understand, they'll ask you to listen
right away.
They're so kind.
That's what it's like to be a senpai.
That's a good way to put it.
They're so kind.
If you're doing it live, you'll learn a
lot from them.
I see. That's a good way to put it.
I use it when I buy something for my mom
or senpai.
That's a good trick. I can see that in
you.
This program was brought to you by
Asamu-san, Chiaki-san, Ragu-Negi-san,
Niko-Emma-chan-Daisuki-Haruka-chan, and
Capricorn-san.
Thank you very much.