Yakan and Idol
What was your favorite thing when you
were a kid?
Idol!
I think I was watching a lot of TV when
I was in 2nd grade.
AKB48, Momokuro, Ebichu.
I really liked those idols.
I had to go to a club when I was in
elementary school.
I was in a dance club.
I was on the stage of the gymnasium.
I sang and danced to Momokuro's Kaito
Shoujo and AKB's Gingame Check.
I practiced a lot of songs.
But I didn't think I would be an idol.
I just liked watching idols, dancing,
and saving money on the disk.
I just liked buying things for New
Year's Day.
Is it a strange feeling to be able to do
it yourself?
It's a strange feeling.
At first, I was working as a model for a
magazine and a play.
Then, I got a call from my manager on my
way home from school.
He said, I'm thinking of making a dance
vocal group.
I thought it was cool to have a lot of
multi-talented people.
I'm not a very smart person, so I can't
do both.
But I was interested in idols, so I
decided to do it.
How is it now?
The number of songs and the large venue
has increased.
Did you have a deeper bond with the
members?
Did your thoughts on idol activities
change?
Each member has given their opinion more
than ever.
I think I'm the same.
I've been thinking about it myself, but
I don't share it.
I think I can share my thoughts and say
what I think.
I think I'm aiming for the top.
I think I've become one of the people
who want to do my best.
I think it's good now.
Did you hate it?
I don't hate it.
I think I can do more.
The second element is an idol.
It's a big part of my job.
I think it's a big part.
I don't know what to say.
What do you mean?
H.Y.007, Ibuki Daichiki GT-O, and Anri-
san.
Thank you for watching!
Today, the 20th, the second album will
be released.
Please listen to it a lot!
And please tell me your favorite songs!