Please subscribe to my channel!
Look at my sleeves!
Kaho-chan! Kaho-chan! Kaho-chan!
I'm not in a hurry!
Because today is our first Kamburi show!
I'm not in a hurry...
The last episode?
Let's go!
No!
I don't want to end it!
I don't want to end it either.
What should I do?
This is...
But this is the same as last time.
That's not true.
It's because of the
drawing.
One, two, three, four.
Sit down.
That's right.
Something is wrong.
What is it?
Hey, it's good.
It's good.
Huh?
My mouth is moving.
It's good.
Is it good?
Do you want to eat?
Rit, do you want to eat?
I ate a little bit.
You're laughing, but you're right.
Do you want to eat?
Eat slowly.
I ate it!
You ate it!
Do you want to eat more?
I ate it!
It moved!
Do you want to eat?
I'm sorry.
Is it good?
You laughed.
No, don't do that.
It's good.
Did you stop for a while?
I'm not sure if I should move.
It's hard.
That's what I'm talking about.
Okay, thank you for watching.
Today's guest is...
360 degrees, wherever you look, idol,
lucky seven, Hoshina, Mirei and...
Yes, I'm the adult, the child, and the
number 9, Matsuha Rina.
Thank you for having us.
We've been waiting for you.
We're so glad to be here for the last
episode.
We're so glad.
We have to do it too.
I'm the first in the class, number 11,
Kobayashi Kaho.
I'm the second in the class, number 12,
Riko Nakayama.
Thank you.
Solemi and Kaho, please send your
questions to social stream.
We are waiting for your questions.
Please send us your questions.
Thank you.
Then, in the first corner,
Shall we bring chairs?
Alright.
Everyone, everyone is going?
No, it's fine.
Alright.
Thank you.
Today,
Oh, right, before that,
Two people.
Thank you.
Let's do a self-introduction.
That's right.
I think there are still some people in
the family who know about it.
Then, let's do it here.
Self-introduction.
That's right. Let's do it because there
are still people who don't know about
it.
That's right.
Let's do it together.
Where should we start?
Let's start from the beginning.
OK.
Then, let's start from the beginning.
That's right.
My self-introduction is...
I'm called ジャンケン, so after that, please
say ポー.
ポー! ポー! ポー!
And when I say, コッチ むいて, you can say
ポーちゃん.
ポーちゃん! ポーちゃん!
Okay, then, everyone, please say ジャンケン.
Okay.
Ready, set, ジャンケン! ポー!
アッチ むいて! ポー!
ジャンケン! ポー!
コッチ むいて! ポーちゃん!
Thank you.
I'm the singer and the dancer, number
11, Koba Yoshikawa.
Nice to meet you.
Yay!
Next, I'll introduce myself.
Everyone, please follow me.
Let's do this together.
Please pay attention to thegething
rapping line.
We will turn the mic around, so please
say RITAN.
Lastly, we will say together, so please
say EIEO.
Let's go.
Rikosan Sanadayoshi, let's go!
Ready, go!
Let's say EIEO together!
Thank you.
Thank you for the
RITAN!
I'm Riko Nakayama, the number 52 in the
class of Sasoriza.
Nice to meet you.
I thought of it before, but I'm also
from Sasoriza.
We're the same.
So I'm a middle schooler from Sasoriza.
I'm a middle schooler from Sasoriza.
I'm a middle schooler from Katagora.
I'm a middle schooler from Kaniza.
I wanted to say this.
I thought we were the same.
We have similar vibes.
Really?
We were at the handshake event
yesterday.
We were like Mirei's sister.
That's right!
I'm happy.
Kaho is
very similar to Ayaka.
We're the same height.
Yeah!
But really,
we're similar to Ayaka.
We are.
You're often told that.
We have similar vibes.
But we have similar ways of talking.
We're similar.
We have similar actions.
We have similar hands.
Like this.
We have similar faces.
We're similar.
Then...
Let's eat one more.
Here.
Mirei, look at this.
Let's eat one more.
It looks delicious.
What is it?
Cookie?
Cookie and tea.
Oh, there it is.
Thank you.
It's tea.
It's relaxing.
Where is the center?
Here?
The center is off.
Where?
This is amazing.
This research center.
It's amazing.
Right?
Where is it?
How do you sit?
This is Rina.
This is Mirei.
Thank you.
It's been a while since we filmed a news
show.
It's been a while.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm glad.
We have questions.
Yes.
Are they coming?
They're coming.
Have a good time.
I'll make some tea.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
It looks delicious.
I want more.
This cup and this cup are different.
It's like a Japanese style.
It looks delicious.
We have questions.
The question is,
How many songs did you master in the
song Ebi-Chun?
How many songs?
We did 19 songs in Osaka.
Did you master 4 songs?
We have 23 songs.
Let's think about the songs.
Let's do a pre-release.
Sakurago Round.
Sorry, Matsuno.
I'm not going to do this alone.
Matsuno, can you do it?
I can.
Then eat a lot of corn cookies instead.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm spilling a lot.
Thank you, Rina.
Thank you.
Let's count.
We did 25 songs.
We did Battle Royale Fect.
25 songs?
Yes.
We did Rock Lee.
We did a lot of songs.
We did 20 songs.
We did Kori Kenyaku Ebizori.
We did Pakuchi.
We did Odorogari Benjuu.
We did a lot of songs.
We did 25 songs.
That's amazing.
It's amazing that we can do so many
songs in a short time.
We can be full of energy.
I don't think I can do it either.
That's right.
That's amazing.
Let's go.
The announcement of the tour DVD
Everything Point 2 that was announced at
the sub-bill meeting the other day and
the pattern of the tour Osaka on the
first day and yesterday Kanazawa.
Here it is.
Please.
It's fast.
Where are we going? I want to eat!
What?
Let's eat!
I can't eat!
We are ABiTU!
Let's go to the concert!
ABiTU!
Fighting!
The first day of the school.
This is the place where the real thing
starts.
Pocky and human.
Pocky and shrimp head.
Drink it.
It's too sour.
What is this?
Is it in your head?
It's in the Pocky.
Come out, Pocky.
I want to get in too.
It's fun.
It's popular.
It's hard to breathe.
It's dangerous to get down.
Hayate is dangerous.
We're going to take a sexy shot
together.
Let's get in together.
What?
It's impossible.
I can do it.
I can't.
Wait.
I'm scared.
It's more fun to dance than to sing.
That's not it.
It's more fun.
I'll watch.
Okay.
It's more fun to dance than to sing.
Thank you for watching!
Let's keep going
When the wish comes true
The memories of being born, the memories
of being loved
My feelings are spinning, spinning,
spinning
That's why I love you, Elfie
I can't make you laugh, but I can't show
you my cute attitude
My feelings spill out like rain
When will that be?
I'm not a blue, but my feelings are not
always honest
I want to tell you now
I bloom for you
This is the bonus talk corner after the
school performance!
There are three halls in this tour, but
we will do this corner in that hall.
Since we couldn't do a free talk during
the live, let's have fun here!
What do you want to eat when you go to
Osaka?
There are a lot of delicious food in
Osaka!
Takoyaki, dojo, okonomiyaki, pork!
What do you want to eat?
Takoyaki, I guess!
I guess I'll have an ice-doc again!
What do you want to eat?
Since we're in Osaka, I'll have
takoyaki!
What about you, Mirei?
I'll have kushikatsu!
What about you, Aya-chan?
Aya-chan, are you going to say it all?
Aya-chan, what about you?
I guess I'll have an egg!
What about you, Rika?
I guess I'll have okonomiyaki!
What about you, Ayaka?
I guess I'll have takoyaki!
I got it!
Let's do our best for our free live
debut!
We're going to be the best!
We are the best!
I'm looking for a girl who's perfect for
a princess!
Prince, that's only me!
Please make a contract with me!
Please make a contract!
K.A.I.I.
Kari Kari Kari Marike!
Kari Kari Kari Yatsudou!
Princess...
K.A.I.I.
Dellonyoh!!
talkin about the stunt
oh,SAVE AN OPEN FACE
cutie
I'll be back!
ing
in
It was fun yesterday.
It was fun.
It was our first time at AkiSky.
It was our first time at a live show
outside.
It was amazing.
What was it?
We talked a lot with the fans.
Me and Aika and Kaho were in the same
room.
Kaho looked really happy.
Aika and I were like,
Kaho is amazing.
It was our first time, so we were
nervous.
But everyone was saying it was fun.
It was fun.
There were only people who couldn't do
it.
It was fun.
It was amazing.
Next to me was Aika.
I was with the fans at the end.
I said, A-A-O.
When I went to Aika, she said, A-A-O.
We were doing it together.
We were imitating her.
I had to say, don't imitate me.
A-A-O is that.
It started from the show.
Now it's Rikuo's theme.
When we were at AkiSky,
we were told to do it together.
Did you do it properly?
I did.
When we were doing it, Aika was next to
me.
I'm glad.
You guys were divided into groups on the
same day.
Yes.
I was the rock-paper-scissors.
Really?
Now we're just randomly deciding.
It's fun to see who you're with.
It's fun.
The places are different.
The places we stand on are fun.
It's nice outside.
It felt good.
It rained a little.
Did you stop when it started?
I stopped.
It was raining.
It was raining when we were in the
middle of the school.
We were in the middle of the school.
Riko-chan was always behind me.
She was always like, what is that?
What is that?
Kanazawa-ji.
She taught me.
I wanted to go there.
I want to go there again if I have the
chance.
We went there a year ago.
But at that time...
There was a big park nearby.
It was like a garden.
We went there to play.
It was sunny so we went there.
We played in the ball at the school.
We played.
We played in the ball.
I had fun.
We were talking.
I wanted to finger flick ShikiAI!
I thought the ball would come to my
face, but it came to someone else.
It was fun.
Me, Rina, Ayaka, and Mayuma were
watching anime on our phones.
We were really focused.
We were watching it on the bus.
We weren't done yet.
We were watching it like this.
Ayaka and Rina fell asleep right away.
We didn't notice it at all.
We were on the bus and we were on for
about 2 minutes.
We were watching it for a little longer.
We definitely watched the first episode
until the end.
We were watching it for the first
episode.
We watched one episode.
We watched it for the first episode
until the end.
We watched until the second half.
We said we'd watch it together.
Maemon fell asleep too.
I was like, what? I was like, I'm not
going to do it alone.
I didn't know that.
That happened in the back seat.
Everyone was trying to survive.
It was a sad tour.
Next episode is going to be a perfect
one.
I don't want to do that.
You guys have done a lot of live shows.
And you did a free live show.
ZEPP is a live house.
What is a live house?
It's where people are having fun.
And they cheer for us.
It's like the one I imagined.
It's amazing.
I can feel everyone's passion and power.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's my first time on a jet ski.
It's a double-deck.
There are various songs.
There are various changes.
So we have a question.
Here it is.
Sorry. There are many.
What is your favorite dance part in
Butterfly Effect?
Dance part?
Where is it?
Do you want to announce one by one?
Let's start with Kaho.
Dance choreography.
I like the beginning of the song.
I like the part where everyone is
beautiful.
What is your favorite part?
I like the last part of the song.
That's cool.
What about you, Ui-chan?
I don't know.
I like the dance because it's very
unique.
I like the part where I can't go back to
the same story.
What is your favorite part?
Riko?
I like the part where she goes like
this.
The butterfly.
That part is good.
There are so many parts.
It's cool.
I like the impression of the song.
Let's do it together.
It's different.
Let's do it together. together.
Which one? This one?
This one is successful!
Ah, this one too!
Ah, this one is the opposite!
It's successful!
Well, this one is natural.
Well, this one is also successful.
It's not the usual pair, but we did our
best.
There are many interesting poses, so it
might be fun to make a pair with the
family members.
What should I do?
Please tell me quickly!
We haven't been to Nagoya in the middle
of the trip.
We haven't been to Nagoya.
It's our first time in Kanazawa.
We're going to a lot of places for the
first time in this tour.
What are you looking forward to the
most?
I'm looking forward to everything.
I like Oita prefecture.
There are a lot of good places in Oita
prefecture, so I like it.
Please look forward to it!
I want to go to Oita prefecture.
You go to Oita after Ehime in Oita
Ebichu.
Ehime and Oita have never been to
I'm nervous.
Is it your first time?
It's my first time.
I wonder what will happen.
Where is the Tsunau Final?
Yokohama.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's my first time in Yokohama.
Really?
I'm going to Kanagawa prefecture.
I'm going.
Soccer?
Yes.
Tour?
Is it okay?
Before that, I'll ask you.
Okay.
I'll ask you questions.
Please send us your questions.
Please!
Anything is fine.
Please listen to us.
We only have this chance.
This is the last one.
The last one.
The tour is over.
Then,
there's FAMIEN.
I watched FAMIEN on DVD.
So I thought I'd go.
I was looking forward to it.
Somen, kakigoari,
and barbeque.
I was looking forward to it.
I wonder if I can do it this year.
We didn't know
if we could eat somen or barbecue.
We didn't know.
I said I'd go.
I was riding in the air.
I was like, I'm here.
We were all in a daze.
It was like a festival.
There were a lot of people looking for
us. We were so happy. We were playing
with our masks on.
We were playing with our masks on.
That was so cute.
We wanted to do that again.
We used water.
We did the watermelon thing.
I thought it was going to be fun.
Thank you very much for your time.
It's not a live performance, but a
festival.
We sing a lot, but we sing while having
a festival.
We eat shaved ice and do that.
I'm looking forward to it.
I want to be an anime character.
What should we do if we get even more?
Last year, it was Kawaguchiko, but this
year it's Yamanaka.
I'm looking forward to it.
I thought you were particular about the
lake.
There are many lakes around Yamanashi.
I thought there was a connection.
There is a school in Ogasuku when I was
in elementary school.
That school was in Yamanaka High School.
I went to Yamanaka High School every
year.
I was very happy.
Thank you for your viewing.
I often went to the forest school.
It's been a long time since I went to
the forest school.
I see.
What was it like?
It was full of nature.
There was a stick-on thing.
I saw that for the first time in
Yamanaka.
That's amazing.
Thank you for your viewing.
Didn't you play with it often?
Yes, I did.
It hurts a little.
It tickles.
I went to a mountain in my second year
of junior high school.
You went there.
Yes, I did.
My friend had a bug.
It was round.
I thought it was an almond, so I touched
it.
It hurts.
Yes.
It was a real bug.
A real bug?
Yes, it was a bug.
I threw it.
It hurts!
It hurts, right?
I'm looking forward to it.
It's like shaved ice.
It's like summer.
It's amazing.
Did you get a question?
I got a question.
I'm going to eat cookies.
I'm going to drink it.
What is it?
Who do you want to form a unit with?
I'm fine.
I got a little bit wet.
Are you okay?
I'm crying.
I'm fine.
Who do you want to form a unit with?
It's hard to choose.
Are you okay?
Did you guys already form a unit?
Mirei and I haven't formed a unit yet.
Really?
Who do you think? Who do you want to
form?
What should we do?
I want to form a unit with Kawa-chan.
I want to form a unit with Chuu-ni.
Kawa-chan, you want to form a unit with
me, right?
I don't know.
But...
I want to form a unit with a lot of
people.
Yeah.
That sounds fun too. Yeah.
I've been pretty...
There's been a lot of two-person groups.
Yeah, Natsu and Hoyu.
Mizuki and Hirono.
And Kame-sama no Yutori.
Yeah.
There's four of us. Thank you.
Four of us are the best.
Yeah.
Who do you want to form a unit with?
Who do you think I am?
I want to form a unit with MIRETO.
I thought so.
I want to form a unit with MIRETO
forever.
I know.
I've been saying this since the
beginning.
I haven't been able to do it yet.
I might be able to do it.
Really? I want to do it.
Rina, you were a triathlete friend for
two years in a row.
Yeah.
I see.
After that, we were in the same group.
So you've been with me for 3 years? 確かに。
That's amazing. でも、ユニットとかも、
If we were to do a unit,
もし、ユニットをやるってなったら、
I'm looking forward to it. 楽しみだな。
I'm looking forward to it. 新しくなりそうだよね。
The atmosphere is different from before.
今までと雰囲気みんな違うからね。
I'm looking forward to it. 楽しみ。
I want to do it with Kaori.
カホリコとも組んでみたいかも。
I want to do it. この4人でも一緒に組んでもいい?
That's good. もうそれでいいよ。
I want to do it. やってみたいよね。
What kind of song would you like to do?
曲はどんなのがいい?
僕はあの曲が好きだよ。 ディアンスが好きだよ。
私はあの曲がすごく好きなの。 本当? ありがとう。
でもね、ミレイちゃんのね、あのあれも可愛いの好きなの。 君にサンキュー。
ありがとう。
恥ずかしいね。 ユニット曲結構私の好きな感じの曲多くて。
本当? ユニットの好き? でも、盛り上がる曲あるじゃん?
でも、なんかマヨマヨのさ、あの、野月さんのね、
あれも、あれも好きだなって思って。
かっこいいから。 かっこいいね。 マヨネットちゃんの当たり目?
もう好きだ。 ミレイちゃんとの。 あーいいね。
スキだね、あの曲も。
So, we are going to play Rose Shake,
which is a song by Circle K's Sankus.
It was released yesterday!
I'm going to go get it.
Thank you, Riko.
There are 3 different flavors.
What should we do?
It looks delicious.
Let's start with the winner.
I know that Mire is aiming for the same
thing.
I'm aiming for the same thing.
I think Riton is aiming for the same
thing.
Let's start!
I know what it is.
Hurry up and take it.
I've never had strawberry before.
Really?
I had it when we were shooting.
I've never had strawberry before.
Really?
Maybe it's not strawberry.
I'll give you a bite.
It's a drum.
Riko, you won.
I'll take it first.
Which one will go first?
This one!
I can't drink vanilla.
Really?
Can I have it later?
Sure.
Since there's something delicious,
I want to do a food report.
Sounds good.
I can't do a report.
Me neither.
Who will go first?
I lost.
Let's go with Kaho.
Let's start from the beginning.
I'll do my best.
Look at this delicious-looking
container.
This cute, stylish mark.
And this cute combination.
I'll open it.
Bye!
It's vanilla flavor. It looks delicious.
It's a very delicious fruit.
I'll eat it.
Please eat it.
Will you swallow it?
Do your best!
I'll eat it!
I think it's better to let it float.
It's delicious! This is a revolution!
Even with the vanilla, you can drink it
forever.
I want to drink it forever. It's a
delicious taste.
How is it?
Thank you for watching.
It's good. Thank you.
Riko-chan, please look.
What is this mark?
Isn't it a rose knife?
Maybe...
How does it taste?
It's good!
The one we had before was crispy, but
it's good even when it melts.
You can drink it while it's hot.
You can drink it when it's too hot.
It gets cold even when you drink it and
warm it up.
It's good when you mix it with the
microwave.
It's good when it's cold.
It's crispy and good.
You introduced us to a good way to drink
it.
Please subscribe to our channel.
It's hot.
It's good on hot days.
Let's start with Mirei.
Mirei!
I don't need that.
I know Mirei.
In this beautiful container,
there's this chocolate frozen.
It looks delicious.
The smell of chocolate is amazing.
It is.
Let's try it.
It's a little sweet, but it's delicious
and hot.
Even when I'm feeling down, it's like
it's making me feel good.
It looks delicious.
I'm thirsty.
I'm going to do it after Rina.
Rina.
Please look at this beautiful pink.
There's crab meat in it.
I'm going to eat it.
Amazing.
There's crab meat in it.
It's so good.
The strawberry is so juicy.
It's mixed up.
It's really good.
It looks good.
Is it good?
Thank you.
Strawberry! Strawberry! Strawberry!
Delicious! Delicious! Delicious!
It's delicious, isn't it?
I'll have some too.
Strawberry is delicious.
Thank you.
I've never had it before.
The chocolate is delicious too.
Choose the flavor you like.
Please look for it.
Go to the nearby Circle K Sanks.
It became like this.
It's delicious.
It's very delicious.
I've been drinking it all the time.
I'm a little tired of time in a little
while.
It's fast.
It's really fast.
It's been only a minute.
It's started.
It's really a short time.
It was fun today, right?
It was fun.
I'm glad we came.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you.
We're both a little tired, but we'll do
our best.
We'll do our best!
We'll be waiting for you guys on tour,
too.
Bye bye!
See you later!
Thank you!
Bye bye!
Good luck!
Thank you!
Thank you for coming!
Bye bye!
Wait!
Don't lie!
No, I'm not!
How was it?
How was it to come to the last floor?
How was it to come back now?
Well,
I think the sixth floor was
really short.
We spent a lot of time together, but it
was a great experience.
I'm glad that we got along with
everyone.
It was fun.
What about Riko?
I think I got to know a lot about
Kaoriko in this program.
Thank you for coming to the program as a
guest.
I think she's gone.
Thank you.
I heard your voice.
Let's wrap up.
Thank you for watching SoRiMi's
KahoRiKo.
Thank you.
This is Shiritui Bishu School, number
11, Kobayashi Kaho.
And number 12, Nakayama Riko's SoRiMi.
SoRiMi's Kawaii Kou!
Bye bye!
We'll see you again at the next SoRiMi's
SoRiMi's Kawaii Kou!
Please!
Thank you for watching!
See you on the phone!
We'll be waiting!