I was looking at the other girls, and it
was totally different.
I couldn't do it. I was so sad.
The final evaluation is approaching.
The students are being chased.
I don't want to be an idol, but I want
to be Ebichu.
Please do your best until the end.
One step to the dream.
Who will take the seat of the new Ebichu
member?
I'm going to do the seduction style.
On the first day of the training camp,
10 students who completed the high-level
lessons are in the second task, the
lesson of the song, I want to seduce you
I will go to the sound and take a video
of each group and it will be over
I want to seduce you
Team Bariki continues to practice with
Ruri who is good at dancing.
Nonoka, the youngest in the class.
The youngest, Yuria.
The three of them are a good unit.
The girls are Remi, who is from Osaka
and is the brightest person in the
world.
Miumi, a sports girl from the handball
club.
And Emma, who has a 10-year dance
history.
Anyway, the three bright girls.
Team Okaiwa, Kanori, Karen, Yuna are the
middle school students and Yuka is the
high school student.
They are challenging the complex
formation as there are more people than
other units.
guardsrin
Thank you very much.
They have practiced in advance
The lesson is going well
Yuka is practicing
Meanwhile, Yuka is watching other
members dance
Thank you
I thought I was pretty good at dancing
But I think the younger member is better
than me
Yuka is crying
I Vis–Equi on SNSbranch concert, lado
йside
I'm a new middle schooler
It Changed when I watched other Japanese
dances
Thank you for watching.
Let's go!
She's the only high school student in
the unit,
but she has no experience in singing or
dancing.
She felt a sense of achievement.
And the junior high school student,
Yuna, looks fine.
I've been doing a lot of things I
haven't been able to do.
I'm a little impatient.
Who don't know?
Just as whether you would gohemت bracket
holds the anxiety for a long time.
I'm waiting for you to come back
I'm not sure if I'm going to sleep
I'm not going to sleep
However, even though they practice,
their anxiety is increasing.
I think that I am not able to do it.
I feel like...
I am not able to do it.
I feel like I'm not getting along with
them.
I think I have to work harder.
The others around me are too good, so
I'm not sure if I can do it.
I'll do my best not to be left behind.
The trainees have worked hard to
practice.
But this is an audition.
Not everyone can pass.
As the final evaluation approaches, the
anxiety is getting to the brain.
I'm going to the waiting room.
We'll go through the high-tech and the
things we want to do, and fix the things
we can't do, and then we'll sign a
contract.
Let's go.
I want to get closer to you, I want to
find you, but I can't stop this feeling.
I want to seduce you, I met you and fell
in love.
I want to tell you, I want to fly to
your town.
My heart is shaking, oh my god.
I want to tell you that I'm not allowed
to do this
I'm not even proud of myself
They have one more day to practice
The second day of training camp has
passed
The third day of training camp has
Before the lesson, at 8am, the students
are in the hall.
The reason why they are so eager to
learn is...
The last song was released on the first
day of the training camp.
To challenge Cinderella of temporary
contract
To finish this song, which had not been
practiced at all
The choreography was put in the head
with the old pitch
Okay.
We'll be back in 50 minutes.
I'm going to perform.
It's hard to perform.
It's hard.
This is bad.
I'm going to perform at a concert.
I'm going to be even worse.
I'm worried if I can remember it.
They are going to perform at their
concert.
I'm going to perform at a concert.
The Ebitu members came to the training
camp to see the audition students
I feel very nervous
I'm very nervous
I have to perform 1000 songs in 4 days
I don't think I could do it last year
I think it's amazing
I'm very curious because there are many
people who think it's good
Let's take a group photo
I want to be a shrimp-chan, not an idol.
I love it.
I've always been a shrimp-chan, and I've
always wanted to be one.
Everyone has been longing for this
audition, and they've been challenging
to become a member.
Before they can show their desire, they
will perform a dance for each unit.
I'm looking for a glass doll that can
make me a shrimp-chan.
I'm sorry, but please make a contract
with me.
I want to be a princess, but I don't
think a princess will look at me.
I'm a princess, but I'm a goddess.
My dream doesn't end.
I'm not a toy. I'm a human.
I want to be a goddess, but I don't
think a goddess will look at me.
I want to be a princess, but I don't
think a princess will look at me.
I want to be a goddess, but I don't
think a goddess will look at me.
Thank you.
Thanks for watching it to the end
See you in the next video
ugui
Thank you for watching!
Then, we showed the original partners
for this guys.
This
Are you still
Isawa Genki.
Thank you very much for watching this
video
Thank you for watching!
Yuka comforted Karen, who was younger
than her.
She could only hold back her tears.
And with the rest of the cast…
I'm just looking at it
I've become a star
I'm sure it will be a success
I'm a star
It's not over yet
Yes, good job
Hold on
She is not able to reach the quality
that can be shown to people by the
practice.
I practiced the choreography last night
and the day before, but I couldn't do
the details.
I wanted to do the details, but I
couldn't do it.
I couldn't do it at all.
I'm so upset.
When I'm happy,
I can't remember where I stand.
I turn white and fly away.
I think I have the impression that I
can't do it.
I'll practice more and come back.
Miumi has been practicing harder than
anyone else.
I don't know where I stand.
I have to be at the second place.
I'm at the first place.
When I look at the other side of the
screen,
I'm at the second place.
I'm so close.
I wind up sticking around.
I've gotten in a swamp.
Castle 봐
But somehow third will come
I want to be an idol, but I also want to
be an Ebitu.
The afternoon lesson starts.
Thank you.
Let's get started.
Let's get familiar with the song.
They practice singing along with
dancing.
However...
You should practice while moving!
They practice dancing along with
dancing.
Let's do it together.
If the choreography is different, we
can't sing in this short time.
Let's think about it together.
Ready, go!
The teacher is also trying hard to teach
the students to complete the
choreography in a short time.
The first attack!
The teacher is trying to teach the
students to complete the choreography in
a short time.
The teacher is trying to teach the
students to complete the choreography in
a short time.
The teacher is trying to teach the
students to complete the choreography in
a short time.
The teacher is trying to teach the
students to complete the choreography in
a short time.
They finished three songs in three days.
Everyone knew it was impossible.
The judges wanted to see the most
difficult challenge.
This is an audition to enter Ebichu.
I wanted to see if I could show myself
entering Ebichu.
I wanted to enter Ebichu and sing and
show myself.
What would it be like to enter Ebichu?
Rather than wanting to be an idol,
I hope that people will want to enter
Ebichu and audition until the end.
I think it will be a good result.
The students who practiced desperately
to learn the songs of the challenge.
But they wanted to become Ebichu more
than learning the songs.
They wanted to show their feelings.
I don't know why they practiced so hard.
They wanted to enter Ebichu, but they
couldn't.
I'm sad.
They practiced hard to enter Ebichu.
I was hoping that I could appeal to the
members.
I decided not to cry until I passed the
audition.
The 10 students who have survived the
training camp with a strong desire to
become shrimp-chewed shrimp than the
others
have suffered from the frustration that
they can't express their feelings well
The 10 students who have survived the
training camp with a strong desire to
become shrimp-chewed shrimp than the
others
The live stream of this day has ended,
and the hall...
I am this girl.
I am Yagirin.
Thank you for watching!
Also,
The last group dance
They want to be the shrimp-chewed
Even though they can't express
themselves well, their dream is only one
That's why
I need to practice the suspicious parts
I'll do my best to perform well
It was fun to dance with everyone, so my
facial expression is complete
They just need to move forward
And then
They are practicing the dance
The 10 competitors who competed in the
audition
They were tied by a hard bond towards
one goal
I will definitely be a member
I want to show that I want to be like
this
I want to enjoy it with everyone so that
I can express my feelings 120%
I will do my best to perform well, so I
will definitely be a member
I want to appeal to the members
I want to express that I want to be
shrimp-chewed
I want to be shrimp-chewed
I want to show my feelings fully and
challenge myself
I will definitely pass
I want to do my best to understand that
I really want to be shrimp-chewed
I want to be shrimp-chewed
I will do my best to perform well, so I
will definitely be a member
They are practicing hard