Thank you for watching!
Translated by Releska
I want to be a bright idol with a lot of
smiles.
I've never been so crazy about it.
I never had a dream like this.
Before the audition,
I always liked idols.
But now I know how hard it is to become
one.
I know if I deserve to be one.
So...
I've never had a strong dream.
I have been doing calligraphy since I
was in kindergarten.
When I was in junior high school, I was
the chief of the calligraphy club.
I have been doing calligraphy since I
was in kindergarten.
I think it's the only thing I can
concentrate on.
I was born in Sapporo.
This is Sapporo Station.
I always go here.
This is my familiar city, Sapporo.
I always use this station when I go to
school.
Sapporo is peaceful.
This is the illumination.
This tree is also beautiful.
It turns blue.
I know.
It's cute.
I was a student representative.
I was curious about what I wanted to do.
And my best friend said she would do it.
I got used to it.
I was used to planes and trains.
At first, I thought it was a train
romance.
But there were too many lines.
That's it.
I feel like I'm crying.
I was talking to him while eating
something.
I was discussing school.
I want to eat Furi-Kura.
I was a student representative and a
club president, but I was a person who
just slept.
I think I was someone who didn't fit the
title.
Sleep? Kanji is...
I love sleeping and I'm always sleeping,
so I'm a sleeping woman.
But I don't know the kanji.
Like this.
I'm the type who always goes to bed
early.
But I couldn't sleep as much as I
thought.
I was listening to music all the time.
I don't think about anything.
I'm going to push you.
I'm going to step on you.
Come on.
I'm not good at dancing.
I'm trying to keep up.
It's fun to talk to them.
I'm happy to hear their dance and their
voices.
I also enjoy talking to them.
I'm happy to hear their voices.
I was told about it.
I didn't feel safe at all at home.
I reported it to my mother who was
downstairs.
My mother took care of me.
I said I was a little lonely.
After all, I was a friendly parent and
child, so it seems that it is lonely to
be gone.
I can't go home often, so I'm lonely.
I got a coupon, so I'll use it all up.
I'll use it all up and come back here.
I'm going to the White Love Park now.
The White Love Park is a candy factory.
There's a candy store.
And there are a lot of candy.
It's a little park with candy as the
theme.
It's like that.
When it's the perfect time,
soap comes out,
and the clock starts to turn.
I'm looking for that.
It's a change of mood.
There are flowers, too.
I'm looking for that.
I came here with my friends two years
ago for Christmas.
It was fun.
I remember this tree house very well.
It was my dream to live in a tree house
after seeing this.
I'm going to Shirakawa Station.
Thank you for coming today.
I'm going to start.
When I was in elementary school, I fell
in love with Keyakizaka 46.
I started to have a longing for it.
When I saw it on TV,
I was interested in its human nature.
I was recommended by my sister.
She was more enthusiastic than I
expected.
She took a lot of pictures and did a lot
of things.
I will do my best to the maximum.
It's just less than what I've
experienced with the favori Mehrusja.
My dream is to keep going my own way
if I am the woman I love.
Thank you for watching!
I couldn't feel anything.
I couldn't feel anything for days.
I've always been a fan of this group.
I didn't feel like I was part of that
group.
I couldn't feel anything.
I'm a bit stubborn, but I think
Hinatazaka is the most like me.
What's the title of your new song?
I'm going to eat rice.
The first group is...
3, 2, 1
I'll go first.
We're a warm group.
I think we're suitable for this.
You're cute, Yuki!
I'm Yuki from Ushishima.
I'm here.
The first group is...
3, 2, 1
I was so nervous that I couldn't even
write.
Recently, I finally got the costume and
the members were decided.
When I was asked to shoot, I finally
thought that I could become a member
like this.
I'm Hinata.
Number 15, Kaho Fujishima.
I'm not nervous, and I'm very happy.
I want to tell my mother as soon as
possible.
I'm a heart that doesn't move.
I was doing a long, and I read the
proof.
I didn't think about it, but the other
kids were saying really good things, so
I tried hard to add it.
I've been studying 論語 since I was in
kindergarten, so I'd like to introduce
my favorite shokus.
志の玉枠,君子は義に悟り、精進は理に悟る。
I want to be a great human like this
shoku, and shine on the stage of dreams.
Thank you very much.
I'm talking about when I think about it.
I'm ready.
Pose!
3, 2, 1.
My favorite part is...
I put my whole body in the picture.
I eat a lot of sweets and sleep in a
taxi.
I think I look more like myself when I
smile.
What is the difference between you and
the other members?
I often wonder why I was chosen here.
But I still think I'll do my best.
I want to live naturally.
I've always loved idols, and I've been
given courage and a lot of support from
them.
I hope I can be a support for someone.
I think it's a job that brings smiles to
people.
I want to do my best to bring happiness
to people.
Thank you very much.
I will continue to work hard without
losing my smile.
I will work hard to become an idol who
can work hard to the maximum extent
without losing my smile.
I'm KAHO FUJISHIMA, 16 years old from
HOKKAIDA.