Tonight is a special occasion. For
Yasumoto Kobayashi, who was born in
June, a surprise birthday party for the
members is held.
They give presents with gratitude to the
members
What is this?
I don't know
And they write down their feelings that
they can't say out loud
Their feelings
There are three of us
Please continue to be friendly
A happy birthday party start!
ㅠㅠ
Tsukuba Eiz Buri
Avalanche
The Welt
Itwe
Tsukuba Eiz Bub
Thank you for watching!
Because she's a girl.
Now, we will have a birthday party for
two people
Chie-chan, you look like a housekeeper
Chie-san, please say something to
celebrate
Why are you laughing?
I'm happy
Please make a funny joke to celebrate
I did it
Happy birthday, Yasumoto Kobayashi!
Yes
And, more than anything, today's prank
was a huge success!
Yeah!
Bye bye!
Bye bye Saipan!
Saipan, you did it!
I've never seen that before!
I make it everyday!
Thank you!
Now, we have a present for the two of
you!
What is it?
The present the members chose with their
hearts to make the two happy!
First, what present did Matsuno choose
for the two of them?
First, Aya-chan
I always do weird things to Aya-chan,
but please take care of me from now on
too!
Thank you!
I don't have enough, but please take
care of me from now on too!
Let's start with Yasumoto
This is really scary
This is the one I wanted!
It's a
I asked my dad to make this many times!
Sometimes, your Japanese is weird
You can ask for it
Thank you!
The two of you started dancing
What? Yasumoto is crying?
Wait, I'm not crying
Matsuno is crying too
That's good
The other members are under pressure
This is the one I wanted the most
And what present did Kobayashi choose?
This might be hard to understand
First, I'll put air into this
I got it
It's a hard to wear Shinkansen
I see
I'm not crying!
It's good!
It's a pillow!
Yay!
Please calm down, Kobayashi-san
How is it, Kobayashi?
I use it!
I don't want to see it anymore
It's the first time
Who is the least confident?
I'm scared!
Almost everyone!
Everyone!
Let's start with Hirota
No! I really don't want to!
No!
A present from Hirota for the two of
them
It's heavy, but it's this
Yes
I haven't said anything yet
The innkeeper has been caught
Aya-chan is the one who cares the most
about everyone
I want you to be more honest
Yes
Congratulations
I've been thinking that I can't bother
others, so please be more spoiled.
What is the present for Kobayashi?
No, I don't have anything for you
Sorry, sorry
You are right, you don't want to attract
attention
What is it?
Tea
I don't know what it is
What is it?
Kaho likes tea
So I want her to drink it
It's a set of tea from a green tea shop
That's good
She drinks it
She likes tea
Thank you very much
I thought of Ayaka's present as a tomato
What is the present for Toma's love,
Dekopin girl Yasumoto?
What is this?
Salt
Salt?
I was surprised
I was surprised and dropped it
Pink salt is the best for tomatoes
It's my favorite salt
Also, I think it's interesting that it's
called Shichimi leek salt and Yuzu salt
Because tomatoes are salted and it's
slippery
Actually, my brother loves this kind of
salt
But it's expensive
So I can't buy it easily
We always reach out our hands but he did
it with his eyes
That's right
That's why I was surprised
Next, the present from Nakayama
You look so relaxed
He is kind and funny
I love you, Aika-chan
I don't want to say anything
Kaori-chan is still crying
Kaori-chan, let's play a lot
Thank you
Shall we open this from Yasumoto?
No, no
Kaori-chan
From Kobayashi
Can Dekopin open it?
Why?
There is a order
Because there is a order, Nakayama will
open the bag by herself
Let's go
Wait
Kaori-chan
What's wrong with you?
We are not going
What happened?
Who are you?
Ahhhhhhhhhh!
What happened?
We are not a team!
Not yet!
Kaho-chan...
Riko has this too
Kaho-chan has always...
Kaho-chan likes this series
I got a message the other day
Riko-chan's series is available, so you
can buy it
Riko bought it already, but Kaho-chan
said you can buy it
Wait, wait, wait!
I found Riko's series, so wait for it!
Wait for it!
I see
Thank you!
And...
There is still one more
No, no, no
Study hard!
Go, Kobayashi!
I don't know how to do the number
division!
I don't know!
The present for Yasumoto is...
A skirt!
Oh my god!
What is this?
It's cute!
Aya-chan!
I want to see Aya-chan's face
Please change your clothes
It's a good chance
Yasumoto rarely wears skirt in private
She changes her clothes as a present
Yasumoto-san, please
It's cute!
Is this a duck mouth?
What is this pose?
How do you feel?
I'm shy
It's cute!
I'll try to do this
That's good
One more time
Thank you
One more present
What is that?
It was fun
I want to remember
I want to do this
That's good
Nakayama took out a rubber balloon
Why did she get a rubber balloon as a
present?
We were going to play with balloons when
we stayed in a hotel room
It was really fun when Yasumoto made us
laugh with balloons
How did she make us laugh with balloons?
Let's see
It's recommended to blow a balloon like
playing a gold-plated instrument
Let's try it
Music start!
What is this?
Almost
Happy
Ahhhh
Can I make a sound effect on your face?
Encore! Encore!
Do it with your right hand
Once again, the music is very popular
Music start!
What is this?
Is this a turban?
Hoshina broke it
That's amazing
She regained her spirit and gave a
present to two people from the mountain
Well, Yasu
What?
What is it?
I'm happy that you did it like this
Congratulations
Thank you
She is so happy
Kaho, I think you should be more
confident
You often say that you don't want to
wear a mini skirt, but I think you
should be more confident
Congratulations
Thank you
The present for Kobayashi is...
A watercolor colored pencil
It's cool
It's like a drawing
Kaho-chan always draws on a sketchbook
but she doesn't paint
Mayama secretly watched Kobayashi
drawing only black and white pictures
A colorful pencil as a present
Thank you
You paint well
Yes, I will paint well
And the present for Yasumoto is...
I want to send a letter to Yasu who has
grown up recently
Yasu, you have grown up?
That's not it
I thought it was a letter
I don't think I would write a letter to
Yasu
Oh no!
It looks like an egg
That's wrapping
It's difficult
What is this?
Hand cream and argan oil
I don't like Yasu to be sticky
I use it only a little or use it on my
hair
Can I use it on my whole body?
Can I use it anywhere?
Yes, anywhere
It contains vitamin E and is very good
for your health
Why do you use it only on your hair?
Do you use it?
I use it too
Next, a present from Hoshina
Aya-chan, thank you for making me laugh
I'm worried that I might be worried if I
wear a towel
Don't do that
I'm going to have a lot of fun with you
I'm going to use it on both of you
Kaho-chan, you always make me laugh even
when you are tired or not feeling well
Please keep smiling
Thank you
What is this?
This is
If you put the chilled juice in it
And mix it
You can make frozen
Oh, that's good
I want my sister to use it
Please use it together
I haven't drink frozen before
You can drink it at home
Thank you
Thank you very much
That's good
And the present for Yasumoto
What is it?
Sentai Ranger?
Peach color?
What is it?
I can't understand
Please enjoy taking a bath
Thank you
That's good
Please take a bath
Next, the present from Kashiwagi
Lai-chan
Yes
There were many things happened until
now
What happened?
There were many things happened between
you two
Please be friendly
What happened?
What? What?
She is crying
I'm sorry
You had a lot of things
She is a girl
I'm sorry
Kaori-chan, thank you for always being
so sweet
Please let me tackle you from now on
The present for Kobayashi is...
Cute!
It's a good one!
I wanted to buy one!
And, Yasumoto who has just solved
something
Good morning
Wow! What is this?
What?
It's very fashionable!
I thought Aya-chan would be cute!
It's a bandana
It's cute!
The one you put on your hair?
It's the place where I was studying the
art of accessories
At first Ai-chan said it's fashionable
to wear a hat
But I thought I should wear a hairband
instead of a hat
Try it on now
It's cute!
Say welcome
The presents filled with love
With a smile and tears
Yasumoto and Kobayashi
The hand-made birthday party will be a
climax after this
Kobayashi, there is a letter from the
same generation Nakayama
A letter?
The youngest of the shrimp family, the
same generation Nakayama and Kobayashi
Because I'm with you from the ordinary,
I wrote my feelings that I can't say to
you in a letter
Well, to Kaho-chan, Happy Birthday
Thank you
I feel very relieved when I'm near Kaho-
chan
I'm having fun
I feel relieved
This year is the third year of junior
high school, so I have to study hard
Use the junior high school drill
Let's study hard together
And I want to go to many places
Will you die?
Nakayama's voice is getting hoarse
I'll be in your care forever
Riko Nakayama
Thank you
It's been a long time
When they were reading the letter, the
person next to them was the first one to
answer
The answer that I don't remember
It's good
I heard the words that I was very happy
and relieved when I was near her
I didn't tell her my true feelings
I'm glad I was able to enter the show
with Riko
It's the same
Grandma
Grandma, it's not grandma
Grandma, the main character is over
there
I didn't think about it
Here, Yasumoto-san also received a
letter
Mayama, you're back, right?
You're amazing
I don't think I can give him a letter
Mayama was lying to him in a shy way
They are the longest friends among the
Ebitu members
What will the letter Mayama write for
the first time say?
Mayama, I love you
Where should I start?
Why did you start from the middle?
You should have edited it yourself
I don't know what to say
This is the first time I'm writing a
letter to Haya-chan
I don't know what to say
For now, hello
Hello
Haya-chan doesn't like to be called a
good girl
I don't say it often, but I think she's
a good girl
Because no one is worried about being
called a good girl
The good girl that Haya-chan imagines
may not lie, complain, and be liked by
everyone
But I don't think I'm getting along with
Haya-chan as much as I am now
Because I don't think she'll come from
the bottom of her heart
I think I was depressed when I became
the MC of the three of them and I was
worried about not doing well
I was happy that you said no when you
didn't like me and gave me advice
Thank you for your patience
I've become more reliable and I don't
talk about it much these days
But you can rely on me sometimes
I'll be very nice to you
You want to be nice to me?
I love you Haya-chan
Always
I'm sorry
Thank you for noticing me when I was
depressed
Thank you for listening to my story
I look forward to your continued support
and happy birthday
Thank you for your good work.
I don't know.
What did you think of the letter?
I thought of the time when I was the
most worried in my life.
Mayama was the one who always helped me
at that time.
I'm so nervous.
I can't express it in words.
I'm so overwhelmed.
You remembered a lot of things.
It was a good letter.
Thank you.
You two received a letter. How was it?
Kobayashi.
I want to be friends with you.
She is a real person.
She has a soul.
Happy birthday.
Yasumoto and Kobayashi.
I haven't forgotten the other person
until June.
June 25th is my birthday.
Happy birthday.
I'm sorry.
Who is it?
So, when the birthday party is held
during the preparation,
Yasumoto's V-Sendam will be closed.
BBQ! Let's go!
Next time on Ebichu Tastas, we'll be
having a barbecue that's a wish of the
members!
And the Ebichu Game Project is also in
full swing!
This program was brought to you by the
following sponsors.
It's so good!
It's the scream of the heart, right?
Yes!
The scream of the heart!
Please subscribe to our channel!