This week's Ebichu Tastas is the Ebichu
Women's Power Contest
I made too many fried chicken today,
should I stop?
The members who show a more automatic
side of themselves
Did you do it?
What is the power of women that Ebichu
thinks of?
And also, a perfect monitoring of the
food scenery that shines with women's
power
Then, let's start the calm Ebichu Tastas
Jun! Jun! What should I do with the
heart of the
Monatorium! Monatorium! Monatorium!
Junior high school student!
We will add many things to the private
Ebisu junior high school!
This program is brought to you by the
sponsors you see.
It's too funny.
I cried.
Now, it has started. Ebichu Tastas!
It has started.
I have to turn off the air conditioner
to prevent Hoshida-kun from breaking his
mic.
That's right. From now on, everyone will
use air conditioner.
The mic has become air conditioner.
What are we doing today?
The first Ebichu Girls' Power
Championship!
I didn't think this competition would
exist until now.
This time, we will test the girls' power
in various ways that Ebichu should have.
Who will be the best girl power?
First, before we start the test, let's
ask who is the member with the highest
girl power.
The member who has the highest girl
power in Ebichu is...
Yasumoto-san.
Yasumoto-san, you will do it.
I will try to do my best while I am not
good at it.
I think I am not as good at it as
everyone.
Aya-chan.
I don't say that I have the girl power
if I really have it.
I think that's the case.
Please stop it.
Anyway, the two of you don't have the
girl power.
Once again, we check the members who
have the girl power.
Mayama and Hoshina.
Everyone chose Mayama and Hoshina.
By the way, Mayama and Hoshina, what do
you think is the girl power?
I think they have the most cosmetics.
They have a lot of cosmetics.
By the way, Hoshina was also chosen.
What do you think about Hoshina?
I think she looks at the mirror.
And she often touches her hair.
She doesn't change much, but she is
still pretty.
She doesn't change much.
She always looks at the mirror.
I think it's important to always be
pretty.
It is a pre-evaluation that Mayama and
Hoshina, who are conscious of beauty,
have a high girl power.
Who is the really high member?
This time, the special judge will judge
the girl power.
Yoshi Nana, a communication manners
instructor.
He will judge various women's
I will judge harshly.
May I have a moment?
The theme is girl power, right?
Yes, the theme is girl power.
What's wrong?
It's amazing.
Is it a girl?
No.
Yoshi is a former man.
He is a former man.
He is very beautiful.
Please say more.
He is a former man, so he is pursuing
the ideal image of a woman.
I have to be conscious of women and men.
I have to be in love with women.
Yoshi is conscious of her high girl
power.
Let's have Yoshi verify the girl power
of the shrimp.
First round is...
The first round is the girl power of the
shrimp.
The girl power test is not only about
fashion, but also about the inner
appearance.
So please be aware that it is not about
the appearance.
In this test, you will be given a
question about the situation in which
the girl power is required.
If you can answer with a good girl
power, you will get points.
The first question of the girl power
test.
The first question.
You were invited to go to the amusement
park by your friend.
But you had another schedule that day.
How do you refuse?
Please write it down on the paper.
It's okay to write it down as if you are
always writing to your close friends.
You can make it yourself in this
setting.
I always write it down.
First of all, Matsuno's answer that she
actually uses it often.
Sorry, I cried.
I have a schedule that day.
I'll tell you when I'm free again.
My friend's schedule comes to me.
I'll tell you when I'm free.
We're doing that.
How about this?
This is one point.
Why?
If there is no heart letter, it is the
same as a male mail.
It's like a girl.
It's a girl power.
Please answer with a higher girl power.
Next is Mayama's answer that the member
evaluation is higher girl power.
Thank you. But actually I was drunk that
day and I put it in. Please invite me to
another day.
Wonderful.
She got 8 points.
As expected of Mayama.
Yes.
Where is this?
The most wonderful thing about this is
that you can put the word thank you at
the beginning.
As the person who invited, you are
worried about it.
But you accept it as a thank you for the
invitation. This is wonderful. You have
a high girl power.
When you say no to a mail, you should
choose a word that makes you feel happy,
not a negative word.
Many members have already said sorry,
but Hirota got a high score.
When he heard the difficulty of the
answer, he was surprised.
The second question of the women's power
test.
The question from the super embarrassing
situation.
How will he answer the difficult
question?
The next question is...
While eating with friends, I suddenly
farted.
What is a girl-like response?
Please say this in a high-pitched tone.
Hoshino-san, please make a sound of
farting.
A cute sound.
After that, you should follow the fart
you made.
I got it.
Hoshino-san, please make a sound of
farting.
It's a long fart.
Please make a sound of farting.
Something came out, right?
Okay, then let's do cute one.
Cute!
It's a boy.
If you fart like this, it's not a boy's
fart.
Please pay attention to Hoshina's really
shy expression.
I'm in a hurry.
Hoshina's shyness is highly rated.
She has more points on her facial
expression than her cheating.
Let's continue.
Yasumoto-san.
Yasumoto-san seems to have noticed that
her cuteness is important.
What is her answer?
Yasumoto-san, let's continue.
A woman is coming out.
I'm cute.
Done?
What is this?
4 points
Amazing
It's Watanabe's 3 points
It's an advanced level
It's embarrassing but it's funny and
humorous
It's cute
Let's continue
Matsuno, let's go
I farted
What's wrong? This is delicious
It's good
It's a good habit of girls to shake it
like nothing happened
I see
So it's similar to the two of you
So it means that you don't shake it
But there was someone who shook it
I got it
So you're an advanced person too
I'm an advanced person
So it's either one
I see
Ebichu found out that there are various
patterns in the female power
So the third question is
The theme is to answer the lines that
seem to be very feminine
What kind of answer will come out?
Oh, Yasumoto
Matsumoto
Let's go
Are you injured? I'll give you a bandage
Wonderful
3 points
You shouldn't shake it too much
Hoshino
There's trash on it
2 points
Yasumoto-san
Is it heat?
It's zero
What is the power of women?
The members who answer
I borrowed this towel the other day
I want to wash it and return it
Wonderful
Let's go on
Kobayashi-san, it's your turn
I'll take a note of the amount of time I
took a break
Good
Hirota, it's your turn
I made too much fried chicken today, do
you want to eat it?
Fried chicken is good
Nagayama-san, it's your turn
Thank you for coming today
How was it? You just showed your charm
I'm good
Everyone is saying thanks to you
Kashiwagi
This is my usual thanks
What is this?
It depends on what you say
That's right
What is it? Kashiwagi, squeeze it out
Kashiwagi, do your best
Chuu-san
I'm the one who's the best
It's a good song
When Chuu-A showed her true power,
Kashiwagi was surprised
Kashiwagi cried
It's too funny.
I don't know but...
I want to give it to her.
It's okay to be shy.
The tears of the loan shark is worth 1
point.
So, the members who have been crying out
loud with the most girly lines.
As you can see, the current score is 1
point.
Now, what's the content of the next girl
power check?
The second round is the monitoring of
the girl power of the shrimp.
The second round is divided into two
teams of four people.
The team will monitor whether the girl
power is good or not in a separate room.
The second round is to monitor the usual
behavior and determine the girl power.
The members will be divided into two
teams and experience the daily scenes of
eating and cleaning.
The monitoring teacher will add points
to the girl power.
As a result of the monitoring, Mayama,
Yasumoto, Matsuno and Kashiwagi will
check their girl power with their meals.
Hirota, Hoshina, Kobayashi and Nakayama
will challenge to clean up.
First, let's check the cooking team's
cooking skills.
We will be watching the cooking team's
cooking skills on this monitor.
Sensei, what are we checking?
We are not checking the table manners.
We are checking whether they are
enjoying their meals and how they treat
their guests.
We will be watching how much they are
enjoying their meals.
So, there might be some people who are
misunderstanding the table manners.
It might be too strict.
After this, the women's power monitoring
will begin.
The members who have high female power
during meal time are monitoring the four
members.
Please sit down.
Thank you for coming to our house today.
Thank you.
Please put it in the bowl.
Rina's bowl is quite...
How do you do this?
But you don't know how to put it out.
I'll give you a separate plate.
But your expression is dead.
I'm nervous.
I don't know what to do.
How about raising your elbows that high?
That's a little rude.
Women's power is to tighten the armpits.
If you tighten your armpits, you look
like a woman.
By the way, I saw this.
Now, you're giving out chopsticks and
stuff like that.
Do you usually do that?
I do it for Mayama.
You do it for Mayama.
I do it for Rina.
I'm surprised that Matsuno moved.
I'm trying to do something.
I see.
You think you're giving out chopsticks,
right?
I think it's better to give out
chopsticks.
I'm not good at eating like this.
You can do it.
You can do it yourself.
That's a good idea.
It depends on the person.
It's not good to do everything for them.
It's important to listen to them.
Please turn the camera.
I'll take a picture of the temperature.
Thank you for coming to my house today.
Thank you very much.
Let's have a wonderful night tonight.
Lucky.
It's a toast.
It's like a saturday.
It's delicious.
I'm nervous.
It's my first time to eat.
It's your first time.
I'm not used to it.
What should I do?
I'll eat it with fish.
Matsuno will eat it with fish.
I see.
I haven't said it yet.
I'm curious if you can say it's
delicious after eating it.
I see.
I'll eat it with fish.
It's good.
Matsu-chan is also eating.
Kashiwagi also ate it, right?
Kashiwagi-chan also ate it.
It's a waste because the fish's face is
frozen.
Please move the fork.
You think it's too much, right?
Please subscribe to the channel.
I can't bite it off.
But I can't bite it off, but I can smile
and say it.
Does Yasumoto do that?
Yes, she does.
The dressing is delicious.
I'm glad.
I made it myself.
What's the special taste?
It has nuts in it.
Wow, it's fashionable.
It's good, right?
What's wrong, Sensei?
I think the two on this side don't look
delicious even if they eat.
When they eat, they smile, which is very
feminine.
I love eating.
You look happy.
I'm happy.
Thank you for your viewing.
I'll give you 2 points.
The first time I ate 2 points.
The people who are with me are healed by
their smiles.
Shibagi is very nervous.
Shibagi looks angry.
I'm always with Yasumoto. Is it okay?
I want to give Yasumoto points, but I
don't have any.
This is the end of the women's power
monitoring.
Thank you very much.
Was it delicious?
It was delicious.
I couldn't eat it because it was so
delicious.
Are you okay?
Matsuno-san, you ate a lot, right?
Yes, I ate a lot.
I enjoyed this atmosphere the most.
That's the most women's power.
I love eating.
I love it.
Matsuno enjoyed eating the most.
The second half of the women's power
monitoring will continue next time.
Please look forward to it.
《Sakuraebi's Front Line》
《Ebi Chu's Research Unit 《Sakuraebi's》
《First One Man Live》
《Sakuraebi's》
《Third One Man Live》
It's been about a year and three months
since the group started.
The original song of Sakuraebi's is
finally completed.
What kind of song is it?
The original song is finally performing
for the first time.
I want to find my answer with you
If you say you like me, the world will
begin
I want to find my answer with you
We start to wish strongly
Thank you for listening大阳
Please subscribe to my channel!
Let's dance together!
And another song
Here is a surprise
This is a song for 6 people
Maachan
Serizawa Moa
The first performance with 6 people
I want to be by your side
I don't want to make a mistake
in the promise we made that day
I want to be by your side
I want to be here with you
I want to see the beautiful scenery
I want to be with you
Don't give up
Don't doubt
Keep running
Don't give up
Don't doubt
Thank you for watching!
Until that day,
on the way to the destination of our
dreams,
we will be shining.
Look, now it's definitely shining
We are SAKURAI BEES!
Thank you!
Who finished the concert?
Is it different from the last one?
Yes, it is.
Everyone's faces are different.
So I think each of them did well.
SAKURAI BEES, someone want love?
SAKURAI BEES!
Next time, we'll have the final of the
women's power competition.
Maybe Nakaima hasn't done anything yet.
I'm doing it for now, so I'll wait.
The shocking end of the cooking
competition is...
What?
Next time, we'll have the final of the
women's power competition.