The BOSS and KOBUN have finished their
performance.
Thank you very much.
Last time, I had a set list of what the
members who will be appearing in the
show would like to do.
I hope that BOSS and KOBUN will be able
to do a great job.
No one sent me a list.
I asked them later.
Why didn't they send me a ballad?
Why didn't they think of sending someone
else?
They all said they thought NO NOKA would
do it.
They all said YUNO would do it.
It's all people's fault.
That's why the list was like a ghost.
But I think it was a good set list for
BOSS and KOBUN.
I think.
I'm glad there was no ballad here.
I said it at the live show.
I thought the three of them had a lot of
determination and hard work.
There were three or four songs that I
did for the first time for the three of
them.
I was on stage the day after.
I had a lot of fun watching it.
I want to thank everyone who came to see
me.
The singing is also better than before.
In this project, I want to sing this
part to everyone.
I want to hear this part of the song.
I just want to hear it.
I was able to hear the parts that I
couldn't hear.
I was satisfied and everyone said it was
fun.
I'm sure everyone will enjoy it.
I think I was able to do it.
They joined the group a year and a half
ago.
I have one month left as a member of the
group.
I thought it would be the best if the
three of us could teach them directly.
I was really happy to be able to make a
live performance with the three of them.
They have really grown.
They have no choice but to grow.
Of course, I also gave them advice.
Sometimes I was strict and strong.
But they absorbed things really fast.
Of course, my strength is...
I've always been dancing.
I really like singing.
I like music, but I'm not good at
singing.
But today, I felt like I was really
fighting.
I think it's because I had the effort to
sing that much.
I was surprised that the teachers and
the people who listened to me were able
to recognize me.
I practiced a lot.
I realized that practice and effort
don't betray each other.
I was able to prove that.
I tried to perform on stage today.
Yuno has a really mysterious charm.
Iov 엄 going to have fun.
There may be things that Yuno thinks she
can't do yet,
and there may be a lot of anxiety,
but Yuno is just moving on stage,
and I think Yuno's character is very
strong.
Yuno's character is not easy to find.
That's what I'm going to show you today.
I think it was hard to have so many
lessons.
I was happy that she enjoyed it.
YUNA is the type of girl who works hard
and looks good.
I'm glad that she was on stage today.
And I think NONOKA is the type of girl
who works hard.
I've never seen her like that.
So I was worried about her.
I thought she was sleeping.
I thought she was taking a break.
During the lesson,
she was taking a break.
She was practicing in front of the
mirror.
She was done with her lesson.
But she was practicing in front of the
mirror.
She told me to do it while I had the
But I thought she was doing too much.
Is it really hard?
I think she is hardworking.
That's why her singing and dancing are
growing fast.
I felt that her performance was getting
completed.
I saw the three of them dancing and
singing close up.
I also learned from the three of them.
I was happy to see the three of them
growing up close up.
I realized that this was the only
concert that only these four of us could
do.
Thank you so much to everyone who came
and supported us.
It was fun.
See you again.