Yes, Kashiwagi Hinata produced performances 10, 13, 14, 15 Boss & the minions ended successfully. Thank you very much.
This time, the Boss & the minions, as in the previous years, I always ask the members what they want to do.
The members of the group would give me their suggestions on what they wanted to play, and I would then put together a set list for them.
But none of them sent me a single ballad.
I asked them later, "Why didn't you have a ballad? I asked them later why they didn't have a ballad, and they said, "Didn't anyone think of including one? I said, "Why didn't anyone think of including it?
I said, "Well, I thought Nonoka was going to put it in, or Yuno was going to put it in, or Cocona was going to blame everybody else, and it was just a matter of time before it was done.
Everyone blamed everyone else, and what we ended up with was a set list that looked like a ghost in terms of physical strength.
But I was glad that it was Bostkovens' setlist.
I was glad we didn't play a ballad.
As I said at the concert, the weapons of the three of them are their dedication and desperation.
I thought their dedication, desperation, and hard work were their strong points.
And since there were 3 or 4 songs that were new to the 3 of them this time, I thought it would be great if we could show that on stage.
It really showed on stage, and it was a lot of fun for me to watch, and for everyone who came to see them.
And the singing, too, was a lot more fun this time than in the past, because the singers were asking everyone to sing.
I was able to ask the audience, "I want this girl to sing this part," or "I want to hear this girl sing this part," or "I want to listen to this girl sing this part.
I was satisfied because I could listen to the parts that I don't get to hear often because I just want to listen to them.
I was satisfied with the show, everyone said they had a good time, and I'm sure everyone at the Fumiri who came to the show enjoyed it as well.
I have about one month left in my career as a new member of Ebitu and about one month as Ebitu, and at that point, the three of us had joined.
At that time, when the three of them joined us, I thought that they would be the last ones who I would be able to directly instruct and teach in various ways.
I was very happy to be able to create a live performance with them.
The three of them have really grown up. They have so much room to grow.
Of course, I gave them lots of advice, sometimes harshly and sometimes strongly.
Cocona, of course, has always said that her strong point is dancing.
Cocona said that she was good at dancing, and I said that I liked singing and music, but I was not so good at singing.
I think the fact that Cocona was able to sing so well is due to her effort, and I think that she was able to learn from the teacher and me.
I think it was because of her effort that Cocona was able to sing so well, and I think it was Cocona who proved to me that practice and effort do not betray you.
I was reminded of that after today's performance.
Yoon-ho has a really mysterious charm, and of course there may be things in his singing and dancing that he still doesn't know how to do, and there may be a lot of things that he's worried about, but I was able to see him moving on stage, and I was able to see him in action.
But just by watching Yoon-ho on stage, I felt that Yoon-ho's character came out very strongly, and there are very few characters like Yoon-ho.
I was most happy to see that Yoon-ho had a lot of fun in today's performance, even though I know he had to work hard and take a lot of lessons.
Yoon-ho is the type of girl who is suited to work really hard, so I was happy to see that he showed that a lot on stage today.
I have never seen a girl who practices so hard or works so hard as Yoon-ho.
On the contrary, I was worried that she was sleeping, or if she took a little rest, she would practice in front of the mirror all the time, even in between lessons, when everyone was resting.
I told her to review in front of the mirror while it was still there, even though the lesson was already over, but she really did it, to the point where I thought she was overdoing it.
That's why he is developing his singing and dancing so quickly.
That's why their singing and dancing are improving so quickly.
I have watched the three of them dance and sing up close, and I myself have taught them some things, so I was really happy to see their growth up close again.
I felt again that the performance by BOSS and Ko-Boon and the others was a concert that only the four of us could do.
Thank you so much to everyone who came and supported us. It was a lot of fun.
See you again.