So, this year is the birthday party?
Yes, it is.
It's a kimono for my grandmother.
What is that?
It's totally different from what I
imagined.
One of the guests said,
there is a gyaru.
I was like, oh, this is a gyaru.
So, I decided to go to the gyaru forest.
I see.
And I didn't write it on the map.
You didn't write it on the map?
Isn't it too much?
I didn't write it on the map.
I'll write it on the map.
Yakan and Idol
Welcome to the show. I'm Yakan, a former
student at Viva Home.
Let's welcome today's guest idol.
This is the idol.
I'm Yawaka Yasumori from Iginari Tohoku.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, Yasumori-san.
Thank you.
Thank you. Nice to meet you.
It's been a while since we had a New
Year's holiday.
I didn't expect it to be this special.
How is your New Year's holiday?
I had a day off for the first time in a
while.
Really?
I think I've heard of it.
Yes.
You told me about it.
I had a summer vacation in Tohoku for 5
days in a row.
It's been a while since I had a day off.
I'm happy.
You're a year older than me.
Do you have any plans?
I have a kotatsu at home.
I want to relax in the kotatsu.
Is it an indoor kotatsu?
I recently became an indoor kotatsu.
I was an outdoor kotatsu when I was a
high school student.
I couldn't stay at home.
I thought so.
I turned 20 this year.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
I'm going to be an indoor kotatsu.
I'm happy to stay at home.
You're going to be an indoor kotatsu.
Yes.
Is it a New Year's party this year?
It's a New Year's party.
Did you take a picture?
I took a picture.
What color is your furisode?
It's my grandmother's kimono.
It's different from the image I had.
My grandmother has two kimonos.
There are red and light blue kimonos.
I wore a red kimono at my friend's
wedding.
I wanted to wear a light blue kimono at
my friend's wedding.
I see.
I wanted to see my grandmother's happy
face at the wedding.
I think so, too.
I think you're a family man.
I knew it.
I'm a family man.
You're a family man.
Did your mother wear a kimono?
My mother wore a red kimono.
I wore a light blue kimono.
What a wonderful story.
Do you show your furisode to your fans?
I will post my personal Instagram on my
birthday.
Your fans are watching your video.
I think so, too.
That's a good story.
Your daughter will be in the fourth
generation.
I bought a new obi.
I can wear this obi for a long time.
If I have a child, I want to wear this
obi.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I wasn't aware of the gyaru at that
time, but the audience said,
There is a gyaru.
Oh, is that so?
I was told that.
This program is
Nanana-san
Yuri-san who loves WAKARIN so much
Takusan
Ria-san
This video is brought to you by Succhan.
Thank you everyone!