The N Stephanie
Nteri
Fight
Test
devrait
withdraw
Oh, Arawaa
Sakaori
Hmm
I slept well
I slept well but I feel like I slept a
lot
Because
The place I slept last time was
Last year
March?
It's been a long time
It's been a long time since I woke up
Nice to meet you all
Hello to everyone who has not been for a
long time
Are you watching? It's already started,
isn't it? It's really been a long time
since I wore this costume
It's been about a year, isn't it? But
it's been about 10 months, isn't it?
Isn't it amazing? How is it? Nothing has
changed
My height and appearance have been so
long, but I haven't changed at all
That's how I feel, but I think I should
look back
I think a new member is coming today
Where is she?
Is she not here yet?
What kind of girl is she?
Is she still here?
Konkon!
Hello!
Sorry!
Konkon!
You just said Konkon with your mouth,
didn't you?
I didn't say it
Are you okay?
I'm sorry
So, the two of you are here
Hello
First, I would like to greet everyone
who is watching
I will go first
I'm Mizuki, number 1 in Shirito Ebisu
Middle School
Thank you
Please go ahead
I'm Kobayashi Kaho, number 11 in Shirito
Ebisu Middle School
Thank you
I'm Riko Nakayama, number 12 in Shirito
Ebisu Middle School よろしくお願いします
Are you okay?
I'm nervous
It's a happy feeling
But it's okay
I hope you can see their cuteness and
happiness
They are watching us with warm eyes
Right?
It's okay, it's okay
It's a show for two people
It's the same as the previous show
I was alone and I was very nervous
But there are two people
So when you are in trouble, you can
cooperate
I think it's okay if you can proceed
with two people
Okay, so...
It's frozen, but...
Is it okay?
It hurts so much!
It's okay, right?
Let's do our best!
Okay!
So, about this show...
Let's start with the explanation.
Well...
Is it okay?
Can you explain?
It's starting, right?
Is it okay?
I don't know the explanation of this
show, so I'd like you to explain it.
It's a good show!
私たちが シェーツ エビ76に 無事 入学した ということで
夜の夜の ここの 実験室で 秘密の 実験を 行って
立派な 生徒として エビ中に 化学反応を 起こすための 実験過程を
観察してもらう という番組です!
Thank you! It was really easy to
understand, right?
It was easy to understand, but the
reason is because I'm reading the
script!
Are you okay?
Well, Mizuki-kun, you're going to
participate in the experiment today too!
I'm not really nervous, but I wonder if
it's okay?
I'm nervous and I'm trying my best to
make a character, but I'll do it.
Is that what you're wearing for the
experiment?
It's really cute.
It has a number on it.
I don't have a number on it.
There's a shrimp in it.
The shrimp's eyes are off. Are you okay?
It's in the
shrimp's eyes.
Look, it's jumping out.
It's been 10 months since I've been
wearing this costume.
I can't help it.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I've been wearing this costume for 10
months, but I don't have shoes.
It's different from the previous
costume.
I can't help it.
I've been here for a long time.
It's a two-man show, so I'm going home.
But...
I'm wearing this pillow every time I'm
with Kimizuki.
I'm sorry.
I'm attached to this pillow. I'll leave
it to you two.
What? You're leaving again?
But...
Wait!
You're Kaoriko, right?
We're making this show together.
But...
Even if it's just the first corner...
Please!
It's only the beginning.
Yay! I won!
But I don't know what will happen if I
say it.
Well, then, I'll say it for a little
while.
I won!
And, if you look at it like you were
doing it,
I think it's better to ask questions to
the viewers.
If you can interact with the viewers,
you can do it.
I think it's good. I recommend it.
Amazing!
It's deep. How should I say it?
I'll say it this time, so you say it
yourself.
Please ask questions to the viewers of
Soremiro. Please choose one at the end
of the program.
We will answer all the questions. Please
send us lots of questions.
We are waiting for you.
Please make Social Stream lively.
OK.
We will proceed like this.
Shall we start the corner?
Yes.
The first corner of the commemoration
period is...
Are you ready?
I feel nostalgic.
I've been doing this for the first time
in 10 months.
I'm quite nervous.
Excuse me.
There's a chair.
I'm sorry. Thank you.
Let's go to the corner.
Okay.
First...
Let's sit down.
Excuse me.
This is fun!
This is great!
Okay.
The first corner of the commemoration
period is...
The experiment corner to see if you can
tell us who you are.
Yay!
So, this corner is...
We just joined Ebichu, so we want you to
know more about us.
Okay.
We haven't been told anything about
ourselves yet.
We're going to do a quiz about
ourselves.
Since we're here, let's have Mizuki
answer.
Me?
Yes.
I'll answer.
Is it okay?
They asked us to come here, but I
haven't met them yet.
This is the second or third time.
I don't know if they know this more than
the fans,
so I think the viewers will think about
it together.
I'll use my ability to move around and
do my best.
Then it might be okay.
I'm not sure about that, but let's try
it.
Let's try it.
First, in the first corner...
First, here...
There are 4 cards, A, B, C, D.
Please draw one from there.
I just have to draw one, right?
Please choose one.
What should I do?
I'm nervous!
Please.
The question is...
What animal do you want to see first
when you go to the zoo?
I'm going to draw this.
I'm going to guess.
Please guess.
Are you going to draw something?
Two people?
Yes.
Minseo, you have to think and answer.
Are you going to draw this?
Yes.
Two people?
What is it?
Yes.
Please draw again.
What should I do?
I'm going to draw A.
I'm surprised. I'm not sure if it's the
same, but it's not the same.
I don't know. I don't know the animals
in the zoo.
I haven't been to the zoo recently.
What kind of zoo is it? What should I
do?
Should I draw a picture of it?
What is it?
I can see it!
I'm sorry.
What should I do?
You two are going to think about it now?
Yes.
What is it?
There's no animal that I like.
There's no animal?
We haven't won yet.
Then I'll draw that.
What should I do?
That's it.
But I'll draw the yellow one.
I'll go with orange.
Then I'll go with the animal that came
to mind first.
Is that okay?
Okay.
I want to see it.
What should I do?
If you want to see it, you can't.
But I'll think about what I want to see.
I want to see the
What kind of animal is there?
I'll repeat the same thing, but I want
to see the animal that came to mind
first.
You didn't say 《Dobutsu》.
You said 《Dobutsu》 by Shouni.
I can't remember the song.
I made a mistake.
This is dirty.
OK.
《Dobutsu》
I think I got it.
Is it okay to answer with one?
One.
It's like two people are in one.
That's right.
One.
Is it okay?
Is it different?
I don't know.
Can I see it?
Can't we see it?
I think it's okay to answer with two
people.
Cool.
Cool, right?
I don't like it that much.
But it's the first one I think of.
Okay. The first one I think of is... Can
I say the answer?
The first animal I think of is...
What was it again? The first animal I
want to see in an animal park is...
Koala!
So cute!
What?
What's the answer?
From Koala?
The first animal I want to see in the
zoo is a lion.
I thought it was that kind of animal.
The character is cool.
Riko said it was cool.
I said it.
It's a big animal.
The lion is a king of beasts, so I think
I'll take a look at it for now.
Isn't it scary?
I want to raise a demon.
A demon?
Is that possible in the zoo?
But it may be different.
I don't know.
No, it's not. I want to see it.
It's a lion.
It's cool.
That's why I chose orange.
It's perfect.
It doesn't match the color.
That's good.
The answer is a lion.
It's a lion.
It's out.
What about you?
Monkey. 可愛い。 言い方かわいい。
言い方が可愛いね。 ウチだったら猿って漢字で書くの。
猿って漢字あるの? あるけどもう。
全然可愛さが違う。 猿さんか。 外れちゃったな。
大きい輪になんと思うイメージが一番最初に頭に浮かんだの。
私は動物園で最初に思い浮かんだのがコアラだったの。
コアラかペンギン?
あ、ペンギン!
あやし、カンガルー出てきた。
カンガルー?
でもライオンの方が強かった。
面白いね。
私はね、コアラしか頭になかった。
コアラが好きだから。
コアラが可愛い。
見たことあるかは分かんない。
見たことあるかもしれない。
じゃあ、もう一問やろう。
じゃあもう一問。
じゃあこの中から選ぶの?
あ、この中から一問選んで。
C. Well, I chose C.
I chose C.
A, B, D.
What will come out?
Is there any question that is easy to
answer?
Well, whatever.
I'll choose A.
The question is...
Well...
カホリコが犬を飼うとしたらつけたい名前は? If you were to buy
a dog, what would you name it?
難しいこと言うね 本当に 犬苦手なんだよな 当たるわけないでしょ
当たる人がいたらすごいよ じゃあ書いちゃいます 書いて書いて 赤にしよう
博士になった気分で 当てられちゃう どうしようかな
でもさ種類によるよね 犬の種類による そうだよね 結構ね 大きい犬とか
ちょっと小さい犬とか それによってイメージも変わらない?
変わる いいじゃん 何でもいい 何でもいい 何でも 何でも
あれ? 開かない 大丈夫? 大丈夫 何だっけ あれ忘れちゃった 忘れちゃった
ですね
簡単なの? これメガネしても変わんないな 全然分かんないよ 思いつかないよ
えー? 何しよう
名前かー 私猫飼ってるんですけど 名前つけるとき 特に何も考えなかったんだよね
何しようかなー 犬でしょ 犬
犬? 書いてる音がそろそろ聞こえる
すごいね
It's so simple.
Me too.
It's simple.
It won't close.
It's fine.
Okay.
Is it okay?
What should I do?
Anything is fine.
I only have one thing in mind.
I think this is fine.
I think it's different.
The name I want to name my dog after I
think of it is Pochi.
So cute! Pochi!
But I thought of Pochi.
But I'm not.
I'm Patrash.
What is this?
I don't understand.
I like that one. I want to call it.
Patrash.
I wanted to call it.
I want to call it Patrash.
I want to say it.
You're going to bite me, Kaho.
Patrash.
Why Patrash?
It's like a conversation.
Oh, that's why you want to say it?
Yes, I want to say it.
That's why you chose Patrash.
I've heard of Patrash.
It's cool.
Patrash.
I didn't think of something so cool.
It's very simple.
Coco.
Cute.
It's a toy poodle with brown color.
It's perfect.
And Coco.
It's a simple name.
I wanted a toy poodle with brown color.
Same.
I still want it even now.
It's cute.
If a cute dog like Coco's name is cute,
I'll be a boss.
It's so cute. Are you raising a cat?
Yes, I'm raising a cat. What's your
name?
Ryu. Oh, cool.
It's cool. It's not written. It's not
written.
It was an animal problem. It was good.
It's funny.
I think I know a little bit about
Kaoriko.
I wonder if anyone who got it right.
I think I know.
It's simple.
I wonder.
I hope you understand.
But that's it.
Mizuki-san, you can't eat marshmallows
because you didn't get it right.
It's a reward.
It's a reward. I love marshmallows.
It was here. I knew it.
It's right in front of me.
In front of you.
There's a stick.
Next one?
You can see it.
Can I show you?
Yes.
Do you know that I love marshmallows?
Wow!
I told you that I love marshmallows.
I said a lot of important things.
But this time it can't be helped.
It's time for the next corner.
I was wrong in this corner.
I couldn't get marshmallows.
We're going home.
Wait, wait, wait.
From now on?
But if you ask me so much...
Please, please.
I don't want to.
Then, let's see.
I did it!
Then, next corner?
Next corner?
Let's go.
Let's move this.
What is this?
I think it's here.
What's next?
Am I okay?
You're okay.
Thank you.
It's better if you say it.
No, it's not.
Okay, let's go.
What's next?
The next corner is this.
Are you okay?
You can read it.
If you study about a person, you might
find something interesting.
Experiment corner!
Is it a person?
Please explain.
I'm sorry.
This corner is about a great dance that
shows what kind of middle schooler and
famous people were in this world.
Adults.
This corner is about finding a great
hint to become an adult.
Miihi-senpai, please.
Please?
Me?
Please give us a question.
I'm a substitute.
From the beginning, I'm supposed to be
here, right?
Yes.
Well, I'll just ask a question.
This one?
You can't look at it. You can't look at
it.
What is this?
What?
This is...
It's written here.
I don't want to see this.
Really?
You can show it.
Here we go.
What is it?
It's from a long time ago.
Born in 1847, February 11, in Ohio, USA.
Where is Ohio?
8 years old, went to elementary school.
University?
10 years old, makes an experiment room
in the basement of the house.
Drinks medicine to make friends fly.
Friends suffer from stomachache and get
angry.
You know a lot of things at 10 years
old.
It's disgusting.
12 years old, working as a newspaper
seller on a train.
He was working when he was 12.
He was 15 years old, and he was about to
be pulled over by a train.
Wow.
He's cool.
But now they imagine and write.
I don't understand.
He's a great man.
He's good at history.
I'm not good at it.
字幕提供者はご覧のお願いいたします。
I don't know. I don't know the name or
the face.
The name and the face...
Aren't we Japanese?
But we're in America.
We're from America.
We're foreigners.
Really?
What is it?
Do we have to say the name?
Yeah, that's right.
I don't know the name.
I can't imagine the name.
I can't imagine the name. 何でもいいの?
I know the name.
You can put the name in the
person you know and imagine if you can't
see their face.
It's close.
It's a lab, so it's Rika's.
Rika?
This little one is a lab.
Imagine it and draw it.
Okay.
A medicine?
Is it dangerous?
It's not dangerous.
Okay.
If you write it in blue, it will be a
little uncomfortable.
I'll write it in black.
Are you going to write it vertically?
You can't write people.
Elementary school and university are
amazing.
And you're going to write it yourself?
I'm going to write it in the basement of
my house.
This is also edited.
I haven't written it yet.
Let's write a big picture.
I want to write it quickly.
I'm not saying write it quickly.
Think about it.
I really don't know.
Let's write a big picture.
How many pictures are there?
Pictures are okay with anything.
It's really good.
People who watched it, you know, right?
I want to see it.
It's a wonderful picture that remains in
legend.
Do you know?
I don't know the name of the person.
I only know Kamakura.
I've written a lot.
Maybe his hair is growing.
I can imagine it.
I don't know how old this person is.
I don't know how old this picture is.
I don't know who wrote it.
I think my chin is going to get in the
way.
It looks like you're digging.
I'm not looking at it.
I'm looking at the image.
I'm writing a postcard.
That's gross.
I know what you're thinking.
I feel like I'm writing something.
But you're good at drawing.
You're really good.
Who is this?
Who is this person?
I can't see.
I only have my hair drawn.
This might be a low-pace.
This is bad.
I'm drawing my eyes.
That's gross.
Who is this?
I'm drawing my eyes.
I'm sorry.
I think it's a new one.
I don't think it's a hint.
You don't have to read the light.
I should have read the light.
It's an old machine.
Let's read the light.
I think there's something in here.
This is definitely for everyone.
How about you two?
I can't think of a name.
Name?
It's probably from the picture.
I think it's probably from the picture.
Anything is fine.
I think it's from the picture.
Let's buy some medicine.
That's right.
I want to fly from the sky.
This is it?
Really?
Thank you so much
I'm a person of the past
I don't know
I don't care what the name is
You don't care what the name is?
What was the name that you said earlier?
Patrasche
I said it
I'm sorry
I don't know
Did you write it?
I wrote it
I used this for the first time in a long
time
My cat ears are cute
Not cute but
I think it's cute
Today
Let's see
Kaoriko
The song ended
Oh no
What should we do?
It's fine
Okay
Both of you
The drawing is so bad
This time I'll do it too
Kaoriko-chan
No
Let's do both at once
One by one
Which one is better?
Okay, then
Together
But
There's no one in the beginning
But there's no one
This is Japanese
I'm
This person
Draw
Oh
James Sky
Why?
That's
It's cool
So
But
I think it's good
It's amazing
After all, the person in the beginning
Why did you choose this?
Because I want to fly
It's close
I'm a person who flies
But James is
Someone who seems to be a foreigner
Certainly
I stuck
I thought it was cool
Amazing
I'm so good at imagination
No, no
After all, the person in the beginning
I should have come in the first place
It's amazing
No, stop it
No
You look tired
A little
I'm still in a hurry
I'm too experienced
Then
I'm doing a lot of drawing
No, no
Help me
I don't care
No, please don't do it
I'm a foreigner
Patrasche
Cute
I'm a little chubby
This is that
Wait, I can't see
Chakurya
I should have written it
I'm too experienced
This is amazing
I made a normal face
Patrasche
The name is like this
The face is like
I'm feeling
I'm getting sucked in the chin
You two imagined something like that
Okay, answer
From this ridiculous hint
This is the name of Kaho-chan
I want to put it on
No, no
Answer
I just saw it
Do you know?
I know
I definitely know
Is it okay? I will announce it
The answer is
This
Ta-da
It was Edison
It's totally different
Edison?
The person who made the deck
Edison
The experiment
I don't know
The car is shining
The experiment room is the hint
I thought so
I thought it was a temporary
It's not a hint
I think you wanted to see
what kind of imagination
they have
I don't want to
It's embarrassing
It's okay to say it
Who wrote this?
I did
I didn't write it
It was Edison
Edison is walking a lot of life
I was surprised
I quit school in elementary school
I was drinking medicine
I broke my stomach
I was surprised
I gave a great answer
Really?
Yes
That's it
If you touch Edison
Something might grow
It was the experiment corner
It was fun
Did you understand?
I didn't understand
There are few hints
It was difficult
Patrash
I'm really going home this time
There were quite a few
Are you going home?
It's been a long time
I'm going home
From here
Let's do our best
Okay
It's sad
That's all
It was the dance director
Mizuki
Thank you
Bye
Do your best
I'll do my best
It's sad
Really?
Senpai is amazing
Is it the Soucha team?
I'll do my best
Let's do our best
Next
The next corner
What will happen
Ritomasushiya
The experiment corner
Yay
I'm nervous
This corner
We have to draw a card
We have to do the experiment
It's a heart-pounding, heart-pounding
corner
I'm nervous
Are you ready?
Should I bring it here first?
Wait a minute
Sorry, are you okay?
I'm okay
Where should I put it?
Okay
Sorry, Kaho-chan
I'll explain the rules
Here...
What was it?
Here is the topic
Here are the conditions
So, you have to draw this and...
You have to draw the one you want to
draw.
Okay, Riko-chan, let's start drawing.
I'll start drawing.
I can't see it yet.
Wait, wait.
I'll draw the one with the red one.
I can't see it.
I can't take it out.
I did my best.
There are so many.
What should I do?
I can't take it out.
I can't see it.
I heard it earlier.
Look at it.
No way!
In 5 minutes,
make Mizuki-chan-senpai laugh!
Make him laugh?
The condition is,
use a pillow.
Pillow?
There's a pillow.
This is for Kaho-chan.
This time, the topic is...
We're going to make Mizuki-senpai laugh.
But the condition is to use a pillow.
Within 5 minutes.
We have to call Mizuki-senpai for now.
Alright. Mizuki-senpai!
Is he not home yet?
Mizuki-senpai?
Is Mizuki-senpai not home yet?
Mizuki-senpai!
Yes!
Oh, I'm glad!
What is it?
The next thing we're going to do is to
use a pillow to make Mizuki laugh in 5
minutes.
I'll do it now.
I just have to be here, right?
Yeah, if you can make him laugh.
How about that?
I wonder if it's okay.
I wonder if I'll laugh.
The pillow.
First message
笑ってください。 私どこにいればいい?
私どこでも。
じゃあ、はい。
え、はいなの?
二人でやるんだよね。
何やるの?
全然決まらない。 行きやりやしかないよ。
全然思いつかない。
언 Earth
What was it?
Marshmallow!
Marshmallow, what is it?
I don't know.
It's a pretty big marshmallow.
Let's go with this one.
I want to go with this one.
Then, let's do that one.
Okinawa, please come to my place.
Thank you.
You're too fast.
I can't do it.
Let's go together.
I don't know.
Who will judge my laugh?
That's right.
I'm the one who's laughing.
Riko, do your best.
I'm done with my role.
Let's go together.
I'm waiting for you.
I don't want to.
This is not the end.
You two are no good.
Show us your skills.
Who?
I'll do it.
Everyone will laugh at once.
I'm ready to laugh.
Everyone is watching this moment.
I'm watching.
What?
I can't see. It's pitch black!
So cute!
But what should we do?
Let's do the same thing.
I'm not a cute character.
Can I say something?
I used to do a show called Kimizuki.
When something happens,
If you say, ZUKO,
It will be okay.
ZUKO?
Yes, let's do it together.
Ready?
This way?
You can fall from the center.
You can fall from here.
Which one do you want to fall from?
One, two, three, ZUKO!
I don't know.
Let's teach ZUKO.
ZUKO!
It's best to go all out.
That's right.
Use this when you're in trouble.
I'll give you this ZUKO.
I'll have you two take it.
I'll take it.
I think I failed the experiment.
I wonder if it's a failure.
But I was told this ZUKO, so it's okay.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
Why are you going?
When you're in trouble.
ズコー!
ズコーやってね、2人。
意外とね、これ、ファンの人ね、好きだから。
そうなんだ。
ズコーやってとかね、結構握手会とかで言われるんだ。
だから使うといいよ。
じゃあさ、みずきちゃんはこっちじゃん。
私はズコーってこうするしかないよ。
ズコーってこうするしかないよ。
You laughed at that!
I'm sorry.
I didn't use the pillow.
I'm glad.
Is this okay?
This experiment is over.
It's over.
I'm glad you taught me.
Please use it.
Let's close the corner.
What was the name of the corner?
Please subscribe to my channel.
What is Miruki Senpai doing?
No, I'm not.
What is she doing?
She is doing the Ritomas Sushi and the
experiment.
That's all.
Thank you very much.
I'm going home.
Bye bye.
What about the pillow?
I'll take it.
Please take good care of the pillow.
Bye bye.
Wait, at the end...
Oh, right.
What should I do?
Okay.
So,
It ended so quickly.
It was fast.
But,
It was so fast that
the time for the experiment
was so short.
It was fun.
I'm sorry.
Let's give a brief comment.
Let's start with Kao-chan.
Kao-chan?
I was so excited.
I thought I could do it well.
I had fun.
I'm glad.
Okay.
Next is Riko-chan.
Today, Mizuki-senpai will do it with me.
I'm a little bit tired.
Next week?
It will continue from now on.
Next week, next week.
It will be just the two of us.
We will do our best.
Please watch it.
Let's answer the questions.
Let's see...
A question...
Which one is good?
What should I do?
Seriously?
Let's do this one.
But isn't this better?
This one doesn't matter.
I think this one is better.
This one?
This is the usual question.
But it's okay.
Today's question is...
Which one is good?
Read it.
What has your mom been angry about
recently?
I wonder if she's angry.
She's always angry.
For example?
She always tells me to get ready early
today.
But I didn't get ready.
I was lying down on the sofa and didn't
get ready.
That's not good.
I'll get angry too.
Thank you.
I'm scared of you.
You're a good girl.
But I'll get angry one day.
It's always like that.
I used to get angry.
But it was a small thing.
I forgot about it.
Okay.
Anyway, today's question is...
This.
Let's close it.
It's kind of amazing.
That's it.
Thank you for watching until the end.
Thank you.
Let's go.
That's all. We are Shizuebishugaku.
Shizuki Wan-Go 11th Kobayashi Kaho and
Shizuki Wan-Go 12th Nakayama Rikoo.
This was Soremi's Kaori-Kot!
Bye-bye! See you next time!
Please subscribe to my channel!