I'm Miu Murayama from Tokyo.
Today I'm at the location of the music
video of FU-PAN.
I came to the room of Ban.
Wow!
Ban, you are hungry.
I've been dancing to BAM since I was a
trainee.
BAM was the first song that I remember.
It was the first time I danced to BAM
for the 3rd generation.
That's why I came to shoot a music
video.
I've always loved drawing since I was a
kid.
I went to the zoo with my family and
drew pictures of animals.
I used to like drawing giraffes.
I drew giraffes and painted them.
I've loved idols since I was a kid.
My favorite member is Kira Masumoto.
I love older people.
I've been getting along with older girls
in junior high school.
I love black clothes.
I often wear black clothes.
I'm the one who wears black clothes in
the city.
I like black penlight colors, but
there's no black.
If you have a black penlight, please
show me your head color.
If you have a penlight, please show me
your head color.
I'm nervous right now.
I can't show my face.
I think I have a lot of facial
expressions, so I make a lot of faces.
I'm good at fighting.
I'm here.
This place is much bigger than the last
one.
So, they put water in here and danced?
It's so bumpy.
They danced in such a bumpy place.
I came to the place where Oozora-san, my
favorite face, was dancing.
It's so beautiful in the spring.
I love drawing, so I drew this
landscape.
I scattered the cherry blossoms.
The one in the middle is...
a person who is like me.
I'm going to dance.
I came back to the hotel.
The road was narrow, so I could feel the
thinness of the seniors.
The place where Morita was shooting was
high and amazing.
Thank you for watching.