You don't hold the mic too high, right?
Yes, that's right
Let's hold it about 10cm lower
22 days until the end of the year's
Ebitu Shintai-sei Ohirome Live
Meanwhile, Sakurai Ema and Nakamura Yuna
visited a place
Today, we came to visit a shrine
Yes, on December 17th, we have our first
Ohirome, so we came to pray for our
success
So this time, they will be close to
their first successful live
And
I want to go to Fukuoka, so I'll stop by
Yunanchi
The first Ohirome live in Fukuoka
Do you come to shrines like this?
I haven't been recently, so it's been a
while
It's been a while?
Yeah
Do you know that families always come to
shrines at the end of the year?
The end of the year?
Not the end of the year?
No, no
Year end
Year end?
Do you go to the year end?
I go every year
I go to the shrine three times a year
What?
Really?
Three times a year?
Three times a year
I heard that it's good to go to three
shrines at the end of the year
Really? I didn't know that
In Kyushu and Shikoku regions, which
started from Fukuoka, where Yuna was
born,
there is a custom of visiting three
shrines for the first time
They arrived at the shrine where they
will visit
Onotersaki Shrine is located in Iriya,
where the local culture lives
Actually, they have visited here before
When the new member challenges the final
audition
I went to the Salta Hiko shrine
I went there before the training camp
I passed the audition
How about you, Yuna?
I'm very shy
I went to the shrine and prayed
I hope you pass the audition
And the Onotersaki shrine we visited
this time is
It is a shrine that celebrates the god
who was active in the early Heian
period, Takamura-ko Mono
The Onotersaki shrine is known for its
many works of art and entertainment
I hope you will be able to spend time
with the god of the work of art and
entertainment
The famous actress Atsumi Kiyoshi, who
played the role of Torasan, also went to
this shrine when she was young
Later, she was chosen as the main
character of the movie, The Man Who Hurt
the Man
Even now, many celebrities visit this
shrine
Thank you for watching
OK?
And finally
Please give me two EMAs
I wrote, I hope you can make the lunch
live on December 17th a success.
Your handwriting is beautiful.
Thank you very much.
I do my best in my own lessons, but I'd
like to ask you here.
This is the first live performance since
Yuki graduated, and I think it's a very
important and eye-catching live for the
fans, so I asked them to make it a
success.
I wrote, I hope you can make the lunch
live on December 16th and 17th a
success.
We will be on the stage on the 17th, but
on the 16th, Hinata will have her
graduation live.
I think it will be a very important day
for the fans and the members, so I wrote
this because I wanted to make it a
successful day and a day that will be a
great memory.
The success of the first live
performance, and the graduation lunch,
so that the members and fans can have
the best day.
EMAo, Hono, who filled their wishes.
It's perfect.
I think the rest is just us working
hard.
I was pulled.
I thought I'd do my best.
I'm not sure.
22 days until their first live.
Please look forward to their
performance.
Usually, they can't spend much time
alone except for lessons.
So, they use the time to have a girl
talk session.
Shabu-shabu was delicious.
It was delicious.
Yuno-chan said that Shabu-shabu and
lettuce are delicious.
She said that.
I tried it and it was really delicious.
It was delicious.
I liked that too.
Marroni-chan.
Marroni-chan was delicious.
I was full, so I couldn't eat more.
I only ate a little bit.
I ate sweets for dinner.
Sweets are really different.
I was going to order two.
I think sweets are really different.
I have two stomachs.
I have a stomach for food and a stomach
for sweets.
So, it's different.
What should I eat next?
I want to go to the Monja.
Let's go together next time.
I want to do that.
I want to do the uniform.
I said the same thing.
I want to do the uniform Disney.
I want to go to the USJ.
I've never been there.
It was really fun.
But I was small at that time.
It was the season of Halloween.
I couldn't enjoy it at all.
I was scared.
The USJ is amazing.
It's very real.
I want to meet Snoopy.
Snoopy is a blue and red monster.
I want to do a lot of things.
I want to go to Disney.
I want to go to the USJ.
I want to go to the Illumination.
I want to go to the outskirts of the
prefecture.
Outskirts?
I want to go to Fukuoka.
Then I can stay in Yuna's house.
There is a hot spring in the hot spring.
It's like a slope.
I was scared because I almost drowned.
I was a little girl.
I was small, so I was scared to go to
the pool.
The pool is also scary.
I can't swim in the pool.
You can't swim.
I can't swim.
I swim 5 meters every year.
Really? You can stretch your hair and
swim.
I can stretch my hair and move, but I
can't move forward.
What do you mean 5 meters?
Isn't that too little?
I can stretch my hair and move forward.
But I can't move forward.
You can't move forward.
I can't move forward.
How many meters can you swim?
I can swim 25 meters.
I can't move forward.
I can't breathe even if I raise my head.
You can't breathe.
I can't breathe.
I'm sorry.
I met two mice the other day.
Two big mice.
Dove mice?
Yes, Dove mice.
I've never met a mouse before.
Me neither.
I don't want to meet a mouse in person.
I want to meet a mouse and a mole.
A mole?
I heard that moles are common in the
wild.
What?
Do they dig their own graves?
Yes, they dig their own graves.
They come out from the bottom of the
house.
Then, they come out.
I don't like it.
They are like a peck of ham.
It's about time.
Time is up.
Time passed so fast.
I couldn't eat.
It was delicious.
Thank you for your cooperation
They are watching Emma and Yuna's first
appearance on TV
Wow, you two are the same age, right?
Born in 2007
Thank you
Thank you for watching!