Yakan and idol
I really like people
I really like talking to people
That's why I'm doing a lot of live
streams
But I have one goal in my life
Can I announce it?
Is it okay?
I've said this before
I want to meet as many people as
possible
I want to spend time with people
Why is that?
Is it important to meet?
There are many things that you don't
know if you don't meet
I think I don't know much more if I
don't meet
I want to meet and talk about what I can
do
I think I can talk to people and make a
relationship with them
That's probably my life
I think that's a job I can do
You're really a manager
That's right
That's great
I feel grateful to meet people
I think it's only idols that can't do
anything but wait
There are people who can't come to see
me
I want people to laugh at me
I want people to think of me
I'm happy when I'm happy
I want to meet
I want you to come to see me
I don't think anyone should come to see
me
I see
I'm thinking about three things that
fans think
You were listening
Yes
You're cute and sensitive
You're kind and sweet
Everyone thinks I'm sweet
You're beautiful
You're beautiful and cute
You're sharing with fans
I'm too much of a delivery
I'm not a bad person
You're a money-saving person
What is that?
You're a person who's into money
Please stop
I don't accept that
You don't accept that
I can only talk to MCs
In a group
I want to talk to people
I can't show everyone who I am
You want to show everyone?
Yes
I want people to know
I want to share
You want to share Fujita Aeri?
We want to share folder games
I see
I want to see cute clappos
You want to see cute reporters?
I want to see cute reporters