Ebitune's videos
I can master the rubik's cube
Yes, it started
Rubik's cube
Well, last time
My voice is low, sorry
Last time, I did the rubik's cube
I did the three
I did it, but after that
I talked a lot about elves and got away
from the rubik's cube at all, so I'd
like to do this again this time, but
this was difficult.
I did it when I got home, but I didn't
do it at all.
There are various videos and various
youtube people, so I was doing this
while watching it.
I couldn't do it at all, and I thought
that it was completely different from
the usual three.
It was difficult.
I want to try again.
I was told that I would start with
white, and I was told that I would start
with white, orange, and blue.
I thought I had to listen to the story.
I'll do my best.
I'll put them together.
How should I do it?
I'm used to using three.
I don't know what to do.
Is there anyone who plays Do Big Cube in
the Ebichu Family?
I'll do it when I did it in June.
There's someone who said, I'll try it
too.
I don't know if that person is still
going on.
I don't think I've done two.
How do you do two?
I've been breaking it up.
Why are you coming down?
What should I do at a time like this?
I don't know how to do this.
I broke it again.
I'm breaking it again.
I think I should start from white.
Oh, I got it!
Only one side.
I got only white.
I don't know how to put this from here.
I don't want to break it.
I don't know how to do this.
I made it from white, but I'm going to
make it from blue.
I'm going to make it from blue.
Oh, it's coming.
I made it to 2.
The third one is to make the white the
same.
Find the blue and the red goes over
there.
I did it.
I made it to here.
I'm breaking it, but how do I do this?
It came out!
I made it this far!
Wait!
If you look at it this far, it's pretty
complete, isn't it?
I'm glad I read this properly.
It's called a perfect one-sided.
Everyone knew that I had to read the
instructions.
I'm going to go to step 2.
I'm going to adjust the position of the
cube.
I've put it in several places, but I can
do it if I look at it like this.
Like this or like this.
I'll adjust it a little.
I don't know.
Ah! This This This!
She got a message again.
What?
Wait, the back and front are aligned.
Green and blue are aligned diagonally.
White is also aligned.
The back and front are aligned.
I did it!
I was surprised!
Thank you!
I couldn't do it because I was watching
the video at home.
All the pieces are in order. I'm scared.
I did it!
It's a miracle. How did I do it?
I thought I could do 2x2. What's next?
Look at this.
4x4? 4x4?
What is this?
It's a block.
I think it's a block of red bricks.
It's so small.
I feel like it's big.
I don't know how to put it together.
It's hard.
No one has done it.
No way.
I'll try it.
Have you ever done this?
This is the first time I've seen it.
I'll do it.
I'll have you break it.
I think it's hard to break it.
4x4
Where should I start?
But this is...
Is it yellow again?
No no no
Is it white?
I don't know where to start
3x3 is impossible
How should I put them together?
What?
When I did the triangle, there was one
in the middle.
I did 1, 2, 3, 4.
I put 4 together.
It's 2, 2, 2, 2.
It's hard to move.
See, I made 4 in the middle.
I think this is white.
No?
White, white, isn't it white?
I think it's not.
I'm doing what I want to do, but I'm not
sure if this is right.
Oh, like this.
Oh, wait. I'm doing what I want to do.
But...
It's too heavy. It doesn't move at all.
We finished the video and decided to
send this video to policy official
Let's use martyr keycap
I don't know what to do.
What should I do?
What sound is there?
It's difficult.
What should I do with this?
Yellow... Why does it come with this?
Yellow... White... Blue, green, red,
orange...
How do you make it?
I got them all.
Only the middle.
I got the middle.
White, yellow, green, blue, orange, red.
I'm going to make a bed from here.
So, Rubik's cube.
I can't do this now.
I can do this.
This is also...
I could only get four in the middle.
Rubik's cube is difficult.
I got three.
And,
I broke it.
Look at this.
What is this shape?
I don't know if you can see this.
I was able to put this together in one
video.
I'll show you how to do it.
Someday, someday.
Like this, it's not a time attack.
I hope I can do it.
I can do it a little faster.
Someday, someday.
I'll do my best.
This is impossible.
It's impossible.
I'll ask the staff to do this.
Did I do it well?
I had fun.
I enjoyed making the Rubik's Cube.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye.