A night time job title.
And...
Three...
Okay!
I don't need it!
I'm a fortune teller.
Oh, you love fortune telling.
I love fortune telling.
Recently...
I've been doing fortune telling for the
youth festival and stuff.
But recently, I've been doing it for
people who can see.
People who can see my past life and my
past life.
Oh, I've met someone like that.
There's someone like that.
There is?
Yes.
Who is it?
I'm into spiritualism.
I see.
And my guardian spirit...
Apparently, my guardian spirit changes
periodically.
Your guardian spirit changes
periodically?
Oh, I see.
That's because you're protecting it.
By the way, if I don't use it,
What's your favorite guardian spirit?
Recently, I've been into golden hair.
I'm wearing an emerald green dress with
long hair.
I'm wearing an angel with big wings.
Isn't that a Hollywood celebrity?
I'm wearing a golden emerald green
dress.
And you're wearing wings.
I'm wearing wings.
I'm wearing an angel with wings.
That's it?
But apparently, no one wears an angel.
I've never heard of it.
I was told that I was a pure and good
girl.
I'm glad to hear that.
You're a fortune teller.
I've never been with someone like that.
By the way, before you get to know her,
Who do you like?
Before that,
I was with a very tough Greek man with a
shield and a seal.
He was paying me so that bad people
wouldn't come near me.
You were with a tough guy with a shield
and a seal.
That's why I thought there were only
good people around me.
I'm the only one who's good enough to
think I'm good.
For example?
I know you're a good person.
I'm glad to be around the members and
the people around me.
I'm glad to be around my friends.
How can I say this?
You're blessed by people.
I'm blessed by good people.
Including that, you're blessed by the
guardian spirit.
Do you like fortune-telling on TV or
fortune-telling at a shrine?
I like going to shrines.
Shrine?
I like going to power spots.
But you're at a power spot now.
That's right.
I think it's good to give happiness to
the guests.
It's hard to hear.
But it's a good sound.
To be continued.
I sent it to you by the sponsor of the
runner Kazu, Masuo, Nicho, Pink Panther
Yasu.
Are you excited recently?
Please be excited a lot.
Thank you very much.