At代 us to blow girl你看
Hello, everyone!
We're here!
Speaking of this place...
What is it?
What could it be?
Yes!
Bicycles!
It's nostalgic!
It's been a while, right?
I wore a bench coat that time, so it's
really hot in the cold winter.
There's one person in here who can't
ride a bike.
Who is it? Who is it?
Ah! There you are!
You're a fucking javan!
I don't ride a bike.
So today, I'd like to show you how to
ride a bike!
Yay!
Last time, Tachibana couldn't ride a
bicycle, so Yuna and I taught her.
And she was able to ride a bicycle.
That's right. Thanks to you, she was
able to ride a bicycle.
I'm so grateful.
So we all want to do cycling together.
That's right. If we can do it, we all
want to do cycling together.
So, please leave it to us today.
Thank you.
Let's go to the Roshiru River.
Please.
I'm from the Roshiru River.
First, I'd like to show you our body.
Please leave it to us.
No, it's okay.
First, I'll start with you.
I'm a little...
I've been riding for about 10 years.
How cool!
How old have you been riding?
I'm 5 years old.
You're a pro.
That's amazing.
I'll go.
Please.
It's cool.
Tokimono, show us your technique.
I'll show you my electric bike skills.
Wow!
Amazing!
Thank you.
I think you can't ride it yet, but how
much do you think you can do?
I'll try to do it as much as I can.
Wait a minute.
By the way, this is not a school
uniform.
What is this?
This is called a brake.
It's a brake that you can stop while
you're running.
What about this one?
It's the same.
I see.
One time.
Can I go a little further?
Yes.
That's good.
I see.
I'll get off at once.
I think it's better than the one he
rode.
I agree.
I think I'll get more.
First of all, you have to introduce
yourself to the bicycle.
To the bicycle?
That's right.
Name.
Age.
Blood type.
What you like.
It's important to be able to say it.
That's right.
Then I'll go with the example.
I'll go with the example.
Good morning.
I'm MIYU.
I'm 17 years old.
Blood type is AB.
What I like is to sleep.
I'm worried about the future.
Don't say such heavy things.
I recommend the mountain type.
That's good.
You're in a state of mind.
With a bicycle?
We're good friends.
We're good friends forever.
I see.
Then I'll introduce myself.
Please.
Hello.
I'm SHINJU.
I'm 19 years old.
I'm a large person.
I'm the same age as the tire of a
bicycle.
That's cute.
What I like is to read manga.
I'll ride a bicycle while reading manga.
That's dangerous.
That's good.
I'm worried about my wallet.
Are you okay?
I'm really okay.
I want to go find my wallet on a
bicycle.
I see.
Please help me.
Thank you.
Did you understand each other?
We understood each other.
Let's start the preparation exercise.
The preparation exercise will begin now.
I will do the preparation exercise now.
Please teach me the exercise
alternately.
Can I do that?
I'm a veteran, so I'll start with you.
Can I do the teaching at first?
I will start with the Achilles tendon
exercise.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven,
eight
Next is bicycle.
1,2,3, and more!
Good.
Next is bicycle.
1,2,3, and more!
Like this.
Good.
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10,11,12,13,14,15,16,1
7,18
I see.
Next is bicycle.
Let's ask Yura-san to show us the most
important posture.
1,2,3,4.
Like this.
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10,11,12,13,14,15,16,1
7,18
Good.
Thank you.
I hope there is someone would be novel
about what I would do for Yun-Pin after
riding a crack circumstances hell ride.
I'm not a professional.
So, you two are going to be the bad
guys.
Leave it to me.
Can I have a moment?
No.
I'm sorry.
I'm not scared.
So, we're going to be the bad guys.
Let's go.
Hey, you.
Can you help me?
I'm fine.
Hey, Katsu.
I don't know.
How was it?
Did I break it?
No.
I'm fine.
Wow.
You got scared.
I'm having fun.
We had fun.
I think we're good.
Are we okay?
What should we do?
I think we can get on.
Let's get on.
I'm so sorry.
Are you okay?
Look forward.
We can get on the first car.
So, it's okay.
Look forward.
And step on the gas.
Step on it.
Step on it more.
Good.
How do you feel?
Let's stop.
Stop.
How was it?
I'm scared.
Do you want to get rid of it?
Please.
What else?
Ghosts?
We can do that.
Let's do the insect.
Let's go.
Please subscribe to this channel.
How is it?
I can do it!
Let's try it!
Like this?
Yes, like that.
Can you bend it?
Oh, it's me!
You're good!
You can bend the saddle in the direction
you want.
Is this the saddle?
Yes, that's it.
Bend it straight.
Good, slowly.
Good.
That's it.
I'll let go of your hand.
I'll hold your hand.
Can I hold your hand?
Hold it straight.
Put your weight on the right side.
And put your weight on the middle.
Good job!
You don't need to do anything.
I see.
Just like this.
Put your weight on the left side.
That's right.
Good job!
I got it!
It's good.
Can I stop?
Yes.
Let's go!
Okay.
Go!
Are you okay?
But...
Did you get it?
It's in the middle of the lake.
In the middle?
Wow!
Amazing!
It moves.
It's spinning...
Do you want to try it?
How was it?
It was good.
Really?
That's good.
I think this is a good place.
I'll hold the handle.
Please put the handle.
Please put it.
I'm sorry.
I can do it.
I'm happy.
You're good.
It's amazing.
Oh!
We did it!
I'm okay.
Wow!
Yay!
Amazing!
We did it!
Thank you!
Wow!
I'm so happy!
Thank you so much!
Wow! Everyone!
It's amazing.
Let's take a look around.
Yeah, let's take a look.
From the top of the mountain?
But it's a straight road.
Yeah.
I'm so impressed.
I'm so happy.
I'm so happy that everyone can ride a
bicycle.
Everyone can ride a bicycle.
I'm so happy.
I can't say I can't ride a bicycle with
this.
I agree.
Let's go around here.
Okay.
Let's go.
I'm so happy.
It's a long way.
Let's go!
Go!
I'll try to balance my weight.
You can do it. You got used to it.
Let's go.
Keep your posture.
Good.
It's okay.
Keep your posture.
Good.
I got it!
I think I got it.
You're doing great.
I'll speed up.
I got it!
Thank you for watching!
We got on the train!
Amazing!
Thank you so much!
It was great!
Thank you!
How was it?
It felt good!
It was the best!
I was dreaming of riding a horse for a
long time, so I didn't have a back
wheel.
Really?
I was able to ride a horse thanks to you
two.
Me too.
I was able to feel the happiness of
riding a horse because you helped me
last time.
Thank you for the wonderful experience.
Thank you very much.
How was it, Ms. Aka?
It was really good.
I was able to ride a bike well.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Let's all get a certificate at the end.
That's right.
I'll take this.
Thank you very much.
See you next time.