Like videos of shrimp!
Kokonato!
Nono-chan!
We want to introduce ourselves in
English!
I'm number 13, Takara Takano.
I'm number 15, Kazami Nonoka.
So, why do we want to introduce
ourselves in English?
We want to introduce ourselves in
English with Kokubo Yama.
I'm a junior high school student. You
know?
We want to do that.
In English.
Today, we want to introduce ourselves in
English.
Would you like to call your teacher?
Ms. Marina!
Please!
Let's introduce ourselves.
The flower is...
Sakuragi!
The woman is...
Kokona!
I'm number 13, Sakura Kokona.
Please!
That's what we want to introduce
ourselves.
We want to introduce ourselves in
English.
That's so cool!
That's amazing!
If we can do this in other countries, we
can use it, right?
We can use it in any country.
I want to do that!
That's amazing!
What is this?
Belly button mermaid?
Here?
Belly button mermaid.
What does it say?
That's amazing!
Belly button mermaid.
Mermaid.
That's amazing!
The flower is...
Sakuragi.
The woman is...
Kokona.
Belly button mermaid is a hessodashi.
Belly is the meaning of the word
hessodashi.
It's a hessodashi with a belly button.
This is the word belly button mermaid of
Ebichu.
Does it mean that a button comes out?
Belly button is a hessodashi.
That's amazing!
Please subscribe to my channel!
And the number 13
Number 53
Cool!
Please try it
It's cool
Amazing
The flower is
Sakura
The girl is
Kokona
I'm Kokona Sakura
The very bottom moment of attitude
Attendance number 30
She's not saying anything
Her pronunciation is beautiful
Thank you
You can't do it like that
You're getting nervous
This is fun
I want to do it
The word is
Non-non
Nanoka
Maru
I want to be a white cloud that is blown
by the wind
Attendance number 15
Nanoka Marukata
I'm Kazami Nanoka
Nice to meet you
This is
English student
I don't know
This is Non-non-nonoka part
Please try it
I'll read it from the bottom
I want to be a white cloud blowing in
the wind
Attendance number 15
Nanoka Kazami
It's like that
I want to be a white cloud blown by the
wind
This is the sentence
I want to be a white cloud
Blowing in the wind
I see
The order changes a little
If you read this in a row
I want to be a white cloud blowing in
the wind
Wow
That's great
Let's try it together
Yes
Ready
I want to be a white cloud blowing in
the wind
Attendance number 15
Nanoka Marukata
Nanoka Kazami
Let's try it alone
And
I want to be a white cloud blowing in
the wind
Attendance number 15
Nanoka Marun
Nanoka Kazami
Cute
The intonation is still not good
It's a little embarrassing
It's very good
I want to try it in English from the top
Non-non-nonoka
What?
Like that
If you try it together
Non-non-nonoka
Maru
That's great
It's nice
The order is really beautiful
If you can say it quickly
That's right
I want to try it
Attendance number 16
Nanoka Kazami
Next, let's write the English we want to
use for live.
What do you want to write?
If you want to write English abroad,
I'll write this.
Please start with Kokona.
Let's make a voice.
I can't speak in the corner, but I'll
speak in English in Japan.
I'll start.
Make some noise.
I've heard this before.
It's cool.
There are words that make people excited
at festivals abroad.
I'll use this.
Make some noise.
It's cool.
It's like Kokona.
Is it like Kokona?
I'll use this.
Thank you.
I'll start.
Let's make people excited.
I'll use this.
What will it be?
Let's have fun.
Let's have fun with this.
I see.
I can use this.
Let's have fun.
It's cool.
I'm excited.
It's easy to use these words.
It's easy to use.
I don't think it's used abroad.
I think everyone can understand.
I think I can understand.
Please try using it.
I'm tired.
Thank you.
I'm happy.
Let's start.
Put your hands up.
It's good.
It means to raise your hands.
It's used in overseas festivals.
Please try using it.
I want to use this.
It's good for before the rap.
It's cool.
It's cool because it has a rap part.
It's cool because it's used before the
rap.
I want to use it.
It's cool because it's used before the
rap.
It's like clapping.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Let's clap together.
I think it's okay to put on the word
let's.
I see.
I'm sure I'm using let's.
Let's clap together.
Cool.
What else?
What are you saying?
Let's sing together.
Let's is also a word.
I see.
Let's sing along.
Sing along means sing together.
This is also a word that is often used.
Let's sing along.
Is it the same with dance?
Let's dance together.
Let's dance.
Let's dance is not long.
Long is often used in a set when singing
along.
Dance is used in Let's dance or Let's
dance together.
I see.
Let's dance together.
Even if you sing together, the words are
different.
Let's dance together.
I see.
Singalong or Singason?
Singalong.
Did you sing that?
I didn't know.
Singalong.
Singason.
Let's sing together.
I see.
I said that.
Singalong.
That's the Singalon.
I want to say the pronunciation of the
word.
Singalon.
I remember when I was selling songs.
Let's sing together.
Please listen to Singalon.
How is it?
It's perfect.
Thank you for introducing yourself to
us.
We will use it.
Thank you.
So we learned English.
It's cool.
Japanese is also beautiful in its own
way.
But when you use English, it's
different.
It's cool in English.
It's different.
I want to try it. It's difficult.
I want to try it.
I suddenly introduced myself in English.
I was surprised by your pronunciation.
I want to try more.
I want to learn English pronunciation.
I want to go to countries where I want
to go when the coronavirus is over.
I want to go to many places.
We have never been to the US.
So I want to go to places where I can go
with nine people.
Where do you want to go?
I want to go to America.
I want to go to Los Angeles.
I want to introduce myself in English.
Where do you want to go?
I want to go to the countryside, but I
want to go to Korea.
But in Korea, you can also introduce
yourself in Korean.
You can also introduce yourself in
English.
I want to go to Korea.
I want to go to Korea today.
You have a lot to think about.
I want to introduce myself in many
countries.
I want to try it.
It was fun.
That's all.
We want to introduce ourselves in
English.
Bye bye.
Next is YUNO.
Hello, I'm a junior high school student.
YUNO.
I like My Pace.
I'm a 14-member member.
Hi.
What's wrong?
You're the best.
Did you get it?
I'm sorry.
I was lost.
I always say hi at first.
I'm not a high school student.
I see.
YUNO introduced herself before My Pace.
I'm not a My Pace.
I'm a 14-member member.
Next is KOKO.
Everyone, please do it together.
Please!
Sakuragi!
The girl is...
Tomora!
Hello, I'm Kokono Sakuragi, the very
bottom mama of Ebichu.
I'm 13! Thank you!
Everyone, if you've watched Ebichu's
videos, thank you very much.
I think you know this person, but Yuna
always introduces herself in English,
right?
So I want to say, it's me!
I want to do it in English, too.
I want to do it.
I wanted to do it, so I did it.
I see.
Thank you very much.
The next person is...
Please, everyone!
Thank you!
It was like a world.
That's right.
It's nice to know that the two of them
speak English.
That's right.
The girls are like birds.
The birds are very close to the harbor.
That's why it's a good place to meet
them.
That's right.
So, let's go!
I'll go with you.
So, everyone!
Please say something you want to say.
Let's go!
I want your heart!
I want everyone's love!
I want you to be happy!
It's a concert, a concert!
Memories!
I want to see the audience!
It's nice.
It's a nice concert.
What?