1% of flutter and 99% of heart-pounding
Congratulations!
This week's Ebichu Tastas will have a
full rotation test
And then
A face came out from the back of my head
Where did she learn this mysterious
knowledge?
And also
You can escape from the prison
Ebichu's amazing skills are being shown
one by one
It's folding
It's beautiful
There are many strange things
Ebichu Tastasu Start
I'm crazy about you, I'm a heart-throb
Monotrium, Monotrium, Monotrium, Junior
High School
Try adding all kinds of things to your
private Ebisu Junior High School!
Ebisu Justice!
This program is brought to you by these
sponsors.
To be continued
The Shiritsu Ebisu University entrance
exam
Challenge Ebichu member
The 4-character idiom quiz
Hanabana Fuuka
Singer song writer
Lack of study
And
Dance with your belly button
The entrance exam is 10 questions each
The line is 80 points or more
Half of the answers are 0 points
The 3rd question is a foreign language
Start
English
Kaioku reveals the grand plot
Miss Nini's Masao's оз
Do it go wrong this time
This is the confident Ebichu member.
The answer is Benkei's crying.
Will everyone get the right answer?
Let's start with Kobayashi.
It's Kodaki-jiji's crying.
I see.
Kodaki-jiji.
What does this mean?
It makes you cry, right?
But he doesn't do it.
He's crying but...
Kobayashi, I'm going to cancel your
payment.
No!
And Nakayama-san, please.
It's Yowane's crying.
What does it mean?
It's the atmosphere of the word.
Yowane and crying are the same word.
Let's see the other members.
Benkei's crying.
The answer is correct.
Thank you.
Why did you high-five her?
I thought she was going to study.
I see.
Didn't you learn it?
I think she did.
The fourth question is also in Japanese.
She will be challenged to write a short
essay.
Here is the question.
Think of a sentence using the word,
「とどのつまり」
「とどのつまり」 is a word that is often used
when it comes to a conclusion or a point
where you reach a conclusion.
How does Ebichu respond to this
difficult question?
Let's start with Hirota.
The meaning of 「とどのつまり」 in me has been
released.
What do you mean by that?
What does that mean?
It's like a time.
Like a time?
Like a time when you are stuck.
Yes, a time when you are stuck.
So it's like you are released.
Next, Kashiwagi.
My mom's 「とどのつまり」 is not working at all.
「とどのつまり」 is stuck.
Next, Kobayashi.
The meaning of 「とどのつまり」 is stuck in the
way to the venue.
「とどのつまり」 is stuck.
「とどのつまり」 is really stuck.
It's a word that is often used.
Many Ebichu members interpret it as a
word that describes something being
stuck.
Mayama-san, please answer
In short, we have to answer the
questions that the teacher has made
That's correct. Congratulations
I feel like I'm going to throw up
Good luck
Here, the oldest Mayama will show off
her knowledge
The other members will not give up on
the same answer until the end
Challenge the remaining questions
Next is science questions
The insect butterfly that flutters in
the sky
Answer the question by changing the
growth process in 4 steps
Let's see
Let's do it together
Please open it
It looks like this
Gross
Is that the first one?
Is it the egg?
From the egg
It's the egg
And Hirota, too
The larva, the larva, the egg, and the
larva
The shape is the same
The egg, the larva, the larva, and the
larva
They are in the right order
Hirota and Hoshina are correct
But inside
There is a member who drew a butterfly
that has evolved in the world
Yasumoto, is that a peanut?
It's a larva
From a larva, a face comes out
The shell of the larva comes off
and the wings that were closed open
And Mayama's is...
What was the first one? A pizza?
From a larva, it comes out of the soil
and it can make a face
It's very similar
This character is the same
Kashiwagi, is that a symbol?
What was the first one?
It's a leaf with an egg
The egg grows
The egg grows?
And it opens a little
and it becomes a butterfly
So, 3 and 4 are 3 and 4
And Nakayama-san, what is that?
You drew a tree
You drew a tree as the main character
A larva
It's far away
Kobayashi, who drew the tree well, is
also incorrect
After that, he cleared the questions
well and as you can see, he got a lot of
points
Can Nakayama, who still has 0 points,
get his revenge?
The 9th question
Marco Polo is a man who is similar to
the Token
He introduced Japan as a country of the
Japanese
I see
Answer the question that is related to
the Japanese
What is it?
Is Marco Polo a person with a big head?
Marco Polo...
It depends on the time of the year
It's a person with a golden hair
It depends on the season
A person with a golden hair?
A person who remembers foreign words by
their hair
I don't remember, but Marco Polo...
The answer is...
The golden country, Jipang
It's a phrase that we've heard once,
but...
During the debut...
First, let's go with Nakayama-san
Yes
Is it the right answer?
I wonder
The country of kindness, Jipang
That's the good thing about Japan
The good thing about Japan?
Kobayashi-shi, what is it?
The mysterious country, Jipang
It's the mysterious country, right?
I think so too
Kashiwagi
The country of gratitude
That's right
Thank you
Thank you, Kashiwagi
When they realized that Japan is a good
country...
Mayama and Hoshina have a wonderful
world
And the final question for Ebi
University News
Hoshina News
We often hear about the brain water,
which is one of the Japanese regulations
Please answer without omitting the word
brain water
This is omitted right?
Yes, brain water
I've never heard of it
I don't know
You've never heard of it?
I've never heard of it
If it's omitted, it means it's long
How long is it?
That's...
It's just an image
You've never heard of it
Yes
I think it's unconsciously in your head
While the members with the highest
grades are running the brush, Nakayama,
who is alone, has a relaxed smile.
The correct answer is the Ministry of
Agriculture, Forestry and Fisheries.
It's a problem that you can easily
understand if you touch the news a
little bit.
The oldest, Mayama, and the college
student, Hoshina, were correct.
What about the other members?
Kashiwagi, you were faster than I
thought.
Kashiwagi, please.
Me?
No, maybe.
Agriculture, Aquatic...
Agriculture, Aquatic, Aquatic...
It's like a word that even Kei sensei
can't read.
Next, Nakayama, please.
Agriculture, Aquatic...
Aquatic, right?
What does it mean?
Don't ask me the reason.
It's Kei's mood.
We're listening to such a bad thing.
The other members also wrote answers
with a mood.
Everyone, let's watch more news.
So, that's it.
The exam is over.
Now, the results of the Ebi University
entrance exam are announced.
The results of the Ebi University
The first place is Hoshina Mirei
But not all of them passed 80 points
The disadvantage is Nakayama
It's a reward, right?
Yes
What are you writing?
But, it's not just this
What is it?
This is just a test for your academic
ability
There is a next test
This is not the end of the entrance exam
They don't know why, but they go to the
next place
Hurry up and go home
What's the temperature?
No, it's cold
Don't talk about the temperature
You can't tell the temperature when
you're watching
The Ebichu members are in a large
meeting room
What are they going to do here?
In this series, Ebi University, there is
a system where you can pass if you have
a good one
So we will do a one-game interview
One-game is easy
If you can show us your good one-game,
you will pass the Ebi University
So we invited a special examiner to do a
one-game interview
After graduating from Tokyo University,
he has a long history of joining a world
class company
He has passed many difficult exams, he
is a professional examiner
For some reason, he is a comedian
He is a very crazy person
Please show us your one-game
I will say something difficult in
English
In English?
Her nagi girl meadomis
After the one-game interview, Ebi
University has started to give out one-
game
The examiner will be given a 10 yen
coin, and you will get 0 to 30 points
for the one-game
If you get 80 points for the one-game,
you will pass the Ebi University
Now, we will start the one-game
admission for the Ebi University
Who wants to go first?
If you raise your hand, the points will
be high
It's high
Let's go, Mayama-san
Good luck
First, Mayama Rika will show her one-
game
I'm Mayama Rika from Shiritsu Ebisu
Junior High School, and I'm here for the
Stardust Promotion
I'll be showing you how to remove the
joint on your left shoulder
The shoulder?
Ishii sensei, please touch this and I'll
remove it
Like you're holding an egg
Can I do it?
Here I go
Ah! That's disgusting!
What? What was that?
Pay attention to Mayama's left shoulder
Pay attention to Mayama's right shoulder
It's easier to see if you look from
behind
Mayama's first game, take off the joint
Pay attention to Mayama's left shoulder
Hurry up and tie it
Wow, you can escape from the prison
You can go into a small space like this
Mayama, does it hurt?
Not at all
But sometimes during a live, when I'm
dancing, it goes like this
It hurts
It comes off?
Yes, it comes off and sometimes I get
stuck in a different place
It hurts
You're stuck in a different place
AAAAthrough
I'm sorry, I don't know how to feel that
So, please give us the score
30 points
Actually, when we have a company's
briefing, the first person to raise
their hand is the person who cares about
the content
That's why they are chosen
That's it
Next, Hoshinaga, who is the first place
in the academic test, will challenge
Hold it like this
and stick it together like this
Can you do it?
No, we can't
Normally, you can't do it
Kiya thinks that it's a game that no one
can imitate
My dad can do it, but there are people
who can't.
Since the test tube is ready, the score
is 20 points.
Next, Hiroto will show off his body.
My mother taught me this technique
I do it often
I can make my tongue smaller than a
human's
Pay attention to Hiroto's mouth
It's smaller than you think
I want to try
Can you show me your eyes?
What is this?
It's folded
It's folded beautifully
It's funny
Can you do this, too?
Yes
My father taught me this
I think this technique will continue to
Hirota's children
Is this technique popular?
There are many strange techniques
Yasumoto finally showed off his unique
skill
It's a technique, but there may be a
trick or trick
There may be no trick or trick, right?
There may be
On the contrary, it's new
It smells bad
Is this already started?
No, no, no
What should we do?
Please liven up together
Ready, go!
Really Hilarious
More, more, more
Whichever is fine
Oh No!
This is amazing
A sharp move
The TV
Ouch!
That's all.
Thank you very much.
I think...
If it was a relative's uncle, he would
give me 1000 yen.
The hurdle of getting the first game was
high.
This time, Kobayashi's challenge a game-
like technique.
My hobby is drawing.
I draw a combination of animals.
For example, a dog and a duck.
Kobayashi's one-game, Combination of
Animals, is a technique to draw a three-
dimensional animal by combining two
types of animals.
But...
So, Ishii-sensei, what is it?
I'll draw a peach.
Peach!
This is a combined creature drawn by
Kobayashi.
Please edit this part out.
Peach!
And you can draw it on the spot.
It's amazing.
It's very impulsive.
It's an originalist.
It's amazing.
There's no under-drawing.
It's very fast.
It's very TV-oriented.
It's done.
It's done?
It's cute.
It's Zozonga.
What? What?
Zozonga.
The name is already decided.
It's good.
With a great performance, she got 40
points.
She got 40 points.
But you finally got the sense of the
first game.
Yes, I got the sense of the first game.
I want to forget about Tejina.
That was a good flow.
Kashiwagi is aiming for high score with
this flow.
My specialty is to make a sound with my
mouth.
With your mouth?
Yes, I'll do my best.
I'll do my best.
Wow, amazing!
It sounded really good!
It sounded better than I expected!
It's amazing!
I thought you were going to use your
fingers.
Me too!
Can you do it with the music?
I'll do my best.
You can do it like this.
The test is going to be tough.
Can they clear this test?
Yellow
Amazing
Can you show us the previous one?
Can you do it in a row?
I'll do my best
Here I go
Yellow
Amazing
I don't know the answer
That's great. Have you done this at a
live show?
No, at a radio show.
A radio show?
This is for a radio show!
A radio show!
I was born in Japan.
That's great.
The winner of the first game is...
And the last game is...
The academic test is all wrong.
Nakayama is in a big trouble.
I can see the possibility of a big
reversal.
This game is Nein's true into, Game will
continue at istne Progress theres blind
scan game maybe every vibrating music
will soon stop.
I can sneeze without sound
When I'm talking with my manager, I
can't sneeze in this atmosphere
So your manager doesn't notice?
No
Amazing!
No one has noticed this before,
Nakayama's secret, sneeze without sound,
first time to be shown
I can't show it now
I'm at level 1 now
You just did it?
It's over?
It's silent
Did you succeed?
Takey, you should listen to it now
Only the members know?
Ah, it's out
Ah, it's a 10
What?
Please pay attention to the small
movements of Nakayama's head
Thanks!
She is not able to say anything about
the game.
She has only 10 points.
I don't want to play anymore.
The final score is.
As you can see, MAYAMA, KASHIWAGI,
HIROTA, HOSHINAGA, and EBIDAI have
passed.
And she is suspended from the game.
I only have 1600 yen.
Is that okay?
The shrimp is soft.
The last player is NAKAYAMA.
Please answer with a strange face.
Wait a minute.
I want to eat shrimp, too.
Thank you. See you next week.
Next time, it's Hiro and Aika's birthday
solo live special.
I've got a lot of things that I think
are cute.
It's all my exhibition.
Aiai World is open.
What is a live with a lot of cute
things?
That person from the panda.
I'm going to do a live with a lot of
cute things.
I'll see you next time.
This program was brought to you by these
sponsors.
Oh still alive
I did it!