I'm Riko Endo, a sophomore from Saitama
prefecture.
I came to a place to meet a dog today.
This is my first time meeting a dog at a
grocery store.
Daifuku-kun is on his knees.
He was a little greedy and died, but he
was very cute.
Today I came to take a walk in Columbus
Park.
I've loved animals since I was a kid.
I often played with my dog at the house
of a neighbor who had a dog.
I will play the song, Why I didn't fall
in love.
I've been practicing this song for about
a month.
I've been practicing this song for a
month.
I was very anxious at first, and I
wanted to make it a little easier.
I wanted to try it, so I chose this
song.
Today is the first day of practice.
I rented a studio and came to practice
the drums.
I came to the studio to practice today.
Today, I came to shoot the drum video.
This group called Sakura-zaka has a lot
of charm that other groups don't have.
I naturally fell in love with Sakura-
zaka.
I will do my best to show the results of
my practice for about a month while
playing with the feelings of Sakura-
zaka.
Thank you for watching!
When I was a kid, I was a very quiet
kid.
I went to the same elementary school as
my friend, and I had a different friend
in junior high school.
I met that kid for the first time in a
long time, and he said,
You're not a laughing kid, are you?
I was a kid who didn't talk much.
But recently, I've been laughing more
and talking more.
I think I've gotten a little more like
myself than before.
When a kid like me sees myself, I want
to be like that.
I want to be someone who admires me.
Thank you for watching!