I was so depressed that I thought I had
no choice but to face the night.
I was so anxious that I thought I would
end up in the night.
It's getting more and more fun.
Yes, I'm having a lot of fun.
Please talk more.
I might end up listening to you.
Please do.
I'll talk to you.
Please.
I was simply told that if I sing, my
family will praise me.
That's how I started singing.
I was living in a complex when I was
little.
My brother was smart and good at sports.
It seemed a little bright to me.
I felt like my family was really
accepting of me.
I wanted to be recognized by them.
If I sing, my family will pay attention
to me.
That's how I started to continue.
What kind of songs did you sing at that
time?
I sang the songs that were popular at
that time.
I sang songs that were popular at that
time.
You were praised a lot.
Yes, I was praised a lot.
That's why I became a singer.
When I was young, I wanted to be a
singer.
I was praised a lot.
People said I wasn't special.
There were many turning points.
But my first experience was
that I was recognized for my singing.
Do you have a way of communicating?
Yes, I do.
I thought singing was more meaningful
than music.
Can you show me something?
I thought singing was the same as
expressing yourself.
I was able to get attention by
communicating with people by singing.
I learned that singing is fun, so I
realized that I can't do it just by
having fun.
That's right. That was a little early.
But you must have put a lot of effort
into it.
I think there was a little bit of a
hesitation.
You were recording in your own room?
Yes, yes.
You were using Oda City?
Yes, I was using Oda City.
I was using free software called Oda
City,
and a USB microphone.
I didn't even use an interface.
I was trying to do it when my family
wasn't around.
I was recording.
So you were told that you would be fired
if you were in the band?
Yes.
I was told that I would be fired.
Oh, really?
Yes. I was told that I would be a civil
servant.
I said that I would not sing anymore.
I would go to college and become a civil
servant.
I was told that I would be a civil
So you had to hide and check yourself.
That's right.
That's why I became like this.
When I sing as myself,
I'm scared.
I wanted to sing as myself,
who is not a singer.
I wanted to sing without anyone knowing.
I'm sorry, but I'm not going to do it.
I'm really sorry, but I'm not going to
do it.
Normally, it's a plan.
It's a plan to give it to me.
That's right.
But I thought it would be better to say
no.
So I decided not to do it this time.
When you listen to the story,
you really admire someone who sings.
It's completely different from the way
you sing to become that person.
It's different.
I think there are many people who admire
being a musician.
They want to be like this person,
they want to be like this person,
they want to make music.
I think they've experienced that.
That's right.
That's how I see it.
I think the sense of music is different.
As I said earlier, I thought it was one
way to express it.
I've been singing as a means.
What's important is to express yourself.
If I refer to someone else, I can't
express my personality.
That's why I'm able to do it.
I don't listen to specific people, and I
don't refer to them.
That's why I'm able to cover vocalists.
I can't do it for a person who's not a
vocalist.
I want to add something more human.
I enjoyed being able to express it on
this side.
You were able to cover Vocaloid songs.
Is there anything difficult about it?
Is it a kind of
It's difficult.
In the first place, humans don't sing.
That's right.
There are also lines that are impossible
for humans.
But that's interesting.
When it's difficult, I feel like I want
to challenge myself more.
So, every time I finished recording, I
was able to get something.
I was able to learn new expressions,
like,
I'm a little better at this.
I was able to grow and it was fun, so I
kept trying.
I think I can show my character in
various ways depending on the song.
In the song, I showed my character in
three different ways,
but I was impressed that Yama-san was
able to express it well.
I was able to release the song while
thinking about that.
When Haruo Tsugeru hit the music scene,
a famous artist called Yorukei was
popular.
There were many artists who were the
theme of Yorukei.
I was able to get involved in that
genre.
I can sing rock like Mahi,
I can sing ballads, anything.
I wanted people to know that I can sing.
So I'm trying to make music that doesn't
have a genre.
I'm glad I got the chance to do it.
Thank you.
So you want to put on a new mask today?
Yes, I'm going to be doing a renewal
this year.
I don't know if you'll be able to see it
well, but my vision has improved.
That's important.
It was hard to see, so I was able to
blink.
You couldn't blink before?
I couldn't.
Thank you for watching.
My eyes were open.
Your eyelashes were open.
Yes, they were.
That's tough.
Do you order the mask to match the shape
of your face?
Yes, I do.
I take the mold off with a plaster.
If you make it too perfect, you can't
make it perfect.
Yes, that's right.
I think many people have asked this
question.
Why are you wearing a mask?
I'm not sure.
When I'm showing my own characteristics,
I think I'll be a little biased and
listen to the music.
I don't think it's a good idea to do
that.
So I want you to enjoy your music as
clean as possible.
I want you to enjoy your music as clean
as possible.
That's why I'm doing this kind of
activity now.
When did you decide to wear a mask?
To be honest, I didn't want to do a live
performance at all.
But Haruo Tsukeru hit me and asked me to
do a live performance.
I kept refusing to do it.
I thought I would definitely get a good
vibe when I performed live.
I was really resisting. I didn't want to
show any mercy.
I really wanted to hear only the song.
But it's okay to do a live broadcast, so
I thought I'd try it once.
So, how do you show yourself on the
screen?
I was thinking of putting on a mask
while we were having a meeting.
Did you have any particular thoughts
about the mask?
I was originally going for a full face.
You look like Daft Punk.
I was hoping for a full face like Daft
Punk.
It's like when you come to know the
vocals,
your singing doesn't help get in your
voice.
That's what I decided.
So, the designer asked me to develop my
accent without asking me too much.
LGR
I've never had the experience of
enjoying music alone.
I didn't know what it was like to enjoy
music.
At first, I felt like I was being
judged.
I was doing it.
I was always worried that I wasn't good
at singing,
that I was being thought of,
that I was being disappointed.
I was always feeling a sense of
inferiority.
It was hard for a while.
Did you discover your singing skills
after you started singing live?
Yes.
Do you listen to your own music after
you sing?
Yes, I do. I'm really depressed.
That's the hardest part.
I can't sing live because I can't keep
up with the video.
I can't keep up with my own ideal.
I don't sing 100% of the time.
It's natural, but I wonder why I can't
do it.
I feel that every time after a concert.
During the final of the tour,
I couldn't forget the concert in many
ways.
I couldn't imagine the venue.
There were so many people coming.
And I was listening to my own voice.
When I saw the situation where so many
people were coming,
I was a little scared.
I wanted to give 120% of my power.
But it didn't work.
After it was over,
so many people came.
They came to support me.
The staff supported me so much.
They supported me.
I thought I might not have been able to
return it properly.
I was pretty depressed at that time.
It happens often.
The reason for being depressed is...
Singing and my individuality.
I often feel depressed because of that.
At that time, it was very terrible.
I was so depressed that I couldn't get
up.
But when I got into that situation,
in my experience so far,
I usually ran away from that weakness.
So I thought I was going in a bad
direction.
I thought I was going in a bad
I said there weren't any vocalists or
songs that had influenced me in the
beginning.
But since I started this activity, I've
met a vocalist I really respect.
It's Leo, the vocalist of a band called
ARI.
We're both in charge of the band.
We've been getting along well.
He's been thinking about me all the
time.
He noticed that I was depressed with the
actor, Fujii Shuka,
and they wrote me a very beautiful line.
Oh, that's what it is.
I have this routine before I do a live,
so I thought it would be nice if we did
the same thing.
Thank you for watching.
He taught me from the beginning.
No matter how bad I was, I couldn't go
back to the basics.
Thanks to that, the live was getting
more and more fun.
I was like, what should I have done?
It's not just a word to say, but it's
like we're scooping up together.
He always helped me a lot.
I didn't think I'd meet a vocalist I
could respect so much.
I was so moved when I went to see the
live performance.
I thought I was singing so hard and it
was so heart-wrenching.
I thought I had done a good job at the
live performance.
I was thinking about my own mistakes and
I was looking for perfection.
Live performances are...
I wasn't in a place like that.
I realized that I had to entertain the
audience
because they were listening to my songs.
I realized that I was too late.
Wow.
Yeah.
I realized that recording and making a
live performance are different.
I realized that after a year.
This title has many meanings.
It means to fight against the night in
Japanese.
I talked about the night in Side A.
It's a song that symbolizes the night
that hit with the spring.
It's a song that's included as a night
artist.
It's a genre that's only for me.
I want to be a part of that.
So I want to deal with that first.
I'm very pessimistic and lonely.
I have to deal with my own weakness.
I'm a hit singer who has been on the
show since the spring.
I don't think I'm good enough to Joe
bisschen.
I'm always worried that if I don't
release my own song,
I'll end up with a single hit.
I'm worried that I'll end up with a hit
song that will hit the spring,
or that I'll have more songs that will
represent me.
I think that's what's been on my mind
this year.
There are many meanings to the title,
but I thought I had to fight against the
night.
That's why I chose this title.
This year's battle is going to be a big
battle.
I thought I could only put this title on
this year.
I'm aware of the album,
but I think there are many people who
write songs
based on the theme of the album.
I think there are many people who write
songs based on the theme of the album.
We release songs that we want to sing at
different times.
We release the album with the meaning of
a bundle.
So, to be honest, we don't have a
uniformity.
When we were thinking about how to put
the album title,
we decided to put the album title on the
album that we wanted to achieve that
year.
We thought we had to face the night.
So we decided to try writing songs.
That's amazing. I'm looking forward to
it.
It's a task for me.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it too.
I'm sorry to say this many times,
but I don't think I have musical talent.
Especially writing lyrics and composing
songs is a challenge.
I think that if you keep working hard,
you can achieve something.
But writing lyrics and composing songs
is difficult.
I didn't adjust myself.
I didn't try to escape from the night.
I'm thinking of trying it out.
I'm really just a normal person.
I'm thinking about how many songs I can
make as a normal person.
I can't say it's fun.
I'm making it while worrying.
I want to be in the same situation as
the current listeners.
You're trying?
Yes, I am.
I'm really trying.
I think I'm in the same situation as
everyone else.
I don't know myself.
I'm not like that.
I'm trying my best to not be a one-shot
shot.
I'm struggling right now.
Maybe, for those who don't know,
the song might be a hit and make them
happy.
But I want to tell people that I'm doing
my best
as a normal person.