Thank you for watching.
The new member of the day is...
Yukata Sugata.
He was shooting a live photo that was
also on sale on Famien 21.
He took the picture of Yukata Sugata.
And...
The last episode of Ebisu Shopping!
New members will be introduced the
official goods of Famien
New members are ready to take photos for
the photo shoot.
I came to Yukata for the first time in
two years.
It's been a long time.
Really?
Yes.
Thank you for your hard work.
It's my first time this year.
I don't know how many years it has been.
I've only worn this shirt a few times
when I was a kid.
It's been a long time.
They are dancing with their hearts.
The shooting starts.
It's fast.
It's like this.
It's okay.
It's bumpy.
It's like looking at the camera.
It's like this.
Thank you.
I want to be more and more excited
I won't be a white person just like that
Of course, the senior members too
I want to be more and more excited
And, Yasumoto, who was back in the
activity the other day
I want to wear a big one like this
Then
I want to be more and more excited
It's dangerous
The camera is
No
For some reason, Nakayama also starts
shooting with my camera
Actually
Now, they are addicted to the photo
Among them, the photo of model Yasumoto
is her favorite
Please take more and more
OK, one more
This day, after professional cameraman
shooting, Nakayama's shooting time was
made
Next, shooting at the inn
Thank you
Aroma
Next costume is from the 90s
She wears a retro fashion to match the
stage
Yow
Then
What's popular now?
I don't know
It's really popular
On the manhole, on the manhole, there's
a song called dancehall
On TikTok?
Yes
If you find a manhole, you have to dance
on it
Really?
Yes
Riko-chan, if you stand on the manhole,
there's a dancehall
You know it?
I know it
On the manhole, there's a dancehall
You're so kind
Let's do it
I don't know at all
I have to do it
I'll do it if I find it
Mayama, born in the 90s, can't keep up
with the 2000s
Like a female
Wouldn't you beYes ago
Over there
lawer
What
While operating, opportunity
Enforcin the
teacher
They are teasing me.
Red people are teasing me too.
Rika-chan is going to get hit by them.
A female spy.
They are going to hit me.
They are going to turn.
They are cool.
They are like a boss.
But they can't decide what to do.
That's all.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
Thank you for watching.
The shoot is finally over.
What kind of photo will they take?
Let's find out!
And,
What are you doing?
Summer Ebisu Shopping!
Now, the three new members will
introduce the official goods of Bamien
as the members appear on stage.
What are we going to introduce today?
Today we are going to introduce the
products that are perfect for this hot
weather.
Especially, there are a lot of products
that are perfect for August 21st and
22nd.
Yes, that's right.
First of all, this is it.
Ta-da!
The first item is a live T-shirt from
Famien21.
This is a T-shirt from Famien21, a
summer live show called Shirito Emi Chuu
Asu, which is a hot topic all over the
world.
It's cute.
What did you think of it, Nanaka-chan?
Yes, I tried it on.
I tried on M, but it's cute.
It's comfortable and the color is cute.
It's good to wear it with any clothes.
What about the design?
The design is a new member's egg.
Hey, hey.
It's very new and it's very nice.
It's a cute single shirt with us.
In addition to T-shirts, this time...
What is that?
There is a new member.
It's hot.
This is an aloha shirt on such a hot
day.
This is an aloha shirt limited to the
day of the fan meeting.
How is it?
It's a good match.
This is the best.
It's easy to wear it live.
I put a slit here.
This is private.
I'm a little angry.
This is fun.
I think that the fans of Kokura will
come to the fan meeting in this style.
Please.
I'm a little angry.
I'm so happy to be angry.
What is the point of this video for
AROHA?
I'm a little angry.
I'm angry.
The second episode will start.
The video is refreshing.
I want you to watch this video.
And the next item is this.
Ta-da!
It's a rubber badge.
Yay!
The third item is a rubber badge with
the number of the members engraved.
This is the first member color that we
have since we joined.
It's a good thing that each member has
their own goods.
I think red goes well with various
clothes.
I'll press red.
Light green goes well with various
colors.
It's cute to wear it on your face or on
your video.
White goes well with various colors.
White goes well with light green, but it
goes well with white.
Try it on your face.
It's okay.
Please subscribe to this channel.
And the last item is
This is
Ta-da
It's not for live
It contains 10 colors
It's a psyllium that can make the member
color shine
Wow, amazing
Let's shine it
This is the third one
Purple
This is also a pen light that can make
all 10 colors shine
This is a pen light
Cute
Next, next, next
This is white
What is the price of this new pen light?
It's 3,500 yen
We will also find out who bought this
I hope you will buy it
Thank you
That's all for the summer shrimp
shopping!
Yeah! Bye bye!
We are waiting for you!
There are many other goods that will
liven up the live show.
Please check the official fan page of
FAMIEN!