The third round of the second round of
the new member audition!
I will never lose to the desire to
become an idol!
How old are you?
I'm 16 years old.
You are a junior high school student.
What are you doing now?
I'm a double dachi.
Double dachi?
I'm in a club team.
There was a Japanese competition last
week.
I was in a club team.
You are a junior high school student.
They have various specialties.
I'm 15 years old.
I'm a high school student.
I studied law at a junior high school.
I studied painting.
Are you a junior high school student?
I'm not.
Do you play classical ballet?
I'm a high school student.
absorption standard
CHEERING
she's used to try it
her finger's from head to toe
wait, I'll ask her to do it
she's trying two
can I try again?
you got it
personaje
I'm nervous
Kumamoto prefecture
No?
Oh, Hiyoshi
One more
I'm nervous
I'm really nervous
I'm nervous too
Well... let me think, relatively
speaking
Far cultivation can't make things easy
See you next time!
The first audition was a success!
I didn't know anything about the
audition,
but I was happy to sing and perform my
favorite songs.
I did my best,
and I hope that fits the image of the
new members of AB2.
The students gathered from all over the
country with their individuality.
How old are you now?
I'm 18 years old, the first grader of
university.
You were in Nagoya, right?
Yes, I was in Nagoya doing idol
activities.
What song did she choose for the dance
audition?
The first repartory of the debut, ライビング.
The reason is?
This song is the song I sang when I was
in Nagoya as an idol.
It's the same as the feeling before the
event, so I sang this song.
I admire the charm of Ebichu's
performance.
Her performance is amazing.
The members talked about this before.
I'm looking forward to meeting the
members who really love Ebichu and take
care of her.
I'm thinking about it.
Thank you for watching.
I'm the same age as Kaoriko-san, but I'm
glad I was able to perform a song by my
favorite singer, Ebichu-san.
I like Kaoriko-san, and I really like
all of them.
The second screening, which was thought
by 50 students, has ended.
Thank you for your hard work.
There were some students who I thought
were good, so I'm looking forward to the
next training.
I haven't seen the individual parts yet,
so I'd like to see the person next to
me.
I'd like to make it feel like that.
What is the new member that the head of
the Evis Junior High School, Fujii,
wants?
I want to be in the current Evis Junior
High School.
I want to be comfortable, but I also
want to be independent.
I want to be able to stand on my own.
I want to be a shining child that can
let the new wind blow on the way.
Thank you for watching!