Please select a card.
Thanks for watching.
Nogizaka fifty years down the line like.
From now on, up the relatively rockin'
price.
O. A lot of D back...
O XX X XX X X X
X X X X X X
Saikoto!
We will be doing the video quiz Bro
minus
talking here, with some entertainment
coming up soon as well
Last year, Nobizaka46 brought a lot of
news to the world
We will introduce the small news of the
members
Tonight's news is from July 8th, 2022
Kuromi's senpai wind is getting stronger
Yoda is looking at his relationship with
his senpai
Yakubo's eyebrows disappear due to the
rhyme
Ioki rediscovered the charm of fighting
Akimoto received a gift of a joke every
day
That's all for July 8th B-class news
I didn't know until I heard the story
Kuromi's senpai wind is getting stronger
This is me
I was imitating you
The first time I thought Kuromi's senpai
wind was getting stronger
was at the Under Live in March
I was imitating Maaya-san
I was imitating her
When we were in a line, I was doing this
to her
I was like, are you OK?
I was doing this to a nervous junior
I see. This is not a time-travel
After that, a student came in
The school was close to the Nissan
Stadium
The students and Kuromi were talking
There was a Kuromi Field in the hallway
Kuromi Field?
It was like a Kuromi Town
They were talking from this angle
It was like zero distance
Zero distance? That's amazing
The student was not doing a public
service
When I heard Kuromi's voice, I felt like
I had to go to the prison
The student was told like this
At first, I was happy that she came
I think Kuromi is great
When two people gather, everyone goes to
the Kuromi Field
That's Kuromi Field
Look, there is no picture of Kuromi
Field
I didn't take it
I want you to take it in the future
It will be held regularly, so I will
definitely take it
I want to do it
What did Kuromi-senpai talk about?
She reported her nervousness
Report her nervousness?
She went out to the hallway?
Kuromi-san was like, how are you?
How are you?
She said, I'm good
What is good?
Thank you for helping me with my work
No problem. I have a picture of my
student ID
That's not good
Did you see it?
I saw it
I see.
I think she should join a different idol
group.
She should stop her.
Interesting.
Next.
Yoda.
Why do you care about relationships?
It's heavy.
I want to get along with everyone
regardless of seniority or juniority in
2022.
You are a black-eyed girl.
Black-eyed girl.
You admire her.
I admire her.
Yoda's admiration.
Black-eyed girl already did it.
I thought so.
But I was alone on my day off.
I was talking to the TV.
I thought I couldn't achieve it.
So, I invited my juniors.
You look forward to it.
Who did you invite?
YUNA SHIBATA.
I invited Rika and KAKKI.
I also invited her to her house.
I'm going to get along with her.
You are all in a relationship.
You should get along with her.
Don't you invite UME?
I'm not confident.
I can't invite her.
There was a member who could invite her.
I want to invite her.
You are a black-eyed girl.
She will definitely invite you.
Please invite me.
You should invite her.
You should book her with someone.
She won't come.
Why?
You can't invite her.
I often don't go beyond the invitation.
I'm worried that she doesn't want to go
with me.
But I want to invite her.
What happens without her?
This is interesting.
Next is this.
This is a picture of Jingu.
This is a picture of the day I came to
see her.
I drew this picture on the day I came to
You look like a mother.
I like that.
Is there a video?
I want to see it.
You look like an adult.
You look cool.
You look good.
You look beautiful.
You look like a child.
You look like an adult.
Is this okay?
You can draw this picture.
Thank you.
Next is IYOKI.
Is this a bath?
I took my friends to a small bath on my
way home from school.
That's good.
I liked that.
I didn't know that after I came to this
place.
I spend a lot of time alone.
You have a good hobby.
I drink milk from a bottle when I'm
done.
You are happy.
You are cute.
Is this true?
Is this a real GACHAPIN?
There is green.
You are cute.
This is a picture of a bath.
This is a picture of a bare face.
This is amazing.
This time I have a real picture.
Let's continue.
This is scary.
You send a gag every day.
I was with Hayashi every day.
I was able to make a gag every time I
met him.
Hayashi is a gagger.
I give him a gag.
I give him a present.
I have never used it.
I want you to show me.
Can I show you what I got?
I got it, so I'll show you.
I will show you Hayashi's gag.
Please show me.
This is a piece.
What did you say?
I didn't use it.
This is a piece.
I showed him a piece of my teeth.
I gave him a piece.
I don't know what it is.
People who make a gag are like that.
I can be recognized someday.
I can be recognized someday or I can't
be recognized someday.
Do you have a gag that you named
yourself?
I haven't made it yet.
Since the summer ended, I started
imitating KUROMI.
I changed my name.
I want you to make a gag that you can
introduce yourself.
That's good.
Do you have a gag that you can introduce
yourself?
I will introduce myself as Hayashinso.
Please do it.
That's good.
I will use it.
Hayashi is Hayashinoki.
Hayashinoki is good.
How about Hayashinoki?
Hayashinoki.
Hayashinoki is cuter.
Hayashinoki should be a little like a
palm tree.
I see.
Hayashinoki.
Hayashinoki is like a palm tree.
That's KUROMI.
Please show me KUROMI's palm tree.
I will show you.
KUROMI's palm tree.
That's a selfish thing.
What are you doing?
I was thinking about it.
I made it my own.
I want to make it my own this year.
Don't put your hand above your head.
Why are you giving me a lesson?
This is for you.
From here, we'll be covering Nobizaka
B-class news from September.
Sakaguchi, this year also forgotten.
Endo, the love that was left behind
becomes the main.
Kaki, a message from Kamakiri.
Yumiki, the joints of her grandmother
are beautiful.
Hayashi, success in the Miiraka of
Mikan.
Yakumo, eating churros in the toilet.
This was the Nogizaka B-class news of
2022.
I also forgot this year.
Yamashita posted a group photo of the
3rd generation of blog.
I was there.
Yamashita posted a photo of me alone.
Is that true?
This is there.
Is Sakaguchi there?
Yes.
Where is Sakaguchi?
It's between Yoda and Renka.
There is a blog again.
This is now.
The back of the photo is cut.
Why?
You can just go forward.
I take this photo when the 3rd
generation of blog is gathered.
I think this is forgotten by me.
I take a picture again.
I take a lot of pictures because someone
is in the middle.
But this is gone.
This is gone even when I'm practicing.
Everyone may not have noticed.
Show me again.
This is gone.
This is moving.
This is like a psychological photo.
This is fast.
Can you move like that during practice?
This is moving backwards.
You can put this in UME.
You can put this here.
I'm not a person.
Call UME.
I will bring it to the first place.
Next is N.
Is this also a Yakubo?
That's right.
What is it?
This is a story of YAKUBO MIYA.
I started to get jealous of him after
two days.
You don't just say you like him.
I started to talk to RUNA HAYASHI.
I said I like him more.
You are cheating.
I'm not cheating.
I'm just talking.
I will be hated.
He calls me by a special nickname.
I started to call him RURURU.
From now on, call me YASHINOKI.
RURURU is stronger.
I like it.
I want more.
I like SAKU.
You should get along with other people.
I'm glad you like me.
If you block this, you will be alone.
I want you to have a sense of decency.
You can talk to RUNA HAYASHI.
I'm being called a big name.
Is it a big name?
The title is a big name.
I may be hated.
Do you hate me?
I don't hate you.
I can't say that.
You can say it.
I'm scared.
I don't know what to do.
Everyone likes SAKU.
You get along with SAKU.
I want to get along with SAKU.
It's good to get along with SAKU.
I don't like it.
The distance between you and SAKU is the
same as me.
I'm the best.
Let's ask SAKU.
Which is the closest to you?
No, no, no.
Please give me a rating.
Who do you think is the closest?
distance
The distance between you and yourself.
SAKU, I've been with you for a long
time.
I've been saying that.
It's Hayashi.
From this feeling, it's YAKUBO.
YAKUBO's love is not enough.
Me?
You're so cute.
You said you liked me so much.
You're making me so lost.
Your love is not enough.
I'm sorry.
I'm not looking for love that you like.
What are you doing?
I don't even have eyebrows.
That's what it is.
Show me your gag.
No, not that.
Why is it a tease?
Throw away the tease!
That was a beautiful flow!
Why is it a tease?
I'm going to make you like it.
You know the story of Kitakaze and the
sun, right?
Kitakaze comes because he's cold when he
tries to take off his clothes in the
wind.
I'll take it off with the power of the
warm sun.
It's the sun, right?
Saki-chan.
You're wrong.
You don't know the story of Kitakaze and
the sun, do you?
You didn't change anything.
So, please do it like that.
Next.
This is it.
It's a little bit.
What is this?
Is there such a flow?
But it's not like we've put together a
flow like this.
Of course.
I wanted you to see this message.
What is it?
Good luck, Saki-chan.
It's a black eye.
It's just a black eye.
It's a black eye from the side.
Really.
Every year, I see it on B-class news.
That girl.
Itoko-chan.
She's cute.
Miki.
She came to see me at Kamakiri.
I don't know why, but Kamakiri.
I was expecting this flow.
I can't think of anything but that.
So, there's Kamakiri, but there's
Kamakiri next to it.
It means, good luck.
Let's move on.
Yumiki.
What is this?
The joints are beautiful.
The joints of the old lady.
That's right.
My grandmother was in her 70s or 80s.
I didn't know that.
That's a witch.
The knees and elbows of this old lady
are very beautiful.
I want you to see it.
It's beautiful.
It's shiny.
That's amazing.
The knees are beautiful.
Where is this?
This is the knee.
Is this a knee?
I don't know.
I don't know where it is.
Did you ask about the knee?
It's very beautiful.
There is a secret.
The elbow and knee?
It's a secret that you never touch your
elbow or knee.
The elbow and knee are beautiful because
they were raised.
It's like an oil.
Is the old lady's elbow and knee
beautiful?
My elbow is black.
It's not black at all.
My knees are black.
It's erotic to show your knees.
You don't have to show it.
I can show it.
Is that true?
Your knees are not black.
Is your elbow okay?
It's beautiful.
I was embarrassed.
You are naked.
Your knees will be beautiful in the
future.
I want to participate in the knee one
grand prix.
You don't want to participate in the
knee one grand prix.
I see.
Thank you for watching this video.
What is this?
Is this a Mikan flower?
On Valentine's Day, Higuchi-san gave us
a Mikan flower.
I drew a picture of the name and the
face of the person.
I saw it at the end of the event.
I drew a picture of the person and gave
it to you.
I thought the picture would be cut off,
so I decided not to eat it.
I dried it while adjusting the air
conditioner.
This is like a dry flower.
This picture is still there.
This is still there.
This picture is dirty.
This is hard.
This is zero moisture.
This melts the hardness.
Did you give HIGUCHI that much?
I took good care of it.
Did you give HIGUCHI chocolate?
I didn't give it to him.
He only gave me one.
Hey.
I'm just happy.
Did anyone drink the juice that you
bought?
I bought it.
This is amazing.
This is like a drug store.
Is this a collector?
I bought a refrigerator recently.
I also moved SHINUCHI's tea.
You are a person who can't throw away
things.
I can't throw it away or drink it.
Where do you usually put it?
I put it next to my shoe box.
I put it next to my shoe box when I go
out of the house every day.
I don't know you, but I think you are
dirty.
You still have it in your case.
Next.
What is this?
I am a sophomore in college.
I took remote classes for a year.
I don't have many friends.
You are a college student and you are
doing this kind of work.
I don't have many friends because it's
hard to make.
I really want to eat CHURROS at college.
I sell CHURROS in the kitchen car.
I'm a little embarrassed to eat bright
food alone.
CHURROS is a very Western food.
I really wanted to eat CHURROS.
I bought CHURROS and hid it in my
jacket.
I ran to the toilet and ate CHURROS
alone.
You are a pitiful story.
I have a picture.
Is this a toilet?
This is a toilet.
I don't understand.
You should have said that you would eat
CHURROS with a stranger.
I can't do things like CHURROS.
You don't go to strangers.
Do you have a college friend?
I have a college friend.
Everyone came to me.
Thank you for watching.
How can you get your friends to come to
you?
I haven't done anything.
I want to open a yakubo field.
Me too.
I think so.
After that, I eat hot dogs alone.
I feel sorry for you.
Someone should invite you to that place.
Saki-chan will come.
Saki-chan won't go.
She won't go.
She may come because she likes me.
Saki-chan doesn't like you.
That's strange.
But you should eat churros at the
university.
I want to eat churros.
I'm worried about what to do in the
future.
Will you come?
I recommend the emergency stairs.
I see.
Everyone is sad.
Is it like that at the university?
I can hear footsteps on the emergency
stairs.
I can understand when someone comes.
I'm glad.
Why are you talking about sad things?
To be continued.
In the news broadcasted over the past
two weeks,
the results of the
Nobitaka B-Q NEWS
The winner of the 2020 is
Kuromi from April
She is going to be an idol
Kamakiri
There is one more
It's like a drama in June
Rainy morning
Please let us have them
Kuromi was really good this time
She was really good
She was really good from the
impersonation
She is really popular
She is famous in various radio shows
I'm thankful
She is amazing
She was touched
How?
When did she do that?
When we were talking, she said she was
really good at impersonation
Recently
When I said let's do our best, she said
let's do our best
Let's do our best
She is amazing
I'm thankful
Hayashi rice
3,2,1
Manatsu Akimoto graduates concert mobile
Thank you for watching.
unbelievable