It's reflected in the sea.
It's beautiful.
It's shining.
It's golden.
KAN-chan is here again.
She is the sun that takes care of us all
day.
Good morning.
Thank you for your cooperation today.
It's beautiful.
It's dazzling.
I saw the sea. It's amazing.
We'll be together all day.
We'll be together from the beginning to
the end.
I'm happy.
It's amazing.
I can't see it directly.
I don't know what I'm looking at.
I'm happy.
Happy New Year!
This is the first project of the year.
We have prepared a great project.
The last project is to watch the sunrise
and sunset on the same day.
What does that mean?
We just saw the sunrise on the Pacific
Ocean.
This time, we will go to the Japan Sea
and watch the sunset on the same day.
We can go sightseeing on the road to the
Japan Sea.
We can enjoy it.
But, we have another mission.
We have another mission.
If we mix the Pacific Ocean and the
Japan Sea, we can make the sea.
The sea?
We will mix the Pacific Ocean and the
Japan Sea.
We are on the Pacific Ocean now.
We will put the water in a cup and bring
it to the Japan Sea.
When we bring the cup, one of us must
hold the cup.
Which one of us should hold it?
You can't leave it.
Do we hold it all the time?
When we sleep?
We hold it all the time.
Do we hold it all the time?
If we break it, we can't go sightseeing.
We have to go to the Japan Sea.
We have to wait until the sun sets.
No way!
Are you serious?
Yes.
Water is important.
We have to wait until the new year.
What a plan!
As a precaution, the staff put the water
in a plastic bottle.
So, we can spill it.
We can go to the sea.
We can go sightseeing.
We want to go sightseeing.
We don't have such a chance.
We will do our best.
Let's go to the sea!
Please subscribe to this channel!
We can't ride it!
It's cold!
How can we ride it?
How much do we put in?
I think we can ride it a little bit.
Yeah, we can.
So, let's put a lot in.
Go! Go!
Please subscribe to this channel!
I'm rampaging.
My shoes are Moist!
I'm getting wet!
My shoes are wet!
You're good at it!
Thank you, Ms. Matsumoto.
Thank you.
We're going to the Japan Sea side.
We're going to the sea side.
We're leaving!
How's the water?
It's fine.
When we started,
we were running on the beach.
It was so muddy.
I spilled it!
You should be careful.
You should spill all of it.
Right.
Even if it's just one drop.
It's fine.
Let's do our best.
I spilled it again.
Don't drink it.
It's dangerous.
If you hold it like this, you'll get
drunk.
Can I drink it till the end?
It's quite dangerous.
Car is dangerous.
Car shaking is dangerous.
I want to put a wrap on it.
That's true.
It was better to have less.
That's right.
It's a good amount.
But, if you put water in it, it won't be
broken.
It's dangerous.
I'm in front of you.
But I'll carry it properly.
I'll do my best.
We're in the same boat.
Yes, we are.
We're on the same boat.
Leave it to me.
I hope it's okay.
It's shaking a lot.
I'm shaking too.
We have to keep our hands in sync.
Should I ride it like this?
Let me borrow it.
Thank you for watching. Please subscribe
to our channel.
Thank you for your viewing.
You're moving like a cameraman.
It says SAKURAMI.
It's a place near SAKURAMI Onsen.
We've come this far.
We haven't finished the whole thing yet.
You're good at holding it.
But it's still early.
We're just getting started.
But it's going well.
It's going well.
We've done it well.
Do you want to do a two-shot?
Let's do it.
You look good.
I got along with Kesi.
We can go on.
Let's go.
I'll do my best.
Bye bye.
I want to go
It's cold
I want to go to hot spring
Is it around here?
Not yet?
It's a fish-shaped hot spring around
here
Really?
Is this it?
I want to go
Is it not?
I have to see the sun
I see
I came here
Let's eat a fish
It's good
I admire
Yeah, yeah
I'm just saying
But I want to eat something delicious
I want to eat
What is famous in Yamagata?
What is it?
I want to eat soba!
I want to eat real tobacco.
Is it different taste?
What is it?
It is like a mountain road.
It is really a mountain.
Please protect us.
We will protect you.
Let's do our best.
See you again.
Ta-da!
Wow!
It's a waterfall!
Otaki?
Otaki Drive-in
We're at Otaki Drive-in!
It's a path that leads from Sendai to
Yamagata.
It's amazing.
It's a mysterious place.
It's a bit rough now.
It's even more impressive.
It's so beautiful.
There's a Tamakon at the Otaki Drive-in!
I wanted to eat it!
Me too!
So let's go while eating it.
Yeah!
Yamagata!
I want to enjoy Yamagata that I feel!
I'm excited!
It's good!
It's a good place!
Right?
I feel a little bit of Yamagata or
summer.
That's right.
It's amazing!
I'm looking forward to it!
We are going to eat Tama-konnyaku!
It smells so good!
It's round.
It's a real one.
I'm hungry.
Let's eat!
It's so cute.
It's delicious.
It's good to eat in winter.
Please subscribe to my channel.
It warms me up.
It's really good.
The taste is a little strong.
It's well-seasoned.
What can we eat next?
We finished eating.
Thank you for the meal.
It was delicious.
We can do our best after this.
We'll do our best with water.
Bye bye.
We're in Tendo!
We're here!
Ta-da!
This is Tendo!
I think it's a small town in Shogi.
I think so.
It's very famous.
We're here!
Yay!
There are many shops.
There are many hot springs.
This is the first town we've been to
since we entered Yamagata.
I see!
This is the first town we've been to
since we entered Yamagata.
I see!
The water is still clean.
I'm getting tired.
You've been holding it for a long time.
Do you want to change?
Can I?
Please hold it.
I'll stand here.
I'll do my best.
It's nice.
Yamagata...
Yamagata is famous for soba. I want to
eat it.
I hope we can eat soba. I want to eat
soba.
We ate tamakon.
A bus to Tendo Onsen is in front of us.
I'll run.
You're still energetic.
You're energetic. It's good.
We'll move around Yamagata like this.
I'm surprised.
I broke it.
I'm scared.
There are still many.
I ate them all.
I was surprised.
I'll do my best.
Thank you for the meal.
I'm going to sleep.
To be continued.
Thank you for watching!
THE해칠우는다
Your smile is cute.
I'm going to take a picture of the
camera.
Cheers!
Cheers to the cute cat!
I'll do my best after this.
I'll do my best.
I'll do my best more than I did in the
past.
I'll do my best.
Thank you for watching!
It's a nice atmosphere.
I think Tori-soba is famous.
There are various soba.
I'm glad.
You have it.
Yes.
You eat it as you have it.
I eat it alternately.
I see.
What will happen if I put this?
It's a mistake.
Really?
It's the same as spilling.
I see.
I'm sorry.
Where is Yamagata?
Aomori, Iwate, Miyagi,
Hanyu?
Aomori,
Miyagi,
Niigata?
Wait a minute.
I'll stop.
I see.
This is...
Please subscribe to this channel.
The soba is here!
It's here!
It's chicken soba.
It looks delicious.
It's so big.
It's cold and warm.
It looks delicious.
It's good.
Let's eat.
Let's eat alternately.
I'll watch over you.
I'll eat first.
Let's eat.
It looks delicious. It smells good.
Can you see it?
Let's eat.
It's good.
Really?
It's really good.
The noodles are chewy.
I love it.
It's really good.
Try it.
Thank you.
I can eat as much as I want.
I see.
Yamagata is good.
Itadakimasu.
You don't like it, do you?
I want you to try it.
You can feel it as soon as you put it in
your mouth.
It's very good.
It's really good.
It's chewy.
I'm eating alone.
Is there any good technique?
It's OK. Leave the water to me.
Thank you.
It's delicious.
I'm going to eat it with a spoon.
You hold it in a unique way.
Like this?
But, it's not a good way to eat.
It's good.
What time is it now?
It's about 12 o'clock.
It's almost time to go.
I think so.
We are going to go now.
It's almost time to go.
I think so.
I think we can leave this here.
I see.
Because it's chocolate.
We can eat it at the same time.
I think so.
We can leave it here.
It's OK.
Let's eat it.
It won't decrease.
Really?
Let's put it together.
OK.
Do you want to spill it?
I'll put it.
We have to show it.
I think so.
One, two.
It's chocolate.
We'll go to the Japan tour.
We enjoyed it.
We can eat it.
We won't give it to you.
We'll eat it and go to the Japan tour.
Let's go.
Let's go to the Japan tour.
Please subscribe to this channel.
We can see the sea soon.
It was long.
We were so excited.
How was it?
It was a good dream.
It was fun.
It's not over yet.
But we have to get to the sea from here.
Yes, we have to.
But it was good. I felt the charm.
The mountain.
The mountain and Miyagi.
I'm awake.
We can see two seas in a day.
Yes.
The opposite sea.
We can go there.
It's not only in Tohoku.
It's also attractive.
Is this in the town?
No.
It's in the town.
It was fun.
It was a great and interesting
experience.
I was too serious.
I didn't film it.
It's over.
Please subscribe to my channel.
See you later.
Let's take a video.
We arrived at the beach.
This is Nihonkai.
We are here.
We are finally in Nihonkai, which
started from Taiheiyo.
We are moving in a moment.
Thank you.
Let's make a lot of memories with such
thoughts.
Let's do our best.
But the sun is not here.
I think so.
Can you see it?
It's the sun!
I can't see it.
It's bright around here, so I think we
can see it.
It's a sunset now.
We can't see the sun.
It's getting dark.
We can't see the sunset.
Really?
We can't see the sun.
But we enjoyed the atmosphere.
We did.
We can see it.
Thank you, sun.
Thank you.
We can see it.
We can see it with our heart.
We enjoyed the sunset.
We have another mission.
We can go to the sea if we mix the ocean
and the sea of Japan.
Let's do it.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Before hitting the Big Ekima coming soon
Genpuro?
Yes.
Oh, I know that rolling hair.
Yeah.
Start.
Did it thunder?
A penalty shot.
Go.
Is it okay?
She didn't know the stop button.
I can't do it!
What are you doing?
Look at me.
Wait a minute.
Where did you go?
You are good.
You do it at such a time.
Where did you go?
You are crying.
Look at me.
I can't do it.
Mission failed.
At the end...
Please subscribe to my channel.
Water.
But there are a lot of traces of hard
work.
It's okay.
Thank you.
Do you have this water?
What is this?
I'm going to put the freshly caught sea
of Japan in the water.
The sea of Japan is beautiful.
Yes, it is.
We have finished the sea of Japan.
Next, we are going to put the freshly
caught sea of Japan in the water.
What will happen?
I'm not sure.
Let's go.
Yes.
Wow!
It's the sea!
We made it!
It's amazing.
It's a result of our hard work.
That's right.
It's beautiful.
We made a precious water.
It's the sea!
How was it?
Well...
It was a place I've never thought I'd
see.
I'm glad we were able to do this
project.
Yamagata is a really nice place, so
please visit.
I really wanted to come back.
I know it's moving, but it's nice to
have a place where you can't walk.
You should try this place in the
morning.
It might be fun.
It's a good place for a morning walk.
We decided to bring the water from the
Pacific Ocean to the sea.
Let's show off to the members.
We made the sea.
Let's show off our research.
Let's display this.
I think it's something we can show off.
It's amazing.
Let's display it.
Thank you for watching.
Please support us this year.
Bye bye.