This week's Ebichu Tastasu is a
continuation of last week's winter
project, Fuyuen!
The popular theme park, Tokyo
Doitsumura, will be the stage for the
Fuyuen Photo Contest!
Let's catch up on the members as we
enjoy the performance!
Ebichu Tastasu, start!
Replay
Ending notice
subs by maro!
I'm so into you that I can't stop
I'm a heart-throbbing boy
Moratorium, moratorium, moratorium
Middle school students, moratorium
Add all kinds of things to private Ebisu
middle school
Middle school students
Ebisu middle school
This program is brought to you by these
sponsors.
Ebichu Winter Expedition, or in other
words, winter expedition.
Start!
Last week, they went to a theme park in
Sodegaura City, Chiba Prefecture.
They enjoyed an attraction in Tokyo's
Doitsumura.
This time...
From now on, we'll split into pairs.
You'll take a picture of a memory.
You'll be paired up.
You'll decide who you'll pair up with.
I'll choose you through a putter golf.
That's unexpected.
You're already in the picture.
It's nothing unexpected.
To decide who will pair up, they'll play
putter golf.
They'll putt in order.
The member who has the closest golf ball
to the ball will pair up.
Matsuno is paired up this time.
So, they'll be split into pairs of two
teams and three teams.
First, the oldest, Mayama's putter.
Mayama, please.
Please do it as if you are going to put
it in.
Yes, hole in one.
Hole in one.
Do your best.
Mayama, hole in one.
Please.
I'll go.
It's going in.
Good working!
Don't say, Hole in Yang.
I see.
The closest one to the mountain is the
one with the pen.
Yes, that's right.
Next, Yasumoto.
Will it be Hole in Yang?
Yasumoto. Yes.
Hole in Yang.
Yang!
Unfortunately, it didn't become Yang.
What's the situation when it becomes
Yang?
Next, Hirotaka's challenge.
Will he make it?
Southpaw Yan
Wait, the camera will take a picture of
you
Sorry, I'm the only one
Let's go
3 people are separated
I think everyone doesn't want to pair up
Hoshina's challenge
Where is he aiming?
Where do you want to go?
I'm good at taking pictures of people I
love
That Yan
I see
I understand
He's aiming for Hirota's ball
Will he make it?
He did it!
That's good!
As he said, he nailed it!
Next, Kashiwagi will challenge
By the way, where are you going,
Kashiwagi?
I don't know
Yasuyan
What?
It's Holy Land
It's Yayan
Yayan is far away
Yes, it's far away
For example, you can decide Holy Land
Holy Land
In a cup
What would you do if you put it in a
cup?
If you put it in a cup, it's great
Kashiwagi, Holy Yan
Yan?
Wait, Yan?
She said it's dangerous
At the end of Kashiwagi's scream,
Yasumoto's ball
will go pia
As you can see, there are five people
left.
There are two people left.
Then I will challenge Kobayashi.
Where is the scary thing?
It's healing
So you have to get closer to the teacher
than the orange
It's like curling
Curling? OK
Go for it!
Will Kobayashi be able to get closer to
the teacher than the kashiwagi?
It's subtle
To be continued
It's a triangle relationship.
I thought of something good.
What's wrong?
Most of the good things about Nakayama
are bad.
I'm asking.
I'm going to break the triangle
relationship.
What are you laughing at?
For some reason, Nakayama is going to
break the triangle relationship.
Where is the ball?
Please do it for the show.
Nakayama.
I'm very scared.
That's good.
I see.
Can you see that?
It's far.
It's far, but...
So, the result of the pattern golf is as
you can see.
Hirota and Hoshina are a pair.
Yasumoto, Kashiwagi and Kobayashi are a
trio.
And, Mayama and Nakayama are a pair.
Please take a lot of pictures.
It's great!
So, let's begin the contest to take an
amazing picture
Protocon Test Start!
The members who won the Grand Prix will
receive a luxurious prize.
First, the team with a triangle-shaped
face, Yasumoto, Kashiwagi, and
Kobayashi.
What should we do?
I don't have anything I've worn.
Something you've worn?
I'm not sure if I can wear something
from Germany.
You're not from Germany!
I wear it once a year.
I wear it once a year, but...
I don't wear it much during the day.
The appearance is...
There's something from Tokyo, Germany.
I'll just go with that for now.
Wait, let's take a photo.
Let's take a photo.
What they found was the theme park's
classic, the face-revealing panel.
They decided to take a photo here.
It's like a character from an anime.
Ready, go.
Wait, you should write the word, Germany
Village.
That's important.
Master, that's important.
Next, Kobayashi becomes the cameraman in
the place of the master.
Amazing, Higashi is very satisfied with
the results.
Why do you laugh so much?
One picture of Kobayashi full of vigor
confirms why, in the following part of
the interview.
The next issue for the team in charge of
meeting the trends is……
Please subscribe to my channel!
I'm not wearing my illumination right
now, but I'm going to enjoy it.
The regular customer of Tokyo
Doitsumura, Kashiwagi, is wearing her
illumination.
It's daytime, but is it okay?
Okay, cheers!
Okay!
Thank you.
Wow, it's beautiful.
After that, they continue to shoot
Kashiwagi and Kobayashi.
What kind of one will be completed?
On the other hand, this is the Mayama-
Nakayama pair who came to the children's
zoo.
Mayama wants to take a two-shot with a
cute sheep.
But...
It's too far away.
It's okay.
She gives up taking a two-shot and aims
for the moment of feeding.
Can I bite this?
Second comedy
I'm scared.
The distance between Nakayama and the
sheep is not narrowed.
All of them have a subtle expression.
The cameraman changes.
Nakayama shoots Mayama.
I'm scared.
Which one is it?
It's a black one.
Rika-chan, look this way
Oh my god!
Cute!
It's good!
It seems that they got an ideal picture
And in Flower Garden, Hirota and Hoshina
are seen
Hirota is aiming at Hoshina who is
sitting on the bench with a particular
low angle
If you take a picture of me, I'll be
gone.
It's important to have you sit in front
of me.
Is that so?
I'll look back a little.
But it's cute.
I'm pretty cute.
The shadow is cute, too.
Cute.
It's like a shadow.
It's true.
Shadow comes out beautifully.
It's like a youthful feeling.
It's common.
The sky is nice, so today is good.
Oh, it's good.
A picture of Irota's sense.
Please subscribe to the channel.
Meanwhile, Yasumoto, Kashiwagi and
Kobayashi are standing in front of the
store and discussing something.
No way.
They are hungry after shooting.
Thank you.
It's warm.
The camera is in her right hand, and the
banana chocolate in her left hand.
I'm happy.
Was it this good?
Thank you.
I'm happy to eat something other than
omasumi.
You're the best at controlling your
energy.
She's so in a good mood.
She hardly takes pictures of Yasumoto.
Will she be okay?
And the two of them are at the
children's zoo.
I can't believe we're taking pictures of
animals.
Aren't they cute?
Since Nakayama won't come near the
sheep, they change their strategy.
They compromise and take pictures with
illustrations.
After that, Mayanma continues to take
pictures of animals and mountains.
What kind of pictures will she take?
On the other hand, in the flower garden,
Hirota again aims for a particular
picture.
I'm going to take a picture of someone
taking a picture.
That's cute.
Yes, it is.
That's a good idea.
Furthermore,
Please subscribe to the channel.
They decided to walk away from the
camera to take a photo
What kind of photo did they take?
They might have taken second swear word
After this, the members will show their
individuality
Who will shine in the Grand Prix?
Did you take a picture?
Yes!
So we are here at the Aozora Stage
It's nice, isn't it?
It's Aozora
Yes, it's Aozora
It's so beautiful
It reminds you of the Yoyogi Gymnasium,
doesn't it?
Yes
It's the first time I don't feel the
wind
You don't feel the wind but it's cold
because there is no sun
It's cold
So we will hold the Photo Contest for
the Winter Gala
If you announce the winner, we will vote
at the end
Please vote for the winner other than
yourselves
It's obvious that Komeishi will vote for
Asoka
We will vote for ourselves
The Photo Contest for the Winter Gala
Finally, the members will announce the
winner
First, Hirota and Hoshina
First, Hoshina's work
Do you have a theme for the photo?
Nanohana and me
It's not me
Hoshina's work
The theme is Nanohana and me
Let's see. Here it is.
Wow, beautiful.
Is this model Hirota?
Yes, I'm Aika.
So, you're saying that this girl is you?
Yes, that's right.
It's definitely not Hoshina-san, right?
Yes.
Isn't this nice?
Nanohana field, right?
Nanohana field is my specialty.
What's this?
You took it a little diagonally.
I did it on purpose.
You did it on purpose.
Next, Hirota's theme is tourists.
What kind of finish will it be?
Here you go.
It's the opposite, the person who's
taking it.
I see.
What's the secret to this?
It's like a bug that's taken from a
flower.
So it's a bug's eye?
Yes.
So it's a bug's eye.
So it's not a caterpillar or something
like that.
It's a tourist.
It's like a bug observing it.
It's like a cute girl is there.
So a bug found a cute girl?
Yes.
So it's like a story.
Next,
Mayama Nakayama's pair.
This is the work Mayama took.
It's cute, right?
Which one is the goat?
You know, right?
The goat isn't alive, right?
No, it's not.
There's a deep reason for this.
The theme in me is
if there's a German magazine
that specializes in this,
and Mayama is the camera man,
that's the theme.
So I wanted to make the goat
the main character,
and have the animal go see it.
That's the plan.
So you won't show the real thing here?
By the way, was there a real thing?
Yes.
I was at the zoo,
and I thought, oh, there's nothing.
So you thought, oh, there's nothing.
So you saw the real thing.
I also gave it food.
You didn't bring it?
This is the cutest.
And you want to go see it.
You wonder if it's really there.
Or maybe it's not here.
I thought it wasn't here.
Next,
we'll look at Nakayama's work.
Do you have a theme?
The theme is to introduce a goat
that I met in a German village in Tokyo.
That's a long one.
To introduce a goat
that I met in a German village in Tokyo.
What does that mean?
Let's see Nakayama's work.
It's suddenly real.
And there is no Mayama.
What is this?
Is this Mayama's hand?
This is the moment when I feed him.
It would be funny if this hand wasn't
Mayama.
There is really a hand.
And Rika's hand is beautiful.
I see.
I'm glad.
It's strange that an idol has only a
hand.
And the last is the three people who
were enjoying Germany.
First, Kashiwagi's work.
Do you have a theme?
Theme?
Go to Germany with children.
Kashiwagi's work.
Let's see.
What is this?
In the middle is a German village
character.
This is Angie.
Is this a girl?
Isn't this a graffiti?
No.
Is this right?
Is this official?
Is this eye official?
Really?
I'm not sure.
Her eyes are blurry.
What is this?
Is this a light?
Yes, it's a light.
Angie is shining more than the others.
I see.
The back side is shining, too.
I'm not like the sheep I was just now.
Is this similar?
I don't know.
I've seen it again, but I don't know.
I can't say anything.
Kobayashi's theme is The Tokyo German
Village.
Here it is!
Is it like this?
The light is shining through
It's pure white
This is a failure
You are doing it on purpose
If you look at this, you can tell at a
glance
I can't tell at all
It's white
I can't tell if it's German or not
There is a point
Hina's skin color is the same
Ayaka is the same
Also, German village is the same
Basically, all are white
The last is Yasumoto's work
The theme is hungry
The last one is Yasunosu's work.
It doesn't look like German village.
It's German.
This is the color of the tent.
It says soba.
I expected soba.
It's soba.
It's hungry.
I thought everyone would attack with a
beautiful one.
I dared to make it look like a daily
life.
I made it look different from others.
It's realistic because it has a daily
life.
It's a break.
What do you think of this?
I want to eat banana chocolate.
This is banana chocolate.
I see.
You ate it.
The announcement of all the entries is
over.
The winner will be decided by the vote
of the members and the audience.
Who will get the luxury goods?
The winner is...
Nakayama.
Congratulations.
The winner is...
There is no shrimp in the car.
The entries are Kobayashi, Yasumoto,
Hirota, and Chu-ei.
Why did you choose Hirota?
It looked like a poster.
I think it would be completed if I put a
German village.
It's not German village.
What about Kobayashi?
It has no impact.
I thought the master of the village was
dangerous.
What was dangerous?
I thought the master would come.
I thought I had overcome it.
I thought only Kobayashi would come.
No one thought the master would come.
You are not good at it.
The winner is Nakayama.
The winner is...
The passport of TOKYO TOYS MORA.
Congratulations.
Really?
Please show it to the camera.
It's been a year.
Really?
Is Nakayama a person who is happy?
I'm the happiest person I've ever been.
Is it a peach?
It's good.
I was happy.
Really?
How do you feel about winning?
I will come to see a lot of
illuminations.
I forgot the cold.
It's a good comment.
Congratulations.
This is amazing.
You can use it for a year.
This is for one person.
I will come alone.
How do you do it?
I think I will be arrested.
Next time, the final show of winter
park.
Please look forward to the next time.
I'm glad that Riko-chan talks to me a
lot like this.
Thank you.
The members are very kind.
Thank you for watching.
We are looking forward to seeing you
all!