Ebichu no Douga Toka
I'm Inata Kashiwagi, and I'm going to
talk about baseball love!
This time, I'm going to talk about the
charm of baseball and Tokyo Yakuza 2
arrows by myself.
The charm of baseball is that I want to
support it.
I also...
I saw the game in 2015 CS.
I had a wish to win and cheer for the
team.
I watched the game of Swallows.
So I naturally became a fan of Swallows.
I...
If I were to pick a player I like from
Swallows,
I would pick the first player I fell in
love with, Shouhei Tateyama.
I really like him.
When I heard he was retiring, I was on
my way home.
I went home crying without even looking
at him.
I like his personality, but I also like
the way he plays.
He's so cool.
I saw him throw a CS, and I fell in love
with him.
I thought he was cool.
But his voice is higher than I thought.
That's a great point.
I recently changed my uniform number.
I'm Murakami Munetaka, 55 years old.
I'm the best.
Other people, including Tateyama, are
all Sanzu.
But Murakami is the only one who is
Murakami.
Murakami or Munetaka.
I'm sure he's got the fighting spirit,
energy, and power to beat the enemy.
He doesn't look like he's in his 20s.
I want him to lead the team without
getting hurt.
I'm looking forward to seeing him.
To be honest, I've been a fan of his for
5 or 6 years.
I don't know much about him before that.
I'll pick a player I like and a player I
think is good.
Director?
I want to see him.
I think Nobu, the director.
I'm looking forward to seeing him.
I can only put Tateyama-san here.
I'm really lost.
I want to see Tateyama-san and Shima-
san's battery.
Gaia, Aoki-san.
There are too many people I want to put
in.
Wait a minute.
I didn't think it would be this hard.
I thought I'd already decided.
Yamasaki Kotaro
I'm Yamasaki.
It's okay. I'll go with Yamasaki.
The person who puts it in here will win
the first and third.
Valenti
Sakaguchi
I'm Yamada.
I have a lot of short hair.
What should I choose?
I have a lot of short hair, but I don't
think it's fixed.
Recently, I've been thinking that
Escobar is amazing.
I want to put it in.
But for some reason, I have Oobiki and
Hirooka.
And I got Hirooka.
Escoba!
No way!
Ah! Wait! No!
No! Wait!
No way!
No way! There's no Escoba!
What? Wait! Wait! Wait!
There's no Escoba, and no Oobiki either!
Ikeyama or Miyamoto!
Wait, wait, wait!
No, no, no!
You're kidding!
We have a special guest.
It's Miyamoto.
Nice to meet you.
Wow, the Kashiwagi family.
The Kashiwagi family
We're going to hear from the Kashiwagi
family, Miyamoto Shinya!
Miyamoto Shinya
Thank you again!
You're a big Yakult fan.
I'm not saying I'm a big fan, but I like
Yakult.
My father has been a fan for about 40
years.
So your father knows more about Yakult.
Yes, he knows a lot about it.
It's rare to see a Yakult fan.
It's rare?
When I first came to Osaka, I thought
everyone in Tokyo was a giant fan.
So I have the impression that Yakult
fans are basically a little different.
Is that so?
Now there are a lot of people, so I'm
very grateful.
But a little while ago, we didn't have
that many fans.
In the old days, we only had giant fans.
It's natural to be full of fans.
Now, all baseball stadiums are full of
fans.
But in 2013, when I retired, there
weren't many people.
Oh, really?
I couldn't join the baseball team unless
I won.
The year I retired was the last time I
played baseball.
So I think I made a little money by
playing five games.
And Valentine's Day is the year I hit
60.
So I joined the baseball team.
Do you want to join the giant fans?
What do you mean?
Giant fans, Harada's fans.
I don't know.
When I first went golfing with Harada, I
was so nervous.
I was so nervous that I don't even
remember how I hit the ball.
My father is a fan of Nagashima 3, and I
was in Osaka because of that.
I was trying to get into the Giants.
You couldn't?
I couldn't.
I'm not sure.
My best 9.
I don't even have a chance to ask you
how it was.
I was in real time.
That's right. You're almost a member
now.
I didn't expect you to be an ace cover.
I thought I could do it if I could be a
major ace cover.
I haven't been fixed as a short.
I got a big blow with FA.
Nishiura and Hirooka are not in Fuga.
I've been teaching them for two years.
I want them to do their best.
I want the Japanese to do their best in
the catcher, second short, and center,
which is called the center line, rather
than the foreign players.
Nishiura and Hirooka are always
complaining.
My father is really looking forward to
Nishiura.
Is that so?
I've been looking forward to it.
Strong teams have good catchers and
short players.
I was a short player, so I thought I had
to raise a short player.
I haven't had enough for two years.
A little longer.
If these two are in trouble this year,
they should get a good short.
I want them to be in danger.
I've been involved for about two years,
so I want them to do their best.
I want them to do their best.
I want them to do their best to the
point where they can't be relied on.
I wonder which one I should choose.
I'm not sure.
I want them to do their best to the
point where they can't be relied on.
Can I ask you about the players you've
been paying attention to recently?
Murakami has done well in his first
year, and he's been scaling up this
year.
Anyone can see that Murakami is amazing.
I'm definitely Yamazaki.
I think I've been a bit of a pushover in
my first year.
Oh, really?
I'm the type of guy that's like us.
I'm not a home run player.
I want the team to be able to execute
their strategy when they want to.
But there were a lot of players who
didn't even know what I was doing.
I was the first to come up and I dropped
the second team.
I was the one who was really serious
about it.
I think I'm probably the most serious
player in that team.
I've been working hard this year.
I don't think I'm the type of player
who's going to be dropped by the second
team.
But I've been used and removed from the
I've come this far, so I'm not giving up
this year.
I want to be able to beat him when the
team is in this situation.
I want him to be able to endure it and
use it.
Yamazaki and Kotaro are the ones who are
going to be eliminated.
And then there's the pitcher.
The pitcher won't come out.
He won't come out.
Players who are ranked higher in the
draft are in trouble if they get some
kind of power.
In that case, Terashima, Hara, Hoshi,
etc.
I think it'll change a lot when those
guys come in.
But I think it's important not to raise
a professional player too much.
To be specific, when you're 18, it's a
delicate time to see if your bones are
really made.
But when you're 18, you're not sure if
you're really made.
If you ignore this, you won't be able to
do it for a long time.
What do you like about Tateyama?
What do I like?
The first time I watched Yakult's game
was on TV.
That was the 2015 CS.
Tateyama was throwing it.
I saw something coming in that form.
I felt like I wanted to support
Tateyama.
I think he knows this, but he has a lot
of surgeries.
We joke around and say,
his goal is to become a demon.
I think it's about how many scars he
left on his body.
He's a surgery maniac. He had surgery
after he retired.
Did you know? He had surgery after he
retired last year because he wanted to
study training.
There's no one like that.
I've never heard of it.
He's completely M.
He's like, do you want to get that much
scar?
But every time he changes,
He's a through-and-through surgeon.
I was working as an ace, and I was
winning a lot.
So I was on the team that could not lose
a game against Tateyama.
I went twice.
You don't know, do you?
I don't know.
How old were you born?
I was born in 1999.
You were 5 years old at the time of the
Olympics.
Now, Samurai Japan is a professional
international tournament.
The 2004 Athens Olympics was the first
time I went all-pro.
Until then, the Olympic history was that
amateurs were competing.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Before the Athens Olympics, the Sydney
Olympics,
professional baseball was banned, and I
went to the Congo team.
I couldn't win a medal.
So I decided to go all-pro at the Athens
Olympics.
I think you know, Kashiwagi, and
Nagashima were the coaches.
I went to the Olympics.
Unfortunately, I lost the semi-final,
but I won the third place and got the
bronze medal.
When I lost, I couldn't go home,
so I said, let's go to the Italian Pro
League together.
What?
I said, I'm going all-pro,
and I thought I'd win all the gold
medals and come home.
But I lost the Australian semi-final
1-0.
But I thought, I can't go home to Japan.
I was seriously talking about going to
the Italian Pro League.
I was a rookie,
but I was allowed to play as a
professional.
I went home crying.
In Beijing, I was beaten up so badly.
I couldn't win a medal.
I lost to Hoshino, the coach.
I lost all the games.
I was beaten up on the internet.
I didn't know how to read the internet
back then.
I might be in trouble now.
What do you like about baseball?
I don't know.
I think it's related to my group,
or to my live performances.
I go to see the baseball games,
I say hi out loud or whatever.
I feel a lot of gratitude from the fans.
I see.
But baseball is like watching baseball
players.
I think it's interesting that you don't
know what's going to happen until the
end.
I see.
There are quite a few baseball games
that win in the end.
It's often said that baseball is a drama
without a plot.
Even from the 9th inning.
Sometimes you can make a comeback.
I did it a few years ago.
I turned it over about 10 points before
I became a coach.
It was a game that turned it over about
6 points when I was there.
It's interesting to do that.
When you make a big comeback, you don't
have that atmosphere at first.
Somehow, I got a point.
I think people who come around here are
pretty nervous.
I've come this far, and if I'm out, it's
not good.
There's a place like that, so there's
pressure.
I'm going to play in the first half.
It's fun when it's like, I don't care
anymore.
I've been to Noidona three times.
I had a pitcher named Bross in my first
year.
He's been playing perfect about seven
times.
So I didn't get a runner.
And then I was a defensive player.
I wasn't a regular at the time.
I was in the second division of the
Mamoru Ikei.
So, in a perfect match, you can't make
any mistakes.
So I was really nervous.
So, in the 7th or 8th round, I was
really nervous.
I can't forget, he was using a slider
and said,
Mr. Goto,
who is now a Giants coach,
Mr. Goto was a dead baller.
At that moment, I thought,
Wow, that's great.
You were nervous?
This is how you can make mistakes.
Oh, I see.
So, when you think you can't make a
mistake,
you should make a mistake.
I thought about it that way.
He was doing the Kegyo No Hito.
Next, Kazuhisa Ishii was doing Yokohama
Stadium.
He was doing it 7 or 8 times.
There was a surgery,
so he asked the director,
what he should do.
He said, I'm good.
I said, don't say that, just go.
And he did the Kegyo No Hito.
The third time was Gatoumuson.
It was a Rakuten match.
When I noticed it,
I felt like I had gone that far.
When you're defending,
in the Kegyo No Hito,
even if you can make a hit,
you have to make mistakes.
It depends on the score.
If you're 1 point behind,
you don't have that much room.
But if you get 5 or 6 points,
you can do that for a small pitch.
I thought that was the way to go.
I was defending like that.
I got hit by a no hit no run in CS.
That was the first time in my baseball
life.
I was playing baseball all the time in
elementary school, and I got hit by a no
hit no run.
It was my first time to lose a game in
Takeda.
I got a lot of points in those two
years.
I think that no hit no run of Sugano-san
is still in the fans' memory.
There were a lot of foreshadowing the
day before.
I was playing a game that I was supposed
to win.
I was making a lot of countermeasures.
But one of the players didn't play the
game.
That's why I had to teach him how to
play.
But when the game was over, he was a
player who was cute.
If you lose tomorrow, you're the ones
who will win.
You have to do your best on the scene
tomorrow.
If you say that, it's a no hit no run.
It's like, it's over.
It was like that.
I have one question.
You lost 16 consecutive games last year.
How do you feel about losing?
At first, I thought I'd win if I kept
losing.
I thought I'd win anyway.
But I started to feel like I was going
to lose.
That's right.
It was my first time losing in a game
with more than two players.
16 consecutive losses means I haven't
won in almost three weeks.
I've been playing the game for three
weeks.
I know.
It's like a hotel room.
It's funny.
I thought it was the same when I was a
player.
I can see that the player's body isn't
moving.
It's completely different from usual.
I wonder what the countermeasures are
like at that time.
When I'm playing, I think about what I'm
doing.
It's hard.
When you're over 10, you wake up at the
alarm clock in the morning.
Your eyes are open, but your body isn't.
You're like, wow, I'm here again today.
You wake up with a frown on your face.
You watch sports news.
You're writing a pre-selection picture.
I know the day before, but I'm writing a
pre-selection picture.
I was thinking, how can I beat him?
Everyone, including the batting coach,
is thinking about it.
They're all doing this and that, and
they're all thinking about what to do
with the members.
But it didn't go well.
The last game I won was a big blow.
At Yokohama Stadium in the space ship.
I won, but I didn't win.
I was in a bad mood.
Yokohama Stadium in the space ship.
I won.
I was making a big deal of the players
when I won.
I thought I'd lose again.
I've lost 16 straight times.
I understand how you feel.
I thought it would be okay because I was
laughing so much.
I buzzed first and won 5 points apart
and lost by a reverse.
What's going on there?
It's hard for the fans too, losing so
many points.
On the contrary, I worry about the
players.
I know.
I wonder if they have something wrong
with them.
There are about 9 points, but the
players do feel the pressure, but in the
end, they can't move their bodies.
But the coach can't do the difficult
things himself.
So all you can do is ask.
You ask for a strategy, and the coach is
the one who decides the final strategy.
We don't do the strategy ourselves.
We come up with a strategy, but we only
ask for it.
I'm asking so much that I think, was I
supposed to be this clumsy?
It's like, please, coach, please,
please, please, please.
The most important thing to win is...
I'm sure there are other things besides
pitchers.
First of all, not just pitchers.
I've been in charge of it for two years,
so I have a lot of responsibility.
I think it's more important to look five
years ahead and form a team than the
next year, the next year, or this year.
First of all, I think it's tough.
I know that the fans want to see that
kind of thing as soon as possible.
If you play 143 games in a year, you'll
have a lot of teamwork.
You can't win just by momentum. Momentum
is important.
So first of all, you have to make an
effort to build yourself.
But when it comes to pitchers, you
should throw a little more.
After all, there are many players who
don't throw because they say that the
shoulder is a consumable.
And pitchers have to throw it.
I'm wondering if there's a way to
improve without throwing.
This may be a Yashio's idea.
Yashio is a line touch.
If you throw a line, you can't throw it.
When you're camping or throwing, you
have to throw a lot and soak it into
your body.
I think it's not going to get better.
I want you to go back to the origin.
There are a lot of ways to train now.
I think there's a good one and a bad
one.
But in the end, you have to throw it to
learn.
Even if you have a great body, you can't
throw it where you want to.
Baseball players often say that they are
athletes.
I don't think I'm an athlete.
I think I'm a technician.
Baseball is a game of throwing, running,
and running.
And you have to be smart about running.
There's too much to do.
It's a matter of physical strength, of
course.
But you need a lot of technology.
If you have the strength to rely on a
lot of practice, you can practice a lot
of technology.
If you don't have this physical
strength, if the engine is small,
For example, if you throw a 100 ball, it
will collapse.
But if you have an engine like this, you
can throw about 200 balls.
Then you'll definitely learn the
technology.
It's simple.
It's hard, but it's a job, so you have
to work hard.
It's not easy to get better just by
throwing a little.
I'm going to improve my team's strength,
but I have to improve my strength.
If you don't get stronger, you won't be
a strong team.
I just want the players to work hard to
catch up.
I think that's how it's going to change.
I think it's a good team if they can do
it independently for the next two years.
I was serious.
Thank you.
Today, I had Miyama-san come as a
surprise guest.
I think the people watching on the
screen are thinking,
I'm so happy to see you like this.
I heard a lot of stories today.
The last story is that I'm standing on
the stage as an idol.
I think you're talking about baseball,
but I'm thinking about me.
I feel like I'm getting advice from you.
I learned a lot from you.
I was really happy to have this
opportunity.
Thank you very much.
I thought you were talking about
baseball, or Swallows.
Swallows.
I thought you were talking about
I was like, ah, ah, ah.
It's precious.
I've experienced it, and I've met
Miyamoto.
I don't think I've had a chance to hear
such a deep story.
I'm glad I was able to hear it.
I was really happy this time.
I'm sure the TORONTO fans and baseball
fans didn't expect this.
I'm sure they'll watch this video.
I'm sure the fans of Soarers and
Miyamoto will watch this video.
I hope this video will spread to
everyone.
I hope there are people like me who will
become Soarers fans.
Like Miyamoto-san said, before joining
Yakult, she was a fan of the Titans.
There are not many Soarers fans around.
So, like I told Riko-chan about the
charm of Soarers and baseball,
I will talk about Soarers and increase
the number of Soarers fans.
I hope there are people like me who will
become Soarers fans.
I met a lot of people who are involved
in Yakult and learned a lot.
I'm not paying back in a sudden, but I'm
trying to do something in a sudden.
I'm trying to do something to repay my
little power.
I will continue to support Tokyo Yakult
Soarers with all my might.
I will continue to do my best!
I met Miyawaki-san!
Thank you very much!