Ebichu's videos
I'm Riko Nakayama, the 12th member of
Shishiki, the main character of Shiri-
cha Ebisu.
I'm going to improve my female power!
I tried making fluffy omelette, but it
didn't go well.
So, I'm going to make various dishes as
a revenge.
Let's get started!
I'm going to make an omelette.
I'll choose the ingredients first.
Eggs.
Eggs, milk, and butter.
I didn't add mayonnaise when I made
fluffy omelette last time.
But, a fan told me that mayonnaise would
make it fluffy.
I've never made it, but I'll try to add
it.
I'll try it.
Please subscribe to my channel!
I'll mix it.
Butter.
I'll heat up the frying pan.
I'll put it here.
Is this too much?
Milk.
I'll put it in.
Salt.
Mayonnaise.
Is this enough?
I'll put more.
I'll mix it.
I'll remember it.
I put it in.
I'll mix it.
Where is the result of my practice?
It's coming.
I'll mix it.
I'm going to make a scratch.
What?
I'll put it on a plate and deceive it.
It's done.
It's fluffy.
It's a bit different.
Please subscribe to my Gyo channel.
I'm going to make fried rice.
First, I'm going to wash the rice.
I'm scared of this.
I've done this before.
I'm going to pour the water I washed.
I'm going to boil it.
Start!
It's ready.
The rice is ready.
Oh, it's well-baked.
I'm going to cut the ingredients.
What do I need?
I'm going to make fried rice.
I'm going to cut eggs.
I'm going to put eggs.
OK! The eggs are ready!
Sesame oil.
It smells good!
Seasoning! Salt and pepper.
I think it's a chicken stock.
Rice.
Go!
Please give me a high five!
It looks good!
I'll add salt and pepper.
I'll add chicken soup.
It looks good.
How does it taste?
It's good!
I want to make a round fried rice, so
I'll put it in this bowl and make it
into a bread.
I'll do it!
I can do it like this, right?
I've finished making fried rice!
I'll make a hamburger!
I'll do my best!
I'll cut the vegetables!
How much should I cut?
I think the ingredients for summer are
important.
It looks watery.
I'll add milk and eggs.
It looks good.
I'll add them.
Please subscribe to my channel!
Oh, it's a bit strong.
It's strong.
It's a bit hot.
It smells good.
I'm going to cook a hamburger.
Do I have to remove the air?
It's strong.
It's hot.
It's stuck!
I'll turn it over.
What?
I'm hungry.
I can hear the sound of cooking.
It's coming.
Please subscribe to this channel.
I'll eat hamburger steak first.
I'll put some black pepper.
OK.
It's done.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Today, I'm going to make spring rolls.
I've never made spring rolls before, so
I don't know how to make them.
But, I'll try to make them.
The ingredients are lettuce, the most
important one, shrimp, cucumber, and
carrots.
OK.
But, it's not good.
I've turned it over.
I'll leave it here.
I'll let it go through easily.
Did I break it?
I failed.
I put it on a kitchen towel and put it
back.
I'll cut the vegetables.
The next plan is to put the vegetables
on the kitchen paper and put them on the
cutting board.
I'll put the lettuce on the kitchen
paper.
I'll put the cucumber on the paper.
I'll put the carrot on the paper.
I'll put a lot of shrimps on the paper.
I'll put the shrimp on the paper.
I think I can do it well.
Please subscribe to my channel.
What?
But...
I have to cut it.
I'm cutting it.
It looks like a real spring roll.
I made a real spring roll!
Please subscribe to my channel.
I'm going to make meat and potato.
I forgot to cut the shirataki.
I'm going to cut it.
I broke it.
I'm going to cut it in half.
I'm going to eat it.
It looks delicious.
I'm going to eat it with white rice.
I'm going to season it.
I'll add water.
How much?
I don't know.
I'm going to season it with soy sauce,
cooking sake, mirin and sugar.
I'm going to add meat here.
It's ready.
I'll cut it.
I'll season it.
Soy sauce, mirin, sake, and mirin.
It looks good.
I'll taste it.
Itadakimasu.
It's thin!
It's thin.
What should I do?
Soy sauce.
Mirin.
Sake.
Sugar.
OK.
Itadakimasu.
This is the second time.
Wow!
What is this?
Is it sweet?
Is it salty?
I don't know. What should I do?
What?
It's stuck.
I've finished it.
I'll put the sauce on it.
It's done.
Today, I'm going to make tofu steak,
which is my speciality.
I can make really delicious dishes just
by grilling tofu and putting chopped
vegetables on it.
So, I'm going to make them today.
Momen-dofu, oba leaves, myoga leaves,
and cucumber.
I think kinu-dofu is also good.
It's easy to eat.
I'll cut it into this thick pieces.
I'll cut cucumber.
I'll cut it to put on the top of the
steak.
cut毛布
I'm going to cut up the myoga.
I'm going to cut up the ainiwa.
Oh, I didn't know that.
I'm going to put all the myoga on top.
This is ponzu.
I'm going to put potato starch and
sesame seeds.
I'm going to put potato starch on the
tofu.
I'm going to put a lot of olive oil.
I'm going to put the tofu in the pot.
I'm going to put a lot of it.
All right.
When the meat is browned, turn it over.
I'll put the meat on the plate.
Is it OK?
I'll put some cucumber.
I'll put some shiso.
I'm going to add some powder.
And I'm going to add some ponzu.
It looks like a lot of things.
It's done!
I'm going to eat this with ponzu.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I ate all 6 dishes!
I've never cooked such a dish in a day.
I may have done it wrong, but I'm so
impressed that I could cook it.
I'm going to eat fried rice which I'm
most confident in.
It looks great!
Let's eat!
Mmm!
It's just delicious!
The moisture is gone and it's nice and
soft.
I added a lot of sausages, so that's
good too.
But, the taste was a bit light.
It would be nice if I could eat it with
sausages.
I should have added more salt and
pepper, but it's just delicious.
It's perfect.
It's delicious.
I'm going to try the omelet next.
I ate an omelet the other day.
I've been making it for a while.
This is the first time I've added
mayonnaise, so I'm going to taste it.
I'll put it on the ketchup.
I'll enjoy it.
I'll eat it with ketchup.
It's good.
I don't know what mayonnaise is.
But, it's fluffy.
I can feel mayonnaise.
It's good.
I wonder if it's good to eat with or
without mayonnaise.
It's good!
I ate spring rolls.
I used a lot of butter when I grilled
the chicken breast, so it's good.
It's good.
I don't know how the next one will
taste.
I'm going to eat raw spring rolls.
The texture of the skin is different.
I think it's a little hard.
I'm going to eat it.
I'm going to dip it in the sauce.
Thank you for the meal.
Hmm?
Ahaha
Hmm!
The chili sauce is amazing!
Ahaha
Hmm?
What is this?
I made this with ketchup and other
things.
Thank you!
It's really good!
I think I can eat this without any
problem.
I was shocked by the chili sauce. It was
so good.
Anyway, the chili sauce was good.
Next!
I know that the vegetables look hard.
But, they look good.
I think they are greenish.
Carrots are good.
I'll eat it.
What should I eat first?
I'll eat a bite of potato first.
It's a little hard.
I think it's a little bland.
Carrot
It's hard!
It's hard.
The meat is good! The flavor is well-
absorbed.
The meat is good.
But, I need to study more.
I made vegetables at the beginning.
I don't know how to make it hard.
1. Cut sliced..."
2. cut sliced ​​meat
Should I have put it in later? Or should
I have done it on a higher heat?
Should I have done it on a low heat?
I don't know. I'll look it up.
Next, I'll try a hamburger.
A hamburger.
I'm worried that it's not cooked inside.
I'll try it.
I'll cut it in half.
Is it okay?
I'll try it.
I think it would have been better if I
added more vegetables.
I don't know if it's the effect of the
nutmeg, but it has a nice aroma.
It's good.
I can feel the nutmeg.
It's a little bit.
It has a nice texture.
I like it.
I don't like the outside of this steak,
but I'll keep it because it's dangerous.
I found out that it's pinkish.
I'll eat my favorite dish, tofu steak.
I'll eat this after a long time.
I'll eat this because I got a lot of
useful things.
Let's eat!
It's good.
It's stable.
It's good. It may look bad, but it's
better to put a lot of it.
I really like this. It's good.
I ate all of them, but I'll rank them
among the dishes I made today.
The first place is this!
The first place is the tofu steak I
made!
I haven't had it for a while, but it's
good.
This was the first place.
The second place is this!
The second place is fried rice!
I think it's not the taste but the
appearance that made me the second
place.
I think I wanted more salt and pepper
for the taste.
The third place is this!
I think it was worth making it many
times.
And the taste was also good.
The fourth place is...
Raw spring rolls!
The sauce was delicious.
Thanks to the sauce!
If it wasn't for the sauce, I might have
been at the bottom.
But these two...
5th place is...
Nikujaga!
The vegetables were really hard, but the
sauce was really good.
The sauce was really good.
The vegetables were hard.
I realized that I didn't need water for
the meat.
I was 5th.
I was 6th because I didn't cook the meat
inside.
If I had cooked the meat more, I would
have been 6th.
I was 6th because I didn't cook the meat
inside.
I made a dish with the plan of improving
my cooking ability.
I made it, but I'm still scared if the
members eat it.
If I have another chance, I want to try
something more difficult.
I want the members to eat it.
Bye bye.