Ebichu's video
Good morning
It's already past
Everyone is wearing a mask, so I'm
wearing one too
Everyone is wearing a mask
Kaho-chan is wearing a mask too
Good morning
I was wearing a mask and I was wearing
one too
And today
Thank you
I'm 21 years old
Thank you everyone
Thank you
Congratulations
I'm going to open it
I went to my favorite treatment
I did my hair
It's smooth
I checked today's additional treatment
I will do my best today too
Good morning
We are SSATC
Thank you
What do you want to use in the future?
The future of SSATC
Look, the waves are so cool.
Oh, but there are too many people.
Miha is done.
Yeah!
What do you want to do?
Let's go!
Fighting!
Thank you!
Alright!
Wanna do a
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday dear Pocchan
Congratulations!
It's been a while since we started, but
can you show us the stage?
1, 2, 3!
Happy birthday to you
Congratulations!
Happy birthday to you!
Thank you!
So, Kou-san, do you have any dreams of
being 21 years old?
Well, being 21 years old means that I
want to be an adult in the world.
Of course.
That means that I always hope to be a
healthy human being.
I want to do my best.
Thank you very much!
Thank you for your continued support.
Thank you for the good day.
Thank you.
I was surprised.
Let's have a better day after this.
One day left to commemorate.
Everyone, please give a lot of applause
and congratulations to Kaho-chan.
There was.
Kawasaki Koe and Po-chan's birthday is
today.
We celebrated with my mother-in-law.
Happy birthday.
I was surprised.
We celebrated with my mother-in-law.
It's always on my birthday.
After the rehearsal, we did this.
I didn't have a good reaction.
I'm sure you're motivated.
I'm not even hungry.
I'm not hungry.
You're motivated, but you're not.
The concept is different.
I was in the staff room of MCD.
I thought you could hear me.
I didn't hear you.
I'm glad.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
The Kansai performance is over.
Thank you.
Nagoya performance.
I don't want to.
It was a performance in Osaka today.
I'm sorry I couldn't show it to the
people who were looking forward to it in
Osaka.
I want to go there again.
I'll cover it and go there.
Please wait.
Let's do our best for the final
performance.
We'll do our best.
Thank you.
The concept live performance is
different from the concept live
performance.
We're moving in a very conceptual way.
We're moving, too.
Everyone's moving.
The stage is moving, too.
We've been able to do a different
approach to the live performance.
Thank you.
We are 12 years old this year, but I
didn't think we could get so much new
excitement from the live performance in
12 years.
I think it's a live performance that
will be a great lesson.
It's a live performance at this time of
year, so we can see the faces of our
fans.
Our fans are also restricted.
We are used to clapping, but how do we
clap? How do we move? I think we can do
it even more.
I think we can make the fans happy by
moving.
It's the first day of the live
performance in Omiya, and the new
members are watching it.
So I felt like I was putting my elbow on
my shoulder.
I've been performing with Kineo and
Yusuke for the first time.
I realized that there was a side to each
other, and I realized the good taste of
the previous season.
I'm happy to have experienced various
Ebi-chu this year.
I was very impressed.
The last song was very close to the
family and our members.
There are many people who say that, but
I really felt it.
I was surprised that everyone was
clapping while listening to the last
song.
I was talking to the teacher about the
ideal image of the final form.
That's the first performance.
The words that we wanted to say to
everyone,
and the things that we wanted to do with
everyone accepted them.
And everyone made their debut with all
their heart.
I'm really glad that we've done this
much.
Of course, in the MOVE,
we always watch the performances,
and we're more motivated.
Plus, I thought that if we don't have
the power of the family,
we wouldn't be able to complete it.
So, with the family that's been with us
until now,
we're a group.
We're going to go to a new direction.
We're ready for every step.
I think it was such a performance that
everyone could say it together.
So, I'm really glad we were able to do
MOVE.
And I'm really grateful to the people
who came.
I think it's a lot of performances.
We've been at the audience for a long
time,
and it was the first day we saw the
audience.
We were like, oh, it's moving.
I wonder if we'll make it down the
stairs with just that impression.
When we're rehearsing,
there's no stage or stairs,
and we put tape on the floor for the
number of steps.
We were doing that, but if it was that,
we'd be in time.
But when there's a step,
there's a lot of parts that we can't
make it in time.
We were adjusting on the spot.
It was a different feeling from the
usual rehearsal.
We felt a little bit of a pinch.
After all, there are a lot of things to
do in the rehearsal.
There are a lot of things that have
changed.
There were a lot of things to check.
But among them,
the only thing we can check is what we
do at the dressing room.
We were doing the most important thing
on stage.
That's what I was relieved about.
I was honestly enjoying it from day one
But I was like,
Ah, I think the tempo was a little off
there
I went home, got the video,
and I was able to make the choreography
more simple
I was able to teach it in a simple way
I found a reflection point in myself
Um, Omiya?
Not Omiya, Omiya is the first day
I went to Kawasaki and Nagoya
And then I went up the stairs
I was like, will I make it in time or
not
I tried it on the day of rehearsal
If the venue is different
If the distance changes a little
It will be difficult
I think it would be best to check it out
in rehearsal
And I think it would be best to go to
the stage
I watched the live performance of MOVE
Of course, I was serious about the
performance
I was serious about the performance
But it was a different performance
It's fun to see and to hear
It was a live performance with my heart
dancing
I got a lot of voices saying that it was
really cool
I think I was able to show a different
side of me during the rehearsal
I'm glad
I'm nervous and I'm going to be full
soon
I'm sorry I'm short
I have to show that I have room for it
I have to show it
I'm doing it
I have to change depending on the
situation
I was able to open my senses
I didn't think I could see it so soon
So when I went on stage
I was really grateful
I was happy
Really, just the sound of the club
I feel like I'm eating with the sound of
the club
I was able to eat a lot of rice
I had my last live performance in Poland
20 years ago
I'm 21 years old, so I can't change in
three days.
I can't change in three or two days.
I'm trying to perform as elegantly as
possible.
I'm doing a concert with a concept.
We've been watching the video we did
last week.
The video is completely different from
what we're doing.
I was surprised that the first song was
so clear.
The video was very clear and the members
were in the right spot.
I thought it was very beautiful.
There was a dance video on the way.
I thought the concept live was fun.
I had a lot to do.
I was nervous about the rehearsal last
week.
I was worried if I could do it.
I have to concentrate.
Yusuke said he would change the stage.
I'm nervous.
I was worried if the members would clap
because they usually dance together.
I saw that scene for the first time at
the live performance.
I was impressed that the members were
doing it without a pen light.
I also thought it was a good scene.