Love house idol
What will happen to me in the cubicle
hermit weighing 3kg?
Upcoming picture
3rd time as Air-Amé‡ Ice Ice Scripture
icon Idol
It's Gold Kiwi
Gold Kiwi?
I don't have any specific reason for it
What do you mean?
I like Gold Kiwi the most among fruits
Really?
I eat it every morning
Every morning?
You can say that
You eat it every morning, right?
I eat it every morning
I wake up in the morning, drink water,
and eat Gold Kiwi first
I see. When did you start eating it?
I don't know
But I've been eating it for about 2
years
I used to eat regular Kiwi instead of
Gold Kiwi
My sister knows a lot about it
She told me that Gold Kiwi is more
nutritious and has better vitamins
So I eat Gold Kiwi every morning
You've been eating it for 2 years, so
you must have eaten about 700 of it
I've never thought about it
That's amazing
Do your fans know about it?
Yes
That you eat it every day
I once said Gold Kiwi on a radio show
When I was asked what my favorite food
is
I like omelet rice when it comes to food
I still ask if Gold Kiwi is healthy
You're a talent
Really?
You eat it every day
I eat it every day
But I don't eat Gold Kiwi in winter
Is it seasonal?
I think it's because it's warm now
It's warm this year
I don't eat regular Gold Kiwi in
November
But I still eat it
You eat Kiwi for most of your diet
Yes, Kiwi
I want to see the Japanese Kiwi
Association
Do they have it?
I think they do
I've only seen a Kiwi doll on TV
I'm scared
Do they have it?
They do have it
If you ask them, they'll promote it
Some people eat it every day
I eat your Kiwi
You're a good liar
I want to raise it
You can raise it?
I think you can go to a Japanese farm
Do they grow from the tree?
From there?
Let's go to a Kiwi farm
That's a good idea
There's a Kiwi farm
There's a Kiwi tree and a plum tree
Do they grow from the bottom?
You should go there without knowing that
I'm a good liar
I'm not laughing
You're good
You're very particular about it
This program is brought to you by
Mr. Kintake,
Mr. Rilu Daisuki,
Mr. Kei,
Mr. Hiroki,
and Mr. Pilon.
Thank you for watching.
Let's keep warm and keep going!