Emotions spread, fill it up, don't stop
Channel love,
Don't talk about it
Let's go, let's go, let's go
Last month, at Saitama,
A famous autumn outdoor concert,
Shoo On!
This was the 5th time,
And the stage was surrounded by
beautiful nature,
And the song was heard!
Let's make a few love drinks!
We want to be happy, happy and happy!
The performance was announced on that
stage...
The new generation's performance has
been decided!
We will be performing at Makuhari
Festival on the 17th!
With the new members of Sakurai Emma and
Nakamura Yuna,
the university performance will be held
on December 17!
So, Zenma Shimicsu will be joining the
new members on their journey to the
first stage!
This time, they will be filming for the
magazine BLT, which will be their first
job!
Thank you.
The two visited the studio in the city.
Good morning.
We are shooting for BLT.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Since they became new members,
the magazine BLT was filled with
interviews.
BLT is a new type of TV news that shows
all the beautiful ladies,
including the actresses and idols.
BLT is also a magazine with a deep
meaning.
The first interview was with a junior
high school student.
What is your strengths?
I'm positive.
I'm a little shy.
I'm also a little honest.
The more you talk, the more honest you
are.
What are your shortcomings?
I like to be honest.
I like noisy and 3 days of sleep.
What is your hobby?
I like to make cake.
What kind of cake?
Cake with a
If you could go to a foreign country,
what would you do?
I want to travel.
I've never been abroad.
You want to go abroad?
Yes.
Where?
I want to go abroad.
What is your favorite food? アイス。
アイス。 アイス。
You have to live without this.
You have to be happy.
I cried.
I love ice cream.
You love ice cream?
You love ice cream that much?
I always say I love ice cream.
In fact, there are many pictures of ice
cream on Instagram.
If you continue the interview,
you can go to bed hungry.
I'm not hungry, but I'm hungry.
You like to eat.
If I'm not full, I want to eat
something.
Emma's interview was about food.
Yuna's interview starts.
Please tell us your strengths.
I have to give up until the end.
What are your strengths?
I can't stop eating.
What's your favorite food?
Meat spaghetti and hot pot.
Is there a reason for this?
I like meat spaghetti made by my mother.
I live in Fukuoka, so I often come to my
house.
Yuna is surprised.
Do you like movies?
I like Titanic.
I cry a lot that my head hurts.
I don't watch movies often, but I like
it the most.
Her favorite movie is Titanic, which was
released 10 years ago.
She likes it.
Do you want to try it in private?
Please look forward to the next.
I'm not good at riding a
scary Z coaster. I've never ridden it
before, but I've recently
reached my height limit. So I want to
ride it.
I see.
Yuna has reached her height limit at the
age of 15.
Her height is 152 cm.
That means?
When I measured her height at high
school, she was 154 cm.
She has been defending her lowest seat
in the shrimp for many years.
She has finally broken the record.
She is the lowest member in the shrimp,
2 cm lower than her.
However, 15-year-old Yuna is still
growing.
Please pay attention to the hot height
battle in the shrimp.
Next, an interview with the two of them.
Do you have any questions for each
other?
What is your first impression of her?
She is very close to me.
She was always smiling.
She was nervous at first, but she was
always smiling.
I thought she was cute.
She was really cute when she smiled.
She was smiling like a baby.
I thought she was a cheerful girl.
What is your first impression of her?
She was cute when she spoke.
I was jealous because she was so quiet.
She was really cute.
What do you think is the most fun thing
about being in the same team?
I like singing and dancing to Ebichu
songs.
I want to do a tour around the country.
I've never been to many countries.
I want to eat delicious food and hang
out with people.
Is that what you want to do?
Yes.
What do you think about her new member?
I didn't realize that I was still in
Ebichu.
I'm looking forward to it, but I'm also
worried.
I want to do my best to become a bigger
person.
I want to do my best for the children
who have worked hard together.
I don't have a good feeling about it
yet.
I'm going to continue to do lessons and
live shows.
I'm sure there will be some hard work
and some things that will be hard to do.
I want to be a beginner.
I want to make people want to see my
work.
I want to do my best.
After the interview, he wraps himself in
the shooting costume and the gravure
shooting starts.
I want to take a picture of my face
here.
I want to do this.
That's good.
Then, face straight.
Yes, that's good.
Good.
Please move.
Move like this.
Like this.
Yes, that's good.
The two are so smooth that it's hard to
believe it's their first time.
They answer the cameraman's request.
This is the completed photo.
In addition, this time, not only photos
but also video footage will be sent to
the two of them to convey their charms.
Thank you for your viewing.
This is a part where you can go back and
forth.
I don't have a lot of time, so I'll do
it like a dance.
I'll do my best to make you happy.
I'm going to dance.
I'm going to dance hard.
Now I'm going to perfect it like roomie.
Let's go to your first match
Next, they both try to film.
Then the cameraman orders this.
Let's do this.
If the camera man is enjoying it, we can
do this.
Let's go!
Go, go, go!
Good, good, good!
You're lying.
I'm not lying.
Why are you laughing?
Thank you for watching!
The shooting is over.
What do you think about your first job?
I don't know if I spoke well.
I'm glad I was able to talk about what
I'm thinking now.
I was very nervous.
When we were shooting together, we were
playing together.
It was fun.
Thank you for your hard work.
My first job was to shoot magazines.
When I took a picture with Emma, I felt
like I got along with her.
It ended in a flash.
Were you nervous?
At the beginning of the pro interview, I
was really nervous.
I didn't know what I was saying.
I couldn't move at all when I was
shooting alone.
The new member and their Gravier are on
sale.
December issue is on sale!