Good evening, we are Doreski and Kore-
Ski MC, Harajiri Iwai.
I am Akane Kumada.
Nice to meet you.
Today's guest is Uka, who we have
introduced in the previous episode.
She is cute.
She is.
She is very friendly and has a lot of
skin color.
She is a girl.
She is. She is fluffy and cute.
Uka's group name is Uka-san, which means
that she is born with a long hair and
hopes for a bright future.
The beginning is exciting, isn't it?
When something changes, I get excited.
When I take auditions, I get nervous.
You have a lot of auditions.
Yes, I do.
Anyway, everything is an audition.
Please tell me how to relax when I get
nervous.
How to relax when you get nervous.
I walk around with my sleeves.
With your sleeves?
I walk around.
I see.
I do that sometimes.
Do you do that?
I only do that when I'm breathing
deeply.
I get nervous when I practice a lot.
Don't you get nervous before you start
to do a story?
I do. Every time.
Why?
I only remember about 60% of the story.
With that story?
It's dangerous. I might forget it.
I was thinking it was dangerous.
I was like, it was dangerous.
You were doing it so close.
Yes.
Your spirit is important.
It's not important.
I should prepare.
You should prepare.
Thank you.
So, let's start today.
Music Variety Dresky and Koresky
Our guests this week are UCCA.
Good evening, everyone. We are UCCA.
I'm Ayumu Kawasawa.
I'm Amo Serizawa.
I'm Ruri Aoi.
I'm Rina Yuki.
I'm Sora Akane.
I'm Riju Murahoshi.
Thank you for coming.
Today, we will ask about each member.
I summarized the members' personalities.
Here it is.
Kawase is a leader, sings well, is good
at talking, and is very feminine.
She is actually a sweet girl.
Murahoshi is serious, sings well, is
particular about things, and likes to
joke around.
Akane is like a big sister, has a lot of
ideas, and is good at self-producing.
She always eats something and is very
flexible.
Serizawa is a little girl, but she is
mature, has a lot of physical affection,
eats fast, and is familiar with trends.
She is a leader.
Yuki is cheerful, is energetic, has a
good brain, is athletic, and is
masculine.
Aoi likes to take pictures, wants to be
on camera, is quick-witted, has an otaku
personality, and loves to be
mischievous.
This is a lot of information.
How is it?
I'm curious.
Kawase is a leader.
Yes, I'm a leader.
She is a very feminine girl, is actually
a sweet girl, and is very talkative.
Yes, she is a little quiet, has a low
voice, and talks in a constant tone.
But she is actually a sweet girl.
Can you see that?
I can see it.
Ayame often comes to the room at the
hotel after the expedition.
I can't sleep alone in the hotel.
Do you sleep together?
Yes.
I slept with her about twice in the
previous two nights and three days.
It's a hotel, right?
Yes.
It's a normal bed, right?
Single bed.
When I wake up.
I don't think it's a bother.
I think so too.
I think it's a little painful.
Yes.
And Murahoshi, you have a beautiful
high-pitched voice, a strong voice, and
a unique world view.
What does this mean?
If the high-pitched voice is beautiful,
it is.
A unique world view is that she wears
clothes like a magazine or a magazine
newspaper.
It's important to have clothes.
That's right.
I like rough things, and there are some
with patterns.
You mix patterns.
And the shape of the clothes is also
fluttering here.
There are various things here.
You like that kind of thing.
Yes.
How about today?
I'm wearing a magazine newspaper.
Magazine newspaper?
I'm wearing it.
You like magazine newspapers.
Today's pattern is shoes.
I'm wearing a heel-shaped shoe pattern.
What about the magazine newspaper?
I didn't write in English.
I wrote in English.
How is it?
It's fashionable.
I don't think it's fashionable.
Why?
I don't think so.
It's a beautiful world view.
It's a unique world view.
Akane is like an older sister, and she
is good at self-producing.
What do you think about self-producing?
I like to think about things.
For example, I had a birthday party the
other day.
I like to think of a theme and make a
live performance according to it.
I think that's why I'm good at self-
producing.
I think I'm making myself as an idol.
And Serizawa is the youngest.
I'm 16 years old.
I can't see you.
You look like an adult.
You have a lot of physical contact.
You are close to each other.
You eat fast.
You are the oldest by accident.
Do you have any episodes that you
accidentally did?
It's a daily thing.
Recently, I made a mistake in the trash
can.
That's terrible.
I put it in a trash bag.
Do you always put it in a trash bag?
We are the same.
YUKI is cheerful.
She is a manly person.
She is cheerful.
She is cheerful all the time.
I understand the feeling of her.
She is manly.
She is a manly person.
She is not manly.
She is not cool at all.
Her dance is like a woman.
Her dance is like a man.
What does it mean?
It's a crab.
She has a cow in her legs.
She has a wide stance.
She is manly.
She likes to take pictures.
Does she like to take pictures?
She likes to take pictures of the sky
and the road.
She likes to take pictures of the
manager.
She is an otaku.
I used to like idols.
I thought I was an idol.
I speak at the speed of an otaku.
Dorekore!
Hi, everyone watching Doreski and Kore-
Ski!
I'm Yurika, an anime singer.
I thought about which one I liked,
which one I liked,
and I like muscle training.
Actually, I'm breaking.
I'm Yurika, an anime singer from Saitama
prefecture.
I sing games and anime songs.
My first album, Kira Kira, will be
released on November 11th.
It's a glittering album with all the
singers, Yurika, in it, so please check
it out.
And we're also having a tour of the
album, and we're having a live concert
in Saitama.
It's held on December 11th, Sunday, at
Heaven's Rock, so please come and have
fun.
That's all from me, Yurika. See you
later!
DOREKORE!
To all the people who are proud of their
songs all over the country!
We have special contest information for
you!
The Japan Composer Association will hold
a national contest to commemorate the
65th anniversary of the founding of the
company.
This contest is open to anyone,
regardless of their nationality.
You can apply for a video from karaoke
boxes such as tapes, dums, and songs.
The second round will be held in Osaka
for the West Japan Competition and Tokyo
for the East Japan Competition.
The final competition will be held on
Saturday, July 22, 2023.
The guests will be Keisuke Yamauchi from
Kitaku, Hokutopia, and Tsutsuji Hall.
The winner of the final competition will
receive 300,000 yen in cash.
You can apply by visiting the QR code on
the website of the National Sports
Competition.
You can also find a pamphlet with the
details of the event at karaoke stores.
Please apply by shaking your hands.
We are waiting for you!
Dorekore!
On November 16th, the first mini album
of the major debut, Youth Poetry was
released.
Congratulations!
What kind of album is this?
This album is the first mini album of
the major debut.
The concept is a youth novel, but there
are many songs that follow the theme.
Please find a nice song that fits the
theme.
Afternoon Graffiti is the lead song.
What kind of instrument is it?
It's a song that feels like a girl. It's
really perfect for Uka.
The costumes are the same.
It's a girl's song that's pretty neat
and like we're in our prime.
There's a dance where she has a teacup
in her dance.
That's pretty Uka-like.
What kind of dance is it?
I'll hold this dance, look at it,
crouch, and turn it around.
It's going to spill all over.
It's a high-speed dance.
You can see it at the live show.
Yes, we have an MV here.
Please tell us about the points of
interest.
This MV has a book-like world view.
There are a lot of books hanging around.
There's a lip sync, too.
It's divided into upper and lower
classes.
It's full of highlights, so please look
forward to it.
Please check it out.
Mr.Iwai, we have a message from our
viewers.
Thank you.
Thank you. It's from Pen Name Teru-chan.
Mr.Iwai, Mr.Kumada, nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
I enjoy recording your show every time.
Thank you.
I'd like to ask you a question or
advice.
I'm not good at being careful and
scolding people.
I'm nervous.
How can I speak frankly like you?
Thank you.
I'll tell you.
When you say something to someone,
you don't say it to someone who is
nervous or scared.
I said it frankly.
When you complain about something,
you don't say it to someone who is
mentally damaged.
You say it with courage.
So you don't complain and live your
life.
How terrible.
What are you saying?
I don't know what I'm saying even if I
say something strong.
I don't think I said something bad.
That's great.
I understand your feeling.
I've never been scolded by you.
But when I was a junior in a club,
I was nervous to point out the mistake.
I see.
But you're not worth pointing out.
You're not worth pointing out.
That's right.
But you're trying to say it.
You're not mentally strong, but you want
to say it.
You're mentally dirty.
I'm dirty?
Do you say that?
I don't have anything right now.
That's terrible.
Please think about it.
I'm hurt.
Now?
What are you going to send?
This is TERU.
I said something strong, so I'll give
you all of this.
I'm sorry.
I will send this program seal.
Please send a message of support and
request.
Please send it from the official website
of the program.
Do you know the Teletama app?
Yes, you can get a quiz about the
program in this app.
If you can answer the question, you will
get a gift from the guest.
Please download the app and try it.
Kumada Koguchi-chan!
If you get the correct answer, you can
announce it.
Thank you.
It's a question related to Saitama.
Here we go.
Saitama has dialects, but what does the
next dialect mean?
Mujikkei.
I've never heard of it.
Never heard of it?
To be honest.
Mujikkei.
Hint.
Yes.
That girl is really Mujikkei.
Cute.
Is that okay?
Yes.
I did it!
Amazing!
Iwai-san, you're really good at acting.
What?
You're really good at acting.
You're cute.
I'm not doing that much.
It was a live performance.
She said, Iwai-san, you're really good
at acting.
Where?
It was real.
I only thought of you.
Can I announce it?
Thank you.
I'm in charge of the second episode of
the series, Vision's featuring Takuma
Terashima.
I'm singing with Takuma Terashima, so
please look forward to it.
And from December 9 to December 11, the
Miyako Premium Live 2022 will be held at
the Rome Theater Kyoto Main Hall.
We will be on the air on Sunday,
December 11.
Please check it out.
Goodbye.