Ebichu's video!
This tour is the most meaningful tour
for Ebichu.
It's the first tour for nine people.
And Hinata's spring tour will be the
last tour.
I hope that the whole thing of Ebichu
Junior High School will be told.
I'm challenging myself.
Hokkaido was a tour that enjoyed unity.
I was sad that I couldn't sing after
that.
It was the first time for Ichikawa and
TDC.
But it was a warm performance for the
fans.
Each day, the songs are different.
The performance of the day of the A
pattern, the day of the secret kitchen,
and the day of the Sugar Graze was
danceable.
The day of the B pattern, the day of the
B pattern, the day of the Sugar Graze.
It was a tour that I wanted to meet the
fans all over the country.
I was happy to have a lot of fun.
I was supposed to meet everyone on the
first day of the A pattern.
I was happy to have a lot of fun.
As the day went by, the fans
helped by making up many.
There were many performances that
betrayed the live performance that the
fans imagined.
Including choreography, there were many
directions that made me feel like that.
As we performed little by little, the
fans reacted so well that they couldn't
help but scream.
The more we performed, the more we were
able to dance together.
I felt that the live performance was
growing.
I hope we can overcome the spring
together in the final.
It's been a long time since I've done a
tour with many voices. I'm looking
forward to it.
I'm glad that the nine of us performed
together.
I was impressed by the number of people
who came to the concert.
I was happy that the fans came to the
concert because they thought about us.
Of course, it's good to listen to it
with a sound source, but I'm listening
to a lot of voices that I like a lot, so
I think that the song's impression is
amazing because I recommend it to the
production team.
It's really good to end it, isn't it? I
feel like I'm doing a tour and I'm going
through it in a moment.
It's a new album, but I want to make it
the best father that I can't think of
with this album, so I hope you can
listen to a lot of albums and enjoy it
together with your body.
I announced that I would be transferring
in December, and the first stage was the
first day of the spring tour.
The spring tour and everything else will
be the last of the Ebichu. I want to do
my best, but I want to make this park
fun and this tour fun.
I'm doing a lot of things in a song.
I'm kidding. I had a lot of fun doing
that. I didn't think about anything, so
I didn't know, so I enjoyed it until the
show.
It was a song that I hadn't done before,
so it was very difficult to show it to
ourselves.
The choreography itself is also quite
detailed.
I thought it was difficult but fun to
sing, and I thought I had a good singing
ability.
The number of times I can sing live is
decreasing with the members of EVIN.
I will enjoy each and every one of them
without regret.
I think everyone is the same.
It's been a long time since I've done a
tour with nine members.
I was wondering what would happen.
It's been a long time since I've done a
tour, so I'm happy to meet everyone in
Japan.
There are many cities in Niigata, Hachi-
Oji, and Tokyo.
Niigata is a city that has been
completed.
Tokyo City Hall has been completed, but
I was happy that the members took good
care of the tickets.
I thought this album was special.
The story is very interesting.
I was wondering how to show the race-
comfortable atmosphere.
I thought it would be interesting if the
story was similar.
The tour is very fast.
I was wondering how many performances
there were left.
This time, I was really looking forward
to the final.
I was surrounded by pan 09.
I thought the blower was the last tour
with nine people, but personally, I
wanted to be the one who can find my
position as a nine-man band.
At first, I couldn't go to Osaka Park
because of the health problem, but I'm
glad that I can go to the last tour with
everyone.
The last tour was held in front of
Ichikawa Park.
I was able to enjoy the time when Hinata
was there.
I'm not good at explaining.
It's really difficult.
I still have a lot of things to do, but
I want to express myself more.
I'm a group member who has been on tour
so far, but I think it's a tour that can
betray what you imagine.
Please look forward to it.
This tour is the 10th anniversary of the
TESTA anniversary.
I'm grateful that I was able to go to
the last tour.
I was able to perform at my hometown's
Ibaraki Park.
I was able to enjoy the time when I was
able to perform at my hometown's Ibaraki
Park.
I think that each song will show a
different Ebichu.
And it's my first album as a member of
B2,
so I was able to sing each song very
carefully.
When I first received the album, I
really liked CURN.
The dance is also a very unique
choreography.
CURN is my favorite.
When I sing, I get very excited, and
when I sing songs that give me
adrenaline,
I get excited and enjoy it.
I think the audience is also very easy
to get excited.
I don't know what will happen at the
final performance,
but I want to do my best to perform
well,
so I don't get my hands dirty.
I want to do my best to perform well.
I've been performing a lot of live
performances, but I haven't done that
much.
I think there are a lot of live
performances in spring.
So I want to sing a little more through
that.
When I'm here, I try to change my style.
I also try to change my singing style.
I also try to stop dancing.
I think about various things in myself.
I practiced a lot.
I changed my style while performing
live.
Hokkaido is the most memorable place.
It was very hot.
It wasn't the air conditioning.
I had a lot of eye contact with people
who passed by me at the live
performance.
I had a lot of eye contact with them.
I had a lot of fun.
I did my best in Hokkaido.
I'm doing my best at all the live
performances.
There was a song that I entered during
the spring tour.
I thought this song would be a dance.
I wondered how the family would dance
when they saw it.
I was happy to see the family dance.
There is no song called KOKO MIRA.
I don't dance to the music.
I don't listen to music very much.
I'm struggling.
The last performance.
This is the last episode of the spring
tour,
so I'll do my best until the end.
This is the first spring tour for nine
of us,
but it's also the last one for nine of
us,
so I hope we can make great memories.
I set a goal for each performance,
and I hope I can show my best
performance today,
and I hope I can sing well today.
I'm going to set a goal for each
performance,
and I hope I can show the best
performance today.
I'm going to do my best.
I'm the most impressed with the
Hachioji.
I'm so happy that we made it with nine
of us.
I'm so grateful for everyone who waited
for us.
I'm so happy that I was praised by
Emiko-sensei for the Hachioji.
I think that's what I'm most impressed
with.
It's different when you have to dance.
It's more fun to dance.
The Taki-Meki Taki-Shin-Matsurun is a
fun dance.
It's fun to dance with energy.
Some of you may remember it already,
but some of you may remember it already,
like the pose of the song,
and the dance of the song.
I hope we can do that with the audience.
It's already the end,
but I hope we can make a great
performance
so that the nine of us can say,
We're going to have fun,
but I hope we can have fun with the
audience.
What's the last performance you want to
do?
I'm Kokono Sakurai.
I'm Koko Boino.
I'm Naka Hajime.
What's the last performance you want to
do?
It's the last performance of the grand
final.
Until now, we didn't plan to do this in
the next performance,
but we did it in the grand final.
We couldn't do it again in the final.
We couldn't do it again.
It's the end.
I feel a little sad.
We can't do it again.
We'll do everything we've done since
April.
What's the last performance you want to
do?
The last performance is the last
performance of the grand final.
What?
The first...
spring tour...
Wait.
It's okay.
The scary part.
It's difficult.
The first one?
I thought it was difficult.
It's scary.
Don't say it.
It's embarrassing.
I get used to it.
I have to do it.
I want to do it when I have to.
But I'm getting used to it.
I thought it wouldn't work.
It's the first time.
It's true.
The first spring tour is difficult.
It's great.
It's not that bad.
What do you think?
We often gather in the room.
We do.
You and Nonoka sleep together.
That's true.
Let's say it.
When we were in Hokkaido,
Nonoka was late because she was
sleeping.
We never slept together.
We slept separately.
So she didn't notice.
I regretted it.
I slept with her.
We woke up together.
We didn't get late.
I'm sorry.
I'll do my best.
What did you do?
We went to the same place.
We ate takoyaki in Osaka.
We ate pork buns.
You didn't eat pork buns?
Did you eat blood?
No.
I ate ice cream.
You ate ice cream?
I was joking.
What do you think of the tour?
It's dangerous.
The tour final is...
The people who came to the tour...
They can enjoy it.
If you make fun of us...
Don't do it.
Don't do it properly.
No.
We'll have new songs.
We won't make fun of you.
We'll do songs we didn't do on the tour.
We'll play songs from the album.
We'll have fun.
The people who came to the tour can
enjoy it.
The next day
I didn't expect the guard who was on
patrol to be a thief.
But he skipped the mission and went
home.
The song strategy was a big success.
But when Kokona disappeared, it was a
set.
We can't beat the lightning.
Well, if it's good, it's all good.
Then let's go to the party.
It's a happy set with a man.
No, no, happy turn.
Let's eat chicken first.
Protein too.
Well, well, everyone has forgotten.
We're not good at it.