Iinari Tanken Taisui! Iinari Tanken
Taisui!
I'm Yasumori Waka! I'm Shichiro Shinji!
Thank you for your cooperation!
We are Iinari Tanken Taisui!
Today, these two are in their private
clothes, right?
Yes!
Yasuko-san is so cool!
So cool!
It's all black!
It's the opposite of the color of the
back!
That's true!
Coolness and cuteness!
So cute!
It's amazing!
I said it was amazing!
Cute!
We came in our personal clothes today.
What are we going to do?
What?
Today's exploration is...
Illumination!
I'm scared!
This year, we will also be at the 4th
floor of E-WINDS.
It's a very old-fashioned way.
We're going to see it together today.
When you see beautiful illustrations,
you want to read poems, right?
Some people are.
Yes, it's a poem.
Why?
So we're going to read two poems that
are far apart.
What kind of standard is that?
Let's take a look at the illustrations
and make them into poems.
Let's take that moment apart.
ー ー ー ー
ー ー New project. biography want to fly
ー ー Ah, did youww • It's already
planned.
competitions.
ーI got injured.
ー ーI thought the four countries friend.
پ
We have arrived at the 4th floor!
Yes! It's raining!
It's raining! It's raining!
We are looking at the illumination of
the 4th floor of Ebins!
It's amazing! It's so bright!
Don't say it's bright!
Let's take a look around!
There is a tree in the middle of the
building!
It's a green zone.
The blue is beautiful.
Let's go inside.
Wow!
This entrance is inviting us.
I want to go inside.
Don't put your hands in the door.
If you put your hands in the door,
you'll be embarrassed.
Let's take care of ourselves.
I wanted to fill the space.
I wanted to fill the strange tension
that flows through the field.
I understand.
That's right.
It's funny.
It's amazing.
It's beautiful.
Last year, it was colorful with flowers.
That's right.
It was a flower last year.
There are flowers this year too.
It's beautiful.
I feel like I'm a princess.
Great!
I wonder if the tension in the
neighborhood is good.
It's a trick.
This butterfly can narrow the distance
between the two.
Something is coming.
You should be confident.
It's a good butterfly.
It's like the Earth.
The Earth was blue.
That's what it was originally.
It's like a Gagarin.
It's like a Wackerlin.
It's not a Wackerlin.
You're good at it.
It's a human thing.
It's a Wackerlin.
That's not a poem.
It's a poem.
Look at that.
Isn't it amazing?
Thank you for watching.
Look at this.
This is a phenomenon.
This is a phenomenon of snow.
This is amazing.
I hope you can see it even without snow.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
You two shouldn't have hit each other.
I was watching.
Look at this.
This is a umbrella.
It's really cute.
This is only seen when it rains.
Of course.
Don't poke.
Can't you all poke?
No.
You have to feel it and soak it.
You have to soak it.
That's right.
If you poke it in the air, you'll lose.
If you go out here,
Go to the blue ball.
Is the blue ball blue?
Only blue.
Who?
I'll go there.
I found a good place.
Look at this.
Oh!
Who?
It sounds amazing!
Even if there is a place where the sound
does not sound
Doremi Fasolassido
It's a masterpiece
Play your own Doremi Fasolassido
Don't laugh
Last year, Doremi Fasolassido was not in
the same group
I see
This year, Doremi Fasolassido is in the
same group
Can you play a song?
Last year, Hina and Rine were singing a
frog song
Can you sing a song?
Thank you for your viewing.
I'm going to stop.
What? You gave up?
If you give up, the game is over.
It's a human again.
It's a Shinto tree.
It's a safe zone.
Thank you for your viewing.
I'm sure I'm shining brighter than the
Illuminations, no matter how dark I
wear.
I'm sure I'm shining brighter than the
Illuminations, no matter how dark I
wear.
Are you wearing the costume that goes
with the performance?
I came in black today.
As expected.
But the performance is different from
the preparation.
From the costume?
I see.
I'm wearing black today to say this.
The production is also solid.
Of course.
Hey, the Illumination is beautiful.
But for me, you are more beautiful than
the Illumination of the
few thousand flowers here.
Yes!
I got it!
I won!
I want to make this video a paid one.
Who? Who?
Who is this old man?
Who is this?
Prettypsychic
This place is sooo damn cool
I can see this soon
So, Tchao Tchao
Looking at Illuminati
It's a world view that makes you feel
like you're going to die.
As a poem artist, it's a little noisy.
There's a customer.
JK is playing the piano now.
It's a normal poem-like contest.
That's great.
So, our illumination has nothing to do
with Christmas.
We're going to do it until February 1st.
Until Valentine's Day.
Happy Valentine's Day.
It's beautiful.
We came here together on Christmas, but
we're so happy to be here on Valentine's
Day.
I'm happy.
Let's eat anything.
Yeah.
That's what I can do.
What do you mean?
It's not a poem.
I hope you guys can say this and it will
be more fun.
It's not embarrassing.
You can say a lot of things without
being embarrassed.
It's all because of Ilmi.
It's nice. It looks like it's written on
the poster.
Everyone, please come to Mori no Gawaden
Terrace to play.
Thank you very much.
See you.