Mechanized
YAKANTO IDOL!
Please tell me more about your favorite
things.
Yes, please.
What's the second one?
The second one is the compatibility with
the camera.
Compatibility with the camera?
Yes, it is.
You know, when you do this kind of work,
you have a lot of opportunities to
shoot.
Yes.
At that time,
It may be a bad point, but I'm a patty.
Really?
It may be hard to understand today.
The table is a patty and the neck is
long.
The neck is long.
It's long.
And it becomes like this.
Oh, I see.
When I take a group photo with six
people,
I'm often told to come a little closer.
At that time, the neck comes out.
Not the body, but the neck.
And when I shoot live photos,
The probability of reflection is very
high.
It's probably an extreme dry eye.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's too dry, so it's almost half-face.
That's a little hard to do this job.
I'm aware that I'm licking my lips.
It's very common.
When I take a picture of the camera,
The probability of reflection is too
high.
It's a little bad compatibility.
I feel like that.
Oh, I see.
It's better to fix it a little.
It's good, isn't it?
It may be so for work.
Show me a pose you're good at.
Let's say you're taking a picture.
I'll take a live picture.
Yes, please.
Three, two, one.
I can't see the neck at all.
If there's someone, it's over.
Come closer.
It's better to go from the body.
Should I go?
The previous cut was cute.
Let's go.
It's good.
Please come closer.
Oh, really.
Only the neck is visible.
But you're a good match with the camera.
Really?
It's very photogenic.
I'm glad.
I'm sure you're taking a two-shot of the
fans during the event.
What kind of thing do you do with the
fans?
Because it's in front of the camera.
I'm always thinking about it when I take
a two-shot.
I don't blink.
I always want to put on lipstick before
I go out.
Really?
I can see the lips in the first half,
but I can't see them in the second half.
That's the lip.
That's a physical thing.
It's not about feeling.
Feelings are the same until the end.
It's the same.
As expected.
It's a good job.
That's nice.
Do you have a talk show?
I have a talk show.
You're good at talking, aren't you?
I'm good at talking.
But the fans are too fast for me to
listen.
I think it's going to be a talk show
while taking social distance in this
time of year.
Will you be surprised?
I'm sure I'll be surprised.
The fans will be surprised, too.
Really?
Yes.
You're funny.
That's nice.
I got a gift for my birthday.
You got a gift for your birthday?
Yes, I got a car and other things, but I
couldn't eat them because they were too
good.
I'm going to eat them.
This program is...
Kit-san
Yukki-san
Sensei-san
Corazon-san
Nananochi Shishi-san
I've been providing this.
Today's recommended gummy is...
It's a fruit-flavored orange flavor.
Everyone, please try it.
Thank you very much.