Thank you for watching.
Hello?
Do you know someone?
I know.
You're a good girl.
Long time no see.
It's been a while.
Were you surprised?
Yes, I was surprised.
You know,
this is...
You know, I don't answer the phone.
Yeah, I don't answer it at all.
I'm embarrassed.
Can you do it?
I wonder if I became a wanko when I was
in high school.
I was a wanko only sometimes.
I said it sometimes.
I was in the car to pick up Nana at
school.
I was.
Rikoko suddenly became an adult when I
was in high school.
That's right.
I'm evolving.
You're not evolving.
You're getting cuter every day.
I really...
I went to the hair salon and dyed my
hair.
Do you know who I am?
Wait, are you right? Pink?
It's not pink.
Oh, it's before that.
Is it blonde now?
Yeah, it's blonde now.
Oh, I see.
Did you see it when it was pink?
I saw it. It was really pretty.
The color and the scent are all the
same.
I want to make it pink. I want to make
it pink.
Really?
I want to do it someday.
I haven't done it yet.
I was surprised. Are you going to do it?
Not yet. I don't have it yet.
I want to do it someday.
Do you have a license for beauty?
I'll take it next year.
If you take it, cut Nana's hair once.
Okay.
If it gets weird, will you get angry?
I won't get angry. I'll do it properly.
Then stretch it out to some extent.
I understand.
I'm going to be very rude.
But I'm pretty rude now.
Well, well, well, whatever happens.
I'll leave it to you.
I'm going to ask Rikko.
I'll do my best.
At that time, you can put on pink.
Can I put on pink?
Sure. At that time.
Do it.
I'll do my best to practice the
combination of pink.
What kind of pink is it?
I think a little dirty pink is good.
Dirty pink?
Something like a dull pink.
Why?
Something like...
I don't know.
Something beautiful...
I like pink like Rikoko's.
I'll leave it to the teacher.
That's Nana's taste.
And...
Nana...
Nana was the most intense...
You were the one who had a fight.
Please watch again.
Me?
Yes.
On the contrary,
I remember
we had a fight.
But Nana said,
I don't know. I hate Riko.
Then I went home.
Then I wondered how I got along.
I think I did it in time.
I remember I went to Nana's house
without thinking.
I think so.
Riko is like that.
That's my personality.
I don't think I've ever apologized to
you.
I'm not crying.
I don't think I've ever apologized to
you.
Really?
I'm sorry.
Who liked the singer?
I've never liked someone special.
But when you go to karaoke, don't you
always want to sing the other side of
the brown car?
What was it?
I did it with Aoi Sora no Masita, right?
Yeah, I remember.
When I was in middle school, I went home
with Nana's house and went home with a
lot of heat in my hand.
I miss that.
I was so nervous that I was watching
someone else.
I was so nervous that I was so quiet
when I came from the front.
I'm so proud of you.
I heard Nana's deep-sea.
Deep-sea? Really?
Thank you.
It was cute. I liked it the most.
Really? I'm glad.
What? Do you think about it?
What kind of lyrics?
When I was asked what kind of song I
wanted to sing, I said I wanted to sing
the song that you made.
Oh, really?
Yes, that's how I realized the song.
I was so impressed with Nana.
Really?
I thought it was very Nana-like.
I'm so happy.
Try singing a little.
No, no, no.
That's weird.
Really? I want to hear the live singing.
Your...
Can you see that star?
That dream, that feeling of mine
Are you crying somewhere?
Just wishing for it to become bubbles
It's nostalgic
Really?
It's nostalgic when I'm in karaoke
It sounds like karaoke
Will there be a new song next?
There will be
Next
Shinkai-san
There is a person called Shinkai Makoto
who is a member of Tenki
I understand
He wrote it for me
What is the name of the song?
It's called Senobi
It's
How should I say it
It's romantic
It sounds sooo good
It's a sad song
The chorus is so sad
Really?
ーWhat was it? ーWhat was it?
ーYou're so far away, looking for a star
that seems nowhere ー
ーDon't go, don't go, you have a pain
that you can't say ー
ーYou're so desperate, it's like a dream
ー
ーBut you'll surely say goodbye ー
ーYou're going on a journeyー
ーTo be continuedー
ーYou're cuteー
ーYeahー
ーShinkai san is cuteー
ーYou're beautifulー
ーPlease promote Rikko san's Instagramー
ーI will do my bestー
ーReally?ー
ーPlease tell me when you get homeー
I'm going to go to school too. I'm going
to go to school.
I'm going to graduate and do it a year
later.
Then, I'm going to stay at my house for
7 days.
Who's Nana's bed belongs to?
Nana's bed belongs to Rikoko.
I always go home with the smell of
Rikoko.
Then I'll stop by again.
Good, Kasuken, stop by.
Then I'll call you occasionally.
Oh, really?
I'll call you.
Nice to meet you.
Is there anything you want to say at the
end?
I'm looking forward to your hair cut.
I want to practice.
I'm not weird.
Please be careful and go home.
Thank you.
Take care of yourself. See you.
See you.
Bye.
Good night.