Thank you for watching!
If you were a spring, would you be a
quail?
I'd be a quail.
I'd be waiting for a dog to come up.
I'd be like, oh, cute!
We'd ride together like this,
and fly a bit.
Sometimes a dog would come up like this.
I'd be like, oh, cute!
That's what I'd do.
I was studying and watching videos
with Chiho Takai and Luna Naito.
I was so happy to meet Yakan.
And Yakan, thank you for the delicious
tea.
I love taking pictures like this.
I wanted to be a model.
I'm happy to have this opportunity to
take pictures again.
This outfit is really cute.
This outfit is cute, isn't it?
The fourth one!
What is it?
I don't know.
I'm not sure what to say.
I'll say, fashionable.
I don't know.
I don't know what to say.
I'll say, fashionable.
I changed my mind.
When I take pictures with the members,
I can't stop talking to the members when
I'm moving.
The reason I talk so much is because I
want to enjoy the time with the members.
I'm lonely when I'm on my way home.
I'm going to talk about everything I
want to talk about now.
When I was asked what my first
impression of Aya Shirahama was,
I said, I'm talking.
I love talking, so I'd like to have a
talk with you at the special event.
I'm so excited.
Well, if I were to take a video of the
members, I would take a video of Aoyama
Nanoha, who is the same age as me.
I personally took a video of N-san, a
YouTuber named N-san, in my camera
folder, but I haven't shown it to the
members yet.
I just showed a little bit of it, but I
wanted to edit and take a video of
N-san, so I hope I can do it with N-san.
And Chiho Takai is beautiful, so I'd
like to edit the video during the live
performance and put together all the
good points of Chi-chan.
And Naito Luna is so fashionable that I
wonder if I can take a video and edit
it.
Luna always says interesting things like
talking, so I'm looking forward to it.
I want to make it like a talk show, like
a YouTuber.
I want to play interesting BGM.
I'm going to ride a roller coaster.
I'm having a lot of fun on the roller
coaster. It's my first time.
I was wondering how it would be.
It was comfortable to ride and the wind
was pleasant.
I saw the picture of a woman on a human-
powered roller coaster.
I thought it was so big.
But, when I saw it in person, I thought
it was a beautiful ride.
It was fun.
How did you feel when you saw the city
of Koedo with a history?
I was told a lot of names.
I forgot the name of the city.
I was told a lot of interesting names.
I'll look it up when I get back.
It was fun.
I heard it for the first time.
When I was in junior high school, I was
told that my hairstyle was not good.
I was challenged how cute I could be at
the last minute.
I went to school today.
I had a hair cut at that time.
I always have my bangs up.
I'm having fun.
I want to do more.
You can do more.
You look exactly the same.
We look alike.
I want to do more.
I'm gonna eat more.
Who is the most stylish idol?
I want to do something like this.
But I'm really luxurious.
I want to talk to A-rin and Ayaka
Sasaki.
I'm very luxurious, but I want to talk
to them.
I respect A-rin because she is always
cute.
I want to ask her a lot of questions.
It's suddenly deafening.
I was able to do it in front of the
camera, and it was really fun.
But to tell you the truth, I've been
avoiding this kind of emergency
situation.
I'm not that kind of character.
I was the type of person who would walk
around and say,
Let's say the emergency line, and then I
would immediately mess around.
So I thought it was a little fresh, but
I was able to walk around and have a lot
of fun.
Please subscribe to my channel!
Naito-san is here.
Thank you.
How did you feel when you first saw
Shirahama-san?
When I was in 5th grade, I was so
excited because it was my first time.
I was like, let's do this! Let's do
this!
I didn't notice it when I was talking to
the girls.
But when I watch the videos and the
videos that she's watching now,
she's so warm-hearted and she's watching
us, Ayano, trying new things.
And she's so nice and doesn't try to be
noticed.
She's so nice and supports us.
I'm so happy that she supports us.
When you came, you said you let me eat
yakitori bonjiri.
Oh, the bento.
Was it good?
It was good.
It was really good.
You're lying.
I'm serious.
You're serious.
I didn't know what bonjiri was at the
time.
You said you liked bonjiri, so you said
you'd let me eat it next time.
You kept your promise and brought me a
bento.
And the first bonjiri was Chi-chan's.
It was really good.
The first bonjiri was Chi-chan's?
That's a misinterpretation.
Did you ask where the bonjiri was?
The bonjiri was in my butt.
You can only get one bonjiri.
That's right.
It was good, wasn't it?
I was filled with love.
What about Lululunpanpan?
Lululunpanpan?
It's a story about Lumpan's bonjiri.
It's okay if the audience imagines
Lumpan's bonjiri.
How about Lumpan?
It's a story about Lumpan.
LUNA is fashionable with her nails.
That's right.
I started Instagram with Shirahama Aya.
LUNA's Instagram is really fashionable.
When I take a story, I ask LUNA to take
a picture of me.
When I wear a cute outfit, I ask LUNA
how to make it cuter.
I ask her to be fashionable.
That's right.
You two have a good relationship.
You're quite different in age.
You two are getting along well.
See you.
Is there a video you want to make
yourself?
A video I want to make myself?
I want to make a video like a YouTuber.
I want to make a video with my own sound
effects.
I want to make a video with all four
members.
I want to do a rehearsal.
I bought a 100 million yen nightstand.
Do you want to do it like a YouTuber?
I understand.
Hello, everyone! I'm Aya Shirahama from
Shirahama Channel!
So, today's topic is...
I bought a 100 million yen nightstand!
Yes, I bought a 100 million yen
nightstand and it's right here.
It's my first time to see a 100 million
yen nightstand, so I bought it.
I'd like to drink it right away.
It's a 100 million yen nightstand, so
I'll try to drink it like this.
I'll hold it for a moment.
It's different from drinking tea at a
100 million yen nightstand.
Please buy a 100 million yen nightstand!
Bye bye!
That's great!
I think nightstands are old-fashioned.
I thought I'd make a lot of things
before I showed you a 100 million yen
nightstand.
But now I'm going to show you
everything.
That's not the problem.
I'm going to show you everything.
I'm already excited to show you
everything.
I don't need a nightstand.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
The first one was a video editing.