There's no place for a lost Jigar.
I don't know what to do with my face.
I think the most important thing is to
have fun.
Words and songs are the most important.
Thank you for your time.
Thank you.
I'm so happy.
This is the line.
Today, we're going to have a night
atmosphere.
Really?
I'm going to have a night atmosphere
too.
You're going to have a night atmosphere.
Yanagisawa, you're going to have a
little...
It's a little...
I'm going to change my clothes.
No, no, no.
Change your clothes.
Please.
Yes.
Thank you.
Thank you for your time.
I like Western music and hard rock.
So I've been playing hard rock since I
got my mind.
With a loud volume?
It's a good exercise.
I thought it was annoying.
Since then, I've had a lot of
opportunities to touch music.
Thanks to that, I've really liked music.
I thought about what was in the CD,
cassette, and record in the house.
I've been able to pull it out and get my
father to teach me a lot of things.
I've been doing that since I was little.
Did your father teach you?
My father is someone who teaches me even
without listening to it.
He would say, listen to this.
He would play the Zeppelin.
My father liked the Duke Purple a lot.
The Duke Purple was playing all the
time.
He saw me, who was a little interested
in Duke Purple's music,
he started to play music a lot.
He played hard rock like Red Zeppelin or
Black Sabbath.
From there, he became quite a maniac.
He played other genres, such as Uriah
Hip and Mountain.
He played a lot of those genres.
I didn't think, this is like this, this
is like this.
But from that time, I had the
opportunity to play various kinds of
music.
I was able to experience the music in a
way that I was interested in.
It wasn't about the music, but the
presentation of the guitar.
The presentation of the guitar, the
phrase, the feeling of the song, etc.
But I was listening to that, so I became
very interested in music in a Korean
way.
I was able to experience the song by
myself.
Did you have any chance to sing
seriously?
Or did you have any chance to form a
band?
I told Yonagisawa that I wanted to form
a band with this band.
I asked Yonagisawa if there was anyone
who could sing.
He invited me and I joined.
I just joined.
How old were you when you joined?
I think I was in my last year of high
school.
I'm the younger brother of Fujiwara
Yanagisawa,
and he's one of my younger brothers.
When Yanagisawa was in the second year
of high school, and I was in the third
year of high school,
we became like this.
I imagine that Shibuya's singing is
amazing,
so I ask him to sing.
Originally, the bassist, Uesugi,
is the father of the band Super Beaver.
He's still, from the beginning,
Shibuya is...
He had something unique.
I don't know what it is, but at least he
didn't have anything for himself.
He was a person who had a single true
path.
He was a person who had a world that
only Shibuya and Ryuto knew.
That's the reason why he was invited.
Uesugi said that a lot.
The appearance is also...
It was quite distinctive at the time.
What was it like at the time?
It was like a self-released cut.
Just thinking about it makes me want to
come out right away.
I wanted to dye my hair,
and I wanted to raise my piercings as
much as I could.
I didn't have a place to stand when I
was lost.
I jumped up, but I was like, I'm going
to go.
If I stand out, something will change.
If I stand out, I'll be popular.
Shibuya-san, you chose a song that had a
big influence on you.
You pushed for the song, I can't do it.
I really thought it was impossible.
That's right.
I'm going to do it myself.
I chose a song that made me interested
in music and started to act.
I chose a song that made me start to dig
various things.
This time, I chose a song called 氷のマニキュア
by Tatsuro Yamashita.
The first CD I bought was Off Course.
I really liked Off Course and I listened
to it because I thought it was great for
me as an elementary school student.
When I started listening to various
things at home, I found Koji's album.
When I listened to it, I was excited.
This feeling is...
I've never felt this before.
I wanted to know the roots of
excitement,
so I tried to find my way around various
things.
I lived with only what I had at home,
but I couldn't live with what I had at
home.
That's why I chose Tatsuro Yamashita.
Why is Tatsuro-san's voice so...
It's connected to your thoughts.
I can tell now, but he's a very
particular person.
He's a great musician and a great
singer, but I think he's a musician now.
At that time, I didn't know anything,
but it was blurred.
I'm sure even children understand it.
I was excited about it.
I was very shocked.
From then until now.
I've been listening to it all the time.
At the same pace.
At the same pace?
How fast is it at the same pace?
I don't think it opens for a day.
It doesn't open.
Do you sing a song to imitate?
I have a good voice.
Great.
But you don't sing in karaoke?
No.
You don't?
You sing songs of various people, don't
you?
I sing.
But you don't sing songs of Tsuruno-san?
No.
I don't know why, but there's a song
that's no-touch.
Wow.
I don't have to put my hand out. I'm a
listener.
You're a real music fan, so you're a
real musician.
I'm just a musician.
I'm not saying I don't know what a
musician is.
I'm just a musician.
When I went to the concert...
・Y kişi ・Y?!?
I went there without permission.
I have a sense of duty.
When did you go there for the first
time?
It's been over 30 years.
I went to see it.
I was there for three hours.
I felt three hours was short.
It was my first time.
It's a blessing.
I can be so moved.
I was so happy that I thought I was
going to die.
We had 100 concerts a year.
There are moments when I feel like I'm
going to die.
And when I saw the concert without
thinking about it, I suddenly felt like
I was going to die.
I really like it.
I'm going to play it.
I don't have any idea what's amazing.
Oh, you don't analyze it?
Not at all.
I'm always looking forward to it.
I'm always talking.
I'm talking.
I don't even know if I can call you a
senior, but I can feel that feeling.
I'm a senior, and I'm playing music
really cool in the first round.
I can't get enough of it.
That's amazing.
Do you go to the music store to say
hello?
No, no.
I'm a customer.
I bought some goods and went home.
I bought some goods and went home to
take pictures of the park.
That's crazy.
I'm happy.
I'm really happy.
I think it's very happy.
What is your favorite song?
I like this song.
I was a guitarist when I was a child.
My father was a guitarist.
Did you feel like you were being taught?
I told my father that I wanted to play
the guitar.
He bought me a guitar and taught me the
C chord.
I was a guitarist when I was in the
fourth or fifth grade.
I was close to Brian because I was close
to him.
I was playing at home all the time.
I didn't like it very much.
I felt it was natural to play it.
What kind of music did you play?
I played hard rock,
and also blues,
and also clap tones.
I played only the riff of Deep Purple's
Smoke on the Water.
I was taught when I started playing.
It's simple and cool.
And the Beatles are better, but you
should listen to them anyway.
I don't know the title of the song yet,
but I listened to a lot of albums to the
point where I was speechless.
That was when I was in elementary
school.
I was listening to a lot of songs at
that time.
I listened to songs that my parents
listened to, like Blues.
Do you remember when you started
listening to songs with your own will?
I started listening to songs when I was
in the 4th grade.
I chose this song, however, in Grey.
I asked my mother to buy a CD of the
song, Grey's However.
Where did you hear that?
Why are you laughing?
You're in shock.
Where did you hear that?
I heard it on a music program on TV.
It's a good song for a child.
Grey's However
I remember that I was really impressed.
I was in the 4th grade of elementary
school,
and there was a girl who knew a lot
about music.
I went to her place and only remember
the phrase I was saying.
And the title was in English, so I
couldn't remember it.
She only taught me how to say, however.
I was saying however, however, and then
I went home.
That's a shock.
That's right.
It's a meeting.
Thank you for watching.
I've liked many artists and music since
then.
But I didn't know that I'd become a fan
of them.
I didn't know that I'd become a fan of
them.
I just knew that they were just crazy
fans of them.
That's how I got into them.
Thank you for watching.
You got into a fan club.
I asked my mom to do it.
I have something to tell you about Mr.
Yanagisawa.
What is it? I'm scared.
Wait a minute.
I got a message from Takuro from Grey.
I'm going to ask Takuro to send me a
message today.
That's great.
I don't know what to do.
I'm sorry to hear that.
I'm very grateful.
Are you doing well?
Yes.
Thank you for choosing How Ever as your
favorite song.
It's been more than 25 years since this
song was released.
I'm very happy to have someone's memory
as a song like Yanagisawa.
I'm a little proud.
And I'm grateful that I'm still active
as a member of the Gray family.
YANAGISA, the world is still in a state
of anxiety, but we are musicians.
Let's work hard to warm the hearts of
those who need it.
I look forward to the day we can meet
again.
Takuro.
Isn't it amazing?
This is amazing.
Thank you very much for the amazing
series.
I'm already on the show, so I'd like to
talk about how ever.
I asked him if he could give me a
message, and he told me how to make it.
I didn't know about this.
It was a song I made when I was moving
to Sugizo's flat in London.
I made it while I was waiting for Sugizo
to come back from the recording,
and I remember making it while carrying
Sugizo's daughter in my arms.
It's just a genius's
It's amazing, isn't it?
At first, the members who listened to
the demo tape were very disliked, and
Jiro said,
It's dark.
I wanted to make it a single somehow, so
I sent everyone in a car or bought beef
bowl.
It's a song that I've been working on
the recording.
According to Tel, I'm singing in
Takuro's voice.
The demo tape was a story about a
guitar, and I was singing with the key
down.
But from the beginning, I was told that
I was the only one who could sing.
I was sad.
That's amazing.
Thank you so much.
Takuro is happy.
I'm so happy.
That's right.
What should I do from here?
I'm probably not coming back.
We just talked about the members'
reactions to the song.
Are the members' reactions to the song
scary?
I'm not sure if I'm saying it's scary,
but I'm still very nervous.
Of course, I have confidence in the
song.
I think it's a good song.
Before I give it to the members, I have
to break it several times and make it
again.
I think this song became like this and
give it to the members.
I'm always wondering what to do if it
becomes like that.
I don't have a story about Takuro-san,
but the words Shibuya said at the live
show.
I put it in my own way and put it in as
a band.
I think it's a reaction that I haven't
been able to convey 100% yet.
When I think about it, I don't get angry
at myself, but I do convey it in words.
I have this feeling in my mind, and this
is how it is.
I don't know if I can imagine this song
now, but for example, if Boo-yan sings,
if Shibuya sings,
if I actually do this in the band, it
should definitely be like this, so I
think I'll try it once.
There are songs that say that.
There are things you don't know unless
you try it.
There are.
There are things you don't know unless
you're a vocalist.
Do you have any advice on how to make a
song?
Basically, I let the members listen to
it after I've finished making it.
You're pretty good at it.
I'm basically like that.
But when it comes to album production,
I've been really into it lately.
For example, I've been asked about the
kind of song I want to sing.
It's a very rough question.
What kind of mood I'm in right now.
What kind of beat I want to hit on the
drummer, Fujiwara Uchida.
I've heard that before.
So I've heard it beforehand, and then
I've got an idea.
Then I'll write my own lyrics and
melodies.
If I remembered the meaning of this
move...
歌詞の部分で渋谷さんに相談することとかも あったりしますか?
あとありますね。結構細かい言葉尻というか、
この接続詞一つで意味変わると思っていて、
どっちもありだと思うんだけど、どっちがいいと思うとか、
俺はこういう意図で書いてるんだけれども、
そのまま伝わるかな?
一見した時にどう感じた?とか、
そういうところを聞いたりします。
Is your trust in Yanagisawa-san really a
big deal?
Yes, it is.
I'm always moved by his music.
I always make the first decision whether
I can be moved or excited by his music.
MC...
...and the way they make it.
I want to tell them this.
I said this at the time,
but they made it into a proper form
and taught me how to do it.
As a band, I think this is something we
should sing together.
I recognize that again.
Whether or not I can be moved by it
is connected to the MC content
when I get to the stage.
It's hard to come up with new words when
you're not impressed.
I can only say it in a abstract way.
Yano Gisa is the one who makes up the
words that I say with confidence.
I think it's amazing every time.
I think he's a genius.
He's building his own thoughts.
I think it's a good thing to say it like
this.
I think Super Uver is a strong band that
speaks out as a Super Uver.
So when they're on stage and they're
speaking out in the middle,
I think they're thinking about it a lot.
I think Super Uver is talking.
Thank you for watching.
I think there are many people who write
songs with that kind of feeling.
It's the will of the band.
I think that's what's getting more and
more solid.
I feel that it's getting stronger and
stronger.
We're able to share the place where the
band exists.
We're here now.
That's the best part of Super Beaver.
We've come to realize that.
I think that realization is stronger.
I think that's what the members,
including the two people who are not
here today,
feel strongly and with the same
enthusiasm.
I'm happy now.
I'm happy every year.
It's fun.
Thank you for your viewing.
I know all the fun.
I'm not the only one who's having fun.
There are people who are having fun
around me.
It's the members, family, friends.
And more than anything, the people who
listen to me.
I'm having a lot of fun.
I think that's the biggest engine of
all.
I feel that every day and I think music
is fun.
A song was born for the people living in
Tokyo
The joy of being found and the feeling
of being separated
I want to be loved inside my heart
I want to be loved by the person I love
I can hear it
I don't want to say anything to you
It's life
We are aware of our position and our
activities are real.
That's why I felt that it was
transmitted so hot.
Super Beaver from Tokyo will release a
song called Tokyo.
I thought this was also very real.
But we ourselves are
still meeting each other,
or meeting each other who have passed
away,
or connecting with each other,
or asking for help,
or perhaps being hurt.
When we were all together,
I wanted to sing each of those meetings
more carefully and carefully in Tokyo.
That...
そうなんですけど、でも僕らにはそうとしか言いようがない。
それと同時に同じように戦う場でもあるっていうのは僕らにとって間違いなくて。
And when I thought about it again, it
was because for us, it was a Tokyo base
and everything was involved.
On the contrary, this song, Tokyo, is
about a person who listens to it,
It's a city where everyone lives, it's a
place where they love and live,
I think it's a good idea to put those
things in the same place as the title,
Tokyo, and listen to it.
I think it's a good idea to put those
things in the same place as the title,
so I think I could make a song that
makes you think about the life, life,
and the people you love.