BBQ! BANBANQ!
This time, the members are waiting for
the barbecue
Forget the program and eat
And I want to grill too
What is it?
barbecue
Let's go
Bichiru Tastas start
We will send you a variety of things to
private Ebisu junior high school!
Ebisu Juskatsu!
We will make this the first barbecue
ever!
This program is brought to you by the
sponsors you see.
Next time, I'll be the MC!
I've watched all of your MCs, so I'll do
my best without making any mistakes!
Good luck, Riko-chan!
Yoishotto!
Can we join you?
Please!
I was biting in front of the store
I was working
So, from this time, Ogatsu-san will also
appear in the opening
Let's introduce the three of us
Hello, I'm Taki-Yuto from Nagareboshi
I'm Chue!
I'm Tairyo!
I'm gonna kiss you
What kind of high five is that?
And I am 360 degree rock star, Hiya
Ogata Kaeki
Ogata who was hiding Hoshina
Missed all the cameras
Nakayama, what are you going to do
today?
Today, everyone is waiting for me
What?
Today's menu is BBQ
BBQ
You've been saying you wanted to do the
waiting part, right?
Yes, I'm happy
I'm waiting
Actually, when I asked what kind of
location they wanted to do in the survey
Matsuno's answer is BBQ
And the prize for the TV show which adds
shrimp?
I like eating, so I want to try BBQ
And more
What do you want to add?
I want to add BBQ
You want to add BBQ?
To answer Matsuno's BBQ love
This time's theme is BBQ
Let's start BBQ
What do you think is needed to make BBQ
the most delicious?
Sauce and meat
I got it
Food
It's close
That's a good idea
Mayushii
I'll make your stomach empty
Correct
The answer is hunger
Before the BBQ, the members will have
their stomach empty
The owner will jump
The rule is that if the shooting star
turns the rope and the shrimp and the
big one jump 100 times in a row, they
will succeed
If they fail at least once, they have to
start over
If you can't do it, you can't eat
barbecue
You can't eat it
What if it's dark?
If it's dark, you can't eat it
You can't eat it
Let's do our best
Yes
The energy is low
They are excited
They are going to jump into the big
river
Let's go
Ready, set, go
They are jumping into the river
Oh no!
Not good at all
He has zero record
One, two, three
He is getting his energy back
Ready, set, go!
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10
I think he is getting better
Ready, go!
It's difficult
2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10
He is getting tired
Who is it?
The members are getting tired
You are getting tired, right?
Yes
How many times did you do?
16 times
84 times left
It's more difficult than I thought
Let's take a break
Everyone, let's take a picture
Wait a minute, who is Tegoshi?
Dad
What kind of ramen is this?
Good smell
Smells delicious
Miso ramen
I said it
He said it
The one prepared by the Chinese movie is
the one chosen by the national ramen
fans
The most popular one in the miso section
of the La Navitaisho
The best one in four consecutive years
Miso ramen specialty shop
Special Miso Thick Ramen
Just smell it
I'll smell it
Please smell it for everyone
I want to eat it
You are waiting too early
You are going?
The BBQ will be bad
Yes, the members who have been working
hard to eat delicious BBQ so far
If you eat this, your efforts will be in
vain
Let's go BBQ
or Miso Ramen?!
What is going on?!
If all of us dinner together then it's
fine
It's totally not very alluring
Yummy
If Iера eat this, everyone will be crazy
to eathhhh
That's right! Let's eat ramen with
everyone today
They'm overflowing their efforts
So, the owner is going back to the house
to reduce the hunger
Let's succeed the next one
OK
Let's go
Ready, go
I don't want to do it
He picked up
You have a good self-confidence
Even if he tries again and again, he
can't reach the 100th floor
It's hot!
I'm hungry
But it seems that he is not hungry
BBQ, let's go!
Wait a minute, what's going on?
Hey!
BBQ!
What's going on?
So, we're going to have BBQ time!
Finally, the members are waiting for BBQ
time!
The ingredients are the original
ingredients that each member usually
uses when they have BBQ with their
family.
First, let's start with the BBQ at
Hirota's house.
The first menu is the BBQ menu at
This is my BBQ menu.
Huh?
There's nothing in there.
What do you mean?
It's not that original.
It's a standard taste.
I see. So you're not going to grill it,
right?
It's not good, is it?
I know that.
It's going to burn.
The BBQ at Hirota's house is a self-
restraint menu.
The BBQ is empty.
Next is the BBQ menu of the Yasumoto
family.
I can see it.
Because it's important.
The BBQ is empty.
My home's original menu is...
Nothing.
I've never done BBQ at home.
Really?
No.
Yasumoto has no BBQ experience with her
family.
Yasumoto is empty.
Hoshina and Kashiwagi are empty.
What do you mean?
I don't do it at home.
No experience at home.
Wait a minute.
Hiroto has done it before, but at home.
There is no original menu.
The other three have never done it at
home.
It's a little lonely to be empty with
four people.
Because half of the members are over.
That's right.
But please look forward to it.
I'll wait for the next one.
I love barbecue.
Miss barbecue.
Miss barbecue in Emi.
What is the barbecue menu of Matsunoke?
Please show me.
This is my original barbecue menu.
Finally, something is included.
Matsunoke's menu is standard barbecue
ingredients.
This white object.
What is this?
Is there a particularity in the process?
Marshmallow?
Is this white marshmallow?
I want to eat
What is marshmallow?
It's delicious
What does marshmallow taste like?
Is it a chicken?
Is it a sauce?
It's delicious
Is it a dessert?
Yes
The middle-aged men who can't hide the
generation gap
And the food of the Nakayama family
My food is this
Only marshmallow
What?
Is the house stupid?
Everyone is eating without marshmallows
Excuse me
Of course, they eat other food in
Nakayama family
But they love marshmallow so much that
they put marshmallow on the plate
Next, what is the barbecue menu in
Mayamake family?
This is the original menu of my family
She is laughing
It's so funny
This is the menu in Mayamake family
The barbecue's main ingredients are
lined up
This looks good too. What's this meat?
Pork and chicken
The pumpkin is good too. It's good for
your lungs
It's good for your lungs
Really?
That was more fun than I imagined
That was funny
That was a boring joke
That was new
And lastly, the barbeque menu of the
Kobayashi family
This is my home-made menu
Please look forward to the next video!
What is the food that everyone is
interested in?
Chinese chives?
It's really delicious if you mix Chinese
chives and bean sprouts
Chinese chives are rare
Chinese chives seem to be burned
That's right! It seems to be burnt
The food of the Mayashike family is here
I'm really interested in Chinese chives
The barbecue menu prepared by the
members is over, but this alone is a
little lonely
The staff has prepared other ingredients
Now, I would like to have a toast
greeting to the MC of Nakayama
BBQ Bang Bang Kyuzo
Finally, the BBQ they've been waiting
for has begun
The members who eat a lot of meat
But before that
Wake up game quest
I'm a demon
Let's open it
Let's do it
No, I'll do it
I'll read it
Ta-da
When you open this treasure box
Be careful of the monsters
Oh my god
Wow!
Monster?
What is this?
I'm so scared!
Oh my god!
I'm scared!
This is Tato san and Umemoto san who are
making the game called Ebi-chuu.
Last time, we came to ask the members
what kind of game they want to make when
making the game called Ebi-chuu.
What did they come here to do this time?
Based on the ideas you gave me, I made a
demo version of the game.
The game project is progressing
steadily, and the demo version is
completed quickly.
For those who want to play it right
away.
First of all, the best gamer in shrimp,
Mayama.
This shooting game is a challenge.
Tap the red shrimp to launch the enemy's
attack.
The game progresses while shooting down
the enemy that comes to you.
The enemy is shooting at you, so tap.
Tap, tap, tap.
It takes a long time.
It's difficult even if it's normal.
You're good.
I think many adults will be addicted to
this game.
It's very fun.
Thank you very much.
Next is Matsuno.
The game is called Running Game.
It's a game where you run away from
obstacles with a swipe.
Run as long as possible.
I had fun and I thought I could do it
with many people
And I thought it would be more fun if I
could get more items like this
It would be more powerful and I could
run faster
Next is Yasumoto
The game that they are going to
challenge is the popular pulling game
They throw and break the character of
the old man
Oh, it's cute
The house is cute
Please play the game so that as many
blocks as possible fall
I should aim at the bottom
Pull the pin
It's so cute
I feel like I have to help the child
because I'm throwing a person
I'm throwing a child
I threw a child
Kobayashi challenges the last
The fourth game is the block breaking
game
The player will bounce the dharma and
break the blocks
The sound of the beginning is good
It's already started
The player moves the white guitar
The black one is a block, so it can't be
erased, so it becomes green
The white one is white
It's okay to be white
When I play, I get excited and I get
excited
I'm not good at games
The members who experienced 4 games like
this
Which one was fun?
The one that the uncle pulls
The one that the uncle pulls?
I think that it's fun to watch and fun
to play
I actually tried it and it was fun to
pull
The member's favorite was the pulling
game
I will take the ideas you gave me back
to the company and consider it
If there is any progress, I will come
here again
Thank you
The member's opinion is accepted and the
game project is going on
The game project is going on
BBQ!
Bang Bang Kyu!
Finally, the long-awaited barbecue
starts
First of all, the members are free to
grill the ingredients
Isn't barbecue more colorful?
It's just meat
But it's cool because I want to eat
Well, it's barbecue
I'm going to grill it
Wow, everyone is really quiet
I want to eat silently
That's right
Let's eat when it's done
Eat with chopsticks, don't eat with
tongs
I'm eating
Is it salty?
The beef tongue in the middle is
starting to burn
Oh no
Hold the plate wide
Yes
It's really solid
Everyone, there is also barbecue sauce
Yes
There is also a sauce for grilled meat,
a sauce for salt, salt and pepper and
orange juice
It's not orange juice sauce
I want to eat
Beef tongue festival
I think we should cook
Everyone, please ask questions about the
small
Everyone, listen
I'll eating
When are you going the restaurant that
Zack always comes out?
It seems that he is going up
Well, Santai boosted this place
I was bull
Here comes the silver fish!
Hoshina, let's ask them!
Are you going to cook the silver fish?
What is it?
Is there anyone who wants to do it?
I'm excited!
Hoshina, what are you doing?
Hey, Kobayashi!
Go back after shouting something in the
sea!
I'm going to eat shrimp!
Go back after shouting something!
I want to grill it too!
Welcome back!
Go grill it!
Here is Yasumoto!
I want to see the food review of
Takiyue!
Yasumoto, you said a good thing!
The food review of Takiyue starts!
I want to see it!
Please watch the food review of Takiyue!
This tomato looks delicious!
It's juicy!
Tomatoes are sweet and delicious when
they are hot!
This is a failure!
Please remove the face of the kashiwagi!
I can't open my mouth!
I was staring at you before!
Food review is difficult!
Let's go to Nakayama!
I will eat it from now on!
I will eat it with soy sauce!
The bug is climbing!
What happened to the bug?
The bug climbed the tree!
Nakayama also challenges the food
review!
Please review the food
Please look at this plump
I would like to eat
It's baked well and delicious
It's baked well
Eat more
I saw the sea
What sea?
Tokyo Bay
I saw Tokyo Bay
Matsuno is eating with his face down
Matsuno, you are not sleepy, right?
No, I'm not
It's delicious
You look like a drunk man
As time goes by, the members' freedom
increases
And it's a good beef tongue
Matsuno is doing something
What is this?
He is eating
Kobayashi
Kobayashi is not eating anything
Kashiwagi and Hirota are eating
What is the barbecue with shrimp?
What's wrong?
It's delicious
Matsuno is like a drunk man
Next time, we will show you the barbecue
with shrimp
The members are having a hard time
Matsuno is confessing
I always put your picture in the diary
And the dream is coming true
Kobayashi Yasumoto's self-introduction
The tea table is big
The storm of the Shin-Kaito
This program was provided by the sponsor
you are watching.