This week's Ebichu Tastas is graduation
special
In March, a member who graduates from
junior high and high school will be
married with a surprise
Then
Tonight, 30 minutes full of tears
Ebichu Tastas Start
Thank you for watching!
And so, the first episode of the series
was completed.
We'll be adding a lot of new things to
Shiritu Ebisu Middle School!
Ebisu New Justice!
This program is brought to you by the
following sponsors.
Ebisu New Justice
New Justice
It's started.
Ebichu-tan, stand up.
You started with a big smile today.
Yes.
Today, there are few people.
What's wrong with you today?
There are Hoshina, Kobayashi, and
Nakayama.
There is a common point between these
three.
What do you think?
All are idiots.
That's right.
I see.
Actually, it has something to do with
today's theme.
I will announce it.
Today's theme is...
卒業スペシャルです。
この3月でミレイちゃんが高校、
堀子が中学校卒業するということで、
みんなでお祝いしたいと思います。
そうか、なるほどね。
なんで静かなんですか?
なぜかというと、今、
3人は別の部屋で嘘の撮影をしてるからです。
そうなんだ。
そう、実はこの時、
3人を別の部屋に案内して、
偽企画の撮影を行っていた。
Of course, this is something that is not
used at all.
I'm doing a mysterious insert shooting.
I'm trying my best to take pictures of
things that are not used anywhere.
So, during that time, everyone is
preparing for the surprise graduation
party.
Thus, the handmade party venue is
completed.
We will have three people, so
congratulations.
Let's surprise them.
After the fake shooting, the three
people who don't know anything are
waiting at the venue.
They are coming.
I'm nervous.
I'm nervous too.
Will the three people be happy?
Congratulations!
Please come in.
Please cover your face.
Don't be afraid.
Please come in.
Look at her expression.
Wait a minute.
Congratulations!
Thank you!
What?
That's what you mean?
What did you think?
I thought you were going to insert so
much.
What did you do instead of inserting?
I was taking a camera pose.
What are you taking?
No way.
So today, Kobayashi and Nakayama will
graduate from junior high school.
And Hoshina will graduate from junior
high school.
I was going to prank them.
I prepared something for you.
Please look behind you.
What is this?
What the three of them prepared for
junior high school and junior high
school is...
a hand-made drawing of the members.
What kind of content is it?
Let's read it together.
This is a hand-made drawing of the
members.
Let's read it one by one.
Let's go to Hoshina.
First, a message for Hoshina.
Let's read it together.
This is a song.
Mirei-chan, happy graduation.
I'm so proud of you.
I think you're watching Mirei-chan
thinking that she enjoyed every day.
Please teach her how to study.
Mayama.
Please.
Just one word.
It's hard to say.
Mayama is better than Iyami.
I'm scared.
Let's read it.
Mirai-chan!
The great thing about Mirai is the
relationship between idols and your
career.
It's not something anyone can do, but
it's cool.
Mirai is the only one who can stand out
from everyone.
So please continue to cherish your idol
life.
That's great!
How was it, Hosokawa?
I was really surprised.
I thought I was going to graduate from
high school.
I realized it.
Next is a message for Nakayama.
Next is a message for Matsuda.
Riko, congratulations on your
graduation.
When you first met Riko, you were like a
cheerleader.
Why are you making a face like that?
I was worried about your face.
Riko now has grown several times more
than Riko at that time.
I think it's amazing that she has a
solid part.
Please enjoy your high school life like
Riko.
We are back.
Master, master.
Excuse me.
It's the end.
Nakayama-san.
If you like, please play with me after
school.
I will introduce you to some recommended
shops.
Thank you very much.
She is a charisma.
Why are you so polite to the younger
generation?
I will play with you.
Nakayama, how do you like this board?
She drew me a star shape that I like.
She drew me a face.
Her design is amazing.
Thank you very much.
And the last message for Kobayashi.
It's okay. You can come closer.
Then Kobayashi started reading the
message from the board.
It's amazing.
It's a reading of the message.
Please read it.
Please tell us.
The message was read by Matsuno.
He read the message.
The face looks like a shoe.
The inside is small.
It's okay.
I think it's a good thing.
Thank you for watching.
It's scary and you cry fast
There are many
I saw it alone
Yes, I saw it again
Go, go, go
Binta, Binta
I'm going to punch you
I wrote it
Master
What is it?
This is Matsuno's
The main character is here
I'm not your character
I'm not crying because of Yasumoto's
message
This is Matsuno's hand
I'm not yours
Because he took the lead
A message from the master to the student
I want to meet my student
Yes
What kind of atmosphere do you have?
Recently, I feel like I have a moment to
think of my face as a master
Please enjoy JK life
I'm so happy
That's good
I'm crying
Kobayashi, how do you feel?
Everyone made this for you
I'm so surprised
Thank you
You are so fast
The surprise for the three of them was a
great success
Let's wrap up
Yes
Mirei-chan, Kaho-chan, Riko-chan,
congratulations on your graduation!
Yes, that's what happened.
Now, we have a big announcement.
Suddenly, a big announcement from the
show.
Ebichu Tastas will continue after April.
I hope you can make friends
And the broadcast date will change from
April
From April 6th to Wednesday, it will be
broadcast from 24 o'clock
We will power up and show you more
And there is one more announcement
So, Kaiki-san, please
This time, I am Kaiki Ogata
The big announcement from Kaiki Ogata
I am going to graduate from Ebichu
Tastas
I've been doing variety shows, but from
now on, I want to put my power into the
band and work.
I hope to be involved as an artist from
now on.
A sudden graduation announcement.
Actually, he has been a big star since
the first broadcast of the program.
Originally he was a rock band musician.
He wanted to write a song called
Moratorium Junior High School in Ebi-
chu.
He decided to graduate because he wanted
to get involved in music activities.
He has received letters from the people
who love Ebichu more than anyone else.
I'm really grateful to Ebichu Tatsutatsu
for taking care of me for a year.
I'm really grateful to him for welcoming
me, who suddenly appeared and I don't
know the name of the president.
And I was born through this program.
I was a junior high school student at
Haruyasumi Moratorium.
When I announced that I had made a song
for the first time,
I was happy that everyone was happy with
me.
I am happy that I, a musician, was able
to get a chance to perform at Ebichu
Tastas.
I am looking forward to the day when I
can perform at the school concert.
Thank you for your hard work for a year.
Ebichu Tastas, I love you so much that I
could die. I love you.
Let's say hello to Kaiki from the
members.
Do you want to go to the back?
Yes.
When I first saw you, I was surprised
It's not just about the star
It's about everyone
I thought we could get along
But you talked to me on the way home
I felt like we could get along
And then...
I was able to support Yubi-chan a lot
And we all came to the live show
We did a show for a year
And we got along with each other
And we became friends
I'm really happy
And...
I hope we can work together as rock
stars.
Thank you for everything.
Thank you for your continued support.
Okay, Nakayama.
Mr. Ogata,
you said you wanted to do it once.
You said you wanted to do it once.
So, I guess...
I want to do it again with 11 people.
I'm happy.
Thank you very much.
Mayama.
Mr. Ogata.
Yes.
I have something to apologize to you.
What is it?
Well...
I'm sorry to say that I'm a pervert when
I was in the middle of the shoot.
I was really reflecting on myself
thinking about what I said to the
musician.
Ogata-san is always kind.
Even if I'm mischievous, he's kind
enough to say,
I'm not a good person. I'm just a kind
person. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Ogata san, you've done a great job in
the old man's team.
You were the MC of the old man's team,
weren't you?
To be honest, I was very nervous about
what it would be like.
Ayaka chan and I were very...
My heart was beating fast.
But I think we got closer through the
old man's team.
When I first saw you, I thought you were
a little nervous.
But when you removed your makeup, you
were a very kind person.
I felt relieved.
Thank you for your help.
Thank you very much.
Now, Kashiwagi.
Well, Ogata-san is really kind.
When I talked to everyone,
and when I was told that I was in
trouble,
I was very happy that he worried about
me like he did about himself.
I think Ogata-san is really important in
TASTA-SUSU.
I'm honestly not sure what will happen
to Ogata-san.
But Ogata-san's place is always open,
so if you're watching TASTA and think
it's bad,
or if you think it's bad just to have
me,
please come back and get your place.
I understand.
I'll come back.
I'll be in your care.
Thank you.
Ok, Matsumoto
I don't know
What is it?
Do your best
It's like...
I don't know what to do
They are very serious
They think a lot for us
I respect them
I wonder what it is
Maybe one day, we will collaborate with
Ebichu and Hiya
I want to collaborate with Hiya and
other bands
Thank you
It's done
When I got to know Mr. Ogata,
he was a great person.
The song I received was
the song I received when I was in middle
school.
I was worried about how I could sing it.
I was worried about how to sing it.
I didn't know what to do before
recording.
I cried a lot while recording.
When I stood there and recorded it with
Kaiki,
I found something that I liked.
I realized that every song was filled
with love.
I think that listening to a lot of
people
is the only way to repay their
gratitude.
We'll do our best.
Please continue to support us.
Yasumoto
Yes
Yasumoto is a person who is very popular
among the shrimp
But he is very kind and open-minded
He is the most popular among the members
This is his message
I'm sorry
Oh no
I went out a minute ago
I'm so sorry
When we first met, I was scared at first
but I'm a stranger
I'm nervous to talk to an adult
I was scared but I talked to him many
times and he was so kind
I thought I was similar to him
I felt close to him
I'm sorry to an adult but I thought we
were friends
I'm so sorry that we lost each other
I hope we can be friends forever
Of course we are
Thank you
I like you so much
I'll support you from now on
Thank you
How was it, Ogashi-san?
I think I've got everyone's thoughts
So I'll make the most of my experience
here
I'll do my best in rock activities
Ms. Kaiキ, thank you for a year's hard
work
Yes. Thank you
Thank you
Mr. Kaiキ, please wrap it up with your
rock conclusion
Thank you for watching!
Please look forward to the second and
third episode of the song, Ebi Chuu!
I'll do it!
See you again!
Everyone, see you later!
It's like I'm in the front row!
It's like I'm in the back row!
Thank you!
Next time, we will be exploring the Ebi-
Chu!
We will reveal a special Ebi-Chu
member's picture!
Also, the members' sense of beauty will
explode in the Ebi-Chu photo contest!
This program was brought to you by these
sponsors.
Cheese!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.