We used to give out tissues at the
station near Makairi Messe, and we used
to do free live shows at Iomola Makairi
Shintoshin.
At that time, I said that I would do a
live show at Makairi Messe someday.
I'm really surprised that it's now
coming true.
It's not only fun, but we've been able
to overcome everything and keep running
towards our dreams.
It's really hard to join a group that
has already existed, but I think it's a
great thing to join.
Julia, Aki-chan, who decided to join us,
the staff who always thinks about us and
supports us, and the kind publicity
staff who have always been there.
I'm really grateful to everyone who is
here.
Thank you for your support.
I'll do my best.
I'm going to the hospital.
That's all.
Thank you for coming to the Super
Exciting Advertising Club in Makuhari
Messe.
I'm Minako Tanami, the leader of the
Super Exciting Crew.
Thank you.
We would like to ask you to pay
attention to the following.
We would like to say that the photo
shooting, recording, and photographing
in the venue are strictly prohibited.
You can stand up and enjoy yourself
within your seat during the performance.
You cannot watch the performance while
standing up.
We would like to ask you to sit down and
enjoy the performance.
You are not allowed to make a loud voice
during the performance.
You are allowed to clap your hands and
enjoy the performance.
We would like to ask you to pay
attention to the following.
Anyway everyone, I will start soon
Ehehe
I am definitely organising the entrance.
Dad!
Hello everyone!
This is Hori's late birthday speech
I was looking forward to this day
Because everyone is there, we can stand
on the stage today
Let's make the best live together!
Thank you for today!
Then wait for me!
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my
god
What's wrong? What's wrong?
I was there!
What's wrong?
Oh, sorry, sorry, sorry
It's okay, it's okay
It's definitely different, it's
completely different
Let's enjoy it together.
Let's enjoy it.
Let's do our best.
Kanami, Junia, Hitoka, Haruka, Aki,
Hiyori.
We are Takimeki Senden.
Go!
Let's go.
Can you do this?
We'll do our best!
Let's have fun!
Thank you for watching.
This was a promise.
Thank you for watching!
Singing in a boy group
It is a truly realistic atmosphere.
It was the most beautiful fan live I've
ever seen.
I'm glad I've been able to continue this
far.
I think it was a live that I could feel
again.
I'm having fun with the internet.
It's always in our hearts.
I hope I can continue to update and see
a lot of beautiful scenery.
Let's make the best live together.
At the center stage, there were four
screens for 360 degrees.
I saw the penlight through the screen.
I thought it was our live.
I saw a lot of lights.
All the members were surprised.
Before the first song started, we all
went into our own world and shared our
feelings.
It was a dreamlike time.
I thought it was a long time, but it was
a very short time.
It was a very short time.
I was able to realize that it was a
great memory.
It was a strange time.
I was able to shine a lot of lights with
the penlight.
I performed my best to answer the power
of the penlight.
Did you enjoy it?
I couldn't have done it without Sendai
V.
I'm really grateful to everyone.
Thank you very much.
I want to go back to the WAKUHARI MUSE.
I want to do my best to go to a bigger
stage.
I will do my best to keep up with you.
Let's go together.
Let's go to a bigger stage.
Please follow me.
Thank you very much.
When I stood by, there were more
penlights than I imagined.
I thought there were many people who
supported us.
I was happy to see that there were
people who wanted to see us.
I was looking forward to the rehearsal.
I was happy to perform on stage.
I was able to stand on stage with
confidence.
I was worried about what to do if I sang
the wrong song.
I was worried about my hair.
Sometimes I lost confidence.
I was able to stand on stage with
confidence.
I think everyone enjoyed it.
It was a lot of fun.
When I went to the second floor of the
TROCK,
everyone was waving their hands and were
happy.
I was able to see a happy face.
I was glad to be an idol.
I think it's not natural to be asked for
so much.
I was happy to be asked for it.
I was aiming for the star's star.
I was very nervous.
I was in the middle of the stage with
Ha-chan.
I thought it was an important scene.
I thought I couldn't make a mistake in
timing.
I thought I couldn't turn it over.
I was very nervous.
I was able to say,
I was aiming for the star's star.
I hope everyone thinks that I'm shining.
I'm going to go to the second floor.
I'm going to the second floor.
It was fun.
This is Gyosei.
It was announced last December.
It's been 10 months since then.
I just had a live performance at
Makuhari Messe.
There were so many people who were
promoting the song.
There were people who were promoting the
song everywhere.
I'm really impressed by the wonderful
scenery.
I didn't even dream of standing on the
stage at the beginning of the festival.
I wanted to stand on the stage, but I
didn't think I could do it.
It was a dream come true.
I'm not a star singer, but I thought so.
I was able to make it happen.
I thought there was nothing I couldn't
do with you.
I thought there was no limit to my
dreams.
Thank you for always supporting us and
making us stronger.
I felt that I was helped by everyone.
It was a miracle to meet everyone.
I'm glad I met everyone.
It was a day I felt strongly.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
I remember the moment when we all came
out and said,
Let's do our best!
and we got on the center stage and
opened the door.
I was so happy to be able to get on the
truck and go to see you.
There were 12 trucks in total for the
second floor.
The set was gorgeous.
There were two seats on the end stage.
The people on the top of the wing
connected to the second floor.
I was able to perform at a concert hall
of an unimaginable size,
called Wakahari Messe.
I was happy to be able to perform.
I was prepared to be in trouble,
but I couldn't hold back my excitement
when I saw you.
I remember that moment very well.
Thank you very much for always
supporting us.
It's because of you that we have the
courage and confidence.
I think it's all thanks to you.
So, from now on...
I'd be happy if you could continue to
support us.
Thank you so much for today.
Sleep well, eat delicious cookies, and
rest.
See you next time!
See you!
Bye bye!
I felt like I was in a dream that we had
a concert.
I felt like we had a concert even after
the concert.
I felt strange.
But when I saw us dancing on the stage,
I thought it was a good memory.
We went to see everyone.
It was the most popular one-man live
we've ever seen.
I was prepared at first, but I was so
nervous.
I was so nervous.
But I was so happy that many people
thought that they wanted to see us.
I remember it well.
It was fun.
There were so many different scenes in
the live.
It was like a second.
I want to go home and look back on it.
I like the encore.
It was a good time.
Thank you for watching the live.
I was happy.
Because I can be invincible
Thank you for watching!
La La La...
Thank you for showing us such a
beautiful view!
The 9th place of each block is...
Thank you for your hard work!
I'm so happy!
It was very hot!
Thank you very much!
It's over.
Oh my god.
It's like a dream.
I can't feel the time.
Is this the time like a dream?
My hair is not dry at all.
Is it over?
I can still go.
It was really fun.
The moment I was on the stage,
there were so many people.
There were so many people.
I was so happy.
I cried.
Everyone was crying.
Everyone was crying when we were on the
stage.
I cried.
It was wonderful.
I want to do it again.
Let's do our best.
The tour was announced.
20,000 people will be in the same place.
Let's do our best.
Thank you for your hard work.
It was wonderful.
The sea of ​​Andite was beautiful.
It was beautiful.
The scenery of the sea of ​​Andite.
That's right.
It was really clear up to the top.
There was no gap.
I was so happy.
No matter where I wave my hand,
someone will definitely wave it back.
I wanted to be more visible.
I wanted to be more in the audience.
I was so happy that so many people came
to see us.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Let's meet again somewhere next time.
See you again.
The world is shining
I can turn my umbrella and be relaxed
I can't walk without it
Someone is crying somewhere
I'll get wet somewhere again
I hope it's not cold
Someone is crying somewhere
I want to share my feelings
I still have a view in front of me
Let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye, thank you for
yesterday
The city after the rain is colorful
I'll draw a fragment of the future on
the canvas of my damaged heart
It will lead me to you
I can say it now, the reason for my
tears
When I'm lost, I remember right away
Even if it rains, I'll smile
Look, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights after the rain are
sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day, the sound
of the rain drops
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights after the rain are
sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day, the sound
of the rain drops
I wear a rainbow dress