Night view and idols
Now, let's get to the ending
Do you have any announcements?
Yes!
The new EP of Team Shachi, which is
currently on sale,
is called,
What kind of difficulties will we
overcome when we look to the future?
Yes! Among them is...
There are many wonderful songs, such as
Edome, which was composed by Enon
Kawatani,
and Hikari, which I also composed.
Please listen to them!
And on Saturday, December 24th,
we will hold a big concert for One Man
Live!
We are very grateful for this
opportunity.
We will be performing a live show to
show our gratitude for this year.
The venue is Tokyo Shinagawa Stellar
Ball.
Part 1 will start at 2.30pm and Part 2
will start at 6.30pm.
We are a band.
We will be performing live shows, but we
will also be performing acoustic songs.
We will also be performing cover songs.
It will be a live show to show our
gratitude for this year.
I think it will be a mature kind of live
show.
Please come and see us.
There won't be a mini-Suka-san, right?
Please come and see us!
Santa Claus? No, I'm sorry. I'm just a
night watchman.
I'll be careful.
I'm sorry. I'll be grateful.
And on Saturday, January 14th, the year-
end,
We will be at the SAPPLA IDOL FESTIVAL
held at Yokohama Arena.
I'm looking forward to the fact that
SAPPLA IDOL will gather once a year.
I'm going to choose a Cinderella group.
I've always chosen Cinderella.
I don't have a cute impression of
Cinderella at all.
I'm serious about this.
Thank you.
I think I'll be number one if I make a
car marathon.
I don't think I can do a live.
Even if I do, I can't do a full
marathon.
Full marathon is 4 hours, so I don't
think I can run a long distance.
I think it's better to show the cute
side of idols.
I think I'll be getting more and more
tight.
I think the only thing I can do for
Kimoto is to be cute at a long distance.
I can't do it for the manager.
I'm looking forward to it.
And after that, we will have a one-man
live.
On January 28th, Saturday, at Aichi
Prefecture's ZEPP Nagoya.
And on February 25th, Saturday, at
Tokyo's Line Cube Shibuya.
We will have a one-man live.
This is also big.
Thank you.
I'll do something completely different.
ZEPP Nagoya is a Tokyo Kingdom site.
Tokyo Kingdom.
I want to push the Tokyo area a little
bit.
I want to do a live.
And on the Line Cube Shibuya, we will
have a festival called Hachikarnival.
We are working on a world festival.
There is a subtitle called Wakuwaku
without a mask.
It's a carnival that takes off your
mask.
An idol who takes off his mask.
Don't you have to go?
I want everyone to come.
I'll buy it again.
Thank you.
I'm waiting.
Can I give you a present from YAKAN?
Yes.
I'll give you some tea.
Please drink it.
Yay!
I prepared Jasmine tea this time.
I love Jasmine tea.
Really?
I hope you will enjoy it.
Please subscribe to my channel.
It's refreshing!
It's delicious!
It tastes like it's going to sell.
Thank you.
Now that the refreshing wind has blown,
I'd like you to close the last part of
the show.
I'd like everyone to come to our live
event.
If you don't come, I'll make miso and
eat it.
Thank you very much.
See you!
I sent it to Kuribon11153
I'm sure there will be good things
tomorrow.