This week's Ebichu TASTAS is the final
battle of the quiz battle
This is bad, I'm going to destroy it!
I'm going to destroy it!
The crazy quiz that runs through the
house
Challenge the Ebichu history quiz that
you can see in the video
Mega wave
It's different
Even the members can make a mistake
Ebichu TASTAS start
Let's activate the 11th silver year
Moratorium, moratorium, moratorium
Let's add various things to the private
Ebisu junior high school
Ebichu Justice
Bye bye
This program is provided by the sponsor
you are watching
Where can I do it?
I like tofu
It took 10 hours
The second half of the quiz battle
The Mayama team and Hoshina team had a
hot battle last time
They got only 1 point and entered the
second half
Here is the fourth stage
Find and find the first question!
Find the answer!
Thank you!
This quiz is a great way to find the
questions hidden in the room.
You can answer the questions you find
within the limited time.
You can find a lot of questions and
answer them all at once.
You get 5 points for each correct
answer.
You get 20 points for answering the
difficult question with skull marks.
By the way, the problem with skull marks
is that there are hints in the room.
Find the hints and aim for a high score.
It's about to start.
By the way...
What about you, Kyuei?
Who is it?
Kyuei?
Hey, you're in the way!
It's a horse!
He's drinking a lot.
This person is...
It's delicious!
Hey, old man.
If you're in trouble, you can talk to
him and he might give you a hint.
The point is how many questions you can
find within the limited time.
A challenge from the Mayama team.
Let's go!
Mayama team, ready, start!
10 minutes from now.
10 minutes.
First, let's find the question.
Oh, that's fast!
Nakayama is so fast.
It's a bit messy.
Let's start with Nakayama.
Nakayama's question is this.
Who is the composer of 《Moon of the
Factory》composed in 1901?
《Moon of the Factory》
Please answer.
Kikukawa Makoto-san.
Who is it?
Wrong!
Thank you!
At that time, Mayama was in the living
room.
I found two.
And in the toilet, too.
I got three.
Collect a lot and go to the answer seat.
This is a difficult question. If you get
it right, you get 20 points.
The question with skull marks. A chance
to get a lot of points.
Answer all 4 questions from Shikoku.
Kagawa, Kagawa Ehime, Kochi, Tokushima.
Correct! Congratulations.
You are getting closer.
This is a difficult question.
Where did the god who saved Taro
Urashima take him?
Ryukyu Castle.
Correct!
Everyone gets points.
This is a good point.
Snakes are reptiles.
Medaka is a fish.
What kind of penguin is it?
It's a bird.
Correct!
Mayama, you got a lot of points.
Kobayashi, will you continue?
What is the opposite of dangerous?
Dangerous.
Correct!
A wonderful continuous correct answer.
Meanwhile, Hirota...
I'm going to collect the questions
first.
He collects a lot of questions and
answers them all at once.
Look at this! Four cards.
It's a game of cards.
The super-rushing Hirotani Taishi.
Kobayashi is...
For some reason, he looks relaxed and
having fun.
Where should I put this?
Here?
There's nothing.
Ah! Stop!
I found it. I'll go and check it out.
Now, Kobayashi is in charge of answering
the questions.
Here it is.
What is the main ingredient of Japanese
sake?
By the way, this is a difficult
question.
The hint is hidden somewhere.
Wait, I'll look for the hint.
Yes, good luck.
Here is a person who finds the hint
calmly.
Hey, hey, hey.
What is Japanese sake made of?
I wonder if you can see it clearly.
Where is it written?
Where is it?
I found it.
He found the hint from the bottle of the
middle-aged man.
He dashes to the answer seat.
What is the main ingredient of Japanese
sake?
The answer is...
Rice.
Correct!
I'll go somewhere else.
Go somewhere else!
What should I do?
How many did you bring?
It's too easy.
Let's see.
This is a simple question.
How many legs does a squid have?
10!
Correct!
Hirota's time-consuming strategy is
going well.
He is getting more correct answers.
And...
Correct!
You are making a lot of money.
This is a difficult question.
What is the date of the birthday of the
shooting star, Chuei?
What day was it?
Can I ask?
Sure.
Grandpa!
Hirota is getting closer to the shooting
star.
I'm...
I'm Chuei's birthday.
I'm the same age as the day before the
amateur game.
I don't know.
It's the same day.
Meanwhile, Nakayama...
I'm getting off.
She looks around the first floor to see
if there's anything left to find.
It's so cute.
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Oh, no!
Now, they're going to try the quiz.
It's a fail.
It's a shame.
Please give me another one.
Another one.
The three classic Wien composers, Mozart
and Haydn.
Who is the other one?
Why do I know this one?
It's difficult.
Yes.
Beethoven.
Correct.
Congratulations.
Everyone, it's the last minute.
The last minute.
The time is coming.
If you get it right, you'll get a good
score.
Hirota asks his grandfather about his
birthday.
I was born a few days before the 1st of
August festival.
It was July 28th.
It was 29th.
29th.
I got it.
This time, he got a hint and went to the
answer seat.
The one from the last time.
It's the one from Nagariboshi Chuei.
July 29th.
The correct answer is...
5 seconds left.
4, 3, 2, 1.
Time's up.
The correct answer is 5 seconds.
Mayama Team has won a lot of games with
difficult questions.
Will Hoshina Team be able to answer more
than that?
Hoshina Team, ready, start!
First, please look at the question
Let's go
So fast
Where is it?
It's fast
Amazing
Cute
Let's go to the question
It's a simple question
Which country's territory is Hawaii?
America
Correct
So fast
Hoshina Team is developing fast from the
beginning
There it is
Thank you for watching!
First of all, I'll go first
I'll go first
Are you okay? Calm down
She brought two
It's a difficult question
What is the main ingredient of soy
sauce?
Soybean?
Correct
Let's go for another one
Let's go for a simple question
What comes after the alphabet O?
P
Correct
Thank you
Meanwhile, Yasumoto is in a room where
no one is looking for
There it is
Thank you for your viewing
Let's go
They are going to answer the questions
first
Oh, Yasumoto has a lot of questions
First, it's Azulea
Why did you try to push it?
Let's go
This one too
Yasumoto
Yasumoto, you look good in Azulea
It's written
What is the name of the primitive fish
that was discovered in 1938 and is
called a living fossil?
Jack
No
It's a sea turtle
Yes, you are correct
This is a difficult question
What is the name of the day of the only
holiday in January?
It's easy
Sea Day
Correct
They are getting more correct answers
and Yasumoto gets a lot of points
On the other hand
I don't know, it's difficult
It's fun
Matsuno is having fun even though she
can't find the answer
Matsuno is coming with high tension
Everyone is coming with good points
I'm out
He regains his composure and goes to
find the problem again
Grandpa, I'm reading a book
He looks around the room carefully
What?
I feel like I found it.
I found it!
Oh no, I'm going to destroy this!
I'm going to destroy this house!
Hey, old man!
What?
Where is it?
I found it!
I found it in the fridge!
Hoshina team is still looking for the
quiz.
Now, hurry up!
Here's a simple question.
What is the food that Tomotaro gave to
the staff?
Kibi dango!
Correct!
Oh, this is a difficult question.
Please write the kanji for the fish.
What?
There's a hint in this house.
Are you okay?
Have a good day!
Hoshina went straight to the kitchen
when she heard the word.
Hoshina team is looking for the answer.
Then...
I found it.
Yonomi found a fish.
I found something.
I found a yellowtail.
I found it.
I can't find a yellowtail.
She wrote the answer and went to the
answer table.
I wrote it.
This is a yellowtail.
I found it.
The balance is not good.
It's a wash.
That's right.
And the last minute.
Matsuno hasn't answered the quiz yet.
I found it.
Will she get the correct answer?
The answer is here.
I found it.
It's coming!
Oh, Matsuno-san is here
Matsuno-san is here
Is it your first time here again?
It's a simple question
What is the title of the literary work
which the famous sword called Hatrash
appears?
I love it
Grandpa
I don't know about your grandpa
Matsuno-san cries out to Ichimoku-san
and Chu Eiji-san
It's a Spanish dog
It's not a Spanish dog
I got it
The previous question is about Hatrash
It's a panda
It's correct
Matsuda-san, you did it
5 seconds left
4, 3, 2, 1
Time's up
I don't know
No, no, no
As a result, the Mayama team which got
the most points is the winner
The series battle is finally coming to
the final stage
The serious fast-forwarded Ebitune
History Quiz!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Be quiet!
I'm a little good at this.
The history quiz where you can look back
on the history of Ebitune with the
video.
Everyone, please think about it
together.
If you get it right, you get 10 points.
Hoshina team, there's a good chance of a
comeback.
Here we go!
Question!
In December 2013,
Ebichu made her major debut as a
Japanese artist.
At the time of her first year and seven
months,
she had the fastest record in the
history of Japan.
She held her own Saitama Super Arena
concert.
Now, what was the first song that was
sung in this concert?
《Unidentified Junior High School
Student》
Correct!
Wow!
I remember that!
Here is the video.
What is the memorable song from her
debut?
The correct answer is...
Mikakurin Middle School X
Let's continue
Here is the question
The correct answer is...
Famiyan of Niigata Risation Lyrics
The two songs that you sang at the
encore, please answer
Mayama TV
Chichinp câmlâ map også hai thankful
Yes, it is.
It's the world!
It was last year, 2015
We went to Niigata too
Yes, we went to Ojiichan
We went to Ojiichan
Do you remember the star dance?
We danced to it
You danced to it
I see
Let's continue
Question
On April 15th, 2014, the joint departure
ceremony of the private Ebisu junior
high school held at the Japanese Martial
Arts Center
You are here now
What is the costume that Kobayashi
Nakayama wore at the encore of
L'Ondedon?
Let's say it ourselves
Lotus root and tendon
Correct
I remembered this
I remember this
Why is it lotus root and tendon?
Because it's London
Lotus root and tendon
It's all in Japanese
It's not a special meaning
It was a stupid reason
Let's go on
In 2015, you performed a non-stop medley
in Kishidan Banpaku
How many songs did you perform non-stop?
Hoshina team
29 songs
Correct
I know this
You have to think where to press
Good luck
They both got 20 points
From now on, they will go into a deeper
question
Here we go
Question
Where did Ebichuga perform the super
ceremony for her major debut?
But
Isn't it the day before?
Please answer
Rakua
Unfortunately, it's wrong
The place where you performed the super
ceremony was in Lazona Kawasaki
Where did you perform at the end of
Indies?
The end of Indies?
Where did you perform your solo concert?
Please answer
La La Porte or Shionoha
Wrong
Hoshina team
Megawave
Wrong
It's not cool to remove the question
with the smile on your face
So
Takumi team is incorrect
The correct answer is
The song that made the girls' hearts
beat faster
It was Akasaka Blitz
The singer was 13 years old at the time
UiUiC
The song that made the girls' hearts
beat faster
Akasaka Blitz
Let's start the question
This question is from the latest album,
Anarchy
In the music video of Unicorn's Abenon-
san, everyone is wearing sunglasses but
Kobayashi's sunglasses is...
Mayama team, you were faster
England flag
Correct!
Where is Kobayashi's sunglasses from?
England
You got it at the right timing
I'm so sorry
I was so close
Question
Oh my ghost
Even if I become a villain, in the music
video
What is the word written on the tag on
Matsuno's forehead?
What is it?
Mayama team
Abalone?
Wrong
White-spotted grouper?
I remember my own name
I see
Matsuno-san, you have a chance
The hint is Yohji-juku-kei
Zujo-chui
Correct
Matsuno-san, do you remember?
I don't remember even if you say it now
Zujo-chui is a word that fans wear
I see
The last question
The super maniac question
In January 2015
The 7 days war between Fujii and Yome
Fujii's talk event was
We are the Sakaba Houroki
But, the talk event that was introduced
The ramen shop that the principal went
to
Nakamoto
Mokotanmen Nakamoto
Thank you remember
Then please see the very rare video of
the first time on TV
Two people who challenge the food record
of the ramen with a high-end atmosphere
It's delicious, it's definitely
delicious
Eat the recommended spicy ramen
It's going to be like this
I can't eat it
Nakayama also challenges spicy ramen
Are you okay?
It was Matsuno and Nakayama who were not
hungry and did not report
The final stage has ended. What will
happen if we add up the points from the
history quiz?
As you can see
So the team that won the Magical Shrimp
Tora Quiz is Mayamo team!
The reward is fruits!
Wow!
It's like a feast!
It's over!
Hoshina is about to cry.
Is this delicious?
Hoshina, is this delicious?
Shut up!
Next time is...
Kobayashi Kaho's birthday solo live
special!
I'm about to cry.
I'm too nervous.
Kobayashi's first solo live.
What will happen?
Coming up next!
We have a surprise guest!
Our game, the game, is finally released!
Please try it out!
Let's go to the theater!
Super macho!
I'm so nervous.
This program was provided by the
sponsor.
I'm so nervous.
I'll do my best.
Will you be invited to the quiz show?
Please!