Let's start singing the song.
Let's sing.
The third day of training.
Nine girls are struggling with singing.
I think they are practicing for the sleep time.
I think it's a little strange.
So, the students who have been dancing and singing non-stop,
have prepared a special program.
We have a special teacher.
Hello, I'm Natsu Nakanishi.
Nice to meet you.
We invite the comedian Natsu Nakanishi to challenge the variety show.
The winner is Chiba Ken's high-class strawberry.
Rin-chan, Rin-chan.
Rin-chan, you can do it.
Yes, Rin-chan.
That's right.
What is the contents of the box?
First, Kashiwagi will show us the example.
We can see the contents of the box.
Please open it.
What is it?
The contents of Kashiwagi's box is here.
Wow! This is awesome!
This is...
Suddenly?
Hirata, be careful.
It's dangerous.
What?
What should I do?
If you touch it, it will be a big deal.
It will be a big deal?
It will be.
You have to be careful.
What?
Let's start.
What is inside Kajiwagi's box?
Ready?
How is it?
Wait.
It's dangerous.
Be careful.
Cut it.
Oh, no.
It's dangerous.
Are you okay?
Be careful.
If you stimulate it too much...
It's dangerous.
Where is it?
A little bit more.
I'm scared.
No, no.
It's cold.
It's cool.
What is it?
Do you have such a feeling?
Is it cool?
Is it water?
Is there water here?
Is it a water bed?
The answer is a water bed.
It's strange.
Oh, no.
Be careful.
A little bit more.
What is it?
Kajiwagi's box is open.
Be careful.
It's cold.
What is it?
It's wet.
Kajiwagi, that's good.
You are touching some skin.
I think I should press it harder.
You should press it harder.
I will press it harder.
One, two, three.
What is it?
Kajiwagi, did you find out what's in the box?
It's a sea urchin.
That's a pity.
It's not a sea urchin.
The contents of the box are these.
Is this a tail?
That's good.
Kashiwagi showed a perfect reaction as a model.
However, when the students challenged...
The contents of Rina's box are these.
It's a little strange.
Let's start! What is the contents of Rina's box?
Ready, start!
Wow!
Ebi!
It's a magic!
You have 1 minute to finish.
Are you okay?
Be careful!
It's not this one!
It's not that one!
What are you touching now?
The wall!
No, not that one!
Not that one!
It has eyes!
It has mouth!
It's wet inside.
Why don't you answer me?
She's been giving too many answers that are too free to ignore the sample.
Nakanishi, who has been in the field for 20 years, has been working hard.
But she has been able to have a good time.
I'll give you strawberry Chiba Berry!
Thank you!
I want to eat it!
I have a campaign.
Everyone is having fun, but this is an audition.
I'm going to make you feel the heat today.
Oh, that's right!
This is an audition!
But the students had to decide on a way to be fresh...
The song that was added the day before, Yuwakushitaiya.
To complete it, they practice it in each unit.
It looks fun.
Yuwakushitaiya, the second part is over.
And then..
Nonoka~~
Delivery outside
Rinno chloro
The
Here we go.
And...
Over there.
Akira's place.
This is the center.
This way?
The teacher who drew the line.
Then, let's count.
1, 2, 3.
Thank you.
We have to go to the second floor without turning our hands.
9 students are 없Ur Jian gurus with all the supportive tubes.
I forgot awand에는
Japanese words
Let's do it from the beginning.
Did you see the difference here?
After 3days with these dislike woods...
They shape the units few days before.
As one of the real groups, they make the combined units.
turn back
Okay, so that is enough
now we go to the next stage
come up
that dough is too much
The subject is Denim!
The youngest Mai remembers the dance in one phrase.
N效a
I'm scared.
I like the song when I see the dance.
But when the song starts, it's a big deal.
I'm not scared at all.
I'll practice with Tatsuya.
I have to practice.
It's dangerous.
See you tomorrow.
I can only go to the airport.
I want to go to the airport.
It's a little bit strange.
Yes.
The dance is also strange.
I will practice today.
I will do it with all the energy.
The final screening is at 10pm the next day.
Considering the remaining time, the time to sleep is short.
The final exam is tied with a hard bond.
But the 9 contestants are rivals.
It's cruel, but only the passers-by can become the shrimp-chewers.
The last one is the only one.
It's a battle with yourself.
The final day of training camp.
The unit is shown their performance at 10 o'clock.
The previous actions are free.
The first person to come to the gym at 7 o'clock 52 minutes is...
I couldn't remember the dance at all.
I only did it in the gym class.
Rina had no experience in dancing.
Even when the task was announced, she could only watch the video.
But she showed great growth in this training camp.
The reason is...
I was just fighting
Because she was trying her best to get here
I'm sleepy
What are you doing?
I'm flying
I'm tired
Midnight
Even the
These three are...
I want to be like Ebichu and I want to be like her.
I want to be like her and I want to be like her.
I think if I perform with confidence, I can convey it.
I want to be full of confidence.
I want to be like her and I want to be like her.
Today is the last day, so I have to do my best.
I think I will not be able to meet Ebichu.
I was crying that I would not meet Ebichu.
I feel less excited now.
I feel more excited now.
I don't know when the announcement will be.
I'll do my best.
But I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it
But I don't want to regret it.
And the Green Salad team?
I'm nervous. I want to make it up to her.
I'm a little worried.
I'm worried about the high notes of the song.
Today is the last day, so I want to be able to show my best.
I want to be able to smile all the time.
I want to be able to perform perfectly.
I woke up at 4am.
But my head is not spinning, so I thought I made a mistake.
I'm worried about the high notes.
I want to be confident and perform well.
I'll do my best.
I have only 7 hours.
I'll do a lot of things.
I'll do this side.
No, I'll do this side.
Thank you.
I'm not doing well.
I want to go to the park.
I'm not doing well. I want to go to the park.
I don't want to reveal my true self
But I want to show that I am real
Then, she came there
Good morning
Yuno came late
I don't know what to do
I...
I feel strong
I will do my best
I see
She has no hesitation
She has strong feelings in her heart
I did it until 2pm yesterday
Today I woke up at 6am
I couldn't do the dance I wanted to do
I was thinking about it
I couldn't do this part of the dance
I couldn't do this part after that
I did it many times and I did it fast
I will do my best
I will definitely be in Ebichu
I will go to see everyone
Please
Subscribe to our channel