Ebichu's video
I think Riko-chan is probably fine
I haven't drunk yet
When we were together
I was about to get drunk
I was totally fine
I don't know how much I can drink
But I think I can drink in a person
I think I can drink in a person
I don't know how much I can drink
I don't know yet
I don't know what to drink
I don't know what to remember
I don't know what goes with it
I don't know if it goes with it
I haven't drunk yet
But I drank the most when I drank with
Kao-chan until now
Yeah
I don't know
I don't know what I can do after that
What is the secret of being 20?
Can I use this?
Sure
What is the secret of being 20?
What?
I'm 20, right?
It's not something I can learn
It was the same in my 19th or 20th year
I was doing a lot of things
So I want to continue that
I see.
Autumn is fast too.
I've been doing it for a long time.
You've been doing it for a long time.
Autumn is fast too.
I'm not sure if I'm getting more
interested in it or not.
I don't have any plans, but since I
started drinking,
I've been having fun and nothing has
changed.
Really?
I'm too happy.
I see.
I've been drinking all the time.
I've been walking around in the street.
Oh, no.
I don't know if I'm drunk.
I'm drunk.
Even if I say it, no one will
understand.
That's not right.
But I can understand what you're saying.
I'm totally fine.
My body is fluffy.
That's not good.
Then I'm fine.
I don't know if it's good or bad.
I'm drunk, but I still don't know.
You'll know.
I don't know yet.
I'm feeling good now.
After this, I'll go to the water.
I have to go to the water.
I know what you're saying.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm going to faint.
I'm talking, but I'm going to faint.
If you notice, you may be sleeping.
I'm not going to faint.
I'm going to sleep.
Really?
I can't bother you.
I have to get into the water.
I see.
I'm getting into the water.
You're good at it.
You're having fun because you're here.
You're making me drink.
You're having fun.
I think you two are drunk.
You're eating too much and sleeping.
It's funny when you're sleeping.
It's funny.
I want to sleep while I'm sleeping.
I want to sleep.
I want to sleep early.
I'm waiting for everyone to sleep.
Are you sleeping?
I'm sleeping.
Why do you sleep so much?
I can't remember the moment I sleep.
You're a good girl.
You have a great smile.
When I was in the bathroom,
I saw your face.
You have a smile on your face.
Your mouth is wide open.
Your face is wide open.
I don't know who said it.
Rikko wants to get angry when she
drinks.
I want to get angry at Rikko.
There are many people who want to get
angry at Rikko.
I want to get angry at Rikko.
There are many people who want to get
angry at Rikko.
What will happen to Rikko?
I want to get angry at Rikko.
I'm drunk.
I'm angry.
I want to drink.
It's funny.
What will happen to Rikko?
I'm drunk.
I thought you were drunk.
I don't know what's going on.
I don't care if I don't have a wallet.
I can go home.
I'm curious.
Are you curious?
I don't remember, but I'm at home.
I sleep on the street.
I was young when I was sleeping on the
street.
I'm getting drunk.
I should have been weaker.
I'm drinking.
I can drink, but I don't drink.
I haven't drunk.
I don't want to be seen.
I'm saying that because there's no one
around.
I'm drunk.
I'm not at my limit.
Everything else will come.
Nothing can beat The
созд
I'm watching Shigходитłbymda if.
I couldn't help it until it was over.
I couldn't help it because it's
I'm also a little bit drunk.
I'm looking forward to it, but you two
are not that drunk.
You're laughing.
I don't know if it's fun.
When everyone drank together.
The staff.
I haven't really drunk with all the
members yet.
If you do it once first.
What happens then?
It depends on the person.
I don't think it's good to drink with
the members.
Are you still going?
What?
I just go home and sleep.
If you go home and sleep.
It's still 6.30.
Isn't it early?
Let's go for a short time.
I'm still drunk.
I'm still in a hurry.
If you don't have a lot of staff, it's
hard to go home.
The sake that Ikura-sensei gave me was
easy to drink.
It's a waste?
I noticed it and drank it.
Really?
I thought the sake was scary.
I opened it.
Is it really okay to drink it as it is?
That's right.
Is it okay to drink it as it is?
I put it in my mouth.
The dance teacher gave me this.
I was surprised.
It's fast.
It's almost 7.30.
It's almost 9.
I'm full.
Is it okay?
It's okay.
I don't care anymore.
I'm full.
Is it okay to drink it as it is?
Can you go home?
I'm okay.
I'm worried.
If I drink this, I'll be drunk.
I'm still scared.
It's a language.
I see.
I heard that people who forget their
memories become Marlion.
I understand.
I heard that there are 20 types.
I don't know which type it is.
Maybe I'm Marlion type.
I'm Marlion type.
I don't know.
I haven't said that yet.
Thank you.
It's delicious.
The thumbnail is cute.
It's tea.
It's chamomile.
Chamomile.
Chamomile is chamomile.
It's chamomile.
Chamomile.
It's a sweet version of chamomile.
What is the worst thing that happens
when you drink one more?
Do you mean that you become Marlion?
I'm Marlion.
I drank six cups of tea.
You mean that you become dark.
I'm getting sweaty from the sixth cup.
You're strong.
I'm getting better.
You're conscious of it.
You're conscious of it, but you're
getting sweaty.
I'm getting sweaty.
I'm getting better.
You're conscious of it.
I don't know how far you can go.
I'm sorry.
I'm getting better.
Why do you say such a funny thing?
I saw it.
I'm getting better.
Don't make me laugh.
Why?
I'm getting better.
Don't make me laugh.
Rikuo is fun.
I did it.
When Fuji-san is here.
Which bridge is this?
This is the last one.
I'm doing it in the middle.
I'm doing it.
The last one.
It's delicious.
I chose the one with fat.
Rikuo is enjoying it.
I'm not.
I think I'll drink with Mayama and
Hoshino.
I haven't drunk with them yet.
I'm not going to lose.
Rikuo can win the war.
I'm looking forward to it.
I think I can drink with Kaori-ko.