Ebichu Tastas new project
Original mini corner festival
Ebichu members challenge three original
mini corners
In the last week's broadcast
Let's write with Fuji-san
I will solve it with chopsticks
Both are the best in Japan
The unexpected talent of the members
explodes
This week, the legendary corner is
finally on air
Yasumoto Kobayashi is laughing
The food is sweet
And the second half of Matsu's Kashiwagi
walk
This is a little bit of a
Super rare live video full of
Ebichu Tastas start
Ebichu members challenge three original
mini corners
Ebichu Tastas
This program is provided by the sponsor
Mini corner festival in Ebichu
First of all
We are waiting for
Kashiwagi
walk
Yeah
Karake
Karake is here
New sensation walk program that runs out
without thinking that you will find
something delicious
It's hot
Hot
It should convey the charm of Tagoshi
Ginza shopping street
Korake
Wait a minute
Only scenes that are caught in food
Well, what kind of walk will it be this
time?
The beginning of the second half
One is Karaage, Koroke and eating
Searching for the next target
I'm just eating for now
I'm also interested in the tea shop over
there
Tea shop
Here
Oh, is it after eating?
I wonder if it's full
Hello
How are you, mom?
Hey, dad
This is amazing
All of this is here
Wow
Is this boss?
Dad, have a nice day
You went
Yes
Wow
But you are a cute girl
Thank you
Do you know each other?
I don't know
You don't know
I got a little bit of a laugh
She is a comedian called Chibinoppo
You are wrong
Idol group
Idol
Chibinoppo
Well, you got it right
You can't lie, Mr.Takiue
But meeting such a person is a great way
to take a walk
Is there something over there?
I want to go
There is something
Really
Another new meeting
Hello
Oh, you
What are you doing?
Are you a cat?
I'm a tiger
Tiger?
Which one?
Cat
Was it a cat?
Oh, sorry
This is a mascot of the shopping street
Togoshi Ginjirou
Over there
Over there?
What?
Something is round
Something to eat round
It seems that there is a recommendation
Let's get a guide
Where is it?
It's round
It's cute
What is it?
Ginjirou's recommended round food
What is this?
It's a Bokkyoku melon bread.
Bokkyoku melon bread.
Is it good?
It looks good.
Bokkyoku melon bread with frozen cream.
It's perfect for hot summer.
Let's eat it now.
Ice cream is good because it's hot.
Is it cold?
Yes, it is.
How is it, Mr. Tashiwagi?
Is it refreshing?
Refreshing lemon.
It's a little sour, but the melon bread
is sweet.
It's good to mix it well.
Lemon.
I'm very satisfied with the kind of
people who recommend Ginjiro.
See you again, Ginjiro.
He continues his walk with melon bread.
Where are you going next?
I'm going to a good town.
There are many people who walk around
here.
This is a feature of this town.
What is this?
It's a Yaki-shoranpo.
Wait a minute.
This is it.
Yaki-shoranpo.
I found it again.
This is a Chinese dish called Ryuki.
Yaki-shoranpo is said to be sold 1000
times a day.
Of course, both of them will eat.
It looks delicious.
Please prepare meat soup with sweet
sauce on top.
First, make a hole and enjoy the meat
juice.
Look, it's coming out.
Great.
Do you drink this?
I drink a lot of meat juice.
It's delicious.
I'm about to cry.
I don't know how to express it.
It's too delicious.
The meat is very juicy.
It's delicious.
How do you put so much juice in it?
Why?
I'm sorry, but I'm asking the shop
staff.
Mr. Kashiwagi's curiosity for food is
not there.
Yaki-shoranpo.
I'm excited.
It was delicious.
Next is...
Recycle soup?
Did you finally get interested in food?
It looks interesting
The fifth visit of the first walk in
Kashiwagi is...
Recycle shop ZAKKU
Let's go shopping after dinner
Amazing
Meanwhile
Yes, Mayama
This year's kabumaki is delicious
I was doing it
Come on
Team Ogiri is addicted to monoboke
I don't know what I'm doing
What is Yasumoto Kobayashi team?
The legendary corner is finally starting
Please see
It started
Yasumoto Kobayashi team
This project is
Socialist in private school
Yasumoto Ayaka and Kobayashi Kaho
I'm thinking of discussing the current
social problems
It's not a prank today
I think it's not
I don't think it's a prank
Please see this decoration
It's very luxurious
It's different
There is a proof
It's a real life
The world is asking for your opinion
My daughter is watching today
I want to show you a good place
As a mother
Yes
Yasumoto Kobayashi's talk
The first topic is about the 18-year-old
election
What kind of opinion will come out of
the two socialists who are in the middle
of the shrimp?
Young people don't go to the election
I don't go
Even if you are pulled down by this
18-year-old
It's also aiming to increase the voting
rate
What do you think young people will go
to the election?
I want that opinion
What should I do?
How to increase the voting rate of
Kobayashi
I think it's good to put politicians in
their favorite things
What kind of food do you like?
I like gyoza
Gyoza?
If I have a gyoza,
I like chives, Chinese cabbage, and
ground meat
I can choose the one I like the most
Is gyoza included in Chinese cabbage?
Yes, it is
I see
If I were to vote for gyoza,
I would vote for the one with the skin
on it
I think it's good
You mean the one with the skin on it?
It's important to choose the one with
the skin on it
If your hands get dry,
gyoza will be ruined
If gyoza is ruined,
it means that Japan will be ruined
Japan will be broken
That's a great idea
If gyoza is ruined,
it means that Japan will be ruined
What are you talking about?
But that's what it is
Fukuo starts from this small place
Everyone, think hard
It's hard
They want to change Japan
They started to speak out of their own
free will
First, Ayaka Yasumoto's voice-recording
broadcast
I'm Ayaka Yasumoto, who has no free time
Everyone,
instead of getting into small things,
I think you can look at things from a
bigger place
and think about things
Ayaka Yasumoto
Uji uji uji
Is it like this?
It's wonderful
She was saying uji uji
Next, Kobayashi Kao's voice-recording
broadcast
I'm Kobayashi
I want to change this country
I want to improve my studies,
but I don't want to be like that
I want to increase my art and music
Wonderful
That was the speech
No, this is not good
I think I'm good at making secretaries
I think it's better to do it in a back-
up way than to go forward
Please let me be a secretaries
Why are you so humble?
How about making a system?
There is a leader, a leader of the era
There is a secretaries who support it
That's right
Cheese
This is definitely a hero
No, it's not a hero
Everyone, it's time
Thank you for coming to the Yatsumoto
Kobayashi TG Group
Goodbye
After the long talk, Kashiwagi Matsu
also went to the home town
There is a secretaries
It's a secretaries
Isn't it that?
I don't know
Let's talk
Where have you been?
How are you?
I'm fine
It's hot and hard
I'm scared
What are you doing?
Hinata, come here
It seems that Matsuno found something
I think I can do it
After this, he found a great treasure
She is a goddess of wood
Goddess of wood
In addition, Ebichu collaborated with a
gorgeous musician
Behind the stage
Fighting
Hinata, come here
Isn't this the evolution of the 100th
child?
This
Which one?
No
This is the evolution of the 100th child
Did it evolve here?
It's amazing
What is this?
I don't know
Can I wear this?
Kashiwagi is interested
Let's take it
Can I wear it?
Are you okay?
How much is this?
Are you going to buy it?
30,000 yen
Please wear a 30,000 yen mask
It's okay
Look at the camera
It looks good on you
It looks like a goddess
It looks like a god
I don't want to see it
Matsuno, do you want to try?
Matsuno is also making her debut
Please look this way
It's okay
I'm scared of the top
Okay
It suits you
Matsuno looks the best
What is your name?
I'm the goddess of wood
The goddess of wood
I came to teach you the importance of
wood
Where did you come from?
I'm the forest of wood
Forest of wood?
How old are you?
38 years old
You're quite old
They both like this face
It's spread quite a bit
30,000 yen
Buy it!
How much is it if I buy it with cash?
I'll pay you right now
20,000 yen
Really?
It's quite cheap
It's the cheapest
I can't buy it
It's up
It fits
Use it for live shows
Theater
K-drama
That's it?
Wait a minute
The manager is surprised
It's like, is it true?
That's true
She really bought it
I hope she has a way to use it
It's a dragon
Yay
It's not a PS
Why is it a dragon?
It's a dragon
Thank you for the show, Mr. Takiue
The first time in Ebichu
The recording of the mini corner
festival is over
What was the member's response?
How was the big-cut team?
Did you do well?
It was good
More than I imagined
All four of us were answering properly
We are
We have more time
This time
You were more into the social issues
I was
I wasn't really into it
No
How was it?
Oh, it's us?
We have a souvenir for everyone
What?
Yes, yes
Then, please take it
There's a Yaki Shoronpo today
It's the same
Hello
Who are you?
I'm the goddess of the sun
It's the goddess of the sun
The goddess of the sun has come
Where did the goddess of the sun come
from?
From the sky above the Tokyo and Minato
These two have bought this
Takenchi bought it
That's right
Please use this
I can buy it
Takenchi can buy it
Then, it's like I bought it myself
Everyone, you have a bad idea
So, if you add a mini corner to Ebichu
The flowers are high
Who is this?
Who?
I'm the goddess of the tree
I'm the goddess of the sun
I'm the goddess of the sun, everyone
In a sense, it will be a godly meeting
Above the sky above the Tokyo and Minato
From here, Ebichu Tastas special edition
Ebichu participated in the festival in
June this year
The camera is attached to the festival
Of course, the live performance
Where are you?
Yatsui Festival
Also infiltrated behind the stage
The video will be released in two weeks
The festival that Ebichu participated in
Yatsui Festival
The entertainment festival of music and
comedy that Yatsui Ichiro-san, a comic
book comedian, is hosting
Thank you
Before the show, Yatsui Ichiro-san and
Ike-chan
And the historical Ike-chan visited
Ebichu's music night
It's getting smaller
It's great
I got a good atmosphere
In the audience
The appearance of the shooting star
Chuu-e
It seems that it was completely private
Chie is there too
Please
I'm sorry
Is it a costume?
It's a costume
It's a nightmare
The highlight of this live show is the
collaboration with the talented
musicians of Edichu
Please say fighting when I say
Fighting
Where are we?
Let's get it!
Edichu
Fighting
Will you come out together?
I told Eike too but I'm scared
I'm scared
I can do it
It's scary
I'm scared
She's nervous before the live show
Then
Water
Finally, 5 minutes before the live show
I'm nervous
I'm nervous because it's a collaboration
with everyone
It's a festival
I want to have fun with everyone like
Edichu
OK
I'll push the play button
It's starting
Heatchu
The first collaboration with Ebichu
is...
The Indian folk instrument Tabra player,
Yuzan
The Ebichu song, Chupacabra
That's all for this week
Ebichu Tastas is the first time Ebichu
has a stay-at-home meeting
At night, they have Takopa
Do you want chocolate kebabs?
No
And in pajama talk...
I'm going to have a love story
Ebichu, love story, open
And then, the hot Yatsui Fest, the
second half
You can do it!
Ju-e!
Yes
I told you not to call me
Special collaboration, coming up!
Let's go!
The second half
This program was brought to you by these
sponsors
Be careful of your hands
What's wrong?
Excuse me, I'm just asking, can I have a
cut?
It's not bad!
Thank you for watching!