Ebichu Tastas started in April this
year.
There is a little left this year.
With the previous famous scenes, the
10th episode of Ebichu Tastas was
announced.
How many times did you answer?
I did it.
In addition, the 10th announcement in
the second half of the program.
The biggest news of the program that the
members have not been informed.
What is it?
The 10th announcement of Ebichu Tastas.
Add various things to private Ebisu
Middle School
Ebisu Justice
How can you work in a useless place?
This program is provided by the sponsor
you see
Run away from the cameraman
I hate that guy
Thank you for watching
This week, we have big news about
EriChuTastas
The current line-up is as you can see,
such as the birthday party of Kando
The next news is this
This one
The 5th Nakayama Riko's tear interview
This is the interview for the part-time
job
This is because Kobayashi imitated it
A famous saying was born
Let's ask Kobayashi to do it
I don't like that guy
This famous saying was born from
EriChuTastas' interview
They thought this interview was for the
customers
They said hello to the customers at the
cafe
Welcome to the Angel Reacts Cafe
Hoshina, Yasumoto, Matsuno, and the
interviewer
Then
That's it for the interview
Thank you
Sorry
Please show us your skills
Do your best
What's wrong?
Sorry
Could you show us?
Sure, it's okay
It's okay?
Yes
Please show us
Welcome to Smile Cafe
That's it for the interview
Thank you
After the interview, the famous saying
was born
This is the moment
Wait, everyone is coming
I don't like this
What's wrong?
What happened to Nakayama?
I don't like this
This famous saying was born from
Kobayashi
You're doing this with your family,
right?
I finally debuted as a sister
Congratulations
You're doing this with your sister?
I'm doing this with my mom
Kobayashi's mom is doing this too?
I'm more
By the way, what kind of situation is
Kobayashi's mom using this?
When my older brother is in a club and I
have to wake up early in the morning
I say, I don't like that guy
Because you have to wake up early too
Good, you're using it properly
Nakayama, how do you feel about being
imitated like this?
Well, I'm glad that I'm still being used
like this
Why aren't you a manzara? I was
surprised
Why are you a manzara? I feel like I'm
going to be evaluated
10 big news of Ebichu Tastas
What was nominated next?
Here is the next news
Super adventure project Ebichu plus
Nakayama Rikou
It's a super adventure called Nakayama
Tastas
By the way, Nakayama, do you have any
favorite news?
N1 Grand Prix
Isn't it a running race?
Certainly
The next news is Nakayama project that
made Nakayama from project to MC
N1 Grand Prix
The hair of the blooming YASUMO
The hair of the dried YASUMO
But the one that made Ebichu excited was
the one that ran away from the hunter
for 10 minutes
It was the running away game
By the way, how was it for the other
members?
It was fun
I want to do it again while running
I like that
While running
But the old men are not normal
I thought they would help me, but they
ran
You ran too, right?
But I found it
You will find it
Why did you work in a useless place?
Who is useless?
That person was also interesting
Who was it? Someone's cameraman
He is doing his best
Mayama
This person was close to Mayama
Mayana was fast
She was really fast
I noticed that the cameraman's footsteps
were moving
He ran away from the cameraman
I thought he was coming to get me
That's what happened
Heavy news in Ebichu
The next nominate is
Next is this
There are few left
I see
Next is this
The first family entrance
The order is decided
Congratulations
This is heavy news
This is impressive
Next news is
Three people are going to family
entrance for Ebichu's summer live
This is an experimental episode
Ebichu is not here
We are on our own
We didn't know whether or not Ogata will
continue
We asked for the first time in the car
Ogata hasn't decided yet
The staff said, let's ask the audience
We decided
The family was kind
Ebichu might have thought it was decided
by the story
But it was decided then
There was no tension in the car
The family was supposed to be fun
But it was an experimental family
Experimental family
The director is here
I have big news for everyone
What is it?
We got a call last week
Ebichu Tastas will continue after
September
Wow
It went like this
It went well
I'm so glad
I'm glad
I'm going to be a member of TASTA
I don't know either
Can I be a member?
We're asking for the first time
We're fine right?
I'm glad
Of course I can
Kaiki san
Thank you
Wait
Stop crying
Stop it
You're making me emotional
Should he continue the big Kaiki?
He's going to leave the decision to his
family
So let's hear from Kaiki san
If you think it's okay to continue,
please stop
Amazing
Thank you everyone
So the decision is made
Thank you for your continued support
You really decided to do it in the
middle of the show?
My heart was pounding when I saw it
It was fun
When I heard it, the family agreed
How was the moment when you decided to
continue?
It was the pre-show before the fan
meeting
I was about to cry before the fan
I was happy
You were not in the mood?
My legs were shaking
I was nervous and there were many things
It was hard
It's hard to remember now
Thank you
Please make a loud voice
You have to make a loud voice
I was shaking
You were nervous
10 big news of Ebichu Tastas
What is the next news?
Let's continue
The next news is this
This
The big news of Ebichu Tastas
Great
This is news
The title is wonderful
The staff is watching the video of how
Ogata loves Ebichu Tastas
Let's watch it
How does Ogata Kaiki love Ebichu Tastas?
It happened in Nakayama's running game
Let's watch it
3, 2, 1
Yes
How was it?
It was good
I'll do it again
Thank you
He said he'll do it again
For the sake of the audience
What was the situation like?
I think I did it 3 or 4 times
Did you do something wrong?
I did a lot of different things
Like the angle
I did it cool
I did this
I did it several times
If the video gets better
I'll do it again
That's great
It's important
There's more evidence to feel the love
between shrimp and octopus
There's more?
Please look at this
This is Ogata's Twitter
When the octopus starts
He always tweets like this
Shrimp and octopus
He's doing it
It's embarrassing
When it's on the screen
He's saying it before the octopus starts
I'm happy
What's amazing is
He's saying it like this
I'll watch it in real time today
I watch it every time
You watch it every time
Yes
If it's not in the studio
I always watch it when I'm at home
I tweet my impressions
There's more
This is from the sports world
The second episode of the sports world
This week's highlight
Matsuno's eyes
Didn't open at all
With motivation
And Takiue's eyes
Are slowly becoming like a sister
He's explaining his own highlights
That's amazing
I really want to watch it
It's like a TV show
Kaiki Kono is doing it
When you can't watch it in real time
You can say
I can't watch it in real time today
This is it
I can't watch it
With emoji
It's embarrassing
When you can't watch it in real time
You can feel the Ebitu
I want to be impressed
I'm really happy
I'm happy
It's beautiful
Even if you're alone
I think it would be nice if many people
watch it even if it's just a story
I'm happy
When the broadcast time of the program
changes, the time has been changed
The big change of Tastasai will not stop
There is another news that I am
interested in
The staff was looking up on the Internet
if there was anything that felt more
Tastasai
Then there was a delivery like this
What is it?
By the way, the T-shirt I wore today is
the official goods sold at the live
venue of Hiya
We are planning to sell and sell soon
Please
You wore it once
I wore it, right?
I wore a Hiya T-shirt at the magic
sports event
Didn't you tell me to wear a Hiya
T-shirt?
I didn't say that
I came to you without permission
I'm using it to advertise the goods
I'm using that program to advertise my
band's goods
No, I had a question
You will be interested in the fan
meeting
I had a question
I thought that if I wore this T-shirt, I
would have a question
There is no such gradation
You are gradually becoming your own
product from Ebichu Tastas
Is there such a gradation?
By the way, there is another one
Ebichu Tastas is also a snake
I love you so much that I die
This is a song from Hiya
I completed the site press
It is not yet available on Amazon, but
you can buy it online
Everyone, please buy it without
hesitation
We are the stock market
You are asking for help
I had a question
No, I didn't
It's okay
If Ebichu Tastas is not a snake, you can
use it as a normal T-shirt
Ebichu Tastas is also a snake
You can also use it to search for Ebichu
Tastas
The gradation is concentrated
There were still more
There are more
Next
This is the news about the new song that
the staff got from the company
Look here
BS Fuji Ebichu Tatsutatsu
Vocal O-Gata Kaiki is on the show
Season 2 is still going on
This is strange but look at this
Ebichu's character is Hiragana
This is not about this show
This is Hiragana
Where did this come from?
And this is not about the season
What is the second season?
We said that the second season has
started
Give back the emotion
You want to give back the emotion?
Gradation Tsubueki
How is it everyone?
I don't know
I'm confused
I'm the most confused
This is a fact that we can't be confused
Where did you get this?
The staff was disappointed
I think they thought that they loved
Ebichu
They said more good things
Gradation
This is not good
Let's decide the ranking
This is a shock
Everyone is first
But if you are first, this news will be
a big hit
This is the most annoying
When all the news are out, everyone will
decide the ranking
What should we do?
I have a lot of Tsubuyaki
There is only a little about the
promotion
Only a little
It's a little less
What's wrong Ayasumoto?
I'm sleepy
What?
It's not good to give back the emotion
Yasumoto is sleepy, so this year's
Ebitutastas 10th news is decided by the
staff's own
Ebitutastas 10th news ranking is as you
can see
Everyone, look back and see how this
10th news is
It was fun
You remember something
You forgot a lot
This is not the only news
There is a 10th news that is suitable
for the Ebitut news
Eh?
Ishizaki-san
You were there
Why?
You were not there
Ishizaki-san is in charge of the song
production of Ebitutastas
There is a big announcement for the
members
Ishizaki-san, please
Ogata-san, please make an official
request
Eh?
What is this?
Next year, Ebitutastas will release an
album
Ogata-san will make a song
That is decided now
Ogata-san will make an official request
That is amazing
Amazing
I am very happy
By the way, this is the first time we
heard Ebitutastas
Really?
I hope we can do it together one day
Chirikurai
Yes, everyone often forgets
Ogata Kaiki is a hot rock musician
He is not a comedian
By the way, what kind of song is this?
I want to know!
I heard that the album will be released
in spring
So I wanted to make spring as a theme
Is it a bit intense?
Or a ballad?
The song is easy to get on
Is it like a entrance ceremony?
It's like a ghost coming to the new
semester
With this disappearing rock
It's like a rock
By the way, this is a song written by a
writer
I wrote a song by a writer
I'm really happy
What is this recording today?
You're raising me up or down
It's hard today
It's hard to express emotions
I'm thinking of covering the recording
of this song with this TASTAS
Please look forward to it
Finally, let's do rock'n'roll
Teacher!
Everyone of the tea drinkers
It's time to reveal my true feelings
Everyone, please look forward to the new
song of Ebichu
Kobayashi, what is this person?
I don't like that person
See you next time
Bye bye
Next time on Ebichu TASTAS
New Year's special
A big party at the New Year's party
M-1 Grand Prix
M-1 Grand Prix, the legendary project of
the New Year's party
And
Saitama Super Arena 2 Days Live Super
Report
This year's last university party
Take it out
And to those who missed Ebichu TASTAS
Ebichu TASTAS is being widely
distributed on the Star Dust Channel
What is this?
I can't breathe
I haven't finished my drink yet
If you want to enjoy more with Nakayama-
chan
Ebichu TASTAS is available for 400 yen
per month
In addition, there are a lot of
exclusive videos that are not released
Search for the details on the Star Dust
Channel
This program was brought to you by these
sponsors.
Let's get it! Check it! Check it!