policies we should six
this I
Natsumassesu
Hello?
Who is it?
Oh, you know me?
Wait a minute.
Don't you know me?
Thank you for watching.
I think I know you.
What? Shige?
I'm Shigemitsu.
I'm Shige.
Why?
I'm Otsukare Tomo.
I'm a little embarrassed.
You don't have to call your fiancé.
I don't.
Are you closing the shop today?
I'm closing the shop.
For A-chan? Of course.
I have to talk properly.
I'm looking forward to it.
What should I talk about?
I can't think of anything.
I wonder if it's a story from the past.
Because you know everything.
I've seen it for a while, but it's a
situation.
You came to my store.
I've been in the store for a long time.
You bought it for me.
I asked him, and he said, are you
working part-time?
Yes, yes, yes.
You were looking for a job.
Yes, I was looking for a job.
I thought I couldn't live in Tokyo if I
didn't work.
I didn't even write a resume, so I did
it too hard.
I thought, please work here.
Oh, that's what you felt.
I was like, yeah!
And I put out clothes.
Yes, yes, yes.
But I also feel like I'm Akari-san.
What are you talking about?
Did you ever work part-time in Osaka?
No, I was never allowed to work part-
time in Osaka.
And I was so tired from going back to
school that I had to go back to Tokyo.
Oh, that's how it is.
I've never worked.
I went to Tokyo.
I have to work when I come to Tokyo.
I've been working for a long time.
I'm going to tell you the trick of being
a customer.
I think I know who he is.
He's interested in clothes and he'll buy
them if he finds good ones.
I see.
It's about who you are.
Yes, yes, yes.
I think it's easier to understand when
you're alone.
I was better at that.
I guess so.
I think it's more like a conversation.
It's more like a conversation.
That's the way Shige is.
That's the way it is.
That's right. He's aiming for a zero.
That's right. He's scared of his
parents.
New song?
Shinjuku?
New song...
Ah, question.
What? Shinjuku?
I'll ask you a question.
Will you release a new song?
I will.
What's the title?
It seems to have love, but it seems not.
It seems to be deep.
The comments are shallow.
Did you find it?
This is the drama.
You haven't seen the drama, have you?
I don't watch drama TV.
Is it a drama series?
Opening theme.
It's a series.
I hope you get it right.
Let's see. Let's watch it in the middle.
What kind of song is that?
This is really pop and super cynical.
Now, on SNS, I wonder what it is.
Everyone gives it away.
Wow, self-portrait.
Give it away.
But that's pretty...
It's highly communicative.
Sometimes, when I see it from my side, I
feel like everyone has the desire to see
it.
It's not funny, but it's cute and
difficult.
It's a cute song, but if you read the
lyrics carefully, it's really cute.
I see.
I think so.
I think it's empty.
Art is also a profession.
You can't stop SNS.
I think it's a momentary thing to quit
SNS.
I understand.
I see.
Is there a dance this time?
Like a choreography?
Everyone dances to the music.
Cute people.
Cute people?
It's pretty difficult.
It's pretty complicated.
Try it.
You can't see it, can you?
I haven't memorized it yet.
I only remember the part where I like
it.
The right and left are still in my
memory.
Try the part where you remember.
So
I'm sorry.
This is an analog phone.
You can think of lyrics by yourself.
Pina-san's lyrics are the best.
A-chan's original song is also there.
There is.
There is, right? There is a little bit.
Do you know which song is A-chan's song?
I know. I know. I definitely know.
It's A-chan's song.
That's right.
Do you write this at home?
I only write at home.
You only write at home?
Yeah.
Oh, it's like it's falling down.
I write when I'm really down.
When you're down?
I write when I'm down.
What if you're down?
I don't write when I'm down because I go
for a walk.
Oh, you're not in a good mood.
So you're not in a good mood, and you
remember the real experience?
Yeah, but when I'm thinking about
things, I remember them better.
I can think of words, too.
When I'm happy.
Future.
I mean, I can't really say future,
but...
I can't imagine myself as 30 years old.
Yeah.
Well, I think it's a few years later.
I can't imagine myself as 30 years old.
I can't imagine myself as 30 years old,
either.
Yeah.
30 years old?
But it's not that far.
I think it's about 15 to 20 years later.
I'm a little curious. 30 years old.
Marriage. Oh, I don't have a marriage
license at all.
But I wonder if I'll be 30 years old.
Oh, I still feel like that. Can you
imagine?
Ma-chan. Housewife.
Wow! Housewife.
Please watch from the link below.
無理主張。
無理主張じゃねえんだわ。
家庭壊す主婦。
家庭崩壊全く無しだよね。
あ、あ、主婦は。
あ、主婦はもう。
終わりへの始まりだよね。
そしたら、なんだろう。
なんか今だからこと言えるみたいなさ。
何?
なんか自分に、俺に。
今だからこそ言える? 言いたいこととかあるかな?
今だからこそか。でも結構普通にいろいろ言ってきたからな。
まぁ話してはいる。 今だからこそ言える。
俺も話すし。 なんでも。
え、なんだろう。
今だから喜ぶって言ったら、シゲガリガリなのにさ。
シゲガリガリなのになんかさ、
胸筋ちょっとあるんすよみたいな感じはやめたほうがいいと思う。
あー。
ガリガリだねって言うと、俺腕の力強いんすよみたいな感じとかじゃないから。ガリガリ
だから。
じっとガリガリだから。ガリガリを誇っていいんだよ。いいじゃん服に合うだから。
いやいや、年齢的にちょっとね、低いですよ。
何でも似合うからいいじゃんよ、服ね。
いやいやいやいや、もうあーちゃんの方が似合うよ。
それはそうかもしれない。
そう。ちょっと、越してきますこれからも。
いや、ありがとうございます。
シロン、はい。 ソウルメイトとして。 店戻ろうかな。 うん。
あ、店戻る?ごめんね。こんなに長い間締めさせちゃって。 全然、全然、全然。
全然、全然。 ありがとう。 ありがとうね。 うん。 ちょっとじゃあ、これからも。
じゃあ、また。 はい。 また、またすぐ。 遊びに行きます。 はーい。
はい。待ってます。 じゃあね。 ばいばーい。 はーい。 はーい。 はーい。
エンディング