We had a very shocking interview
yesterday, but today's guest is Momoiro
Clover Fest's Remi Takagi!
Now, we're going to start our main
segment, where we'll have you do a cute
title call.
I feel like we haven't really done
anything like this before, but we'll do
it again for you.
Let's get started!
Nightclub and Idol
Could you pick a title for me?
Okay
I'll send you
I'm ready!
How was it?
I'm a little lost.
What did you imagine?
I made a heart.
That's a heart!
Can you tell us?
Of course!
Ta-da!
The first one is Itsukara.
The second one is Netflix.
The third one is
Event or Animal.
I can only see four of them.
That's a heart!
My body has callsty wins!
First one is super spicy.
Yes.
I think you all know this, but I like
super spicy food.
I think I often post stories about my
favorite curry.
I ate curry the day before yesterday and
yesterday.
Really?
I eat a lot of curry every day.
So it's not just normal curry?
Super spicy curry.
When you eat at Cocoits, what kind of
curry do you eat?
There is a regular menu.
Basically, it's a curry with a lot of
seafood and a little rice and natto.
Rice, natto, and curry.
Is it super spicy?
Yes.
That's a lot.
I eat a lot of curry, but the spiciness
varies depending on the store.
Really?
I think it depends on the chef's cooking
and the amount of curry.
It's completely different.
Recently, Cocoits has a lot of menus.
I used to eat 200g of rice.
There are a lot of people who eat a lot
of rice at Cocoits.
200g is a small amount.
But recently, it's been 150g.
150g has been added, and many people are
worried about it.
So I added cauliflower rice instead of
rice.
What is that?
Is it expensive?
It's not rice?
It's not rice.
I also eat vegetable curry.
Only vegetables?
Cocoits is amazing.
It's not just Cocoits.
I really like spicy food.
Do you have any condiments to make it
spicy?
I have.
Most of the condiments in my house are
spicy.
Tabasco condiments.
Is that true?
The most spicy condiment is Scorpion.
Scorpion?
Yes.
It's really spicy.
It's a lie.
I want you to try it.
I made a special menu.
There is a curry of 18kg.
It's as spicy as a demon.
If I eat 18kg of potato chips, I can
only eat one.
I can only eat one.
It's very interesting.
If you add Scorpion to the curry, it's
really spicy.
Scorpion is a spicy tabasco condiment.
I also have a hot sauce.
Hot sauce?
I put it on various dishes.
You like spicy food.
I love it.
Please subscribe to my channel.
To the viewers, our locks have been
hybrid.
Please recommend new habits.
Hit pay-up additional 31000yen