I want to be an old idol like THE IDOL.
I want to do everything I can.
I'm not qualified to love you
The reason why my parents met me was
I listened to my dad's song and my mom
fell in love with it
and got married
That's how much I love my parents' songs
My parents raised me by singing a lot at
home
That's why I love singing
I have a habit of singing a lot at home
and outside
When I was in elementary school, I was
playing tennis in the first grade of
elementary school.
I was like a sports girl with a dark
skin.
I had short hair and black tan.
I was mistaken for a boy.
I thought that this kind of appearance
would be dangerous when I was in junior
high school.
I was mistaken for a girl.
I tried to look as red as possible.
My skin turned a little white.
I met a musical when I was in the second
grade of junior high school.
I went to see a musical that my friend
was in.
I was so absorbed in singing and
dancing.
I was so interested in how different
people could express themselves.
I watched the musical and told my mom
that I wanted to be in it.
I joined a musical troupe.
I was still not confident in myself at
first.
I thought I couldn't do it.
I thought I could express myself better.
I thought I could reach the audience.
I felt like my color was broken.
I thought I should try as much as I
could.
I wanted to learn more from myself.
I wanted to be cuter.
If I hadn't been in a musical, I
wouldn't be standing here today.
I think I would have lived without
confidence.
I've only lived for 17 years, but I
think it was the turning point of my
life.
That's where I changed.
I'm RIO SHIMIZU, 17 years old, from
SHIWA.
I met HINATATAKA46 when I was in the
first year of high school.
I wanted to shine in this group.
I wanted to attract people who are
watching and make them smile.
I tried a lot of singing, dancing, and
self-reflecting.
When I first saw them,
I was inspired by the energy and
freshness of other groups.
I was inspired by the energy of other
groups.
Many people told me that I was energetic
and good.
I thought I could shine here.
I've been listening to this song a lot
during the exam.
This is my favorite song.
I'm trying to tell people to do their
best.
I think I've been pushed back by that.
I've been listening to 《Seishun no
Uma》for a long time,
and I decided to take the audition.
I thought it would be over if I gave up
here.
I decided to take the audition after
listening to 《Seishun no Uma》.
I didn't think I'd make it, but I did my
best.
I didn't think I'd make it.
Number 2, Rio Shimizu.
The moment I heard my name, I couldn't
believe it.
I couldn't cry.
I couldn't cry much. I was so shocked.
I wanted to be in the team forever.
I'm still in the starting line.
From now on...
I hope I can keep my first year of being
a member of the team.
I think the time will come when the 4th
generation will lead the team.
I want to be a person who can lead the
team.
The first day of the rehearsal
I wonder if we can finish it.
It's been three days.
But the moment we finished it, it was
amazing.
I talked to Rio a lot, but...
I felt so relieved.
Rio's performance was really good.
I'm glad I can rely on her.
She's a good dancer.
I'm so happy.
I want to be an old idol like THE IDOL.
It's okay. It's okay.
Calm down. Calm down.
Smile. Smile. Smile.
You're going to be like you always are.
Do your best!
What makes me who I am now?
I think I became a person who is
cheerful and has a lot of smiles when I
entered high school and joined the dance
club.
I want to dance to the cheer.
I have the image of a cheer that is a
stadium, so I want to go to the stadium
and dance.
You've got a girlfriend.
Yes, I'm happy.
How about here?
What did you do?
I danced with my friends several times
this summer.
Wow, amazing.
Can I go in?
Yes, you can.
I'm so happy.
Is this okay?
I danced over there.
Where did you dance?
At the edge.
Yes.
This is the view.
It's wider than when I was looking from
above.
It's closer than I thought.
You can see my face clearly.
It's amazing to think that this is where
I'll be buried.
I was so happy to be supported.
I'm so happy to be here for the first
time.
I can't believe how many people are
here.
I miss this place.
Do you remember this place?
Yes, I do.
It's so vivid.
I love the view from the top.
It's beautiful.
When I was told that this is the place,
I was so happy.
I was surprised, but I was happy to see
the whole from the edge.
Here it is.
Here.
Oh.
This way. I danced here.
I always roll around.
I watch it with a flutter.
But in the end, I feel like they'll
always turn it around.
It was a winning strategy.
I thought I could cheer for people
and improve my expressiveness.
So I joined the cheer dance club.
Due to the influence of COVID-19,
I couldn't participate in competitions
and couldn't cheer for people.
I was surprised to hear that I could
cheer for people for the first time this
summer.
I remember it was very fresh.
I may have said it in a bad way, but I
thought I couldn't do it anyway.
I couldn't do it because I couldn't do
it with my classmates.
I was doing it with my classmates, and
when I really could do it, I couldn't do
the best performance.
We talked about difficult things
together and worked hard for two years.
I realized that I had been working hard
for this moment.
I was about to cry when the teacher told
me that my eyes were sparkling.
I can't forget it.
My parents asked me if I would continue
to do club activities.
But I can't forget it.
If I have hope, I want to do my best to
the end.
I'm glad I was able to do it with my
fellow students.
I'm a member of the cheer dance club.
I want to tell everyone in the dance
club.
When I reenacted it, I said,
I will join the Minatazaka 46.
Then everyone said,
The sound of the music was so loud that
I was shaking.
I was so happy that I almost cried.
Everyone was cheering for me.
I had a poem written right after the
event.
Everyone was cheering for me.
I've been cheering for others a lot in
my life.
I hope that my fans will continue to
support me.
I can't imagine what it would be like.
I want to repay my fans with a smile.
I'm RIO SHIMIZU, 17 years old, from
SHIBA.