I listen to it every week.
I don't have enough time to consume
content.
I have about 400 copies.
I'm really following the market price
every week.
The main character is the daughter of
the entertainment production.
The main character changes in the
middle.
What?
I'm going to make this song sell as a
manager.
I feel that the way I see the idol has
changed since I graduated from Takorizu.
I have a desire to make music since
then.
Pikanto Idol
Now, I'm Yakan, a former classmate of
Viva Home Maria Stardust.
I have another guest today.
Please introduce yourself.
I'm Haruna Mai. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
I'm Mai Mai.
Thank you for coming.
Likewise.
You are currently active in various
stages.
You are Haruna Mai.
You have been active in various stages
from autumn to winter.
Yes, I have.
I was in the stage of a play called
Stage Focus Update.
It's a combination of acting and social
dance.
Social dance?
Yes, I did social dance.
It's a difficult thing.
It was difficult.
It's different from the dance I've ever
danced.
I danced with my partner.
It's completely different from the basic
posture.
It was the first time I had a social
dance lesson with a cast of the stage.
I learned the basics of social dance.
I learned a lot.
It was a new experience for me.
I didn't think I had learned it.
I agree.
It was a lot of fun.
I'm sorry, but I'd like to ask you a
question.
I don't know anything about social
dance.
Social dance can be divided into two,
standard and Latin.
Standard and Latin.
You can divide it into two.
The rhythm is different.
The way you put your arms is different.
It's different.
I want to hear your opinion.
It's different for women to put their
arms on their shoulders.
It's also different in how to count.
There are different genres from standard
to Latin.
Do you divide it into two?
The dancer who can dance all of them is
called a ten dancer.
Ten dancer?
That's right.
I've never heard of it.
There are ten types of dance.
There is a dance called Tokyo Koya Osaka
Kouen.
30 dancers will dance on stage.
Are they professional dancers?
That's right.
There are also teachers in the
classroom.
I was in a state where there were a lot
of teachers.
I was able to listen to the teacher's
opinion.
It was very interesting.
It's like a military drama of a social
dancer.
That's right.
At the end, there is a curtain call.
The main cast dances together.
That's the role.
The main story is a combination of
acting and social dance.
The curtain call is a social dance.
I'm wearing a dress.
It's like a fluttering dress.
It's like a dress with a string.
It's like a dress with a fluttering
string.
It's wonderful.
I wore a dress that was shining.
Do you have a picture of it?
I have a picture.
I want you to print it.
Please.
Really?
I took a lot of pictures because I
didn't have a chance to dance in this
dress.
I found it.
This is a dance school.
That's great.
I was nervous because I had to dance and
social dance at the same time.
Yakan and Irun
Thank you very much
I bought this manga on my smartphone and
wrote down all the details
When the new volume came out
This program is
Irun
I sent it to you by the nickname Nashi-
san, which is a regular customer of my
store.
Thank you for your continued support.