GAKANBO IDOL
Can I ask you to give me a title call?
Yes!
My three elements!
Mooo! Thanks!
Can you tell us the three elements that
make up anime?
Here we go!
Ready, set, go!
The first one is a girl manga.
Yes!
The second one is a radio show.
The third one is an idol.
I see!
Written by Syuko Satoi
Please subscribe to my channel!
The first one is a girl manga.
I love girl manga.
I've loved it since I was a kid.
I have about 400 girl manga at home.
Wow!
I have.
What is a girl manga?
I used to love the girl manga,
Kirarin Revolution.
Yes, yes.
I used to love it and read it.
I started to love it when I was in
middle school.
Yes.
There is a manga called
Hatsumitsunihatsukoi.
Hatsumitsunihatsukoi?
It's a manga by Inase Ai.
I wonder how many people read it.
It was the beginning of my love for girl
manga.
It was the beginning.
It's a story about childhood friends.
It's a very basic girl manga.
I started to like the story of the girl
manga,
and the relationship between people.
I started to buy a lot of it.
I see.
I write down all the manga I bought on
my smartphone.
When you get a new one,
do you check if you bought it?
Yes, I check how many I bought.
I have a lot of them.
You like manga.
Have you ever bought it?
Yes.
I bought it and came back.
I was like,
I found it in the cafe.
I have a lot of them.
You like manga.
But I thought I went to a cafe.
I see.
I took a break.
You're right.
I'm doing it.
It's a story about a crush.
A crush?
The story is about a girl from a TV
show.
A girl from a TV show?
I've heard that story before.
The boss' daughter is the main
character.
And there are five boys.
They are in a group.
And the manager makes them popular.
The story is amazing.
The main character changes in the
middle.
The main character changes to a
different high school girl.
I want to read it.
How does the girl change to the manager?
I read it and thought the main character
changes.
I met this manga when I was a member of
Tako Niji.
This manga is about idols.
I see. Even the main character reads
this.
It's about how to move to be popular.
This manga is about that.
I want you to read this.
The story is about a group of idols.
I love crushes.
I love All Night Nippon.
Here it comes, All Night Nippon.
Produced by Uma Uma, Raoshan, and
illuruuluru ilrun.
Thank you everyone!