Ebichu's video
I thought there were a lot of things to
do
Thank you
Wait a minute
Good morning
Your luggage is very heavy
Thank you
My father's birthday is coming up
My mother's birthday is in the month of
last month
I'm already in the month of last month
I'll wait for my father today
Thank you
Today is the last day of the SETA solo
live tour
I'm going to perform 12 performances
today
I will do my best to have a good time
with you
Ignorance is crime
Good morning
I see.
The first song is...
I'm waiting for you forever.
I want to lose everything.
I don't need words anymore because I'm
not in love anymore.
I can't touch you.
The second song is...
I'm waiting for you forever.
The first outfit is this blue one.
The theme of this outfit is red and
blue.
This is a cute shape.
I'm ready to go out.
Are you kidding me?
24 years old.
I know it.
Stop it.
I'm sorry.
I'm ready.
The first outfit is this blue one.
The theme of this outfit is red and
blue.
Thank you very much.
Let's go, Niconama!
Niconama!
Let's go!
I'm going to change my clothes.
I see.
It's hot.
Finally, the first part is over.
I'll do my best.
The second outfit is red.
This outfit is cool.
I'm wearing a garter shirt.
I'm wearing a garter shirt so that my
top doesn't fly away.
My earrings are red, aren't they?
Do they look red?
They look orange.
I'm wearing the same color earrings.
Yay!
This is the last part of the KASHIWAKI
HINATA Christmas Interlude.
I'll do my best to make you happy.
KASHIWAKI, do your best!
Do your best!
Let's make a fun live show together.
Let's do it!
Let's show time!
Thank you for your hard work.
The last part is over!
The last one is...
The one who is crying is...
Hey, you!
I don't know what's wrong with this
song.
It's not a song to cry.
Why is it different?
I don't know.
I don't know how to count the stars.
Please try to get to the end.
Thank you.
Say hello to the camera.
I'll do my best.
I thought Hinata was the one who sang
the last part.
I don't know.
I thought she was singing on stage.
I thought she really liked to sing and
dance.
I thought that was the best fit for her.
I liked her more.
It was a great performance.
She didn't have a break.
She didn't drink water.
I thought it was amazing to perform like
that.
I don't know.
I was really happy to see the fans.
It was amazing.
Hinata's live performance was the best.
Thank you for the performance.
This is the best!
I can't cry!
Yes!
The concert of the 2020 Interlude has
ended successfully.
Thank you so much to everyone who came
to see the concert and watched the live
broadcast.
I'm so happy that I've done everything.
I'm sad that the concert is over, but
I'm really happy.
Thanks to everyone, I was able to make a
wonderful concert.
Thank you so much.
Next, I will prepare for the spring tour
in Ebichu.
See you in the live broadcast!
Thank you for watching!
I don't want to be a burden to my
destiny
I want to enjoy this moment
Take your music now
I'll be shining in the city
Can you feel it?
Take your music now
I'll be shining in the city
Can you feel it?
Everyday
The world is waiting for me
Everyday is alright
Baby, I'm so close to you
There's no other place for me to be
I'm free, I can't make you love me
Ooh, ooh, ooh
Take your music now
I'll be shining in the city
Can you feel it?
Take your music now
I'll be shining in the city
Can you feel it?
Take your music now
Thank you for watching.
I'm not lying, I'm not lying
I'm laughing at the strange shape
Look closely again, there's no time to
cry
I'm not here, I'm not here
The rabbit who knew the way to the end
started running
One, two, three, four, now
Grab it, with a second of zero
Change, change, change
Be careful of lies and truth
One, two, three, four, now
Grab it, it's not me
It was a pair of artificial dolls
Welcome to the endless station
Translated by Releska
I did my best, so I have no regrets.
I'm full of the feeling that it was
really fun.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching. Please subscribe
to the channel.
Good morning, everyone.
I'm so excited!
Thank you so much!
I'm wearing a dress.
I can open the hole.
I'm wearing a hat.
Please, please.
says adaptations of boy band.