Ebi-chu's video
Everyone, how are you?
This is Rikonohie's fourth episode.
I'm the voice of the series Ebi-chu, the
voice of the number 52, Riko Kayama.
This time, the guest of Rikonohie is
this person.
I'm the voice of the number 51, Koba
Yoshikawa.
Thank you.
I'm glad you're awake.
I was wondering when you would come.
Thank you for waiting.
It's been a while since I've been to
Rikonohie.
Last time I went to see Hinata, I was a
little late.
I would like to ask various questions
today.
Thank you.
First of all,
We are 21 years old this year.
Kao-chan was 21 years old the other day.
We haven't gone on a high school
graduation trip yet.
We haven't gone yet.
How many years?
About 3 years.
I can't go because I'm going to go to
school for about 3 years.
If you can go, where do you want to go?
I want to go to the airport.
I want to go to the Shinkansen.
Which one?
Where do you want to go if you get on a
plane?
I want to go to the house temple in
Nagasaki.
What season?
Spring.
Spring is over.
Next year.
If it's spring, the illumination is
amazing.
What is spring?
I want to make a blooming image.
I think spring is good.
Illumination.
If you are on a plane, Nagasaki.
If you are on a Shinkansen,
The fifth place in the middle school
trip is Kyoto.
I want to go to Kyoto again on my
graduation trip.
Do you like temples?
Yes.
Shrine.
I want to go to the temple again.
If it was Shinkansen, it would be Kyoto.
It's a very long train.
If it was Tokyo 23, where would you go?
Tokyo 23?
Do you know Takao-san?
This is a good place.
I like Asuke.
Do you go hiking?
Hiking.
If it's Takao-san, it's a cute place.
If you go to other mountains.
It's quite difficult.
I like Aki.
I like Koyogari.
Koyogari?
It's a mojigari.
I'm sorry.
Mojigari.
If it's that, I'd go to Tsukaze.
It's a good place.
I'm going.
I want to go to the Suneika.
If you go to Suneika, I want to go to
the Ninkyoji.
Ninkyoji?
Is there Ninkyoji in Ninkyoji?
I think so.
I've been there.
I think there's Asakusa.
I think so.
I'll look it up.
I want to go to the Tokyo Tower.
I like the Tokyo Tower.
I want to go up from the bottom.
I want to go up from the top.
I'll do that.
This is what everyone is asking.
What is your motto?
My motto is...
I'll do something.
It's a good one.
My mother...
My mother said she'd do something when
she was a child.
She said she'd do something when she was
a child.
If she did, she'd be a child.
That's right.
I think I can do that.
I'll definitely do something.
I'll do something.
You're definitely going to do something.
I'm going to do something.
Everyone is like, what?
Have you been working on that all the
time?
Yes, that's right.
I'm a little worried.
There are negative aspects.
Basically, I can do something.
I remember.
Is there an episode that you were able
to do something when you were in school?
Yes, I was able to do something when I
was in high school.
Basically, I didn't have to be a first-
year student.
I was a 10-minute before the test.
I was a first-year student.
I didn't like math or physics.
I didn't study at all.
I was a first-year student.
I thought I could still do a little more
in society and the national defense.
I was a first-year student.
I got an 80.
That's amazing.
I was probably right in the test.
I'm really surprised.
I think you should study.
I'm getting used to it.
I think I'm going to be at home when I
have a vacation.
I can't go home.
I have to go out.
What are you going to do?
That means I have to go out in front of
my house.
You don't have to go out in front of
your house.
I have to go somewhere.
You have to go out for a day.
What should I do?
First, I go to karaoke.
I go to karaoke for a day in my free
time.
I go out of the house.
You went out for a little bit.
I watch a movie or a pattern.
I watch two movies.
Can you watch two movies?
I watch two movies and eat something
delicious.
I go out.
I use a camera.
I can kill time.
I can't watch two movies.
I've seen two movies before.
I can't sleep.
I thought it was a good idea.
I watched the movie in the order of the
movie I watched before.
I was impressed with the movie.
I was serious when I watched it.
I thought the order of the movie I
watched was important.
That's okay.
What do you want to do with RIKO?
I'm not sure what to do with
TSUTSUKYUWA.
I want to go on a little trip.
A little trip?
A little trip is fine.
It's a big trip.
A little trip.
Where do you want to go on a little
trip?
I want to go to a traditional place like
Kabakura.
Have you ever been to a traditional
place like that?
Yes, I have.
It's terrible.
Do you want to go to Komokura?
I haven't been to Komokura.
I went there last year.
That's terrible.
Last year...
I went there this year.
I went there last year.
I went there.
You went there.
I went to Komachi-dori, which is a royal
road.
You two did O-Rashinda.
Yes.
O-Rashinda is a movie that people watch.
It's like a drama.
It's a one-on-one drama.
I thought it was a drama.
I was watching O-Rashinda on a computer.
I was analyzing it.
It's about 30 sheets of paper.
It's almost the same.
Both are orange.
I was wondering if I had any worries.
I was wondering if it looked like that.
It's almost the same.
Enoshima.
I want to go to Hasedara.
Oh, you want to go?
Let's go.
We met a new member on May 5th.
We've been working together for about
six years as the youngest.
Do you have any questions?
But it's a mental meeting.
I think it's good to go to lessons
together.
My sister is the same age as Nono.
So I don't have to worry about her.
I feel like I'm really close to my
sister.
Basically, everyone is close.
I think that's the biggest thing.
I think you're the most like a woman.
I'm her sister and sister-in-law.
That's right.
That's what I'm showing.
I was in a lesson the other day.
I was dancing with my right eye.
I've been doing it with my left eye, but
I suddenly do it with my right eye.
But I have to teach you that.
I couldn't remember it at all.
If Nono was in charge of that time, she
would have remembered it first.
I was taught by Hino.
I taught Nono the other day.
I'm 13 years old.
It's strange.
I was like this.
I'm very clear.
I'm in charge of that.
I'm not wrong.
I'm glad to see that you remember me
without being fooled by it.
I'm sorry, but I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm glad to see that.
Congratulations on opening the store
last year.
Thank you.
What kind of activities do you want to
do in the future?
We are a regular program called Kannai
Nefile.
I got a set of oil paintings.
I've never done oil paintings before.
I've never painted oil paintings before.
I'm really looking forward to painting.
I want to make a good design with goods.
Do you have any goods you want to draw?
My oil painting is a little loose.
I want to make a line stamp that has the
bitterness of the members.
I think I've been saying that for a long
time.
But it's hard to find a stamp that's
easy to use.
I use a lot of
It's hard to find a stamp that's easy to
use.
I use a lot of
Who will come?
Who?