Thank you for watching.
Good morning.
That's a good answer. Please keep that
in mind.
Yesterday, we finished the intro. Today,
we will finish from 1A to the end.
Tomorrow, Takahiro-san will come to see
us.
The last day of the camp, the last day
of the presentation. Takahiro-san was
supposed to perform there, but he will
come here tomorrow.
The presentation is in two days. He will
come here tomorrow and see the lesson in
the morning.
Please do your best today.
Taking part in a lecture conducted by
Dr. Takahiro...
And lesson when she feels nervous too.
Kida, remember the choreography.
You have to remember it.
But she still doesn't have the
choreography.
If you get it wrong, the whole piece
will look messy.
You can't express the song.
You can only move your mouth.
She doesn't have enough dance, song, or
expression.
First of all, are you motivated?
Why can't you remember that?
First of all, no one can sing.
It's like, what do you mean you can't
even move your mouth?
We have to deliver the song.
It's our job to deliver the song.
I think Endo-chan is like, let's learn
the choreography first.
That's all I can say.
From today, she will start voice
training, in addition to dance lessons.
The challenge was not only dance.
Overall, everyone is short of breath.
I haven't yet built a singing body.
Meanwhile, some of the features began to
shine upon polishing
I think it will be better if the pitch,
pitch, and accent are a little more
stable.
As for Riko, the song is quite stable
and I think it will get better and
better.
Surprisingly, I think Airi is stable and
reliable.
Like this?
Are you ready?
Takahiro will come and check us tomorrow
morning.
If you don't learn the short version
perfectly by then,
Takahiro won't know where to check.
I want you to finish it perfectly by
tomorrow morning.
I didn't know the choreography and I
just stopped.
I was frustrated.
I saw everyone getting better and
better.
I want you to finish it perfectly by
tomorrow morning.
I want to do my best.
She's not satisfied with everything, but
she doesn't want to give up.
Her feelings are starting to show on her
face.
1, 2, 3, 4, that's right!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5,
6, 7, 8, go!
No matter how much you say you're a
coward, you're not a coward.
You can't be a hero anymore.
No matter how much you say you're a
coward, you're not a coward.
I won't let you go.
I'm Reina Odakura, 18 years old, a third
year high school student from Tokyo.
I think I'm an awkward person.
I've been trying a lot harder because
I'm awkward.
And I've become a person who doesn't
forget to be grateful for the help I've
received from others.
If I could join Sakurazaka, I'd like to
continue to grow with effort and
gratitude,
and leave a good result so that I can
contribute to the group.
Compared to the first two and a half
hours of practice,
I'm not out of breath.
I think I've grown a lot in the first
two and a half hours.
I still make mistakes and I'm not good
at dancing,
but I'm getting better at it at the
speed of the original song.
So it's very important to practice
without giving up.
I think this is the best dance I've ever
done.
The first half of the battle.
I promised not to cry.
At the camp?
But you finally cried today.
I was praised.
I cried because I was praised.
I was so happy.
We were practicing during the self-study
camp.
When someone praises you,
you feel like you're being praised.
You feel happy.
I'm glad we did it today.
Our first time, she praised me
specifically for being so good.
We didn't get to feel that before.
So, I was happy.
Me, too.
Thank you for watching this video.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Thank you for watching.
I know you are thinking that you can't
catch up with the choreography.
But you were doing great in the intro.
You were able to follow the original
song and dance.
If you keep practicing, you will be able
to follow all the other choreography.
You are doing great. You are growing up.
So don't give up and keep practicing.
You can do it. You can do the intro.
You are doing great. You are doing
great.
You can do it. You can do it. You can do
it.
Thank you for watching.
Until the end.
Thank you.
I think Murayama's dance is the best for
this song.
I want you to be confident because I
think your dance is the best.
Murayama has a long dance experience
among the 3rd generation.
But she is always not confident.
I think Murayama is a good dancer.
I'm not confident.
I haven't received any compliments.
I have a thought about you.
I'm scared.
Why?
I don't say scary things.
You're good at dancing.
Stop it.
You're good at singing.
I'm not good.
You're good. You're perfect.
I'm being hit.
I'm sorry.
I think it's an excuse.
I have to do a lot of things at the
camp.
I can't remember the dance perfectly.
I'm happy that everyone is dancing.
I think Miyu is a perfect person.
But she doesn't have confidence in
herself.
She has a high spirit.
I'm so embarrassed.
I really think so.
Rika is the oldest.
I think she's carrying that burden.
That's a complex.
I think so.
I'm the oldest in the 3rd generation.
But I'm not like that at all.
So I want to be able to see everyone
around me.
I think she's thinking about doing it
because she's the oldest.
So I want to tell her.
To be honest, I've always been thinking
about myself,
and I've been thinking about myself a
lot when I'm announcing my group.
I want to practice with the three of us
from now on,
and I want to express myself.
I think you can see how much I've grown
compared to the beginning of this 2.5
hour lesson.
I've grown a lot in this short time.
If you work hard, you can do it.
You'll see Takahiro tomorrow.
I want you to say,
I can do this much.
I want to show you that you can dance
like this.
We think so, too.
Let's keep working hard.
Thank you very much.
Actually, we had a small event for
dinner tonight.
In group activities, it's important not
only to practice, but also to make
something together.
So, we're going to have everyone make
dinner together today.
Not only for ourselves, but also for the
staff.
From buying to cooking, all the members
will work together to make it from
scratch.
Do you like cooking?
No, I don't.
Are you good at cooking?
No, I'm not.
I see.
I'm sorry.
I'm not good at it.
I've never cooked at home in my life.
I like to make sweets, so I'm good at
it.
I like to make sweets, but I'm good at
making omelette.
I think I can make it to the level of
Hitanami.
Do you cook?
I'm good at cooking.
I cook often.
I'm not good at making risotto lately.
I can't wait to see it.
First, we decide on the menu for dinner.
We choose two cards from five cards and
have them make what's written on them.
When the menu is decided, we discuss the
ingredients together.
From now on, we split into the cooking
team and the grocery team.
I'll buy some green onions.
One, two, three.
I'll buy some meat.
Do you use only hamburger?
I think I do.
I think it's a combination of minced
meat and meat.
Aibiki?
What's the difference between minced
meat and aibiki?
Let's buy some tofu.
We have miso soup.
Let's eat it.
It says it's a combination of meat and
tofu.
It's a combination of meat and tofu.
Do we crush the tofu and put it in?
What?
Miso soup?
It's not a magic tofu.
It's a miso soup.
It might be a magic tofu.
Really?
Don't you do it?
I'll put some sweet potatoes in it.
So, you'll put sweet potatoes instead of
potatoes?
Really?
Is it OK?
I think it's OK.
Meanwhile, the cooking team is
preparing.
Thank you.
I want to eat hamburger.
It's not a magic tofu.
First, cut it like this, then cut it
like this.
I'll cut it.
Is it OK?
The shop staffs are back and they start
cooking.
We are going to make Mapo Tofu.
I can't cut it.
It's better to cut it in half and then
cut it.
I could cut it.
I've finished the last one.
Congratulations!
Now, the shop assistant is cooking, and
everyone is having the last spurt.
Are you OK?
Wait, it's so heavy.
But it looks delicious.
It's a potato for 20 people.
I want to show my legs.
Heart.
I'm going to throw it away.
It's going to be broken.
It's done.
It's a boy!
Boy!
I don't know!
Wow!
OK! I did it!
I did it!
Thank you!
We all worked hard to make this.
Please open your hands.
Let's eat.
It looks so delicious.
It's amazing.
It's like a meat.
Is it?
The shape is beautiful.
It's delicious.
It's well-done.
The miso soup is very delicious.
It's a proper miso soup.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I'm sure that for the first time, all
three generations have created one
thing.
Is there anyone who came to see the
concert of Azulim?
Everyone is aiming for something beyond
that concert.
It's not decided yet whether or not they
can be on stage.
I'm very frustrated with myself for not
being able to dance with confidence and
not having enough physical strength to
the end.
I want to be confident in myself!
A-l blaming...