This week's Ebitune Tastas is
challenging a TV reporter for the first
time
Ebitune is interviewing a chicken in
various spots
Sascade
A report battle that is too free
I was talking
Emitiu Sastus start
We will add various things to the
private and private schools
FNC DASTAR
This program is provided by the sponsor
you see
It's a little expensive, isn't it?
Ebichu Tastas has started!
Where are we now?
We are in Venus Island!
There are a lot of foreigners here
today!
I don't know at all!
I'm just looking at it like, what is it?
Today, Kobayashi is...
That's right. Today, she has other work.
By the way, have you all been on Venus
boat?
Yes!
Anyone?
Since we're here on Venus boat, let's go
eat something together!
No, no, no!
I'm sorry!
Sorry!
As expected!
It's not like that!
We're not going to buy anything today!
Why? We've been excited for a long time!
We're going to do something very
important for Ebichu!
Ebichu, everyone is shy, right?
Ebichu is a group that is shy.
Yes, it's a group that is shy.
In the dressing room and the dressing
room, they tend to get together.
Is it okay for us to talk to each other
like this?
No, no, no!
Don't look down at us!
We're idols!
Do you all practice to overcome shyness?
Practice?
Practice? Like, be careful of this?
When I talk to the members one-on-one,
I try to keep the conversation going.
When I get home from the train, for
example, Riko-chan,
I try to talk to the type of girl that I
don't talk to myself.
That's great!
Does that help you, Nakayama?
Yes!
I was listening to you.
We are working now.
Didn't you hear the sound of Nakayama?
No, I didn't.
Everyone is working hard, but not enough
to overcome the loneliness.
So, today's event is...
the Ebitune's
Overcoming the Loneliness, the reporter
battle!
We are Venusport!
We will be interviewing the reporters
without knowing them,
and will try to make it easy for them to
understand the information.
This time, we will be divided into 4
teams,
and will be reporting from different
locations.
First, Hoshina Matsuno pair!
They will be doing an interesting goods
report at a popular store!
The two people who love shopping will be
telling the charm of popular products.
Next, Kashiwagi Nakayama pair!
They will be doing a dog cafe report
with their beloved dog!
What?
I like dog cafes!
I'm scared of dogs though
Why are you happy?
I love animals
Nakayama who is not good at animal-
loving kashiwagi and is happy with it
challenges a report using dogs
Next, Hirota-peer Yasumoto
A lively bouldering report
What?
I want to climb it
It's a dog cafe!
Please wait
The two who are athletic
A report of a body-building experience
What will it be?
Last, Mayama-Rika
A gourmet report of a royal road who
enjoys authentic Korean food
Yay!
But are you alone?
It's okay to say it in one way
Mayama and Rika pair is fine
You are alone
Mayama is doing a royal road report by
herself
Will she be able to convey the taste
well?
A report battle where each team is
divided into 4 different locations and
conducts a broadcast.
Which team will be able to report the
most effectively by blowing away the
shyness?
The top batter is Hirota Yasumoto's
bouldering experience report.
First, let's start with a look at the
report to confirm the flow.
Raise your hips like this.
Wow!
And grab the top of your head like this.
It's important to convey the information
you've gained while being able to
understand it.
I was surprised because I didn't know
the meaning of the colors.
It's fashionable.
Now, the preview is over.
Let's start the studio and the
broadcast.
Let's start the show.
Let's start the studio and the
broadcast.
Today, we will introduce the facilities
where you can experience the real
activity in Tokyo.
The broadcast is connected. Yasumoto-
san, Hiroto-san.
Hi, I'm Aika Hirota.
I'm at an outdoor resort circus.
I'm going to use this outdoor
convenience store and barbecue.
I'm going to use this for barbecue.
She fixed it herself.
I'm going to go inside.
However, there is no Yasumoto-san who
will do it with me.
I'm glad.
Please subscribe to my channel.
No, it's not.
It's not that.
I was wrong.
I'm sorry.
Hello, I'm Yasumoto.
Nice to meet you.
It's a long way to go.
They followed a long way and went to...
Amazing.
So handsome.
He's doing something.
He's coming.
Welcome to the first floor.
Yes.
It's a sport of climbing.
It's a sport to climb a river, small
rocks, and rocks.
I'll explain it to you.
Can I ask you to introduce yourself?
My name is Sharon. Thank you.
Which country are you from?
Ladies in front of the TV,
It's rare to meet such a handsome guy.
Please be healed while you come to play
with your child.
Which country are you from?
It's my first time.
You can't hear it at all.
I can't hear it.
I'm from the Jiro.
The other people are climbing up.
Yes.
It's like climbing up the stairs.
If you hit the ceiling with your head,
you'll get a goal.
Please do your best.
I'm going.
First of all, you're a beginner.
The beginners are free to climb.
I see.
Yasumoto-san.
Don't forget the idol.
Yasumoto-san, it's like a
Hirota is fast.
Yasumoto-san is really good.
Wait a minute, Hirota-san.
Hirota-san, wait a minute.
I'm going now.
Wait a minute.
It's easy.
Only you can do it.
It's pretty difficult.
It's fun to be excited.
That's good.
Even if you're not confident,
I want you to try.
It's easy to grab the dented part.
You have to put your feet on the
slippery part.
It's hard to grab because your feet
hurt.
I think it's a good tip.
That's good.
There's a little difficult climbing.
There's a real climbing.
I've already climbed up.
Would you like to try it?
There's another difficult climbing.
I'll show you this.
The tempo is good.
Next, the difficulty level is up.
Yasumoto is challenging.
Can you do it?
It's high.
How many meters is this height?
This is 7 meters.
It's amazing.
It's scary.
There are many things to see up close.
The height is from the bottom.
It's scary to see it from the bottom.
Can you tell me the tips again?
Please subscribe to the channel.
It's hot.
There is no such thing.
There is a yellow line.
Climb up to that line.
You will reach the goal if you stand on
the board.
Kitagawa will give you instructions.
Please fasten your rope.
You can grab the rope firmly on the
board.
After that, you will jump over the wall.
Please get on the board.
Please start.
Please put your feet in the pot.
What's the pot?
Please get on the board.
Amazing.
Please move forward.
It seems that you can climb up quickly.
Nice.
It's a lot higher.
Amazing.
It's much more open than inside.
You are almost there.
Please subscribe to the channel.
Success!
I did it!
Good!
Thank you.
From now on, it's a safe place
Yasumoto, how is the view from there?
What?
Yasumoto-san, how is the view from
above?
This is...the ceiling is shaped like the
sky
So, it feels like climbing a mountain
I feel like I'm a pro
Why did you put your neck up?
Why did you look like a tagger?
How was the exercise?
I started sweating a lot
I think it's perfect for when I want to
exercise
I think it's good to do it indoors with
your family
If you don't have enough exercise, why
don't you try climbing at the Odaiba?
We will be waiting for you on the stage
Last one
What did you say?
What?
Hirota was good at doing the one where
Yasumoto was doing the fluffy one
That's right
When Yasumoto was climbing, Hirota was
doing the one where she was doing the
talk
I'm glad it wasn't the other way around
If Hirota was still there, Yasumoto
would have done the one where she was
doing the talk
I wanted to see that too
Next is Hashiwagi Nakayama's report on
dog cafe
First, let's start with the scene
Which one is better, the chair or the
chair?
Which one is easier to shoot?
While discussing with the cameraman,
they are thinking about the flow of the
report
Please put it in front of you
And the dog that will be their partner
appears
Can they report while controlling the
naughty dog?
Then, the broadcast starts
Now, the cafe where you can enter with
pets is popular
It seems that the broadcast is connected
Kashiwage-san, Nakayama-san
Hello everyone, I'm Ginnata Kashiwagi.
Today I'm at Venus Fort in Odaiba.
I'm at the pet shop on the first floor.
But Nakaima-san isn't here.
Oh, so this is the pattern.
Yes, so I want to go look for him.
Please do.
I hear a voice.
Nakaima-san?
Nakaima-san, what are you doing?
So cute.
Right now, this dog is in a free release
campaign.
So right now, he's playing with me.
Nakaima-san.
Who's playing with you?
Hello.
What's your name?
My name is...
Ten-kun.
I know that name.
You know that name, too.
I heard it because I knew it.
The two are full of comments.
Next, I will introduce the dog cafe.
Ten-kun and one more dog.
They are not alike.
The food looks delicious.
Ten-kun.
This is a report from the dog cafe,
right?
This is a dog cafe.
You can eat here with your dog.
Let's go.
Hello.
I can eat with my dog here.
That's right.
Do your best.
Do you have any recommendations for
food?
The most popular is this one called one
pack one bag.
One pack one bag?
It's a beef rib meat, but it's very
juicy.
Kashiwagi-san.
I want to eat it.
As a joke, can you say that we want one
pack one bag?
Should I say it?
Yes, please show us once.
The manager's reaction.
Then we should also...
Ten-kun wants one pack one bag, and we
should say sweet.
Sweet?
Should I say it?
I think we should say one pack one bag.
One pack one bag.
Yes.
That's right.
She laughed a little.
Shue-san.
The manager laughed a little.
This is for one-chan.
It's kind.
They ordered the recommended menu.
One pack one bag.
Yes, please.
Please.
Start the food report with Ten-kun.
Here it is.
Let's eat.
Wait a minute, Ten-kun.
Put the sauce on it.
It looks delicious.
Let's eat.
It's delicious.
The egg is fluffy
It melts in your mouth
It goes well with Hayashi rice
Hayashi rice
Nagayama-san, you ate it but you haven't
said your impression yet
It's only Hayashi rice
Yes, the rice is white
What is it?
This rice is so cute
Then, Ten-kun, shall we eat it too?
Then, I
I have something recommended for you
Then, please recommend it
Thank you
What happened?
Did you order something recommended?
I ordered another recommended product
Then, another one will come, so let's
eat it together
Wait
Eat together?
What is it?
Ten-kun is a dog, so he can't eat human
food
Please watch again.
Why? Why?
After this, the truth of Nakayama's
scream is clearly...
I'll have another one, so let's eat
together.
Can you eat together?
I can eat together.
What is it?
Ten-kun is a dog, so he can't eat human
food.
That's right.
Why? Why? Why?
Why?
Spicy
Thank you
Wait a minute
Sorry Ten-kun
He is the teacher of the interview that
I took care of before
Actually this man
Welcome to Smile Cafe
That's all for today's interview
Thank you
Last year, the interviewer tried to
knock out Nakayama
What happened to Nakayama?
I can't do this
Nakayama's enemy has changed to the
manager
What will happen to Nakayama?
Enichu Game Quest
Enichu Game Quest, which started last
year
The game is finally complete!
The release date is set for May 27th
This time, the Enichu members will
challenge the battle part
In the battle part, pull the ball like
this
And then, fire the pin in the center of
the screen
The number of pins dropped will be
damaged and the enemy will be defeated.
When you fire the bullets, the angle of
launch is important.
The point is to adjust the angle to drop
more pins.
This time, we will have a time attack to
see who can defeat the enemy first.
First, Hirota's challenge.
The angle is different.
Which one should I use?
This one! This one!
I got it! I got it!
Hirota has adjusted the angle of launch
well.
She has succeeded in dropping many pins.
I feel like I can do it until I get used
to it.
It's not easy.
It's close.
It's different.
This is it.
After that, Hirota has a hard time
adjusting the angle.
Continued from next time.
This is bad.
Go, go, go.
If you don't get the last turn, you
can't finish the game.
You can't aim?
The direction is bad.
In the end, Hirota's record is 3 minutes
and 22 seconds.
Hoshina and Kobayashi did a good job and
surpassed Hirota.
The last is the most difficult game,
Mayama's challenge.
I don't know.
This technique is useful because you can
stop its roll and stop it as you Royal還
potential.
Can you watch the top-left?
Oh, I can go after it.
Really?
R grandmother's R hey
Oh
巴掌
That was amazing!
The result is...
1st place is Mayama-san.
That's great!
I said I only pull the card.
But surprisingly, I pulled the card.
I want to know more about it.
The game called Ebitune will be released
on May 27th.
It's currently being pre-registered for
the fans.
The number of items you can get depends
on the number of pre-registered players.
For more information, please visit
Stardust Channel.
Next time, we'll have a reporter battle.
The two free-spirited players will be
playing.
Is it good?
Yes.
And Mayama, the super gourmet, will be
reporting.
I've been chosen.
Nakayama and the manager's battle of
I've been chosen. Nakayama and the
manager's battle of
this program was provided by the sponsor
you are watching.