This week's Ebi-Chu Tastas will continue
to explain the true feelings of love.
When I look at the coat, I can smile and
be chased.
Scary!
When the members judge the dream they
actually saw, they will be in an
unexpected situation.
Basically, it's a love-hate
relationship.
Kobayashi's true feelings and love-hate
desire are...
The true feelings of love are clearly...
Ebi-Chu Tastas Start!
The true feelings of love are...
Never Ending Ebi-Chu! Never Ending Ebi-
Chu!
Let's try various things in private
Ebisu Middle School
Ebisu Justice
This program is brought to you by the
sponsor you see
Thank you for watching
To reveal the true psychology of the
members, we have invited an expert to
thoroughly explain the heart.
Last time, Matsuno was watching the
producer in the street light.
The unexpected truth is clearly.
It's a buncho.
I've never thought about it.
But it's true psychology.
This time, we have a psychologist, Mr.
Hamon Nijihiko, to reveal the true
psychology of the members.
Please give us the next psychological
test.
Next is a dream diagnosis.
From the unconscious dream, you can read
the troubles and emotions that you
usually don't show.
This time, we will examine the dreams
that Ebi-Chu has recently seen.
What kind of feelings are hidden in Ebi-
Chu's dreams?
First, we will examine the dreams that
Matsuno has seen.
This dream is a dream I've been seeing
since I was 4 years old.
I've been playing in the park, and I've
been chasing a stranger.
I've been watching this since I was 4
years old.
I've been playing in a pipe like this.
Then a stranger comes and looks at me,
smiles and says,
I'm scared.
A dream that people chase in the park
that has been seen since the age of 4.
What kind of psychological psychology is
hidden in this scary dream?
First of all, the park is like a child.
So if you play in the park, you will be
chased by someone and you will have a
scary feeling.
This is a dream that Matsuno has been
feeling that he should not be a child
forever.
I thought I had to be an adult since I
was 4 years old.
It was pretty early.
I think I had a feeling that I had to
grow up.
You still haven't grown up, so you
haven't seen it yet.
Next, we will examine the dreams that
Kashiwagi has seen.
You were caught by Ryo-ko Yonekura and
Nami-e Amuro.
I was standing alone.
We came together, we were caught, and we
were breathing together.
I'm happy.
That's my dream
You both respect each other
I cried when I woke up
Really?
The dream of two people who Kashiwagi
admires
They shed tears of emotion
What is the meaning of this dream?
Yonekura san is a big actress
Amuro san is a big artist
Both of them represent their own future
So Kashiwagi san
I think both actresses and artists can
go to the top
Both can go?
I'm not an idol now
They are in the same position
No way!
There is only the back of the head
Amazing
Both can go to the top
I want to do both
So you want to go to the top
You admire each other, right?
Next, she will judge Mayama's dream
Mayama's dream is to be chased by a
dinosaur
and fall from the cliff when she is
about to be eaten
What is the result of the diagnosis?
A dinosaur represents the instinctive
part of the person
It represents the real self
The real self is a dinosaur?
Yes, the honest self
I think I need to show more of myself
So it connects with the previous one
Yes, it connects with the previous
psychological test
How much do I have no confidence in
myself?
How much do you have no confidence in
yourself?
You can be confident
Next, she will judge Kobayashi's dream
Ta-da
I can understand it
What does it mean?
I was waiting for the train at the
subway station
One person got off the train
It was dangerous
I thought it was dangerous
I thought he would come to his turn
I looked at the person in the train
Everyone was eating warm rice
What is this?
The passenger who was in the train got
off the train one by one
and started eating warm rice
Kobayashi is watching it
It's a strange dream
The truth is revealed
This is a strange dream.
What does this mean?
The dream of a woman's car is basically
to express love.
This is a big explosion.
The people who get off the train are the
people who are in love before them.
They eat other people's food.
There are people who have a good
relationship.
For example, a friend at school is
talking about love.
I envy them.
I want to see it too.
Are you interested in love?
I'm not interested in love. I'm just a
girl.
I'm a girl too.
You're a girl too.
I met a girl who was in the same class
as me.
She was dating a guy.
She was eating rice.
Kobayashi-san doesn't get off the train.
She said that she was not in love yet.
That's great.
Next, she examined the dream she saw.
When I was on the bullet train, there
were many people on it.
They flew like a roller coaster and took
me to the destination.
It's a colorful world.
What is a colorful world?
I saw a dream of a bullet train when I
was on it.
When I saw a big flying thing, there
were many people on it.
Nakayama was also on the sky?
Yes, they were flying in the sky and in
the forest.
What is the true truth of the dream that
Nakayama has?
I have a dream of falling in love.
Really?
So it's similar to Kobayashi's dream?
Yes.
Nakayama saw a dream of falling in love
like Kobayashi.
She analyzed it like this.
Nakayama-san's admiration is strong, but
it's also more abstract.
So it's like a love in fantasy.
Didn't I come out of the box?
You didn't come out?
The box like yesterday wasn't a closet?
It's a dirty box.
Further analysis of the dream of the
members.
I was very close with the Ebi-Chu
After this, Yasumoto's shocking
statement.
And before that...
Ebi-Chu Game Quest
Currently, Ebi-Chu's game project is in
progress.
Finally, the prototype version of the
Ebi-Chu game is released.
And...
Here it is.
The character design of the Ebi-Chu
members that appear in the game has also
been announced.
This time, for those who actually play
the game.
Pull it as much as you can.
Ah, yes.
It can move.
It's a good feeling.
It's kind of like a squat.
It's like a squat.
Oh, great.
Maita is strong.
So, if you touch this part, you can
change the type of the ball.
What?
What is that?
What is this?
Please try using the long one.
The long one?
That's it.
You can see where the red line is
pointed.
I see.
It's over there.
It's over there, isn't it?
Yes.
Let's go.
Wow!
Great!
Amazing!
Be careful.
This is the boss stage.
The ball has been changed to MX.
The ball.
Please use the ball to make a little
This ball is stronger than the round
one.
I see.
It's a song.
Bye-bye.
But why, why, why?
Oh, it's coming, it's coming
Oh, it fell down
Great
Victory!
This is the end of the first stage
So, the Ebi-Chuu members who enjoyed
playing the prototype version of the
game
Then, about the contents of the game,
such a request
I want a rubber ball
The rubber ball is flying
We will continue to deliver the latest
information, so please look forward to
it
A dream diagnosis that has been looking
through the hearts of the Ebi-Chuu
members
Next, Hoshina will be diagnosed
What Hoshina saw was a dream that a cat
chased away a ghost that lived next to
the house
What does this mean?
In this case, the cat, the pet Moka-
chan, is actually a part of me
And the ghost living next to me is a
family fight
I have to make it a friend
As a pet Moka
So, a kind of family feeling, a feeling
of a parent-child, appeared in the dream
Isn't that great?
This dream is the appearance of the
heart that wants to solve the family
problem
What Hoshina thinks is
I was going to travel in Ebi-Chuu from
the next day
It was the day I fought with Mamoto
about what to do with the bag
That's right, that's the heart
I want to make friends with my mother
That's amazing
Amazing
Next, she will be diagnosed with a dream
that Hiroto saw
For the time being, a dream that I ate a
lot
Did you eat a lot?
A dream that is full of appetite is a
dream that a person wants to try new
things
It's a very multi-faceted dream
That's right
You know a lot of things
I like things like that
The last one is a diagnosis of
Yasumoto's dream
Well
You wrote it roughly
The morning girl I admire is scouted by
Five-san
I'm happy that Yasumoto-san is not
included
I consulted with the members, staff, and
the school principal and my family
I decided to enter
Enter?
It's not a refusal
The dream that Yasumoto and Nanan saw
was changed from Ebi-Chuu
The shocking content that enters the
morning girl I admire
It would be a big deal if it was real.
But the path is still strict.
The lessons are also strict.
It's already hard.
I still want to return to Ebichu.
I said you went, so I'm coming.
It's a little bit like that.
That's right.
That's how I got along with the members
of Ebichu.
Even though it's a dream, what does the
dream of transferring from Ebichu mean?
I'm going to move to Ebichu with the
members.
Yasumoto is too concerned about the
existence of the current members.
It means that he is not free.
I feel like I'm worrying about people's
eyes.
And what is this person's dream?
Ogatsu, do you want to go?
I'm doing rock band in the future.
I want to do a 3-day live in Tokyo Dome
in the future.
I hope it comes true.
Thank you very much.
After that, the best of Ebichu in the
psychological battle.
Next is a psychological battle where the
members read each other's hearts.
Challenge the game to guess the real
thing without looking at the other
person's lie.
As you can see, the members.
The team leader Matsu and the team
leader Kashiwagi are divided into teams.
They deceive the other team with fake
acting.
Pay attention to the members' fake
First of all, who is being played by the
other person?
I got a question.
It's a really painful one.
Psychological battle.
First, the team leader Matsu challenges
the other person to deceive.
One of the team leader's feet are
stimulated.
Who is it?
Act as if you don't read the other
person's heart.
Is the reaction real or fake?
If you analyze the truth and find out
the truth, you will be the point of the
team leader.
The female staff is under the table.
The time limit is 30 seconds.
Let's go.
Massage start.
Everyone, please act.
10 seconds have passed.
10 seconds left.
8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Start.
It was good.
Yasumoto-san, you were like a
It hurts.
I should have been right.
There are various psychological battles.
Thank you for your viewing.
Who was really being stimulated by the
pressure?
The team of the backboard team analyzes
the other person's psychology
So, the team of the backboard team, who
was really being massaged?
1, 2
Rina
Hoshina, I see
Why?
First of all, there is no difference
between Rina and Kaho
The face after the game is too normal
The day after is fine, but after the
game is over?
Yasu, as Maayama said, is too loose
I see
When it started, it was like this
The face that is dangerous is the usual
face of Mirei
You didn't really have a face that is
dangerous
So, who was stimulated by the pressure?
The correct answer is
Rina
Everyone, please act
The face that is stimulated by the
pressure is Rina
Rina
Amazing
Yasu
Thank you
It's the first time you've acted
You did a good job
It's the first time
I thought it was over, but I was told
that you noticed the face
You acted that much?
I was told that you were a very good
actor
Yasumoto's X Japan was amazing
The team behind the scenes
Yasumoto's three-part play was seen
through, but the correct answer was not
Next is
The team behind the scenes will be asked
Who is eating Wasabi Sushi?
I got it
Following the psychological battle
The team behind the scenes will be asked
to cheat the other team
A large amount of Wasabi is put in the
leaf roll
Who is eating it?
You can cheat with a clear acting
Who is eating Wasabi Sushi?
Can the team behind the scenes see
through it?
Please eat
Hirotaka is a quiet person
Is this also acting?
Nakayama, please look this way
Nakayama
What?
I can understand
You are good at acting
Who is the member who really teased her?
The leader team is analyzing the other
person's heart rate
Riko?
1, 2, 3
Riko
Nakayama
What is the reason for this?
For the time being, Hinata is not here
Because she is crying
No, it will be more red
Her ears will be red
So you can tell by looking at her ears?
I think she really cried
Now, the answer is announced
Who was eating Wasabi-sushi?
Who really ate it?
It was Kashiwagi
It was very good
She cheated
It was difficult
It was really bad
Wait, where is Nakayama?
I don't know how to act
Nakayama is crying
Why are you crying?
Don't cry
Everyone can tell by looking at her
The leader team is confused by
Nakayama's natural reaction
And the battle is finally coming to the
final battle
Keyword battle
What does it mean?
This is a 1 on 1 psychological battle
The next psychological battle is keyword
battle
This is a simple psychological game that
you can't see it yourself and you can
guess the keyword written on your
forehead
First, you have to say the keyword that
is a hint to the other person
When you know your keyword, you answer
If you say the answer earlier than the
other person, you win
The team leader team chose Kobayashi and
Kashiwagi
Here
The keyword is Yasumoto
What?
And Mayama
I see
Keyword battle starts
Eye
Everyone has an eye
Head
Please say the keyword to each other
You still don't know the keyword?
Thank you for watching
I'll try
What?
Kashiwagi suddenly tries to get the
answer with the first hint
The hint is eye
Will she get the answer from there?
What is the answer?
Please say it to the camera over there
Mayama?
Riko
Nakayama
What is the reason for this?
For the time being, Hinata is not there
Because you are crying
No, it makes my eyes redder
Your ears get redder?
So you know the answer by looking at the
camera?
I think I cried for real
The answer is
Who was eating Wasabi sushi?
Who was eating it for real?
Kashiwagi
I was so scared
You cheated
It's difficult
You were eating it for real
Wait, what about Nakayama?
I didn't know how to act
I cried
You cried?
I didn't cry
Everyone can understand
The team leader, Nakayama's natural
reaction was wrong
The battle is finally coming to an end
Keyword battle
What does it mean?
This is a 1 on 1 psychological battle
The next psychological battle is keyword
battle
This is a simple psychological game
where you guess the keyword written on
your forehead
First, each person will say a word that
will be a hint to the other person
Answer when you know your keyword
If you say the answer earlier than the
other person, you win
The team leader chose
Kobayashi and Kashiwagi who are smart to
read the mind
The keyword is Yasumoto
And Mayama
I see
Keyword battle, start
Eye
Eye and eye
Anyone can do it
Odeco
Riko
Please say it one by one
Don't you know each other yet?
I'll say it
Kashiwagi suddenly aims for the correct
answer with the first hint
The hint is eye
Will she get the correct answer from
there?
What is the correct answer?
Please say it in front of the camera
Mayama
Oh
So, Kashiwagi wins
Amazing
Why?
It's amazing
Kashiwagi is amazing
You only said eye
How did you know?
The member over there is Yasumoto
So, I thought it was a member
If I said that the eye of the member in
Ebichu is big, it's Mayama
I talked about it with the member
It's because the eye is big
Amazing
I got it
The winner is Ura Bancho Team
This is amazing
Amazing
So, the hot-tempered psychological
battle was a god-like reading of
Kashiwagi
Ura Bancho Team won
Ebichu Tastas will have a coordination
battle with the members' fashion sense
Let's do this
Let's keep it
Let's go to the store
All members will be changed with the
real shopping
We will give the information to those
who missed Ebichu Tastas
Ebichu Tastas is on air on Star Dust
Channel
Let's buy something
I hope you can buy it from now on
That machine is available for 400 yen
per month
There are also many videos that are not
released
Now?
For more information, search on Star
Dust Channel
This program was provided by the sponsor
Mayama
The atmosphere is completely different
I learned from the staff recently
That's funny
Thank you for watching