The 31st single hit the charts!
This time, the center, Asuka Saito, who
has changed her graduation, is the only
one who sends a message to the remaining
members in Asuka, Nara Prefecture.
I'm looking forward to it.
Tonight is the final episode. The studio
is full of emotions.
Asuka, Asuka, shrine?
Cool.
That's cool.
It's a shrine.
Asuka Saito came to the shrine where
Asuka is.
She's aiming for the main shrine to
pray.
Is the hair curled?
Yes, it is.
The man is holding the hair with his
left hand, and the woman is holding it
with her right hand.
It is said that if you lift it up, you
will be happy.
It's terrible to climb up like this.
To be continued.
This is a stone lifting challenge.
Will she be able to find happiness in
the future?
Should I lift this?
How do you lift this with one hand?
It's impossible to lift this with one
hand.
This is heavy.
I can only lift this for a moment.
You can only be happy for a moment.
I don't want to be desperate to be
happy.
I definitely want to be happy.
This is the last.
I'm here.
I can't be happy.
How is it?
I want to be happy.
I've been lifted by this ugly person.
I'm here.
You don't know this feeling.
She wants to lift the bar without
letting go of the bar she put in.
She puts out all the guts she usually
doesn't show to the public.
Grab the happiness.
She's going from the bottom.
That's fine.
It's not going up.
Go!
She can do it.
She's going up.
She did it!
She's the best.
That was good.
I'm so happy.
I want to see everyone with this.
And this is her first time to pray at
Asuka's shrine.
This is the 31st single out now.
Hopefully we won't make him sad.
The best scene when I was in 4th grade
is when Kaki and Endo never sit on the
chairs in the dressing room.
Even if there are a lot of chairs, they
never sit down.
I think everyone in 4th grade is
serious, but I think there are many
people like that.
I'm not saying that you should do that,
but I want you to stay the same.
At that time, the 4th graders were also
talking about their memories with Asuka
Saito.
I want to know why Asuka and Saku-chan
got so close.
I don't know either.
When I was feeling down, Asuka was
always there for me.
She was always worried about me and she
was always there for me.
Endo is Asuka's child.
Asuka is a great name.
There was a reason for Asuka to be so
cute like my child.
Asuka was taking care of Endo like a
mother.
But Endo grew up with Asuka.
I feel like I'm watching Endo's growth.
Endo is a child of the weather.
Endo always says that the sun doesn't
suit him.
I'm a similar type to Endo, so I said
that a lot.
Endo will come to me when I have to be
angry.
I think it's okay.
I think it's okay to admit that you've
been angry a lot.
Endo was invited to my house.
I went to my house with Ume and Endo.
I bought a new sake and I want to open
it with Endo.
I think I've grown up.
But I was with Endo too much, so I have
to graduate.
I think the feature of Endo is the
distance between the screen and the
phone.
Is it close?
I recently thought that Saku-chan and
Endo are the same distance.
I think we've grown up with the same
distance.
I think we're similar because we're
together.
I think we're similar.
I think the smartphone case is a cover
type.
I think so, too.
I hide it with my eyes when I laugh.
I hide it with my hands.
Asuka's Japanese-style restaurant.
Tsutsui is a warming-up of the
revolution.
What is it?
I think Tsutsui is still a revolution.
I'm looking forward to the day when I'll
be awakened.
This song is just behind me.
Even if I'm separated from the left and
right, I'm the only one who's doing the
same choreography.
I want to meet him because he looks like
he's doing this.
Kanagawa is the ultimate weapon of the
north or the ideal type of fox.
Which one is it?
I've been in the second row for a year.
I've been evaluated by seniors and
adults.
I have the image of taking over all the
work in the north.
I don't feel like I'm losing my love for
the north.
I want him to be the representative of
I thought I had a dark image.
But I was told that I had a bright image
and that I was a bright person.
I was told that I was the most desperate
at that time.
I think that's when I got my energy
back.
I've been thinking about a lot of things
since then.
I've been feeling bright since that day.
I was happy to hear the words I wanted
to hear the most.
Shibata is a real, innocent, and a good-
for-nothing.
I don't know what it means.
I always have the image of laughing and
I look very bright.
I have the image of a villain and a
heroine that I don't have.
I think that's when I was the best.
I was the best because I talked a lot
about my grandmother.
I often talk about my family.
I was a little similar to my mother when
she was young.
I thought I was going to get along with
her.
I like family and cynical stories.
That's why I was killed by Shibata.
I really liked him.
Tamura is a mannequin of Nogizaka.
I think Nogizaka is a person who sells
clothes.
If Nogizaka becomes very poor and sells
his clothes to someone,
I think that if he puts a picture of
Tamura on it, all the girls in the world
will want to buy it.
I think that clothes that all Nogizaka
girls wear suit him.
After the selection announcement,
they called me.
I was at the end of the third row of the
previous underground formation.
Suddenly, I felt like I was coming.
That's not true.
So I was worried.
I was told that I was chosen from the
third row because there were people who
were watching me.
I was not surprised at all.
I thought I would think about it, but it
was very encouraging.
I was able to convey it in words.
Hayashi
Otawa group
I'm proud of you.
I'm a very unknown person, but I think
everyone thinks I'm a little strange.
I think I'm the only one in the forest
who uses the power of the little
finger's claw to make people think I'm a
strange person.
I think they're having fun, so I'm Otawa
group.
I think the band is a bandman.
I can sing, and I'm really good at it.
I don't know why, but I want him to say,
when he graduates from Nijizaka,
he'll quit because of his musicality.
That's the worst.
What was that?
You're always being praised.
I get worried when people praise me.
I don't think I'll ever be praised for
lying.
I just come in with a smile.
I'm a bad singer.
The persimmon is from Makoto Shinkai.
What does that mean?
You're talking about Shinkai again.
The purity around persimmons is beyond
my imagination.
I feel that the purity is more than the
inner side of persimmons.
I don't feel weak, but I want to protect
them.
I don't think there were many idols who
made me feel that way.
I want to appeal to Makoto Shinkai.
Persimmons have a perfect purity for a
heroine.
I want to use persimmons when I make a
live-action movie.
Hayakawa is a woman from Anpan to Anpan.
What is this?
I always thought that Hayakawa was
always showing everyone one side of her
face,
making people laugh,
and avoiding the others for no reason.
But the Anpanman hero
has a different look on the outside,
but inside, she has a sense of justice
that never changes.
So I thought that Hayakawa has changed
from Anpanman to Anpanman,
but now she has a different face.
I think she's trying to move forward in
a good way.
Yumiki is a broken speaker.
You're saying bad things directly.
It's so easy to understand.
It's like a broken record.
Well, records are like that, right?
When it bends or scratches, you know
it's repeating the same thing.
No, Yumiki is really like a speaker.
She's always talking normally, but she's
like,
is there a time difference?
I have to think about it and connect it,
or I can't talk.
A broken speaker.
That's what I'm thinking.
But if that's Yumiki,
there's no need to fix it.
Sometimes when a speaker is broken,
you want to hit it.
There are speakers that break down.
So I want to see both broken Yumiki and
normal Yumiki.
I'm looking forward to the future.
I made it from milk.
For beauty.
But when I think back,
I've always been told that Asuka is a
second-generation student.
Originally, there wasn't much
difference.
Especially since Ayane is the only one
left now.
Ayane is the same age, so it's special.
Suzuki is...
It's a mild secret miso.
She has a refined face, so she makes the
place look gentle.
We have a lot of cute girls, but when
Suzuki comes in, it's gentle in the
sense that something is closed.
Ayane has a public image that the world
thinks of her, but she has the exact
opposite personality.
But she's been hiding it for 10 years,
and I think it's been very good lately.
So I think it's a mild secret miso.
If Ayane is there, it will be delicious.
At that time, the last two students of
the first and second grades were having
a chat with Asuka.
What made me happy at the dressing room
recently was that Asuka had been reading
books all the time.
But I didn't know what she was reading
while covering it.
I asked her what she was reading, and
she told me that she was reading this.
I was so happy that I could get to know
Asuka.
Ayane always has the same timing when
she's laughing.
Ayane is the only one who listens to my
favorite books.
But she hasn't allowed me to go home
yet.
It's a place where someone has to break
through.
I was going to go, but I couldn't.
Did you say that?
I said, let me go.
I thought it was impossible.
I think I know why you don't want me to
go home.
I think I'll watch you all the time.
I agree.
When I went to Chima and Maaya, the
first and second grades,
Chima and I had a lot of fun drinking.
Maaya was a good girl.
Asuka is a little bit distant when she's
with four people.
But I took a step back.
I wanted to get physical distance with
her.
I went to Chima and Maaya, but I was
scolded by her.
I was scolded for not eating rice.
Really?
I agree.
Asuka's rice.
Asuka and Asuka.
Asuka Temple.
Here we are. Asuka Temple.
Asuka Temple is the last temple that
Asuka came to.
The first official shrine in Japan was
built in 596.
The Asuka-temple, which is said to be
the oldest Buddha statue, is enshrined.
It is said to be the oldest Buddha
statue in Japan.
It is said that the year is 1414.
The first female emperor named Suiko,
who was in Japan, said,
Let's make it.
It is a temple in Asuka, so it is called
Asuka-temple.
It is also a temple for fire, but the
place has never moved.
Oh, I see.
So, 1400 years ago, it was called
Shotoku-temple.
So, I'm sure you'll be here.
I think you were praying for the same
thing.
It is a place that can be said to be the
entrance to Japan.
It concludes this hit prayer.
What is not here?
The Great Hit Prayer
Ask Any-ASKR
Where Are We Going to at The End?
Thank you for watching!
We've been carrying a lot of things.
We've been carrying all the important
things of Nogizaka with us.
We don't put pressure on ourselves or
show our attitude.
But we can feel that they're trying to
put their feelings into the song.
I want to dance and send them out with a
smile.
What is the last message for Akimoto?
Akimoto Manatsu is the last supper.
What?
Manatsu is always talking to the
members.
She often talks about what she will eat
at the end of her life.
She often talks like a girl.
I think she is the last supper of the
first generation.
We are the last supper of the first
generation.
I hope she will graduate at the end.
That's why she is the last supper.
Iwamoto is the No.1 in terms of gender.
Iwamoto has a great juniority.
It's exquisite.
The way she mixes honorifics and slang
is all just right.
I feel like she's my ideal junior.
Why is she so cute?
Let's go!
I'm Genji Hinadan.
I'm Sakaguchi.
I'm always working hard secretly.
I don't appeal to anyone.
I'm always waiting with my back down and
in a forward posture.
I have the image that they are waiting
for me.
I trust them.
I've said it many times, but I forgot.
Asuka curry, Asuka vegetables.
I only have rice.
He breaks the rules of Asuka.
My fingers may be buried.
Ouch!
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
Ouch!
She is a little bit nervous.
I'm fine.
Don't you change?
Yes.
Out!
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
She is a little bit nervous.
Please subscribe to this channel.
I think I'm a little disappointed
because I'm in the group I was in.
I've seen a lot of people having fun
with a lot of people who were full of
heads and crying before this number of
live shows.
I've seen a lot of that throughout the
year, so I hope everyone will continue
to grow.
I'm looking forward to seeing more of
Nogizaka without me.
I don't have much time, but I'm really
looking forward to it.
Akimoto, you've been crying a lot
lately.
I'm sure you've seen a lot of people
graduate, but you're still here.
Each of us had a lot of things that we
didn't know about.
But I know what she wants to say.
I'm so proud of her for being with us
for 11 years.
I see. She's here now.
That's Asuka's personality.
She's a little bit hard to talk to.
Asuka is also a little bit hard to talk
to.
She's looking up.
But a lot of people are watching.
It's amazing. Each one is interesting.
When I hear the story, I can feel it
all.
Asuka is a great power.
I thought there was no more story about
Akimoto and Sakaguchi.
At the end, it was a running race.
But I was told that you were a comedian.
I'm glad. I thought I'd forgotten.
No, no, no, no.
She's coming to the end.
But she's always like this.
I'll go whenever I want.
Managawa was also called a fox.
I'm so happy.
I'm going to do my best.
I'm glad.
It's great to hear the reason.
I'm so happy.
It's like a symbol of the Nogizaka.
I really like Asuka.
I said Asuka-chan.
I'm sorry.
That's what happens.
Are you two so close?
You're like children.
We've been together for so long.
When we're apart, I feel like I'm going
to be with you.
That's great.
Riki Choshu and Kensuke Sasaki are the
same.
It's like that.
I want you to be with us.
What was Sakaguchi?
I'm a comedian.
The music video for the Saito Asuka solo
song will be released.
Starting today, the birthday live will
start on mobile.
The ticket for the live is on sale!
I'm Mizuki Yamashita. I'm going to open
the lottery.
I wonder if I'll get anything.
Ticketing has changed from taxicab and
bus tickets to receipts.
Eh? Oh! Please subscribe to my channel!