Ebichu Tastas has started
Ebichu Tastas this week is Ebichu Tastas
hotel
The secret of the members is revealed in
private talk
In addition, the second part of the
close-up video of the Yatsui Festival
Ebichu Tastas Start
We ate them for meals.
We hope you enjoy it.
Toyama elementary school students add a
lot of things!
You can watch this program through our
sponsor's 적 Ludenio Akihiko
I can't read it!
That's the best!
Mayama and Takiru
Chue is the
A, B, C, E, D
Chue
You are doing reaction
Mayama is different from the usual
Yes
I've been here since the beginning
Mayama's outfit is like a snack
No
I'm not, I'm just a normal person
You are wearing a normal outfit
It's related to the theme of today
Mayama's outfit?
What's the theme of today?
It's a hotel
I see, it's a hotel
With a casual outfit
And
Hello
Other members are also wearing a casual
outfit
They are watching us
We've been waiting for you
I wanted this reaction
Everyone is wearing a casual outfit
This is a really private outfit
Let's go to the fashion check
Let's go
Who is the fashionable version of Chue?
Fashion check start
First, Yasumoto
My fashion theme is
A casual outfit
I'm wearing a casual outfit
Like this
Do you like this hairpin?
I like colorful hairpins
I'll show you
It's good
You don't wear skirts
I see
What's the fashion point of Hirota?
The fashion point?
This and this are similar
I see
I decided last night
You often wear the same shoes
I show the same
The shoes are also similar
This shoe is amazing
It's like you dropped three fighter jets
It's like an American fighter jet
Next, Hoshina
I chose white and light blue
It's like summer
The hat is also like summer
Thank you for watching
I don't look good in my private clothes
Really?
Yes
Look
You look good
Really?
You don't look good
I talked to my mom yesterday
We talked about how we don't look good
What did your mom say?
She said I look like a child
Wait a minute
You are so focused
I was watching
You are singing
I was listening to music
You were singing at 6am
I was like, I'm going to sleep
What are you waiting for?
I'm going to sleep in my private clothes
I'm going to wear rough clothes
It's not rough
It's rough
It's not like what you said
It's different
I'm wearing a suit
You are wearing a suit
I have a lot of monotone
I'm wearing monotone this time
I see
Matsuno is a model
I've done it before
Let's see the real walking
It's crazy
They decided to watch the runway
All of us
One, two, three!
He was playing
Next, Kashiwagi's clothes
And Kashiwagi
Bacon egg
It's amazing
This is what Naomi Watanabe wore
I saw it when I was watching
Did you happen to wear it?
No, I imitated it
You thought it was cute?
You saw it on TV and thought it was
good?
Yes
What is the theme?
The theme is bacon egg
That's what happens
Next, check out Kobayashi
What is the theme?
The whale that peeped
I had 3 different colors of this shirt
Really?
Why did you have it?
It was cute so I bought it
I was sitting on the train and I wore
the same shirt
I was surprised and I looked at the
store and I saw 2 different colors
So I bought it
You wore it yesterday
It's not this color
This is the most popular one
It's the first one
Finally, check out Nakayama
Did you borrow your father's shirt?
That's terrible
It's not like that
These kinds of shirts are popular these
days
Big T-shirts are popular
Big T-shirts
I bought a shirt that looks like a dress
It's popular
Is this a ribbon on the head?
A ribbon on the head
Is this a point?
It's a point
It's a red one
I see
At that time, they finally tried to
enter the house
Welcome everyone
We've been waiting for you
It's on air
I haven't opened it yet
Rock band Hiya's vocalist, Kaiki Ogata
Today, he's wearing a very plain fashion
What?
This is my house
I've earned a lot of money with this
Tastas
I've built my house
Tastas?
Yes
I've never seen it before
It's the least popular one
Hoshida, your voice was quite loud
For some reason, he left Ogata and Iharu
in the house
The nightclub is starting
I stayed at my house once
Oh really?
You were talking to your mom and didn't
know
You went to your house at night
After the shoot, I called my mom and she
said, bring Hina home
Did you bring a set of your own?
My mom was so excited that she bought
pajamas for us
That was a little bit of a surprise
But it looks fun
Did other members have scary memories
during the tour?
Yes, it was a long time ago
When we were in Osaka, we talked in our
room and suddenly the door opened
For example, the room was so excited
that it was like a
Yagamashi-zono Gacha Gacha Gacha
Wait, wait, wait
I was scared and went up
We ran
Then I was like, you're the one who ran
That was the most scary
Was it different?
Do you have any memories of the hotel in
Nakayama?
When we were in the room for the first
time, we were setting up the room and
slept
Then we woke up and slept twice
Then we had to leave the room
Then we went to the hallway and Ka-ho
slept together
You were sleeping at the same time
You were saying that you were in a mood
We were crying
I was crying and I was saying sorry
I was so scared
Ka-ho was crying so I couldn't cry
There's evidence left in the making
Here is the evidence
I'm sorry
I slept in the room for about 3 minutes
I packed everything
Kobayashi was crying and saying sorry
It was like Nakayama
I was so scared that I set up the alarm
early in the morning
Thank you for watching
I didn't wake up but I woke up and
thought I was late
I was eating squid somen and I was still
late
Why did you eat squid somen?
Why did you eat squid somen when you
were late?
I was eating breakfast
I was talking about the type of
breakfast
I was eating squid somen because I
thought it was dangerous
There is no speed up when you eat squid
somen
Next
After this, they will continue to stay
Next, Yatsui Festival Special
Last week, Yatsui Festival
Gouka Musician and Ebi-Chu
Next, Yuzan and Tabura
They want to be magical girls
They have been on the stage of Rock in
Japan Festival for only half a year
They are the new generation of talented
band
What is their impression of Ebi-Chu?
Please wait a moment
Ebi-Chu is powerful and has 8 members
They are the new members
Next, Chichin Pui
Next, Chihara and Chihara
They are the new members
Next
Let's call them
Ike-chan
Ike-chan is famous in Ebi-Chu Family
Next, Eda-Sakagumi
So far, we have been supporting Emi-chu
and many other people.
We have also provided songs.
With the collaboration with history.
Ganbatteirutochu
Haruki Haruki
And the end of the performance, Ike-
chan.
With sleeves on sleeves.
Chuuen
Chuuen who was coming on a private
stage.
I told you not to call me.
Hello, Chuuen.
Please support Emi-chu with Ike-chan.
Bye-bye.
Do it, dance.
Dance is not me.
I am Gundam.
After the live, Ike-chan was directly
attacked.
Really, usually.
The purity that is not different from
the high school students.
I have been providing.
No matter what job, I will work hard to
be pure and forward.
I think it's a good thing of Emi-chu.
And the last one who appeared.
This person.
Shirazu Shibusa.
Album KINPACHI's recording song.
Shirazu Shibusa was in charge of the
arrangement of the song.
In addition, on the stage.
Bass Ken Ken.
Genuine bassist Ken Ken who is active in
many bands.
Then, shopping specifications and
waiting.
Special version.
Gotta get Todd Adult background music!
Deadly Dive
St 77
Sur隊
Haazard
What a Sunday, what a Sunday
The sun is shining, what a Sunday
The day will come soon after I wake up
What a Sunday, what a Sunday
The sun is shining, what a Sunday
What a Sunday
I'm not going to tell you anything about
the day
Give me back my time
Eh? Why?
What a Sunday, what a Sunday
See you next week!
It's my first time playing at a venue
with this atmosphere
It was very fresh
The audience is good
I felt the same vibe as the people who
play Rice or Dragon
There is an infinite possibility
We can't decide what we can't do, we
just keep trying new things
Let's play together next time
When I asked the members how they felt
It was fun
And Chuuhei was smiling in the back
The moment he got on the stage, he was
like,
He was pulling me
It was funny
It was too much fun
I was so excited that I couldn't speak
I don't know where the 1st to 10th place
is
Our first live performance was in
Shibuya
There were so many things to think about
It was a very exciting feeling
It was fun
Each song was played by a different
person
I felt the luxury of this Yatsui
festival
Thank you for watching!
They came and had fun.
I think it's great.
It was fun to collaborate with many
people.
It's been a while since we did a live
house.
I was very happy to feel the heat of the
audience.
It was hot and exciting.
Ike-chan was also into dancing and
dancing with lyrics.
They did running and everyone was
excited.
It was a lot of fun.
It was my first time meeting Ike-chan.
I didn't feel like I'd seen her for the
first time.
I'm glad I was touched by her.
It was a very hot live house.
It was very hot.
I think I was sweating a lot.
I'm already dry.
Ike-chan, you're not good at running.
Please come to the next year's course.
Please come.
Sakura Ebizu is in the front row.
Sakura Ebizu is finally on the road.
They will be at the world's largest idol
festival.
Sakura Ebizu is preparing for the first
stage.
It's been a few days until the show.
They have no live experience, so they
have a plan.
It's four days before the show.
I invited Sakura Ebizu to the Mezamashi
live performance.
I invited them to learn from their
seniors.
Mezamashi live performance in Odaiba
Yume Tairiku.
They suddenly called Sakura Ebizu to get
an image of the live performance.
This is the first time Sakura Ebizu has
met Ebichu.
I'm a senior who I admire.
I want to see them properly and be able
to admire them.
Sakura Ebizu is nervous.
I can't stop.
That's also a reason.
They are admiring Ebichu and jumping
into the idol world.
Finally.
Good morning.
I'm Chiyuki Ebichu, the morning
champion.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Sakura Ebizu, the first time.
I'm Chiyuki Ebichu, the first time.
I'm scared.
I'm scared of scary girls.
I don't want to meet everyone on the
street.
Sakura Ebizu will have a live
performance after this.
I want you to enjoy watching it.
Please do your best.
I'm looking forward to it.
What was your first impression of
Ebichu?
I admired it.
I'm happy to meet you.
The Ebichu live performance will begin.
At the same time as the start, the venue
is full of tension.
Sakura Ebizu looks at the live
performance seriously.
And.
Thank you very much.
The live performance is over.
Did you get the image of the live
performance?
I was watching the live performance
after the end.
I thought it was Ebichu.
I will do my best to achieve this.
I will do my best to create a live
performance that many people will see.
I will do my best.
Please do your best.
Sakura Ebizu got the power from Ebichu.
And.
Next time.
Sakurami Bye.
The first stage of the Tokyo Idol
Festival.
The second half of the hotel.
Girls talk in pajamas.
What will happen?
I'm not looking at the side.
I'm looking at the side.
Next time.
This program was provided by the sponsor
you are watching.