Please subscribe to this channel!
Thank you for having me today.
I'm Nagoya Red Akimoto Honoka from Team
Setsu.
I'm Kanami Kotouzuji from Chotoki.
It's a strange feeling.
We talk while being filmed.
It's the first time.
We go out to eat together.
I'm nervous.
It's different from when we were eating.
You're a lot of adults.
I'm surprised that we're doing this.
We've been doing this for a long time.
We've been talking with many people.
I'm happy that Kanami is the first.
Thank you.
It's fluffy.
Kanami is...
Thank you.
Thank you for watching.
We formed a unit called MIMIZU.
We were in the same team.
I was in the same team as you.
We were in the same team more than 4
years ago.
We recorded a song together.
I thought you were a great singer.
Thank you.
I was happy to have you.
I didn't have any friends.
Thank you.
I was happy to have you.
I want to be with you.
You are cute.
I went to the BBQ restaurant.
Where is it?
Harajuku.
I went there.
I went to the beef brisket restaurant.
I was impressed by the food.
Really?
It was a desk for two people.
It was like a couple seat.
I was surprised to see the order.
You went to the restaurant.
I couldn't get on the desk.
I was happy.
I was wondering what to do.
I was wondering if I could eat it.
You asked me a lot.
I wonder if I can eat it.
It was fun.
I was wondering how you could eat it.
You are really cute.
You said that the noodles were
delicious.
You said that you liked the noodles.
You are cute.
It was delicious.
You are a good girl.
I went to the restaurant.
I went to eat curry udon.
I went to eat Korean food.
Recently, I was invited to the place
where I ate the spaghetti and the
noodles.
You said that you wanted to go.
We invited you.
You are cute.
We will go soon.
It was fun.
You decided the next restaurant.
I decided.
I was happy to have a chance to go with
my juniors.
You talked about your worries.
I couldn't solve it.
I was happy.
I didn't have a senior who could talk
about anything.
I was the first in the group.
I didn't have a chance to talk to you.
I was happy.
You are cute.
You can say anything.
I'm the only one who says anything.
How many years will you have?
It's not a super-sukisai, but a
tsukimiki-sai.
It's the 8th anniversary.
That's right.
8th anniversary.
It's a pretty big year.
That's right.
It's already our 10th anniversary.
And we've been in the group since we
were the first members.
There were a lot of members changes.
There's a lot of members changes, so
there's Taki-senchan.
That's right.
That's great.
I'm going to cry.
I'm going to read a lot of Taki-
senchan's SNS.
It's so cute.
I can't stop.
I'm a member of the same school as
Shiko.
That's why I'm in the same school as
Nishiyama.
That's right.
It's the first single I've ever
produced.
I thought it was cute.
My voice, my voice, my voice.
Everything.
And the song.
I'm the best in that music video.
Thank you.
Even if I look back now,
I was probably in the first year of high
school.
So I was so cute.
I was like, what are you doing?
I was so good.
I used to be a scary person.
Don't you think so?
When I listen to my old songs,
I think my voice wasn't like this.
There is.
I'm a young person.
I wonder if the people who watch the
video now
enjoyed it.
I think I'm getting old.
Thank you.
Thank you for watching!
What did you think of me at first?
This question is funny.
What was your first impression?
At first, I watched you on YouTube.
You were like a fan.
You were so cute.
Your voice was cute, too.
But when I saw you in person, I was
like...
I was really excited.
I saw it in the book.
You were really cute.
You were like a woman.
You were cute with a smile.
I was happy to meet you.
You were kind.
I thought you were beautiful.
You were beautiful and quiet.
I saw it in a video.
You were like a girl around you.
I thought you were beautiful.
But you were very considerate.
You were kind.
I thought you would be a good group.
I was really happy to meet you.
You were cute.
I was surprised by your face.
You can say that.
You were cute.
I'm happy.
Thank you.
We are both happy.
I have a compliment.
I don't have a compliment.
It's difficult.
I can say this, but I didn't sing at
all.
But the director of the shooting was in
charge of the center.
I think the staff at the top thought
that I had to stand out somehow.
I've only been talking about the lines
since the beginning.
I've been talking about it all the time,
but I'm talking about it even more now.
So when I thought that, I thought that
Kanami had a lot of lines.
So I thought I'd be happy to be able to
sing.
I'm also a great singer.
That's right. You told me that.
I thought that the people who heard
Honaka's lines would be attracted to it.
Really?
I didn't think I'd have such a cute
voice.
I was happy to hear that you said it was
a cute voice.
I want to sing more and work harder on
the lines.
So let's work hard on the lines from now
on.
But recently Kanami is singing a lot,
isn't she?
No, I'm not.
Really?
But I'm not singing.
You're singing?
Really.
But when the singing part comes, I get
anxious.
I know.
That's right.
What should I do?
Tokisumi-chan, how do you decorate?
I take all of them.
All together?
Yes.
I take all the good parts.
That's right.
I use them.
I see.
I have songs that I decide which part is
which.
But I take all of them.
But when I take them, I don't think the
rap part or the part I sing will come.
So I don't take them.
But I take all of them.
But when I have to practice, I don't
think the rap part will come.
But I don't think the part I sing will
come.
I'm sorry.
I taught you something strange.
Kanami is always trying her best.
It's okay.
Why?
But when I think I shouldn't sing, I
think about it.
I think I should do a fake.
I know.
I'm told to do it once.
I'm here too.
I want to see Kanami's recording.
Can I sit next to you?
I can't talk.
I think it's hard.
I want to see the recording.
I want to get the rhythm of the staff
there.
When I do solo live, the staff who plays
the sound of the PA,
They play the sound of the PA with a
bright light.
I see.
The members are taking the rhythm.
It's hard.
It's been 8 or 10 years.
It's hard to do it.
I think I can do it if I do it.
I thought so too.
I'm serious.
Thank you.
Now that we've talked with you, Let's
finish our interview!
I wanna ask you some questions, and show
if you don't mind.
As we've told each other, you were the
сы RPG player.
Thank you for watching.