Coco Yunonoka's Game of Hearts and Minds
CocoYunonoka's Game of Hearts and Minds CocoYunonoka has been working together in Ebinaka for almost a year. This time, they will further deepen their understanding of each other and enhance their sense of unity through "The Game of Conveyance of the Heart"!
Cocoyunoka's
The game of "Sincerely Believe"!
A game in which all participants answer the questions given to them. You must not only answer the questions, but also imagine what the other members are thinking while answering.
Let's go to the first question.
What is your most memorable live performance since joining Ebichu?
A live performance?
Oh, my God!
This is... ummm...
Is that it? Is everything okay?
Yuno?
What?
The first one or the second one?
The later, the later!
Closer to the recent one.
That's it, isn't it?
I already said the answer!
This is the one.
They were all impressive, but...
But I'm not so sure about this one.
University Arts and Sciences Festival
University Arts Festival
Well, this one!
Yuno. I was torn between this and @JAM.
It was our first show.
Well, I guess you could say it's the later one.
It's a big arts and crafts festival!
Unity!
What do you think of the EBichu merchandise?
Merchandise? -?
Speaking of merchandise... ?
We'll use what we use most often?
What we use?
Wait! This is...
This is a hard one to guess...
Let's see... 。。。。
I think Yuno and the others use it the most.
They're the most used goods!
Indeed...
I wonder if this is right...
I wonder if it's not...
Wait!
Wait...
Are there different kinds? No, thank you.
Yes, there are.
You don't have to use it often.
They even wear them over their outfits.
Hey, no!
Yuno!
That's your answer!
I wrote it down, didn't I? That's the answer.
I said the answer.
Let's go then!
Hoodie!
I know, right?
I know!
I used to wear it to school!
Oh, that's right!
I didn't have a black jacket for school.
I wore my own light green one!
That hoodie is so cute!
Yuno...
Yuno already... Hey!
You're giving too many hints!
Don't talk anymore... You're giving too many hints!
Don't talk...
What would you say is the most popular love song among the Ebichu's?
You know, there is one, right?
Yes, I do!
There are a couple I'm not sure about.
Have you ever played them live?
Maybe we've done it live.
Oh...
What, what, what, what?
Huh, huh, huh, huh!
Let's do that one!
Let's do that one.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
That one!
I know, that way.
That's it!
That way. Okay, okay!
Just the other day, over there.
Right!
But Yuno's thinking.
They're both just a day away.
Oh! Well, well, well...
But this way, right?
Yes, this way.
Okay, okay.
OK!
Let's go!
Happy End to Sore kara
Heart to heart!
No more talking!
Yuno, no talking!
Yuno shh!
What would you call an emo song by Ebichu?
There are so many!
I don't know.
I think I might have practiced it the most.
Not the most, but...
I practiced it a lot.
Practiced?
Oh, I see what you mean!
OK, OK!
The four of us sang it with Hinatachan and the others.
Oh, wait?
Wait? Which one?
Let's write it down. Let's write it down!
Let's write it down.
Wait a minute...
Maybe it's a match!
That's it!
Earphones. Riot
Anytime, Anywhere
Earphone Riot.
It's not a "mo"!
Because you practiced with Hina-chan!
That's why.
That's why I didn't get it!
Before the talent show.
I said, "Let's just loosen up and sing.
"Let's sing a song.
I played the song and jumped up and down.
The memory of Earphone Riot
Too big!
Inside me.
It changed the way I sang.
Oh, I see.
And it was the first song with 9 members.
I thought it might be emo.
Eneini!
I know Eneini too!
It's emo, isn't it?
You're right...
Which song is the hardest to dance to?
It's hard to dance to...?
The dance is difficult...?
That's the one!
That's the one I'm thinking of.
The hardest song was...
A little bit...
I don't know...
It's difficult!
That one!
Um...
Well...
Well, it's hard to swing, and...
Not physically!
Not physically! I don't know.
Is it a upbeat song?
Emo song? I mean...
What's that?
What is it? Which one is it? I don't know.
I don't know.
I don't think I'm going to fit!
I'm scared!
Blue Blue Blue Star Name
After School Getaway Box Rock 'n' Roll MX
Tissue.
I know them all!
All different!
Tissue, it's hard!
Tissue, can't you tell which one is which?
Oh, my God.
Like the height.
The blue, blue, blue star is hard to name, too.
Left and right.
It's hard to tell which is which.
You're right
I was confused with Ai's rental.
The first last of Ai no Rental
Indeed, indeed, indeed!
It was hard to find the right expression, wasn't it?
Yes, it was difficult to express it, wasn't it?
Which food seems to be the most popular among the members of Ebichu?
That one, right? That's it!
That one? That's the one!
The one Cocona sometimes wants to eat.
Is it Cocona's? Or Yuno?
She wants to eat it.
Oh! Then I know already!
Do older sisters like it too? That's it.
There's a member who like!
Ah! I get it!
I like them too much.
Ramen Noodles Yakiniku
Meat.
We're almost in agreement here, right?
Ramen...
Didn't she say she wanted ramen?
But she doesn't say that often?
You're right.
She wants meat.
And Hinatachan like it a lot.
Not at all...
I don't fit in anymore.
Let's work hard!
What do you think of Mayama Rika?
Recently...
You know, the one she did in that show?
Yes, she did!
She was the first one in the latest thing.
You were the first one in the latest thing...?
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
Well, this is definitely a match.
Is that right?
The first thing they did recently...?
Recently
Recently ・・・・・ Well...
It's not... It's not a hobby or something, is it?
I mean, it's not a hobby...
It's not a hobby, it's more like... I mean...
I'm enjoying it. I'm having fun with it.
Enjoying it?
Anime
Muscle training
Muscle Training
I didn't know the "muscle" in muscle training.
Which one is it?
I thought it was something like this.
Oh~~~ too bad!
Well, it's close enough.
Oh, no!
It's not a cartoon!
It's definitely an anime!
Oh, surely...!
We did it at the beginning of the recent FC event, didn't we?
I'm sorry, I'm a little slow on the uptake.
What do you mean by "Ayaka Yasumoto"?
Isn't that it?
It's that one...
All the time, all the time!
All the time!
Because it's...
It's famous, isn't it?
Tomato
Songs
Sauna
Everyone is different!
Wait a minute!
These have been our catchphrases for years!
"Lycopene girl." "I love tomatoes."
Why Yuno and Nonoka?
Aya's image is that of a singer.
That's true.
Sauna's a recent thing, right? But...
It's not like she's been doing it for a long time.
That's the image I have of her. Like, all the time...
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I wrote this in a moment.
But they're all different.
Everyone was like, "This is it! I was like...
It's different~...
I'm going to think about it and get it out.
Let's think about it and talk about it!
Let's think about it and talk about it! Let's talk about it!
What do you think of Hoshina Mirei?
This is the one that Mayama-san often praises
OK, OK, OK!
The one Mayama-san often praises
Mayama-san often praises?
Any more hints as far as I don't know?
The person who sees it...
Someone who sees it...
Maybe a girl would like it.
They'll be like, "Wow! They'll be like...
Maybe it's the same here.
You admire it, don't you?
What a girl would love to have!
A girl's dream.
I get it!
"Speaking of Mirei..."
Legs...
Legs.
When Mirei did the last photo shoot...
Mayama-san said
"Let's get those legs out."
He said.
"Cut them more!" something like that
She said that!
What do you mean by "Hinata Kashiwagi"?
When I think of Kashiwagi Hinata.
That's all I can think of.
Which one?
I...
I don't know what to say.
I'm talking about what Yuno and the others like.
"Yuno's favorite thing"?
Not that?
What?
It's not that one or that one? Not that one?
Not that one or that one?
That's what they do at live shows, right?
That's right.
It's one or the other, right?
It's one or the other at live shows, right?
But isn't that it?
You know, like at the college arts and crafts.
You know, the big show, you know.
You know what we did?
You know, Hina-chan...
I like her too!
Hina-chan did that.
At the talent show.
Then that way, right?
That way!
The dance.
Dance.
Yuno, I'm not sure whether to go for the yakiniku or not!
Eh...?
Hinatachan's most favorite food.
Yakiniku, wasn't it?
We did it in the unit.
We also had the laser one.
Hey, that was amazing!
That was amazing!
What do you mean by "Kaho Kobayashi"?
I think we did it before.
I did it on video.
I don't know.
It was a project for "Ebichu no Video".
Oh!
(It's from "Ebichu no Video", right?
(I did it in the "Ebichu no Video" project.
I knew it.
It ended up like this.
I knew it...
It's Kaho-chan's favorite.
That one? A hint.
Huh? This is a hint...
But speaking of Kaho-chan...
Raw ham.
Gyoza.
Raw ham?
Is that what she told to Hinatachan?
That's what I meant...?
It's from Kaho-chan's comedy show.
In Kaho-chan's comic dialogue...
She said, "Bring me a raw ham."
She did buy it!
That was impressive!
Yes, dumplings!
Nonoka and Kaho-chan's dumplings.
I knew it!
Although i won...
She's always loved gyoza.
She's famous for liking gyoza.
Then it was gyoza!
Dumplings!
Not ham!
What do you think of Riko Nakayama?
That's it, isn't it?
You know, at live shows...
You know how they say "Riko Nakayama changes at live performances"?
When Riko goes live...
She turns into OO." Like that!
Oh, I said it already!
OK, OK!
Do you get it, Cocona?
Yes, I got it.
That's what I wanted to say. What should I write?
Maybe this is a place for...
Yajyun-ized
LION...
Lion...?
Oh, a lion?
Wait, I don't get it!
Isn't this supposed to be Riko-chan?
What?
What, Riko-chan?
At the MUSIC festival...
You know how short her hair was?
She had short hair then.
That's when her hair was all blown out.
I heard from Riko that she were a lion when she sang.
Riko told me.
She talks about it a lot.
"Beastification" and "lionification".
Oh, yeah, a lion.
Oh, yeah!
I thought it was that.
The first thing I thought of was cucumbers.
Oh, Yuno thought that too!
"Ah, cucumbers.
"Ah, cucumbers, indeed!
My favorite food.
Oh, so She've been using a film camera for a while now?
No, but She've been using a film camera for quite a long time.
There was a lot! There was a lot!
There was a lot!
There were a lot!
Questions from Cocona Sakuragi!
I'll give you the next question!
What is the song that wakes you up
What is your favorite song to wake you up to?
YunoI listen to this everyday!
I listen to it everyday.
It's perfect for waking up from sleep.
Yuno listens to it too much.
In the morning, that song
replaying in my head.
Eat. The. The Big Eyeball
Eat. The. big eyeball
Omekashi . Fever.
I'm going to do makeup and stuff.
I was wondering if it's that way.
I see.
In the nap room, "Eat the Biggest Loser"
"Eat the Big Eyeballs" is playing in the nap room.
It's on every day.
And I probably won't wake up just once.
So they play it a couple of times.
The first "duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh-duh.
I'll turn it off.
I turn it off at the doo-doo-doo and go back to sleep.
I'd cut myself off and fall asleep.
You're sleeping through the doodle doodle doodle doodle doodle doodle doodle doo.
You're falling asleep
Question from Yuno Kokubo!
What is your favorite Ebichu song that you've ever performed live?
What is my favorite Ebichu song?
Yuno's favorite song?
That's the one!
Isn't it easy?
It's just a moment!
Fuyukoi
Jiyuu e michizure
FUYUKOI
What's she talking about?
You said "Fuyukoi"!
I like "Fuyukoi" too.
I like it.
But I've never heard it live and thought it was fun.
I've never heard of it. I've never enjoyed it live.
"Jiyu e Michizure" ("To Freedom on the Road")
FUYUKOI is the only one
I've never heard it!
I said it on the radio just the other day!
I'll listen to Yuno's radio.
Please listen!
Question from Nonoka Kazami!
Of all the newly released songs by Ebichu
What is my second favorite song?
I know this one!
I think you know the first one
I think you can tell.
The second one I even said.
You mentioned it in the first part of the interview.
You've said it. You've said it.
Goodbye secret base.
Goodbye Secret Base.
Cocona, is that your kanji?
Isn't it this one?
It's like this.
What's wrong with it?
What happened to the machine?
Well, 。。。。 I know what it means.
What's number one, by the way?
I'm number one.
I like "Space is an Hourglass" the best.
I'd appreciate it if you'd say it right.
That'd be great!
Game over!
Let's do this one more time.
I want to get it all right this time.
Please do it again!