such as videos of shrimp
This is...
Yuna?
Which one is the first one and which one
is the second one?
The second one.
It's like...
I said it.
This is it.
It's all impressive, but it's special.
Ready, go!
University
I think I'll get confused if I get it
right.
It's the first one.
The second one.
One...
What is it?
What do you use often?
What do I use often?
What is the hint?
I think Yuna and the others use it the
most.
What is the hint?
It's the most used goods.
What is it?
Is it different?
Is there a type of goods?
Do you often use it?
I don't think so.
Did you write it down?
I wrote it down.
Let's go.
One, two, three.
It's a hoodie.
I wore it to school.
That hoodie is cute.
I'll give you a hint.
Giga's point of view of listening to
music.
Is it going to be like this?
What you're worried about is a list of
songs.
Have you ever performed this song
before?
There must be songs I've performed.
I don't know about this one.
This is the one.
I agree.
There are 2 or 3 songs that I'm not sure
about.
Have you ever done this song on a live
show?
I'll do it on a live show.
Let's do that.
That one?
That one is OK.
The one from the day before yesterday.
I'm thinking about the one from the day
before yesterday.
But this one is OK.
This one is OK.
OK.
Let's do that.
From Happy End.
Don't talk.
I don't want to talk.
What is the most difficult thing you've
done?
That's a lot.
I think I practiced the most.
I don't mean to say I'm mean, but I
practiced a lot.
Did you practice?
I practiced singing with Hinata and the
others.
Wait, which one?
Let's write it down.
I think this one will be the same.
That's right.
Ready, go.
I did it.
It's the second time.
It's not M.
No, it's not.
I practiced with Hiyoko.
I didn't know that.
Before the university entrance exam,
I told her to relax and sing.
I remember that.
I remember Yabana Yotto too much.
She changed the way she sang.
I see.
It's my first time singing against her.
I think it's OK.
It's OK.
That's true.
What's the most difficult dance?
The dance is difficult.
The dance I thought was difficult was...
It's a little...
It's difficult.
What is it?
What's difficult?
The choreography is difficult.
It's not physically difficult.
Is it a Japanese song?
Is it?
What?
Which one is it?
I don't think it's a good song.
I'm scared.
Are you ready?
Ready, go!
What's the name of the star?
The name of the star is...
Dish!
All of them are different!
Dish is difficult!
Which one is Dish?
The one with the long one.
The one with the high one.
The one with the left one.
It might be difficult.
I'm confused with Aina's rental.
Aina's rental is the hardest.
It was difficult to find the right one.
Which one is Dish?
The one with the long one.
It's easy!
I know!
The one with the coconut.
Is it coconut?
I know!
Do you like the one with the long one?
I like it!
I know!
Ready, go!
Ramen!
Meat!
I think I know this one.
What?
I said it wrong.
You said you wanted to eat meat.
I said I wanted to eat meat.
I like Terata.
I like her.
I'm getting nervous.
I have one more.
Let's do our best.
Which one is Dish?
What?
The one we did recently.
The one we did recently?
Yes, we did.
We did it for the first time.
We can match the two.
What did we do recently?
It's not a hobby.
It's a hobby.
We're enjoying it.
We're enjoying it?
Ready, go!
What is the anime?
Kintore.
I don't know the anime.
Which one?
I thought it was this one.
I see.
It's not an anime.
I can't remember.
Which one is the anime?
We've been doing that for a long time.
To Put Them Together
!
Wait a moment.
Kya裝 which criminals
Ancest Isn't을
called you the year
Samuna is not recent.
I have that image.
Wait, this is one moment.
I'm done.
Everyone, this is definitely it.
Wrong.
I was thinking.
Let's talk.
Let's talk a little.
What is this?
This is what Mayuma-san praises.
OK.
Is it what Mayuma-san praises?
I don't know.
The people who see it.
I think the girl will admire it.
It's amazing.
I think it's good.
I think it's the same.
I think so.
I think the girl will admire it.
By the way,
I think it's OK to say it with Mirei-
chan.
Wait.
Ready, go.
Legs.
Mirei-chan.
When Mirei-chan was doing this,
Mayuma-san said,
Let's put out your legs.
I put more cut in.
I was thinking.
What is the answer?
If I had to say Kashiwagi-nata,
I can only think of that.
Which one?
I think...
How should I say it?
Yuna-chan said,
I like it too.
Yuna-chan, you like it too?
Isn't it that?
I did it on the live.
Which one?
Which one do you do on the live?
Isn't it that?
At the university concert.
You did it.
I like it too.
Hina-chan said,
Thank you.
Isn't it that?
I think Mirei-chan is right.
Ready, go.
Dance.
I was thinking about the grilled meat.
What?
This is my favorite.
I did a unit dance.
That was amazing.
What is the second item?
This is...
I did it before.
I did it in a video.
It's the one inside.
This is the one inside.
I like this one.
This is a hint.
What is it?
This is a dumpling.
This is the one that was in Hinata's
video.
This is a big one.
I bought a big one.
I bought it.
This is a dumpling.
I like this.
I didn't buy it.
What is the difference between RIKO and
RIKO?
This is different from the live
performance.
RIKO does something when she is on
stage.
That's right.
OK.
Did you know this?
I knew it.
I think it's this.
Did you know?
This is a beast.
This is a lion.
Is this a beast?
I don't know.
This is not a beast.
RIKO had short hair when she was on the
music show.
RIKO told me that she was a lion when
she sang.
RIKO talks a lot.
She talks about animals and lions.
This is a lion.
I thought it was a cucumber.
I like cucumbers.
Is this a new camera?
The camera is also long.
There were a lot of cameras.
RIKO is the last one.
I will give you the next question.
In the song of Ebichu...
I like the sound of the alarm clock.
I hear this every day.
I like it.
I hear it too much that I can't remember
the next morning.
I'm going to do it.
I see.
I hear it.
I hear it every day.
I don't get up at once, so I hear it a
few times.
I hear it at first.
I hear it.
What song do you like the most?
I've played this song before.
It's a song of Evi-chan.
What's my favorite song?
It is the song Yuna likes.
I like winter love.
I like the song.
You said you liked winter love.
I like winter love too.
I think it's fun to do it live.
I've never heard of it.
I've only heard of it in winter.
I heard it on the radio the other day.
I know.
I'll listen to it now.
Please listen to it.
What is your favorite song?
What is my favorite song?
I know this.
I know the first song.
I've heard the second song before.
I've heard it in the first interview.
Sayonara secret kitchen.
Is it here?
Where is YUNA?
The tree is here.
The tree is near the sea.
I like the first song.
I'll be glad if you explain properly.
We'll do this again.
Next time, we want to do it all right.
Thank you.