This week's Ebichu Tastas is a winter-
themed dinner
They get on a Ferris wheel and have a
good time
Then...
You're an angel
It's obvious
Why are they crying?
Ebichu Tastas Start!
Available now!
This program is brought to you by these
sponsors.
Thank you for watching!
The members came to the mother farm
because it is a winter garden
A race of a pig and bungee jumping
Various rides are also coming to an end
The end of the winter garden is coming
Finally, it is a Ferris wheel
We will have two people ride it and talk
about things we don't usually talk about
I will announce the pairs
First, Mayama-Hoshina pair
This is a year-long pair
Next, Yasumoto-Kobayashi pair
This is a fixed pair
Next, Kashiwagi-Matsuno pair
This is a foodie pair
Next, Hirota-Nakaima pair
This is an N1 pair
There is an N1 Grand Prix
Next, Itaku-Nakaima
This is a pair that Hirota likes
I think various things will happen
Please go to the Ferris wheel
Please go
The pair that rides the Ferris wheel is
as you can see
Today, we will make the Ferris wheel a
special loan
We will talk about things we don't
usually talk about
Then, the Ferris wheel talk starts
Let's change the key
The key is in the box
I will change the bangs
The bangs are bad
The three pairs of bangs check
And the last two people are
The last two people are
Oh, me too.
What?
It is a secret that he didn't say.
Oh, oh, it's a secret.
oh, yeah
I'm scared!
What should we do?
Where should we go?
It's impossible
Can't you see?
It's impossible to go to the lunch table
It's impossible
I can't even look down
It's impossible to go to the lunch table
I'm scared!
I found it!
This is it!
Is it working now?
I found the eye part.
Over there?
I found it.
I can hear the sound of the wind.
Thank you for watching!
What is that? It looks really funny.
Mayama is also scared of heights.
I wonder if I'll be surprised.
It's really scary.
It's scary.
It's dangerous!
It's scary, but it's scary.
It's really scary.
It's scary, but it's really scary.
No, it's scary.
Scary? This diagonal feeling.
I don't like it.
It's going to be reflected.
Then it will be balanced.
It's scary.
It's scary. It's scary that it's not
diagonal.
It's scary.
It's really scary.
It's right below.
Maybe it was like this with the bungee
jump.
I was doing a bungee jump.
It's scary.
I'm going to be a diagonal.
The members are getting used to the
height and the situation.
Then...
What are they talking about? I want to
communicate with everyone.
But they're probably talking about
something different in their rooms, so
it's interesting.
They're definitely talking about
something different.
It looks like they're not talking about
that.
Let's go to the rest room.
Yes!
You can be heard unel enemy
Because you look like you're eating a
face
Why?
A little more
Ah, can you do it?
Sorry
I was completely out of breath
Ah, ah
On the other hand, Matsu's kashiwagi
pair is
This is the reason why I switched to
kashiwagi
Where did you fall in love with me?
I'm in love
The two are enjoying the handsome
shiritori that is in the mainstream
within the members
make up to style what they think was a
line that cool looking guy should take
also would better should we take shot
What's going on?
You're not just looking at the side,
you're looking at me!
So fast!
It's sharp, but you like me, don't you?
She's got a big crush on a handsome guy
I'm going to go to the bathroom with you
Kaa?
You're going to make me cry
Really?
I'm going to cry
In the meantime, Mayama and Hoshina's
long-term couple started talking
about...
I like Adana.
I know.
Sakura Ebisu and others are Adana.
Kaori is also Adana.
We don't have that.
We don't.
Adana is a name.
It's a name because it's a name.
I admire Adana a little.
Adana has two people who admire it.
Adana of Nakayama was the one I admired
the most.
When I heard Ritann, I was like, what?
Oh, I saw it!
I've never seen an idol like that.
Ritann?
Rina?
At first, I wasn't used to it.
I was like, oh, no.
Rina was pretty shocking to me.
It was shocking.
Rina?
Amazing!
I was like, wow!
But I'm a little jealous that she's a
good girl.
But I have a strange sense of sense of
reason.
I agree.
I'm a weird Maya.
But you can go to Riton.
I can go to Riton, but I don't have the
feeling of Riton.
I'm a little reluctant.
Like B-chan?
I don't like it.
It's hard.
I think Maya is good enough.
What?
What is this?
This is funny.
I'm going to say it.
Did you fall in love with me eating
squid sushi?
I can't fall in love with you.
Did you fall in love with me eating
squid sushi?
It was a wind.
I'm sorry.
On the other hand, this is the story of
the trip that Hirota went to the family
on New Year's Day.
I went to Kagawa in the 5th of October.
It was really good. The night sky was
very beautiful.
It was a little late in the morning.
The sun was setting late.
I woke up at about 6 o'clock.
I could see the sunrise and there were
still many stars.
That was really good.
The sky was orange, but I could see the
stars above.
It was really beautiful.
What about this afternoon?
This afternoon was good, but I could go
on a tour.
I don't know how slowly I can go.
I'm looking forward to Okinawa.
I wondered what would happen to the
costumes.
There are costumes for the first tour.
I don't know the theme of the tour.
I'm looking forward to that.
It's the first time to change costumes.
I want to change costumes.
I want to try the color of the light.
This pair is also an idol.
I eat vegetable soup at night.
Are you really hungry?
I like to eat vegetable soup and spring
rolls.
I eat vegetables in soup.
I will try it.
I eat it with bananas in the morning.
I'm hungry.
Bananas are very hungry.
I don't like yogurt and bananas.
I don't like yogurt.
I don't like bananas.
But bananas make me feel good.
I can eat bananas.
The story that looks like an idol is not
exciting.
On the other hand, these two are
relaxing because they are good at taking
pictures.
When I was cleaning the room, I saw a
cute face.
I opened the door and I was wondering
what it was.
There was something like a
If it is spices, there seems to be
something like a
What is
I think I collected it.
You did?
I collected the missing teeth.
I was like, what is this?
When I was a kid, I used to look at the
missing teeth collection.
You looked at it?
I was surprised when I heard it.
Interesting.
You collected the missing teeth and
looked at them.
I was looking at them when I was a kid.
I was a very strange person.
I'm still strange.
You're not strange.
Really?
The story continues.
And...
I'm sorry.
Why?
What is the reason for the tears in
Tashiwagi's eyes?
In the winter garden, the members are
enjoying the sightseeing talk with only
two people
Anu-san, I think cameras are good these
days
I bought a camera recently
Riko brought a camera when we were
shooting
A camera from Nakayama family
I thought I'd use it for shooting only
trains
I think it's good to shoot people
This is what I've been wanting to say
Next time I need to shoot with a camera
I want to shoot a picture with members
I want to do that
It seems that it is popular to take
pictures between members
They take a lot of photos of members
To make a situation
Let it be
From behind
kameraman
from the back
As a camera perhaps
Ask to print
Lila
Tech, this is camera
Which do  Ping
All these
Ignore
I'm going to take a picture of you.
Hey, you're going to take a picture of
me.
I'm going to take a picture of you.
The talk of the rebels was very
exciting.
They entered the second round.
The topic of the talk is getting deeper.
When I first entered the room,
I was a very polite person when I said
my previous dream.
I remember it very well.
I just entered the room.
I was on the way to Golden Week.
I didn't know if I was going to come
out.
I started practicing in April.
I asked if we were going to come out.
I remember hearing that.
I remember it very well.
I didn't think I was going to come out.
I felt like I was saying thank you.
Did you come out?
I didn't come out yet.
I'm going to take a picture of you.
わぁっ
I was worried at that time.
I'm a person who is innocent, but I'm
afraid of it.
I don't think I should fix it myself.
I was afraid of it. I was afraid of
everyone.
I'm sorry.
We don't have a relationship.
That's good.
I'm glad that we're all members.
I like that.
I'm sorry.
On the other hand, Matsu's kashiwagi
pair also talk to each other.
I may be a little shy, but when I was
called a sudden man,
Sudden man.
At the end of last year, an unexpected
situation came to kashiwagi.
Kashiwagi, who canceled all his work and
focused on treatment,
was sending a bright message to the
fans, but he slowly told us how he felt
at that time.
I was worried about how they would
react, but I was happy that they were
waiting for me.
Why? That's obvious.
I couldn't attend any lessons, and I was
sad that I couldn't do anything but
cheer for them.
But I was happy that they were saying
that.
If Hinata wasn't there, you wouldn't be
in the middle of the night.
I don't think they would say that.
Why?
I was so happy that they were saying
that.
I'm so glad. I'm about to cry.
I'm not a finger-tie when I'm with you.
Thank you.
I'm happy.
I feel refreshed.
I'm glad.
Anyone can be 앞에ope!
You guys are laughing a lot.
How was it?
It was fun.
I'm the teacher.
Say again.
Did you hear the teacher's lead?
She was laughing.
I didn't understand anything.
It was fun.
Don't give me the hard drive.
How was the team?
We were just talking about our lives.
You were talking about things you
couldn't do.
You're the teacher.
You're not good at high places.
I was waiting for a long time.
I felt like I was in a movie theater.
You were signing.
Movie theater?
It's like a movie theater.
It's the same coffee shop.
If it was a gesture game, it would be a
movie theater.
We often eat together.
It's not fun.
It's not like that.
It was fun.
We had a day of winter play.
How was it?
It was fun.
Finally, please express your impression
of the day with your face and movement.
I'll do it.
I'm cold.
The next day
Can I get up?
No
The mask is too thick
What did you do?
I'm going to be a camera man
It's rare for you to be like that
Please use your weapon and do a prank
Thank you for watching
I'm going to do it!
Nakayama-san, let's go!
Look at the picture book and...
What?
I'm back to the Twintail!
I'm crying.
I'm so happy!
I'm back to the Twintail!
The game project is in progress.
The production of action games is
progressing.
The enemies character appears in the
game.
Here it is.
The enemies character appears in the
middle school.
Let's think about the new enemies
character together.
First, the enemies character of Mayama
High School.
Lacrosse and Sun.
When you hold the lacrosse, it suddenly
becomes bright.
The personality changes.
It's important.
It's not a mistake.
It's my father's work.
Next, Hoshinaga.
I'm a basketball player, Shunkyu Goryo.
I don't have a good sense of language.
I like cars.
I think that if you combine the speed of
a car and basketball, basketball is the
strongest.
I put a bus on my feet.
Is this person bigger than a bus?
It's big.
The enemies character of Mayama High
School.
Mayama High School.
I think I met him.
So I said,
Oh, it was a face of salt.
I said, I'm wearing a bag on the face of
a person.
The last is Nakayama's announcement.
I don't have a name.
I'm just a single person.
I'm similar to Ebisu.
These people are basketball players.
Every time they stack up,
They get closer to the goal.
Aim for the goal.
Eight people stand together.
This name is the world's number 8.
8.
Will Ebichu's ideas be adopted?
Ebichu Game Project.
Please look forward to the next.
Next time, Ebichu plus graduation
special.
Celebrate the members who graduate from
junior high and high school this spring
with a surprise.
Congratulations!
Please subscribe to the channel.
Please subscribe this channel to be the
Rugged
Please subscribe to this channel to be a
big rencknowledge to wreKS
Thank you for watching!
I did it!