What's your favorite hobby recently?
Recently, I've been thinking that there
are only good people around me.
But when I hear that, I feel like I'm
alone.
I make mistakes in lyrics.
I get nervous and it comes out in my
dreams.
I'm modest before the live.
You're modest before the live.
You're modest.
I'm trying not to get too excited.
I'm trying to be able to do it a little
bit.
I'm trying not to get too excited.
nightstick idol
I'm the guest of the day, Yatap!
Hello!
Let's get started!
Today's guest is this idol!
Welcome to Kimi no Heart!
I'm Kanamin, aka Tsujuno Kanami, and I'm
in charge of the Super Exciting Blue!
I'm so happy to have you here!
It's my first time at a hot spring!
Next is Kanamin!
I'm Kanamin! Thank you!
Speaking of Tokisen, you also had a big
live performance!
Yes! Thank you!
I had a live performance at Makai Remix
in October!
That's amazing! How many people were
there at that time? 7,000?
7,000 people, about 7,000 people
Isn't it amazing that 7,000 people are
watching?
Yes, it was a stage feeling or a scenery
that made me doubt if it was our live
performance.
I had a feeling that I was at my
senior's live performance.
No, no, no, what we've accumulated so
far is that we've come to the fans and
supported them.
I think it was the moment when I was the
most excited in my heart.
After all, there was a big live
performance, so did you do a lot of
rehearsals?
There was a live performance on October
22nd, so it started after October 2nd.
I did a lot of investment rehearsals
than usual.
You did a lot of investment rehearsals,
right?
By the way, how many times did you do
it?
I think I did it about three times in
total.
Three times in total? Three times on
that stage?
Yes.
And the day before?
I did it once a week ago, and the day
before that, I did a lot of investment
in the block.
The day before, I actually did a Makai
Messe on the spot, and I did it all
while I was putting together the stage.
I see.
That's all you did.
And there are a lot of girls in the fan
club, right?
That's right.
There are a lot of female fans, and I
sometimes doubt which one is an idol.
I'm doing a lot of investment, and I'm
wondering which one is an idol.
There are so many wonderful women that I
sometimes wonder if I should be me.
We often get stimulated.
The production was amazing, too.
It was said that the second floor seats
were moved by truck.
There were 12 trucks in the venue, and
only 6 members were there.
There were 12 trucks on the first and
second floors.
12 trucks!
What's moving?
My heart is beating!
I'm so happy!
I'm always thinking about super-exciting
advertisements.
I've always been thinking about special
features.
Have you ever dreamed of special
features?
This program was brought to you by
Kaorin, Ayane, Tomohiro, Gackt, and
Chine.
It's getting really cold, so please stay
warm!
Thank you for watching!