Ebichu's videos
Hello, I'm Rie Hoshinami.
I'm a shrimp chuno.
I'd like to introduce you to this.
ZASM Mineralizing Creamy Concealer
ZASM's concealer is very good.
I'm sure a lot of people use it.
It's very good at covering.
But if you apply it under your eyes,
it's a little...
It's going to get wet over time. I feel
like it's going to get wet with dryness.
And then when I was shooting Rizeka, the
makeup artist was using this creamy
concealer.
He applied it to me, too. And then I put
it on for a day, and it didn't get wet
at all.
I bought it because I thought I'd
definitely buy it.
I'd like to try it on.
I should do it like this.
I'll apply it like this.
I'll tap it.
I'll stretch it while tapping.
It's a pretty thick texture.
I feel a little heavy.
If you stretch it out, it's very light.
It's a good feeling.
It's not only for the under eyes and
around the mouth.
It's also good for other areas.
I think the chip concealer has a better
coverage.
But this creamy concealer is lighter.
I recommend this product for those who
want to do makeup without makeup.
Please try it.
It's a moist concealer.
I'm Rika Mayuma, the third place.
This is my favorite cosmetic product.
It's Canmake Tokyo's Creamy Touch Liner.
I met this eyeliner.
I happened to forget my eyeliner at
home.
I couldn't help it, so I bought it at a
drugstore.
I got this.
I was so happy that I bought it right
away.
The good thing is that it's cheap.
I think it's a little plastic when it
comes to Canmake Tokyo.
It's really cheap.
I can buy it for less than 1,000 yen.
This is actually my third one.
I lost one, and I used up the second
one.
I bought it right away.
It's a product that you can choose from.
Of course, the contents are good.
Look at this.
It's a gel liner.
The core is very thin.
I don't know at all.
I'll write it.
I'll write this.
I can easily write it with light force.
Do you understand?
It's like writing thin and thick.
I can write thin and thick.
I'm using it now, but I can write it
easily, so even beginners can use it
easily.
It's smooth.
The color I'm using now is called dark
caramel.
I was praised by the makeup artist.
It's a fashionable color.
I got a little carried away and I have
three of these.
It's good, so let's match it with me.
By the way, I'm using all 5 colors.
Lastly, this one.
I wonder if it's dry.
It doesn't smudge at all when it's dry.
Here I go.
It's totally fine even if I rub it.
I'm Kashiwagi Nata, the 10th member of
Shiseido.
Today, I'm going to introduce cosmetics.
I'd like to introduce what I always use.
I'm going to introduce eye shadows.
I often get asked which eye shadow I
use, so I'd like to tell you about it.
This is the eye shadow I always use.
It's Kate's eye shadow.
Kate the Eye Color.
I use this eye shadow.
Make taught me that this eye shadow is
very pigmented.
I was so happy when I saw it.
I was like, wow, it's a beautiful color.
So I went to buy it.
I bought it because it was sold at a
pharmacy.
I have four of them now, but there are
many types.
I bought the colors that the makeup
artist actually used and the colors that
are easy to use.
It's 650 yen, which is a very reasonable
price for a wallet.
That's the biggest drawback.
I want to buy more colors of this kind
of eye shadow.
But if it's 650 yen, I don't buy a lot,
but I can have a few.
So I bought this.
What I'm wearing now is...
Wait a minute. It's not this.
This is it.
This is red.
I think it's called Red Brown.
I'll paint it like Red Brown.
It's 032.
It looks quite red, but when I apply
it...
It's a red color, but it's a little deep
brown.
I really want to recommend this red
brown to everyone.
I bought this brown because it's a color
that's easy to use.
I'm often asked where I got this
glittery one.
This is also a little dirty.
I think there were about four kinds of
glittery ones.
It's an eye shadow base.
I'm using this one from Kate.
It has pearls in it and it's creamy so
it's very easy to use.
It's very easy to hold.
This is 032, the red one.
The brown one is 031.
The glitter one is 007.
This one is 001, the eye color base.
Please try it out.
That's it.
Thank you for watching.
Please subscribe to my channel!
I'm Rika Mayama, the number 3 of the
attendance number.
I'm going to introduce anime because
it's one of the best in the world.
I love anime, especially Gintama.
If Gintama is episode 1 of my anime-
loving life, I'd like to introduce an
episode 0 work today.
It's before I became an anime lover.
Here it is.
Otogi Jyushi Akazuki. This work was
released in July 2006.
It was released on Saturday morning, but
I was 9 or 10 years old when I bought
it.
I bought it after I became an adult.
Why do I like it so much?
This work is the reason I got to know
the voice actor Yukari Tamura.
Yukari Tamura played the role of
Akazuki-chan, and I was also in charge
of the theme song.
I was also in charge of the TV
commercial for Princess Rose, and I
found out about the existence of Yukari
Tamura.
She was so cute! Pink, fluffy, and
sparkly! I thought she was an idol!
I found out about her after I grew up
and started to like anime.
I was so shocked that she was playing
the role of Akazuki-chan!
So I bought it again and I'm still
watching it!
I want you to feel this feeling, too.
So I put it all together.
I like this part.
It's called the fairy god Akazukin.
Roughly speaking, there are two worlds,
Erde and Fantabele.
There's a girl named Sanju, Akazukin.
Akazukin is a boy who is said to have
the key to Erde from the witch Sandrian.
It's a battle to protect Souto Suzukaze.
It's a fantasy like action.
The character is a motif of a fairy
tale.
Akazukin-chan is the motif.
The dog-like thing next to it is a wolf.
In addition to Sanjuushi, there are
characters like Shirayuki-hime and
Ibarahime.
When I watch a grimoire, I get excited.
Sandrian is also a motif.
Cinderella is a motif, and it's a work
that can be exciting for those who like
fairy tales.
And the second one is for children, but
the Harlem element is strong.
It's a girl in Sanshūshi who protects
Tōta Suzukaze.
And there's a childhood friend named
Ringo-chan.
The motif is a poisonous apple.
Ringo-chan is also a motif.
So, Elde is the real world, and
Fantabele is the fantasy world.
And they come together.
They're like, I can't leave Sota alone!
It's too much of a family.
Everyone is so attached to Sota.
It's like, how much of a Harlem?
And, um...
There are too many lines that say, Sota!
I thought, why is Sota so popular?
Suzukaze Sota, I'll write it as a grass.
Thank you.
Sota is a so-called decorative type guy.
He's actually able to talk to the grass
and give it energy.
He has that kind of special ability.
So, now, he is a decorative type guy.
I think he was a little top-notch.
The third one.
The Doha Meikyuu is a god.
I said I knew it from Princess Rose, but
when I listen to Doha Meikyuu, I can
feel like I've already experienced this
work.
So, in the chorus of Doha Meikyuu,
there's a phrase that goes,
When I'm trying hard, when I'm having a
hard time, I have a dream, I like
stories.
When I hear this, I'm like, this is it!
It's the Otogi Junshi Akazukin!
It's totally like that!
I don't know if I don't watch this, but
even if I don't watch it, it's a bit
contradictory.
It's contradictory, but even if I don't
watch it, I think it's a story like
this.
I think Akazukin-chan is making a story
when they're having a hard time trying
to do their best.
The last one was a bit rough, but that
means I'm the best Tamura Yukari!
Thank you very much!