An organic game Мы
everCH 필цт
even
this
LET insane
IT
DO
Y
predominant
any
выз
sit
did
We will add many things to the private
Ebisu Middle School.
Ebisu Justice!
This program is brought to you by the
sponsor you see.
It's really delicious.
Thank you for watching.
The competition has finally begun.
Ebi-Chu Autumn's Magi Sports Festival.
Here are the members of each team.
Mr. Akiyama, the leader of the Hachioji
Tourism Association, is watching.
Ebi-Chu is divided into the red team and
the white team.
A serious battle is going on.
The red team is ahead of the other team
in the current 87 vs. 53.
Will they be able to escape as it is?
Then, the fourth event, start!
The race is Magi-Takatobi!
Here are the rules of this competition.
Each team will try one by one.
The team with the highest score will be
the winner.
Each team will try one by one.
The race starts from 90cm and will be
eliminated if they fail.
The winner will only get the one who is
in the top 3.
By the way, who jumps the most?
Mayama.
But, this is different from this.
I can see the height.
Mayama is short, so I think it's better
to see her.
She is a pro at the length of her legs.
The one who jumps the most is the one
who has the advantage of the length of
her legs.
Then, Mayama will jump.
She will jump.
It's impossible.
If she jumps, she can go anywhere.
Then, the first round.
The challenge is to jump at 90cm.
The red team starts from Mayama.
Mayama is at 90cm.
Ready.
I'm nervous.
I jump.
Good job.
It was easy.
She jumps and clears the race.
Next is Matsuno Shirogumi.
Then...
She is watching over me.
She is holding the tower.
She pushes Akiyama's back.
Matsuno is at 90cm.
Ready.
I was nervous.
Next is Hirota Akagumi.
Let's go.
Hirota is at 90cm.
She is watching over me.
The first try
She still has some room
She's scared
White team, Hoshina's turn
Ready
Miya-chan, don't worry
She has room
Her legs are longer
As expected, everyone is dancing
Red team, Kashiwagi's turn
Kashiwagi's turn
Kashiwagi
How good is her jump?
Kashiwagi's 90cm
Ready
How is it?
It was close
That was close
It was so close
I didn't know the timing
She corrected it
It was so close
I'm scared
Next, White team's Yasumoto
She's just like the captain
Then
Akiyama is also watching
Yasumoto's 90cm
Ready
I did it
Akiyama is also clapping
Yay
Next, Red team's Kobayashi
Let's go
Kobayashi's 90cm
Ready
How is it?
It's good
She's good at sports
But I couldn't do my best
You couldn't do your best
Let's do our best today
We still have time
I'm going to die here
I want to go here
She left a mysterious comment
Next, Nakayama
Let's go
Nakayama's 90cm
Ready
Next, White team's Yasumoto
The crossing was too fast and the heel
was slightly caught.
Unfortunately.
The first runner of the second round was
eliminated.
It's not a yay.
In the 90cm, one of the white group,
Nakayama, was eliminated.
In the next second round, in the 95cm,
Mayama and Hoshinaga could easily jump
and clear.
Hirota and Yasumoto also managed to
clear.
Next, the red team, Kashiwagi.
Let's go! Kashiwagi's 95cm. Ready!
Good luck!
Go! Why? Why?
You came here without hesitation
I was able to beat her
It was close
She fell down
In the second round, 95cm, the red team
Kashiwagi fell down
Each team has 3 people left
Next, the third round, 100cm challenge
Let's go
Mayama's 100cm, ready
Go
Mayama's
She did it
Good luck
Mayama and Hoshino still have a chance
to win
They still have a chance
Next, Yasumoto Shirogumi and then
I'll do my best
Akiyama is getting closer
I feel bad
You are not allowed to enter the line
I'm sorry
It's like a barrier
Let's go
Ready
She did it
I'm so happy
Red team, Hirota's challenge
Ready
Go for it
It's important
What's wrong, Hirota?
I can't tell the timing
Good decision
Ready
Go for it
How is it?
Hirota's down
He patted the bar
I got a sand and went home
It's like a hat
It's like a sportsman's tail
White team, Matsuno's challenge
Ready
Go for it
It's crumbling
I want to do it again
There is no more time
Please come back
Sorry
It was fun
Red team, Kobayashi's challenge
Kobayashi's 100cm
Ready
Wow
I did it
Yay
Good job
The 100cm wall is high
Hirota, Kobayashi, Matsuno are
eliminated
The remaining is Red team, Mayama
White team, Yasumoto, Hoshina
The three
From here, the order is a battle
If the White team wins the first and
second place
The chance of turning the table
The fourth round
Challenge 105cm
Let's go
Mayama's 105cm
Ready
Good luck
Wow
Thank you
I will go
Mayama's 105cm
Ready
Wow
It's amazing
It was close
Next, Yasumoto's 105cm
Good
Yasumoto's 105cm
Ready
Wow
The 105cm wall is not small
Where did you get it?
I got it
Good job
Great
Yasumoto falls and Hoshina tries at the
last shot of the white group
If Hoshina fails here, Mayama will be
the first to decide
150cm, ready
It's easy
Still a clear with a little bit of ease
Mayama and Hoshina's shot
110cm
Are you ready?
Let's go
Will Mayama and Hoshina win?
Mayama's 110cm
Are you ready?
Newly
Red group Mayama's challenge
Mayama's 110cm
Are you ready?
So close
Mayama's 110cm
I was so nervous.
I was nervous too.
Did you miss the timing?
Well...
I fell.
I knew it.
Did you miss the steps?
Well...
I thought my butt was low.
I see.
Your butt?
It's like an athlete.
Like a professional.
But you still can't fly, right?
That's right.
If you can't, you can't fly.
Everyone, let's go!
You can do it!
If you can do it, you're first place.
Let's go! Hoshina's 110cm!
Ready!
It flew!
So the winner is Hoshina!
Congratulations!
With a great jump, White Team Hoshina
got first place.
Red Team Mayama got second place.
White Team Yasumoto got third place.
There's still a lot to go.
I'm tired of it. It's getting fun.
Let's ask this person.
Akiyama-san!
Hello!
Can I talk to you for a bit?
Akiyama-san!
Thank you for listening.
Are there any people who are watching
this game and are active?
Yes, there are.
Who are they?
I don't know their names.
I remember them all.
I forgot.
Only Yasumoto remembers them.
Yasumoto!
Amazing! Only Yasumoto remembers them.
My wrist hurts.
You don't do that.
My wrist! My wrist is being grabbed.
With the help of White Team Hoshina and
Yasumoto,
they are only 4 points apart.
The game is heading to the final round.
The final match of the shrimp-chewed
match.
Team match, the match relay.
The match relay is 70 meters per person.
Only the anchor runs 100 meters to the
goal.
The winning team gets 100 points.
As a result of the match, each team runs
in this order.
The red team, how did you decide the
order?
The anchor is...
I'm going to run with the yellow team.
I see.
The yellow team is the boss.
Why did the white team decide this
order?
I don't know.
Because Ni-ne is fast, she runs a lot.
I see. What else?
I'm just going to run.
I see.
Good luck.
This is the last match.
The final match, the match relay.
Let's start.
Team match relay.
Ready.
The yellow team is the first to run.
Mayama is fast.
Yasumoto is slow.
Yasumoto is so slow
She's caught up with the speed
Both Kuro and Hayate are leading
She's leading
Go for it!
She's catching up
Hoshina can do it.
Hoshina, from here.
She's fast!
She's going for it!
How is it?
Wow!
That was close!
But the winner is...
Red Team!
You're so close!
Red Team won!
I'm crying!
I'm going!
That was close!
That was amazing!
Red Team won!
Congratulations!
At first...
I was so close!
I didn't give up!
You're so strange!
I'm always like this!
You were so close!
I was so close!
You did your best!
That was the plan!
You were going to run away?
Yes!
I see!
I noticed...
I'm not fast!
You're fast!
I'm fast but...
Hoshina was faster!
She's so fast!
She's like a person who can be cheated
on!
She's so small!
If she was 2 meters away...
She would have been cheated on!
I wanted a little more!
I'm glad she wasn't there!
I thought she wouldn't be able to do
that!
But she was amazing!
The results are announced!
The total score is...
227 vs 123
Akagumi won!
The winner will be announced!
The winner's product is...
Autumn Scented Set!
Wow
Ok, the leader of the red team
Please come forward
I'm the leader
That's right
The leader of the red team
Thank you
You spilled it
It's a little slanted
Don't spill it
Congratulations
Please say a word from the leader of the
red team
Alright
Thank you
Nice
Next, the MVP award for the member who
worked the hardest
This is
Give me a hand
This is from the head of the team,
Chuhei
Thank you
The MVP of this time is
Mirai Hoshina
Congratulations
What's the prize?
This prize is
20,000 yen
Amazing
Let's ask Akiyama to get the prize
Akiyama, sorry
Do you use it recklessly?
It's scary
20,000 yen
It's not going to be a good prize
Look forward
I see
It's not going to be 20,000 yen
What do you think?
I'm happy
20,000 yen
I'll do it
Close your eyes
20,000 yen
Please open your eyes
Congratulations
30,000 yen is 20,000 yen
Congratulations!
I see!
This mask was bought by Takiue during
the shoot.
Do you want it?
Takiue-sama offered this mask as a gift.
No, I don't want it.
You don't want it?
No way. It's worth 20,000 yen.
Try it on.
I won't sell it.
It's good!
Congratulations!
It fits you.
It suits you. Congratulations!
I don't want it.
Congratulations!
I think this is it.
Actually, there's one more prize.
What is it?
It's the Akiyama Special Prize that Ms.
Akiyama chose.
It's the prize I wanted the most.
Ms. Akiyama, please announce it.
I'm lost.
I want to give it to everyone.
It's a serious event.
I'm impressed that you all did your
best.
But there's only one person who's still
standing.
There's no one who remembers.
I'm a little confused.
I'm embarrassed.
Let's go.
You all did your best, but you don't
know the name.
I know you all did your best.
Please tell me.
I'll give the prize to Ms. Yasumasa.
Congratulations.
Thank you for watching.
It's a high-touch
Akiyama Showa
The product is
Akiyama's autograph on this hat
Amazing
Akiyama and Katsuo
Which one should we choose?
Katsuo and Katsuo
Both
Katsuo
How is it?
The kanji is
Katsu and Otoko
Right
I thought so
Thank you
Amazing
It suits you
Thank you
Yasumoto, you're not going to join the
citizens' marathon
I'm going to run
Please tell us the date
The date
So
That's it for today
Goodbye
Bye
The new project is
And
The person who missed Ebichu Tastas
The low-grade video distribution site
On the Stardust channel
Ebichu Tastas is being popular
I'm going to buy it
I can't get close to it from here
That machine is free of charge for 400
yen a month
In addition
A lot of exclusive images of unreleased
Search for the details on the Stardust
channel
Kain's
TakeshHappy