Ebichu's videos!
Thank you for watching!
I read a fortune telling and it said
that my lucky color is yellow.
So I think it's perfect.
It's so yellow, isn't it?
It's noisy.
I can't see anything. What should I do?
I'm going to put it like this.
21 pieces in one part.
Only 21 pieces out of 550 pieces.
The winner is...
Congratulations.
I want you to flip it over and check it.
I did it.
Great!
I won!
It was just the two of us.
We are going to the rehearsal.
Was the new place this big?
It was huge.
I'm scared.
You are.
Good morning.
I'm Minna.
Nice to meet you.
Let's relax.
I finished the rehearsal. I got all the
songs right.
I have 21 songs in the first and second
part.
I got about 60 songs today.
I turned 21 on my birthday in March.
I can finally celebrate my birthday
today.
I will do my best to turn 21 today.
I'm going to the makeup studio.
I changed my clothes.
I look like this.
I've never worn this kind of clothes at
a birthday party.
I like this kind of clothes.
I asked them to dye my hair.
I think it's great that they dyed my
hair.
I'm not going to do my hair like I do at
a live show.
I'm happy.
The first half of the song is a song
that makes you feel like you can dance.
I don't know if you can feel it, but I
like this kind of song.
There are a lot of songs that are a
little intense, but I wanted to make it
cool.
The second block is a bit of a tune-on.
I'm always doing it in the middle of the
show.
There's an event called tune-on, and I
got a little bit of it.
So the second block is a mature look.
I'll do my best.
She's like an athlete.
She's taking her own tension.
I'm doing it naturally.
You can switch.
If you switch, she'll be more nervous.
If it's me.
She's making her own tension.
Wait a minute.
I'm going to switch.
Thank you for watching.
I changed from the one-posed men's
outfit to this adult-like black one.
The third block.
I wanted to make the third block a block
where I can sit on a chair and listen to
ballads.
I asked them to make it look like an
adult-like one.
I made it look cute and adult-like.
Cute.
The ribbon is also black and white.
I was moved by the last song.
I finished the second part.
I finished all of them.
I'm like this.
It's been three minutes.
It was fun.
I was able to have a birthday party
twice.
I'm glad.
Thank you very much.
I'm finally 21 years old.
It's only five months until I'm 22.
I was very happy to have a birthday
party.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
I finished all of them.
I did my best for this day.
It was fun.
I'm glad I could do it.
I was able to have a birthday party
without being a third-time driver.
I'm sure I'll have a birthday party in
five months.
I finished the first part and the second
part of the show safely.
I'm sure there were a lot of people who
watched the show.
Thank you very much.
I hope you enjoyed it.
And thank you to everyone who came to
the venue.
I had a great time with everyone.
Thank you very much.
I'm going home.
Bye.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm going home.
Thank you for watching.
I'm going to do my best.
Oh, my God.
It's going to start.
The rehearsal is over.
We did it well.
OK.
It's going to start.
The costumes of 4Land5 are 20s, so I
wanted to make it like a kimono, but
also like a dress.
So, I made it like this.
It's so cute.
This is my favorite one among the
costumes of 4Land5.
I'm so happy.
I'm done.
I was nervous.
I finished it safely.
My master warmed up the second part of
the costume.
I enjoyed it.
Thank you.
I finished it.
I tried my best from the beginning to
the end.
Especially the last three songs,
「泣き虫呪文」「人生のパレードとスターマン」
Thank you for watching.
I think it is of particular interest to
me.
I don't really get inspired very often.
I have a bad impression about that song
from earlier,
Now I had been in a state of dreaming,
I certainly am not used to talking
I'm not good at talking.
I was nervous to talk, but overall I was
nervous to do solo concert.
But when I said something, the person
who did the circle and the person who
did the straight was very clear.
That was interesting.
Everyone was kind, so they looked at me
with a face like,
It's okay.
I felt relieved.
When I'm really without audience, I
don't have any reaction, but when I have
a little audience like today,
Even if I can't speak, I can respond
with eye contact or gesture, so it's
very easy to do.
I'm grateful.
I met my fans.
I can see them everywhere.
I was nervous.
I think solo concert is for people who
love me.
I'm grateful that everyone was kind.
Thank you!
I'm going to the rehearsal.
Thank you very much.
I'm nervous.
The point of today's Christmas costume
is my Christmas goods that I sold in
June.
This trainer is the point.
I'm sure there are people who come to
the venue in uniform.
I'm glad everyone said that I look like
a high school girl.
I'm going to get excited.
It's a new life.
I'm going to sneeze.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad.
I'm so full.
I couldn't forget it.
It was great.
It was much better than I imagined.
I'm so full.
It was great.
I think you got it.
I think so.
I'm so satisfied.
I love you so much.
Then, you got more satisfied.
I'm glad I was in a free family.
I'm going to the restaurant.
Good morning.
I brought a lunch box.
I'll do my best.
Good morning.
I'm going to the restaurant.
LSousa
Thank you.
It's cute.
The point of this costume is that I'm
turning 20 this year, so I got a
furisode costume.
The staff and everyone praised this
cloth a lot.
This light blue one.
And the hair is amazing.
This make-up artist made me look cute.
I'm here to take a picture with my
manager.
I'm going to take a picture with
Nakayama today.
You look good.
Congratulations on your 20th birthday.
Congratulations.
You look good.
Congratulations on your 20th birthday.
I'm going to take a picture with my
manager.
Congratulations on your 20th birthday.
Congratulations.
Thank you for watching.
Good job.
I'm looking forward to it.
Ouch!
I'm a special guest today.
Thank you.
It was fun.
Rima was fun.
Thank you.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I'm glad.
It's over.
We are doing 2D now, but we are done.
Thank you so much, Captain.
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
Good morning.
I'm going to perform a cover song now.
It's a pretty laid-back tempo, so I hope
you can listen to it in a relaxed way.
Please listen to it.
I'm going to do a photo time every year
from now on.
Please prepare a camera and take a cute
picture.
Alright, that's it for the photo time!
Did you get a good shot?
Did you get a good shot of the photo?
Let's go to the next one!
I'm nervous!
I'm going to push you.
I'm nervous.
I'm nervous about the inside of my
heart.
I hope it starts, but I'm most nervous
about this time.
I'll do my best to be a cake.
I'll do my best!
It's a wrap!
Wow, it's good.
Thank you for making this because I want
to put a cake on my head.
The costume is a lovely costume that is
not often seen in EVICTUDE.
This is a ring on my finger.
My mother drew the illustration.
My mother is not good at drawing, but
the stylist understood what I drew and
made it.
The accessories are also cute.
The theme is a cake.
I'm looking forward to your reactions.
I'm happy to hear that.
I'm going to change my clothes.
Thank you for watching this video.
Thank you very much.
I was so nervous.
I'm not nervous when I'm on stage.
I was so nervous, but I was so happy to
see everyone's faces that I almost
cried.
I hope everyone will have a good time
with a lot of people next year.
Thank you very much.
See you tomorrow.