Night watch and idol!
There is a segment in this show.
It's the main segment.
Can you say the title of that segment to
the camera cutely?
My three major elements!
There are so many different things to
draw!
It says, cute!
That's right.
The artist is very happy.
This is what you wanted, right?
Yes, I wanted it. I'm glad.
That's good.
This is a segment where you introduce
the three elements that make up your
self.
So, let's get to know more about you,
Negishi-san.
Thank you for having me.
Please tell me about the three elements.
Here are the three elements.
2D1, 2D2, 2D3
Wow!
I can't tell without hearing this.
2D1, 2D2, 2D3
So there are three patterns in 2D.
That's right.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Let's get started.
First, you're doing an anime.
I love anime.
I really love it.
I can't live without anime.
I really love anime.
I'm looking forward to it.
How old are you?
I like Precure.
I liked it when I was a kid.
That's the general way.
I liked anime, too.
I got into new anime when I was in sixth
grade.
There's a work called K4.
There's a work called Kobato.
I met those two works.
I love anime.
I started watching new anime.
I see.
You started from there.
Do you watch it all the time?
I watch anime, manga, and anime.
I love 2D.
You're a real fan.
I like Gundam.
I started watching the Shining Witch.
I really like it.
I watch it every time.
It's a little heavy.
It's different from other Gundams.
It's a little different.
I said it was a school work.
I'm glad I can talk about it.
Thank you.
I love it.
I really love it.
I said it was the third episode when I
recorded it.
As an anime lover,
I'm a Gundam lover, too.
I'm not familiar with anime.
What did you think of the work?
The mobile suit is cool.
I like the mobile suit.
And the two girls.
I was surprised to see the main
character.
The main character of two girls in
Gundam.
I see.
I was surprised to see the main
character.
I'm curious about the relationship
between the two.
Every time I watch an anime, I'm
surprised to see the relationship
between the two.
That's right.
I'm curious about the next one.
I want to see the next one.
Have you watched Gundam since the first
Gundam?
I haven't seen all of them yet.
I've been watching it since the first
Gundam.
That's great.
I didn't think I could talk about Gundam
in the world.
I'm going to lose my floor.
You're going to lose your floor? That's
a dream come true.
I love DS, DSi, and 3DS.
Really?
This program is brought to you by...
Suspender
Ikigami Junichiro
Nano Nigo
Ikeppe
Ikigami Junichiro
Shiro Amada-san
Thank you very much!