This week's Ebichu Tastas continues from
last week
Ebichu Tastas switch
Suddenly an unknown man enters
Furthermore, a quick-pressing switch
quiz is held
Something is exciting
Ebichu Tastas start
By the way, Hina Kashiwagi is off this
week
Final
Music
There are various things to utan around
Ebisu!
Emi Jujutsu!
This program is brought to you by these
sponsors
The members of the shrimp chu team who
have been participating in the switch
manufacturing company since last week
This week's shrimp chu plus switch is
I'm going to the next room.
The first room that Ebi-chuu visited was
the testing room
What kind of room is it?
Last week, we asked Aoyama san, a
professional switch maker
Aoyama san, what is this room?
This room is for checking the durability
of the switch made at the factory
Ebi-chuu plus switch test
With this machine, they check the
durability of the switch
When there are many, they have to buy 5
million times
This is like the semi-finals of a comic
book competition
It's hard to go to the finals from here
And these are the switches that passed
all the tests
The new switch that passed all the tests
Did you pass all the endurance tests?
Elite!
No one has touched it yet
Congratulations!
Thank you!
Enichu Pass Switch Test
Switch speaks
Today, we can only push one person.
Who wants to push?
Wait a minute!
What happened?
This voice is...
Wait a minute to push the switch!
Who is it?
It's a park!
Everyone, you have forgotten the lyrics
in the park.
Who are you?
I'm a Japanese rock band.
I'm a piano vocalist, Kaiki Ogata.
I don't use guitar.
I'm a little bit
Indies band here's vocalist Kaiki Ogata
It's kind of interesting, so I chose it
for the cast member
It's like this, but I've been greeting
you very politely at the academy
I haven't said a polite greeting
Rock is a crime
Do you understand everyone
I just want to be suspicious
I'm afraid I'm a little bit
I'm a little bit
Everyone was watching me with a very
suspicious look
Actually, Kaichi Ogata, who was quietly
participating in the opening shoot of
the program
When Yasumoto worships
He returned it to Richi
Are you okay? I'm not swimming
I'm not swimming, but I'm bleeding a lot
What is that?
Everyone, is the performance okay?
The script is terrible
It's fun
Erichu plus Ogata Kaiki is
So, the new switch is over
Ogata Kaiki's Who's the Winner Quiz
We don't know who the new member is, so
we will do a quiz about Ogata Kaiki with
a new switch
Please look at this. There is a switch
that doesn't have a quick press button
This is a special quick press switch
made with the NKK switches
Everyone can sit wherever you want
Let's do the one in front of you
It's like a Rika's experiment
Eita is over there
Wait a minute, now, I've been trying to
talk to the company for a long time, so
I've been timing it several times.
Let's ask a little bit. Everyone, please
take the switch you want to press with a
strong desire.
Do you understand?
I didn't ask one by one.
I don't think I'll notice if I get this.
What's wrong, Hirota?
It's shining.
Please appeal it yourself.
Yes, switch.
Question 1
What is the thing that Ogata Kaiji wants
the most now?
It's fast.
Kobayashi was fast.
Switch
I see.
The switch is different.
It's different.
Everyone is a little scared.
I'm a little scared.
I'll choose the first one that shined.
I'll go.
Yes, please.
Don't raise your hand.
Do you know?
I don't know.
What?
It will shine when it shines.
It doesn't have a quick reaction.
Are you okay?
Do you want a hint?
I want it.
It's about the food.
The food?
I'm scared.
Nakayama?
Yes.
Courage.
Courage that comes out in front.
I thought I was missing courage after
seeing the current situation.
What did you think, Chie?
Kobayashi was next to me and didn't
understand the meaning of the food.
I'm not in the mood for that.
I'm in a state of being stupid.
Courage is not.
And the food is.
I eat what I do to live.
It's a lamp.
It's like a lamp on your head.
It's like an anime.
It's a glittering lamp.
I got the feeling.
Kobayashi.
Room.
Correct.
To be exact, it's Bunjou Mansion.
What is Bunjou Mansion?
The quick-pushing switch quiz continues.
It's fun.
The first question is correct.
Next question is the second question.
I'll go.
Please.
When you start talking, you don't have
to give it to me.
You can talk to me.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I understand.
What about Matsuno?
It's fun.
I'll do my best.
Let's go to the second question.
I'll go to the second question.
What was the name of the old sea
monster?
Hoshino was fast.
Yokai.
Why Yokai?
I was a yokai including the old sea
monster.
It's very close.
The old sea monster is the real name.
What else?
Matsuno.
Flower man.
This is it.
It's a pollen disease.
It's a flower man.
No.
It's not a flower man.
When was this story?
This is when I was in elementary school.
I'm not a flower man yet.
Please give me another hint.
Kaiki something.
Yes.
Please give me another hint.
Too much luck!
Yasumoto!
A phantom of the sea!
Correct!
When I was in elementary school, I was
called a phantom of the sea
How did you feel?
Well, now that I think about it, I think
it's a simple nickname
I'm sorry
What's wrong?
It's funny
It's funny, right?
You answer everything seriously
Question 3
What is the saddest thing about Kaeki
Ogata recently?
The price of ordering it was too high
That's also correct, but it's about the
clothes
By the way, how much is this suit?
Are you going to announce the price?
Yes, yes!
3800 yen
10,000 yen
Can you stop this quiz?
Did you notice that the quiz changed?
I just noticed
Please give us a hint
It's about the size of the clothes
What about Nakayama?
I grew up and became small
I know!
But it's close, right?
Matsuno!
I ordered it because it was small
Almost correct!
Please give us the correct answer
The suit I made with the previous
pattern didn't fit
I got fat
I ate too much Jiro
I ate too much ramen Jiro and got fat
There are many reasons
Mr.Gayuki Ogata is a ramen Jiro
Remember that
I'm hungry
Everyone, listen
Everyone, focus
Listen, you may be hungry but please be
patient
The last question
After this, it's dinner
Sorry, it's not good to be more popular
than the quiz
Mr. Ramen
Everyone, focus
Wait a minute
The last question
What is Taiki Ogata's recent problem?
Anyone who knows?
Mayama is going crazy
Mayama
Honestly, I don't know what the lock is
Thank you for watching
It's true that he seems to be a little
lost
But it's okay because it's rock
But it's okay, I'm not shaking
I'm worried about the microphone
It's fine
position, but it's not
Hint
The hint is that I'm the eldest son
Yes
I'm the eldest son
I got it
Wait a minute, let's go to Hirota
Hirota is not aware of it
I'm sorry I couldn't understand
I have to take care of my parents
Correct
To be exact, she is worried about her
parents' old age
She is living with her parents in
Hokkaido
I think everyone has the same problem
After the final question, Hirota,
Kobayashi, Matsuno, and Yasumoto are
side by side with each point
They decide to win by rock music
Answer me!
Matsuno's rock music
But before that
Shrimp Chuu Game Quest
The Ebitune members who got lost in the
world of games last week
The game making project is progressing!
The Ebitune game project that was
suddenly announced
What is the fate that awaits them?
There's nothing again
I'm scared of this
The Ebitune game project is progressing!
There's really nothing here.
There's something else in here.
Can I open it?
What are you up to?
Before we start the game, we will be the
players and aim for a level up.
We will have weapons under the desk.
Choose your favorite weapon.
We have a weapon!
We will do this.
Let's do this.
How is it?
Good.
What is this?
It's okay.
When I took it, I was surprised.
There is a lot.
It's okay.
・・・
What?
The letter was under the hand.
To level up, experience the game all
over the world.
Today's game is Jenga.
Yay!
I like Jenga.
To the losing member, 〇〇.
It's a game that's not good.
I did it.
I know.
It's hard.
I have to use a different imagination.
Sour soup.
Let's start the Jenga challenge.
I've never seen anyone who's like that.
Is there anything you can do?
That's the kind of person.
Isn't this forever?
I got it.
It's fun.
That's the kind of person.
I'm going to fail.
Don't do it.
It's different from the first time.
Only when you're in a hurry.
I'm about to fall.
Oh, my God.
Try smelling it.
Oh no, it stinks.
It smells like a wooden person.
Ready, set...
It stinks.
The game project is in progress.
The journey of a dangerous adventure
continues.
The Kayaoshi switch quiz is a
combination of Hirota, Kobayashi and
Matsuno Yasumoto.
The winner will be decided by a rock
song.
Please show us a rock song.
Rock'n'Roller, Kaiki Ogata's Rockin'
Word.
I'll give you a love that will entangle
you.
Thank you very much.
As I said before, I don't use a
microphone.
I'm in front of the microphone.
Hirota Aika's Rockin' Word.
I'm a professional's daughter, so I have
a plus and minus driver everyday, so
this quiz was easy.
It was a speech, wasn't it? Thank you
very much.
It's a word of Rock.
But that was Hirota's Rock.
Don't deny it.
What is it?
If you're still angry with the rock,
turn on the light.
Hirota's Talk's Talk Doofy Squ item will
light the switch for Foxy Way.
Next, Matsuno.
Gundam.
Did you just say Gundam?
She's right next to you.
Matsuno Rina plus a rockin' line is...
I went to Hawaii and bought a bottle of
water.
That was pretty rockin'.
You crossed the border.
She's got a rockin' way of holding it.
She's got a better style than me.
Matsuno plus a rockin' line is...
Miso Ramen Company!
A straight line to Miso Ramen
Next is Kobayashi
I can't do it
Shut up
Kobayashi Kaho plus a rock word is
Stand microphone is heavy
It's like the lyrics of Aida Mitsuo
Kobayashi plus a rock word is
Aida Mitsuo
Next is Yasumoto
Let's go
Yasumoto Ayaka plus a rock word is
I'm nervous today
To be honest, I'm jealous of the adults
I haven't seen in a long time
It's a cry of heart. It's wonderful.
There are many adults I don't know.
We were nervous when we met after a long
time.
I said yes.
Why?
Something
Something is the most ideal.
Yasumoto plus a rock word is
I'm going to see something on the
shooting star.
Now, the last one is Chue.
Chue plus a rock word is...
Please give a rock word of Daibakushou.
Turn the earth upside down.
How is it?
It's a world, isn't it?
Please give a rock word of Daibakushou.
It's not the one I just did.
I got it.
Did you get it, Chie-san?
Yes, I got it.
Please do it.
I didn't get it.
Let's go!
Rock, paper, scissors!
10 A plus a rock word is
Rock Peace
I want to decide the best of rock among
these
The winner is the person who will decide
I can feel it
There is a person who showed the rock
side
Ok, Okatsu-san
Please announce who was the best rock
Yes
The winner is
Yasumoto-san
Yasumoto-san, why?
I think it's rock music that reveals his
weakness and trauma
It's definitely a rock song
Yasumoto-san, congratulations on winning
the award
Yasumoto-san, this is a gift for you
Can I press this?
Let's give it to the camera
It's surprisingly hard
Thank you very much
That's all for Ogata Kaiki's Who eats
what quiz
So, they added a switch to the shrimp
I'm going to Hawaii
I'm going to eat Miso ramen
It made me want to eat Miso ramen
Sakura Ebiz front line
Sakura Ebiz audition held all over Japan
A lot of applicants gathered at the
audition venue
The program camera sneaked in
I asked the president of Fujii about the
response
I felt that he was more than I thought
More than you thought?
Furthermore, when I asked what kind of
girl he wanted
I want a positive girl like Shigeo
Nagashima
What kind of idol is Shigeo Nagashima?
We will continue to deliver more and
more information about Sakura Ebi.
Please look forward to it.
Ebi-chuu Tastas has started.
Yeah!
The next Ebi-chuu Tastas is in charge of
MC Kobayashi.
Excuse me, is the camera okay now?
MC Kobayashi is very popular.
And more.
Hello.
What is the dish to be served with
shrimp?
It's delicious even if it's spicy.
Next time, we will show you the
unexpected scientific reaction of
shrimp.
This program was provided by the sponsor
you are watching.