Yakult Idol
So, we have a main project for Yakult
Idol.
Can you give us the title of the
project?
Yes, I will.
My three elements!
Good, 17 years old.
17 years old, yes.
How is it? You are making it.
I will draw three elements by myself.
Can I start?
Sure.
Here we go.
1. No friends.
2. No teeth.
3. Change.
We did it. Thank you very much.
The main project of Yakult Idol
No friends?
Yes.
I don't have any friends.
I will tell you an easy story.
I got a summer vacation for the first
time.
For the first time?
Yes.
I did it for the first time.
You are making a joke.
You are doing it for the first time.
I had a vacation for five days.
Good.
I stopped social media for five days.
That's a good story.
I was told that I wanted to disappear
from this world.
You wanted to disappear from this world.
Is there something wrong with you?
I was told that everyone went to
Okinawa.
I had a lot of friends.
I went to Disney.
I went to a mouse.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I went to Disney, had a summer festival,
and traveled with my family.
I didn't have a partner to play with.
I talked to my mother.
I asked her if she had a partner to play
with.
Did you have a partner to play with?
I didn't have a friend.
Did you coordinate your mother?
Did you attend?
I was told that I would attend.
It's an era now.
It's an era.
I asked my mother, but she didn't have a
friend.
It was an era.
It fell.
It's an era.
Are you alone?
I have a younger sister.
I was on a school trip.
I see.
I'm not sure if I'm playing with my
sister.
Is it because you don't have a friend?
That's why I'm stuck at home.
You're stuck at home.
I'm not good at being alone.
Is it a plus for you to express
yourself?
Is it a reaction?
I don't want to be seen by people.
You don't want to be seen by people?
What made you start this job?
I...
Are you a scout?
I'm an audition.
You're an audition.
I'm sorry.
You're a good liar.
Let's start.
Who was the audition?
I was admired by Mr. Nobuo.
I wanted to try it.
I was watching a magazine.
I really admired him.
You admired him.
He was very cute.
I entered the audition.
I was chosen as a candidate for the
first place.
You're bragging.
I was chosen as a candidate for the
first place.
You're the first place.
I'm the first place.
I was an audition.
You're an audition.
When I went to the hospital,
I was told that my teeth hadn't changed.
Maybe it's because you want to be on the
front page.
I'm worried about people's eyes.
That's what people think.