Yakan andIDOL
Yakan and IDOL, as we are holdings the
main project,
The nickname given by idol is
please give it to kids and adults.
Mine is
Thank you!
Now, let's learn more about the 3
elements that make up the 2nd season of
the anime!
So, can you show us the 3 elements?
Yes, here it is!
Ta-da!
Now, please show us one by one!
1. Super-exciting advertisement
Oh, I see
2. Ramen from now
3. Fortune-telling
I see!
Please subscribe to my channel!
First, the group of Super Exciting
Advertisement Club.
Yes, it's my group.
When I thought about it, I thought I was
always thinking about the Super Exciting
Advertisement Club.
I've been thinking about Super Exciting
Advertisement Club for about 8 years, so
I put it in.
For example, what do you think about
before you go to bed?
I want to do it with this kind of thing.
I think about it.
I think about tomorrow.
I think about the live show.
I update my blog every day.
I think about Tokisen every day.
I see.
You went to the festival.
Yes.
I went there this year.
I feel that there are more young fans.
Where did you feel that?
When I saw the audience, I felt that
there were many people around the same
age.
I'm doing an online special event.
There are more people around the same
age who come to the event.
I see.
I'm glad that there are people who
support me in my family.
I hope that Tokisen will be known to
more and more people of various
generations and that they will like it.
You're thinking about Tokisen all the
time.
You're amazing.
You've always been thinking about
Tokisen.
Have you ever dreamed of Tokisen?
I have.
I get up in a hurry.
You're still in a dream.
What did you get angry at in your dream?
I can't get my hands on it.
You can't get your hands on it.
You're an idol.
I made a mistake in the lyrics.
I'm nervous about that.
I'm nervous about that in my dream.
I'm more anxious.
I'm more anxious, but I'm more conscious
of making sure that I'm not nervous.
I think it's good in a sense.
I see.
The first one was a heart-pounding
advertisement.
I decided to do it before the end of the
year,
after the end of the year,
so I decided to close it.
What a wonderful story!
This program is brought to you by
Keisuke Nakashima
Jun Matsu
Yuta-kun
I sent it to you with the offer of
Tempura-san of Hokkaido Suetto and Mii-
san.
Recently, I'm addicted to rice crackers.
Please eat it too.
Thank you very much.