Cute
Cute, right?
It's really cute
All of them are cute
It's fluffy
No, it's not
It's not
Thank you
Are you nervous about your live
performance?
I'm nervous about my live performance?
I'm the type of person who doesn't get
nervous.
I was very nervous once.
Of course, when I debuted on the stage,
I was nervous about whether I could
dance or sing every time.
Recently, I was nervous about a live
performance that was held four years
ago.
It was held in two days at the time of
the opening ceremony of the team.
The first day was held by five people.
On the second day, four people dressed
in costumes and brought brassmins to the
back.
I was nervous about whether I could
accept the ceremony.
I don't remember that moment.
I'm nervous about my performance.
I'm usually nervous, but I wasn't
nervous at all.
I was very reliable at that time.
I was always relying on Yuzuki.
I was nervous without any solutions.
I didn't know what to do because I
wasn't usually nervous.
I'm very nervous.
It's my first time, but I'm still
nervous before the live performance.
That's because there's a new song.
It's like a free live performance.
I'm nervous about singing.
I'm nervous about my back before the
live performance.
I'm a member of the team.
Who's going to hit you?
I'm going to hit you.
I've been doing that for a long time.
I like that.
I'm going to hit you as a member.
What are you most nervous about?
I'm not sure.
Everyone is surprisingly nervous.
Akina and Julia don't get nervous.
Maybe the younger group is more nervous.
You're sitting down.
I see.
We also put on an engine before the live
performance.
After that, I told everyone that I loved
them.
That's the set.
I didn't get any answers after that.
I've been doing this for a long time.
I said I loved everyone today.
I said I loved you.
Thank you.
I'm on stage while saying that.
I want to say that I love you.
I'm not sure if I can get a reply.
I get a reply when I read it loudly.
I'm not sure if I should be nervous.
I'm going to be nervous.
Thank you for watching.
Goodbye
Today we are talking.
I've been thinking about questions.
I want to say it again.
I think Kanami is the fashionable
leader.
Even if you look at Instagram and
YouTube, you're doing it yourself.
I think it's very fashionable.
Do you do your makeup and make-up when
you don't go out much on your day off?
I do my makeup a lot.
Even during lessons?
I do my makeup during lessons.
Do you do your makeup during lessons?
I do my makeup.
Really?
I see.
I do my makeup when I get on the train
from home.
I think I know my makeup when I'm on a
lesson.
Really?
I don't know about others, but I think I
know a lot of people.
I don't know when I don't go out at all.
You don't know when you don't go out at
all.
I don't know about clothes, but I do my
makeup when I'm in a local area.
I do my makeup when I'm in a local area.
Fashionable?
How much do you buy clothes at a certain
pace?
I buy clothes once a month.
I think it's not just about the season.
That's right.
On the internet?
I thought it was cute.
I looked up my favorite dramas and I got
a new one.
Are you going to see the new one?
That's amazing.
It's fashionable.
That's how much I like it.
I think it's a good hobby.
I wanted to hear that.
I thought it was fashionable.
It's like a girl's clothes.
Really?
Is it black?
I wear black clothes all the time.
It's easy to match anything.
My goal is to wear bright clothes.
I'm thinking of doing it as my goal.
I see.
When I have a lesson, I wear makeup.
But when I have a lesson, I don't wear
makeup.
I suddenly take an announcement video.
I take a video for the news.
I make my eyes, so I can wear a mask.
What are we doing now?
I'm going to show you the lesson.
Please take a video first.
I'm going to take a video first.
Please take a video.
I have a question for you.
I've been thinking about this.
You often sing the self-part.
I'm worried about that.
Do you change your style?
It depends on the song.
I can't do it well.
I change my style when I'm writing.
Horizon is the anime's lineup.
The anime's world view is the third
world war.
When I talk about dark things like that,
I become a character in it.
I'm the most conscious of myself.
When I sing a cheerful song,
the staff tell me to sing more like
Hamtaro.
Hamtaro?
If there's a request, I'll do my best.
Hamtaro.
I think Hamtaro is a magical word.
If I think I'm Hamtaro,
I'll be like Hamtaro.
I'll try it next time.
Try it on a live show.
I'll be like Hamtaro.
I'm happy.
It's a different color from the
original.
I'm happy.
I like bright and cute colors.
I like pop songs.
I like bright colors.
I like cute colors.
I'll try Hamtaro.
Tell me you did it.
I'm Hamtaro.
I understand.
Thank you for watching.
I'm so happy to have a conversation with
you today. Thank you.
What should we do in the future?
We will have dinner together.
You promised me.
We always have dinner together.
Let's go out together.
Let's go to the camping site.
You promised me.
We can't go in the summer.
Let's go.
You have a driving license.
Do you drive?
I don't drive.
I haven't driven for about half a year.
Let's go by train.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Is there anything you want to say?
I love you.
I did it.
Thank you.