Ebitune's videos
Hello everyone, I'm Riko Nakayama.
Riko's Room
Today's guest is the oldest member of
Shige-chan Ebichu, who is celebrating
its 12th anniversary this year.
Rika Mayama
Hello, I'm Rika Mayama. Nice to meet
you.
This time, we're going to talk about
Riko's Room.
Last time, we talked about Riko
Nakayama's story.
This time, we're going to welcome a
guest. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Can I say this as a greeting?
It may change later, but I'll just say
it as a greeting.
I heard that you've been cutting your
hair more and more without being
noticed.
That's right. My trademark was a
ponytail.
I can still do it now.
I'm doing it at Kannai Devil.
I'm planning to grow up.
I'm 24 years old.
I cut my hair when I was 23 years old.
I cut it a little before the self-
restraint period.
I thought I'd quit this medium at the
time of self-restraint.
I'm addicted to it. I cut it once and I
want to cut it again.
I've been cutting it more and more
without being noticed.
Is your goal hair shorter?
I want a short bob.
I want to keep my hair as long as it is.
It's very popular with makeup artists.
Mayama, is your hair as short as an
adult?
When I turned 30, my hair was very long.
I want my hair to be a little shorter in
my 20s.
It depends on the person.
Mayama has a strong image of anime.
I like clothes, anime, and cosmetics.
Are your fans surprised?
At first, I was surprised.
I've loved cosmetics since I was a kid.
I started makeup when I was in
elementary school.
Cosmetics are part of my life.
I didn't show it when I was a teenager.
I started doing it because I wanted to
do it.
As a result, I have various hobbies.
I didn't do makeup until I entered the
show.
I was almost naked when I was asked to
do it.
I don't know how to do makeup.
I didn't know how to do it.
I don't know how to do eyeliner.
I don't know how to do makeup.
I've been addicted to cosmetics since I
graduated from high school.
I've been using all my money for
cosmetics.
I think it's a bad way to buy cosmetics.
I buy cosmetics that I like.
I used to buy cosmetics.
I didn't spend money on cosmetics.
Which is better, fashion or makeup?
Fashion or makeup.
I like drugstore cosmetics.
I buy cosmetics because I like them.
I buy cosmetics because I want to be
cute.
Please check the Instagram.
I have a brother.
Let's talk about my sister.
OK.
Do you have any memories of your
childhood?
I remember my childhood.
Did you play a lot?
I loved my brother when I was little.
My brother was good at soccer.
I was in kindergarten.
My brother followed me to the park near
my house.
But I couldn't play soccer with him
because I was a girl.
I was told that I was too small to play
soccer.
I was told that I was dangerous when I
was a child.
I was walking a dog with a shovel in the
park.
The shovel looked like a knife to me.
I was scared that my brothers would be
killed.
I hurriedly went to my mother and told
her that my brothers were killed.
I went to my mother and brought my
brother.
He was a man who only spoke.
He was cute, but he was scary.
It's not a big deal.
I loved my brother so much that I
followed him.
I always followed him.
I played with my brother.
I have a sister.
I naturally became close to people of
the same age as my brothers.
I was able to make a good friend.
It was a valuable story.
You are a woman who can cook.
Have you cooked recently?
I recently cooked because I was hungry.
I ate dinner.
I made a salad with frozen avocado.
I made a salad with potatoes, mizuna,
and anchovies.
I made a salad with mustard.
It's easy, so please try it.
The ingredients are rare.
I happened to have it.
I recently made a salad with cream
cheese.
It's really delicious.
I bought it at a good supermarket.
It's a nut-flavored dessert.
It's really delicious.
I haven't made it yet.
I recently made it.
That's delicious.
I'm most impressed with the recent food.
It's easy to make.
Please try it.
What would you like to try personally in
2021?
I want to try anything.
I want to read a lot of books this year.
I always touch my smartphone.
I understand.
I want to be a woman who can read books
on the train.
I want to read at least one book a
month.
I want to read a lot of books.
I met a woman who can read books.
I was attracted to a small bag at that
time.
I couldn't fit in.
I was gone before I knew it.
I was gone.
My bag got smaller.
Yes.
Next,
What a S solo!
Do you travel often?
Do you have the image of traveling with
your family?
Once a year.
I don't travel that much.
What?
Maybe not as much as Neko-chan.
But I like to travel.
I like hot springs.
I like hot springs, so I only go to
Hakone.
When I have a two-day holiday, I go to
Hakone for a hot spring trip.
At my dad's store.
Hakone!
What about that?
Black egg.
Black egg is also a big meal.
I go when it's open, but when it's not,
I can't go.
You eat it.
I only eat one.
7 years?
7 years of life?
It's the other way around.
Everyone, please try it.
I did it this time in Riko's room.
I like to listen to the other person's
story.
I always listen to it.
So, I'm good at talking.
I'm not good at all.
I did it.
So, I wonder how I can talk.
I want to know that, too.
Do you like listening or talking?
I'm often told that I like talking.
Actually, I like listening.
I talk a lot in the studio.
I don't talk to myself in private.
I talk to myself because I have a lot of
members who are good at listening.
I like listening.
I like it.
I ask questions to people I meet for the
first time.
I have to be able to do that.
Is that so?
I haven't been able to talk about anime
until now.
I have to ask questions that the other
person seems to be interested in.
Otherwise, I can't talk.
It's difficult.
We happened to be together.
We happened to be together on the train.
I had to ride with her until I got close
to her.
That's what happened to Riko.
I didn't have much to talk about.
I was in the middle of a conversation.
This conversation is interesting.
The ad is interesting.
I thought about various things.
Thank you.
That's right.
This is the end of the conversation.
I've grown up.
What is the first thing you remember
when you were young?
The youngest.
The oldest memory.
The oldest memory?
I don't remember at all.
I think it was a memory of 3 or 4 years
old.
It was also a brother's story.
I had a brother fight.
I don't remember what happened.
I had a fight when I was little.
I had a fight with my brother.
I threw things at each other.
I understand.
I threw my alarm clock.
My alarm clock broke.
I blamed my brother for that.
I blamed my brother for my mother.
I think that's the youngest memory.
I have a younger sister.
I feel sorry for my brother.
I feel sorry for him.
I have a younger sister.
I blame my brother for everything.
I go back to the past.
At the children's play, mothers arrange
their hair in a cute way.
They arrange their hair.
At the children's play.
At that time, the mother puts her hair
in a bun.
The mother puts her hair in a bun.
The mother may think it's cute.
I hated it.
I remember hiding.
I thought the twintail was cute.
Suddenly, the hair in a bun.
The ideal was a bun.
I thought it was cute to have a cute
bun.
And when it comes to hair,
the magazine that was popular in
kindergarten,
Love and Berry.
Love and Berry, it's fashionable.
The punch card of the inconvenience of
hair…
The real girl did it, and the
arrangement was like this.
The real girl did the real world of
Love&Berry.
At that time, I did a little twintail
like this.
It's Love, isn't it?
The hairstyle of Love is a little
characteristic.
I really wanted to do it, so I went to
kindergarten to do it.
Then my mother told me that she wanted
to do it.
I thought that the twintail was like
this, but it was like this.
I thought that it was a bad twintail.
So I thought that my mother didn't want
to be misunderstood.
You are an adult child.
The name of the material is…
I don't know.
Mayama's name of the material is…
The name of the material is…
What is it?
It's difficult.
It's very safe, but I think I should
live without forgetting gratitude.
I'm always grateful.
So I'm going to say something weird.
I'm going to say something weird.
Thank you.
Are you saying that?
I'm going to the sky.
Is this story okay?
It's not a religion at all.
It's nothing.
I just want to say thank you to my
ancestors.
My grandfather.
He's watching over me all the time.
He said, I'm going to do my best today.
He came back home and said, I did my
best today. Thank you.
Where are you looking at?
I'm looking at the sky.
It's okay to say thank you.
There's no one who's happy to be
thanked.
I was told thank you.
Thank you, everyone.
What about you, Riko?
What is the meaning of the name of the
material?
It's something I believe in.
It's a word that I was impressed with.
Thank you for watching.
I can't be a good friend.
I've been doing this kind of activity
since I was a kid.
I'll do my best.
I don't think I'll ever do that.
You're always on the move during live
shows.
I'm always on the move during live
You're not always on the move.
I'll be honest with you.
I want to be a person who is loved by
everyone.
I just thought about it.
I think I'll be on the show every day.
That's not a problem.
That's the goal of that day.
Please forget it.
Today's guest was Rika Mayama.
Thank you for coming today.
Who will come next time?
Please look forward to it.