Ebichu's video
Today we came to Zootopia Oh My Kame!
Yay!
It's so cute!
It's like a movie.
It's like we're in a movie.
This is a special cafe.
Nick is also in the seat.
Nick was alone, but we're here to see
him.
We're here to see him before the
opening.
We're here to see him.
We're here to see Nick.
Nick is behind us.
This world is so cute.
I was so excited when I entered the
cafe.
It's still morning.
I was so excited that I took a picture.
It's a collaboration.
There are also original goods in this
cafe.
We're here to see Nick.
We are in our corner.
This is also cute.
There are many things.
This is the most important thing.
This is also candy.
Is this really candy?
It's really candy.
This is also a souvenir.
I'm glad.
This is a masking tape.
There are one scene of the animation.
This is cute.
The mask case is also random.
I can't collect this.
I don't know what's in the box.
I've never seen a random mask case.
I agree.
It's a rare case.
This is cute.
Is this a gift set?
This is really cute.
All the characters have different
patterns.
This is delicious.
I'm wearing a mini towel.
This is cute.
I like this.
I can't collect this.
This is cute.
This is a good size.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Each character has its own
characteristics.
It's so cute.
It's amazing.
It's decided.
The drink is here.
It's so cute.
It's really cute.
First, Maya.
Maya is
a cold ice drink with salt.
There's a lot of ice around.
This light blue is
watermelon flavor?
It's watermelon flavor.
There's salt around it.
You can enjoy it while changing the
taste.
I'm a ice candy-like drink that's melted
and hardened.
I'm going to add strawberry juice to
this ice candy and drink it while
melting it.
It's a good idea.
I'd like to try it.
I'll try it.
It's sweet.
It has a strawberry scent.
It's delicious.
It's perfect for summer because you can
drink it without any problem.
I can't get away from it.
I'll try it.
It's delicious.
The salt makes it sweet.
It's watermelon flavor.
watermelon flavor?
It's amazing.
I went to my grandmother's house in the
summer and saw watermelon.
I put salt on it.
It's delicious.
I'm going to eat this.
This is a sandwich plate with a lot of
local vegetables.
I want to make a fruit-like vegetable
motif.
It's a vegetable plate.
I'm going to eat this.
It's a vegetable curry that anyone can
make.
There are plenty of vegetables in it.
Let's eat.
Thank you.
I'm full.
Is it good?
Yes.
It's delicious.
Tuna.
It contains tuna.
It looks delicious.
I've only eaten one bite, but it's
delicious.
It's healthy, but it's also fatty.
It's very thick.
It's delicious.
I'm sorry.
I'm scared.
How is it?
It's delicious.
It's a meat.
It has a meaty texture.
It's a spicy curry.
It's spicy.
It's delicious.
It's very rich in vegetables.
This is good.
It's a summer vegetable.
It's a season now.
It's delicious.
Next, I eat dessert.
There are strawberries.
Corn cream pie.
This is NAKANAORI's corn cream pie.
I eat corn cream pie.
I eat half of it.
There was a corn cream pie.
Was there?
I can put it in my mouth.
I eat it with a rock-paper-scissors.
I drink water.
I put it in my mouth.
I'm very happy.
It's cute.
Thank you for your viewing.
Let's eat.
It has a mild taste.
It's crispy.
The cream inside is very soft.
The sweetness of the corn is also good.
It's really good.
I can feel the helicest.
It's delicious.
It has a mild taste.
The taste is really mild.
It's not too mild.
It's good to eat and get healthy.
It has a strong taste.
It's really delicious.
I'm glad I ate such a healthy menu this
morning.
It's really cute.
It looks cute.
It's the best.
I'm happy today.
It was delicious.
It was delicious, cute, and happy.
It's good.
I want to meet Zootopia again.
Tokyo is held in Tokyo Plaza on the
Omotesando.
It will be held until July 25.
Osaka will be held until August 1.
Please check the website for details.
How was it, Amaya?
It's amazing.
Even fans of the work can enjoy it.
If you don't know the work well, the
food is really delicious.
I think you can be satisfied.
I want you to use it in various ways.
Please come to the event.
Thank you for the meal.
It was delicious.
Special Cafe is the best.
I'm excited.
Bye bye.