The final novel, release date, and the
final product...
Oh, sorry, I wrote it.
Please read it again.
You're so comfortable with your speed.
I'm trying to keep it down as much as
possible today.
Oh, really?
Let's talk at full speed.
I brought gummies that go well with tea.
Wait, there's gummies that go well with
tea in the world?
Yes, I got a T-shirt from the Japan
Gummy Association.
Really?
Yes.
Okay, 3, 2, 1.
Oh, but the neck...
Hello, I'm Yakan, a student of Viva
Home.
Today's guest is
Let's call her!
This is our idol!
Hello everyone!
I'm Uka's Aoi Ruri!
Nice to meet you!
Speaking of Aoi-san,
you joined Uka-san in September 2021.
That's right.
I think it was hard to join Uka-san in
the middle of the year.
How was it after a year?
After a year, I finished all of Uka's
songs for free.
Yes!
It was hard at first.
It took a while to get into the band,
and it was hard at first,
but recently I've been enjoying each and
every activity.
I've come to think that idols are fun.
You've come to think of it?
I've come to think of it.
How many songs did you put in?
I put in about 40 songs.
40 songs?
Yes.
I put in 40 songs.
That's right.
It's true that you join the group you've
been in before.
That's right.
It must have been hard for you to do
that.
Oh, you two joined the group at that
time.
Yes.
But did you enjoy it?
I enjoy it every day.
I'm a full-time job.
You enjoy it every day?
Yes.
A full-time job?
That's great.
What was your original career in this
world?
I was originally walking my dad and my
friend Takeshita.
Well, not walking, but shopping.
Shopping.
He let me do a little shopping.
Yes.
I kept it for a while that day.
But when I went to Tokyo Station,
I happened to find the same person.
Really?
Yes.
I thought, this might be fate.
So I called him and got it.
Wow.
That's how it was.
That's amazing.
It's like a royal road.
Yes, it really is.
Takeshita Street from Kanagawa?
I was a very bright kid back then.
I was very excited about Harajuku.
I knew it.
I took my dad to Harajuku on my day off.
Wow.
So you went in and started dancing and
singing?
At first, I wasn't sure what I wanted to
do.
You weren't sure?
Yes, I wasn't sure.
But I found my dream and I wanted to be
a dancer.
That's amazing.
You're very polite.
Very elegant.
Thank you.
Yes.
Really.
So you joined UCCA in September.
And on November 16th, you made your
major debut.
That's right.
And you were announced as a surprise at
the May concert.
How did you feel when you were
announced?
At the time, I was completely white and
happy.
I hadn't been able to follow the reality
yet.
But as I was getting ready, I realized
what it was like to make a major debut.
I don't know what it was like at night,
but what was it like to make a big
debut?
Did you have a lot of producers and
adults?
I think I got a lot more people to
interact with.
Really?
That's a major debut.
Yes, it is.
Your major debut is on November 16th.
Yes.
UCCA's major debut is on November 16th.
It may be the right time.
A lot of people watch YouTube on a
scroll.
I'm a scroller.
This program is provided by Sora-san,
Kekoda-san, Asa-san, Suminoe Sosuke-san,
and Nikunemunashi-san.
Today's recommended gummy is the lemon
flavor of the Piregumi.
Please try it. Thank you very much.