We finished the 10th year competition
with Shirito Ebichu School Kajiwagi
Hina.
So, these 10 years have been made by
Mayama, Aya-chan, Mirei-chan, and me.
We've been friends since the time of the
major debut, Indie-z.
We've been friends for over 10 years, so
we're called the 10-year-old players.
We've been together for over 10 years,
so we wanted to make a live performance
that felt like a live performance.
That's why we made this set list.
It's a nostalgic medley I used to play
when I was in Indies.
I'm an adult now, so I can't do it
because I'm too old.
I'm a mochi miko in the middle of the
night, and I'm the one who can do it
because I'm a member.
The medley and the mochi miko are the
best.
And the adult rock part.
We've grown up and grown up.
I'm glad that I was able to show
everything at once in a live show that
feels like history.
I thought about various things.
I think there were many people who
supported me in this era.
And also people who supported me before
I debuted as a major.
Today, I was in the front row, and
everyone was nostalgic.
I'm having a lot of fun, and I'm
excited.
I'm crying.
Thank you for watching.
I was impressed by all the people who
were looking forward to this.
After all, the one that made me the eye
was the old indie medley.
I was nervous. I did it in the five
songs.
There are people who know it and there
are people who don't know it.
I'm looking forward to it.
I thought you would see it, but we were
also doing lessons.
I remember the choreography
unexpectedly.
It was like this last time, I mentioned
it like this, but you said it was like
this last time.
It was really fun to do it with the
choreography.
So, the one that impressed me was the
medley,
and the last one, Fantastic Baby Love,
I thought it was good to do it here.
I'm glad I could hear from the fans,
too.
I'm sorry for giving up for 8 years.
I was really worried when I was making
it.
After finishing it, I was happy to hear
that the other members had fun.
I'm really relieved that I can finish it
safely.
There is a performance and a singing
contest plan, so I would like to enjoy
it until the end.
I had fun today.
Thank you very much.