The next day
Good morning
Today is Mary
Yes!
Ta-da! Everyone's cell phone case is now
a shoulder bag!
The ratio is increasing!
Three people!
What happened to Aikito-chan?
She was the first member to make it a
shoulder bag.
What happened now?
I'm going to make it a shoulder bag.
I thought it was a shoulder bag.
It's a twin.
It's fast.
It's like 10 minutes.
It's faster than usual.
It's not.
It's more than a month.
I feel relieved.
It's like the usual place.
Let's do our best.
It's like a big slum.
We started to do a lot of things since
the day after.
We had a live show at the end.
That's right.
I don't want to do this anymore.
I'm going to cry.
Everyone, I think I'm still in a dreamy
mood today.
Tomorrow too.
Yeah.
After tomorrow.
I'll do my best.
I'm sorry.
Good morning everyone!
Today I'm with ZEPP HANEDA TOKYO!
It's my first time at ZEPP HANEDA!
So I'm going to eat lunch now!
This time I'm eating Chinese food!
There's eggplant, shrimp, chili, and
many other things!
I'm going to eat now! Bye bye!
I got an extra bed.
For the rest of this night, I will focus
on Furthermore stigma on.
Lightly
See you!
Little girl lying on the floor
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6
We are showing our best to the staff.
Thank you.
Good morning.
Please come to the monitor.
No.1, it's okay.
No.2, it's okay.
Thank you.
The one I'm wearing now?
Is it the one from LALA?
No, it's the one from Kanami.
It's not from Kanami.
It's because there are three of them.
I see.
LALA.
There are two of them.
Thank you.
Hello.
Bye.
I'll do my best.
How is it?
Look at this!
I got my makeup done!
Today's best makeup artist is...
I'm relieved that she did my bangs.
I'm talking in Japanese today.
It's really hot when I'm on stage.
My bangs aren't broken, so I don't look
like I'm sweating.
That's my bangs magic.
I'll do my best.
I'm going to be the shadow of today.
You can do it, Aki.
I'll do my best.
What's the announcement?
Announcement is...
New single.
It's a new single.
I'm done.
It's already over.
Let's go to the key hole.
There's a water drop.
A moment of tension.
Let's go to the key hole.
Today, we're going to the Summer Heart
Good Tour 2022 with the three key
characters of the Super Tokimeki
Publicity Department.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you. I'm Hiyorin.
I'd like to ask the audience to stand up
and stand in line.
The audience who has sat down in front
of the stage twice cannot stand up and
watch.
Please sit down and watch.
I'll do my best.
I'm sorry.
We'll be back soon.
Are you ready to have fun?
Please pay attention to the members'
hair.
I'll be right back after this.
Let's have fun.
Nice to meet you.
Thank you.
3, 2, 1, start!
Lock on!
Yes!
Let's do our best.
Move to the next location.
Thank you.
Let's do our best.
Bye bye.
Good luck.
We'll do our best after the comeback.
We'll do our best.
I was so happy to see Hyorin's smile.
It's really funny.
I was a little nervous, but I'm fine.
I'll do my best to perform for you to
see.
It's a bit cool, isn't it?
Please look forward to it.
Thank you very much.
I'm back from dinner.
I'm going to eat dinner.
I got pretzels from Sanrio.
I'm going to eat.
I'm done.
I got my hair done.
This is Kuma's room.
Listen to me.
I had my makeup fixed.
I had lunch.
I was so sleepy after lunch.
I was like,
but the makeup artist said I could
sleep.
I was so nervous.
When I got my bangs done,
I was like,
I'm wearing an iron, so I'm going to
wake up.
Suddenly, I was like,
I woke up.
I laughed at the makeup artist.
I was surprised.
It was fun.
I'm going to do my makeup now and have
my bangs tightened.
Oh, who's that from behind?
Hey, Asan.
How's your hair and makeup today?
My hair and makeup today is going well.
I'm going to see it when I'm in a good
place.
Recently, Katakake smartphone shoulder
is also popular.
I'm thinking of buying it.
It's really good.
Let's match the glasses.
Bye bye.
I like this hairstyle.
I'm next at Kitsuji-san indoors.
Page 25
This is Arashi Bourjee.
Thank you for watching.
This one is with tape.
So cute!
I'm going to do the same thing.
Pineapple?
No, no.
One, two, three.
Just like this.
Okay.
Don't go back.
I should read from here? From today?
Yes, from today.
You should read from here.
I should read from here.
Thank you for coming to the 2022 Monatsu
no Heart Get Tour with the Sanrio
Characters of the Choutokimeki Promotion
Club.
I'm Sutaaki Aki, the Choutokimeki Lemon.
Thank you.
Thank you!
The audience sitting in the front row
cannot watch the performance.
Please sit down and watch the
performance.
The audience will shout out loud for the
1000 yen.
You can't jump.
Aki-chan is cute.
Everyone, Zepp Haneda is back!
Please look forward to it!
Please wait for us! Bye bye!
Thank you!
Thank you for watching!
I have one more good news.
Please watch the next video.
Thank you for watching.
On the 25th, the fans will be able to
watch the live show of the show.
The fans will be able to watch the live
show of the show.
But, before the show, the last
Christmas,
the staff of the show will be able to
watch it.
The staff of the show will be able to
I have a lot of memories of this event.
I'm so happy that you guys came to the
last Christmas party.
Please make good memories with us.
Thank you.
It's so beautiful.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven,
eight, nine, ten.
Let's do it together.
It'll be fun.
I can't believe I'm taking these to my
own George Ford.
I don't know got me here.
Thank you so much.
Thank you!
Thank you for coming to the event.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you.
Thank you for coming to Hameda Park,
Tokyo!
It was the first time we met.
I'm glad to meet you.
Thank you for watching!
I'm glad to be able to do it.
Thank you very much.
It was really fun to have you cheer for
me.
Osaka and Sendai Park are a little far
away.
It was really full of flowers.
I was happy to see it.
Thank you very much.
I'll do my best.
How was it, Julia?
It was so sudden.
I didn't think it had been over a month
since the tour started.
Really?
It was already September.
I see.
I hope we can be a little more powerful
at today's live show and get a lot of
support tomorrow.
I'm looking forward to it.
We have a lot of announcements to make.
First of all, we have a new single,
STAR, scheduled to be released on
November 9th.
It's been a while since we released a
single.
That's right.
We've been working on an album.
We also want to do a message to our
fans.
We want to send a message to our fans.
New single STAR.
What?
What is it?
What is this?
Please look forward to it.
We've already recorded it.
Yes.
STAR.
It's a good song.
It's a really good song.
It was a little difficult.
It was difficult.
It was a new challenge.
But it's a really good song.
It's a really good song.
And Christmas is December 24th and 25th.
It's a live performance with a live
band.
Monsieur
I'm not going to be a little bit of a
song.
I'm sure it's different from the
previous songs.
I want to do a lot of cool songs with
the song.
And, I'm going to be with you today.
I'm going to be with you in November.
I'm going to be back.
I'm so happy.
I'm looking forward to it.
We have a lot of plans.
Please look forward to it.
Thank you very much.
Let's have fun.
Next is Osaka.
Thank you very much.
It's been a long time.
Takisama!
It was fun.
It's a song called Nako.
Saitama Super Arena 2021
Saitama Super Arena 2020
I only did it live.
I didn't do it.
I'm nervous.
It's not related to the world.
Live sound source
It's recorded.
In the previous single.
If you listen to the sound source,
I found a cute voice.
What?
Namiwa-Ruki
Puka
Puka Puka Puka
It's like a space.
There's a cute voice.
I want you to listen to it.
Puka Puka Puka
Let's ask.
Who was it?
I think it was one of us.
I don't know. I think it was one of us.
Let's ask who it was.
That's all for today.
It was fun.
I heard that it was the first time I
heard it during the live.
There were a lot of people.
It was a new experience.
I hope you enjoy it.
Thank you for watching.
What did you write for ME난 it today?
it is.
hundreds of thousands of каждый
Bye bye!
I hope you enjoy the music video.
I love the song, I want to perform it
live soon.
I want to sing it as soon as possible.
I really want to sing it.
This is the first song.
Thank you for watching.
I wanted it.
But I can't explain it.
What song is it?
November 20th.
Oh, November 20th.
I'm going to sing this song.
It's amazing.
It's a 10-piece song.
How many times do we have to do it?
6 times.
1 2 3 4 5
I really wanted to do this.
I'm so happy.
I'm going to do my best.
I've never done this before.
I'm so happy.
I'm looking forward to next year.
Last Christmas is the best.
Sakiya, Senri, good luck!
We're so excited!
Please subscribe to our channel!
We'll be waiting for you!
Bye bye!
I'm going to go around the live Zepp
Haneda.
Please come and see me.
Everyone is helping me.
I've been here once to do stretching.
I'm going to do it.
Robbie is a second floor.
So, Puss is going to do it.
I'm going to do it.
Thank you very much.
I found a staff who is collecting the
contents of the pet bottle.
Thank you.
This is the limited digital lottery of
Choutokimeki.
This is the fan club.
Thank you for watching!
1st place, A-SHOW
Please press the button below to
participate
Here we go!
3 places!
Please press the button below to
participate
I have a photo of me in the drawing
board
I will put the image on the drawing
This is different from the photo of the
jacket
This is different from the photo
It is different from the photo of the
jacket at each venue
I am a genius of the dance team
Everyone, please pay attention to me
Thank you
This is the A prize
This is the T-shirt of the members
This is the B prize
This is the morning call
This is the T-shirt of the members
Please participate in the contest
I will introduce the shoes
Here
Cute
I was wearing a carry case for Tiori-
chan.
Cute key holder for everyone.
Towel! This towel is a towel fabric that
absorbs moisture well in the pool.
So it's okay to sweat a lot.
T-shirt! I have a little decoration, but
you can also wear it as an over T-shirt.
And...
This is a photo of my name.
Oh, cute!
So cute!
5 of them?
5 of them!
Please buy them!
That's all!
That's all for today!
See you next time!
I'll watch it.
Can I watch it?
Together.
They don't notice me at all.
I can't wait to eat it.
No?
Oh, Nagouru's PR manager is having a
meeting with everyone.
S كいすき Suki Suki Same here as usual.
Bye bye!
It's done!
Yay! They noticed!
Please click Subscribe and Like again.
Thank you!
We want to deliver the biggest
excitement to as many people as
possible.
Through this Makuhari Messe, we want to
be a good library that can step up
further.
We want to polish our performance so
that we won't lose to this company.
I'm really looking forward to seeing the
smiles of the 1000-year-old brothers.
I want to make a lot of memories.
I think it would be fun if the six of us
could go to various places.
On October 22nd, let's go! Dokusen
Makuhari!
I'm always crying
I wash away my dirty thoughts
Otherwise, I can't walk
Let's go anywhere
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday
The cityscape after the rain is
sparkling
It's like my heart is...
Everyone, play the sound of the puddle
Play the rainbow piano
Please subscribe to my channel!
I wonder why?
When I smile, it seems like the world is
shining
I can relax by turning the umbrella
Otherwise, I can't walk
Someone is crying somewhere
I'm getting wet somewhere again
Isn't it cold?
Someone is crying somewhere
I want to share my feelings with you
The scenery I don't know before my eyes
Let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye, thank you for
yesterday
The cityscape after the rain has been
colored
I drew a fragment of the future on the
canvas of my heart
It will be filled with the fragments of
the future
I can say it now, even the reason for my
tears
When I'm lost, I immediately remember
Even if it rains, I'll smile
Look, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye to me from yesterday
The cityscape after the rain is
sparkling
It's like my heart is a clear sky
I play the sound of a rainbow ball
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye, goodbye to me yesterday
The town after the rain glitters
It's like my heart is a flower
I dry my tears
I wear a rainbow dress