Ebichu's videos
What is this?
It's a blackout.
I don't know.
I don't know at all.
What is it?
I don't know if you're doing it.
Blackout?
But I didn't work much.
I didn't work.
It's actually very strong.
Oh, it's strong.
Maybe.
I don't know.
But I didn't work.
In the MV.
I was drinking tea cups.
I was drinking tea all the time.
I didn't know.
I don't know.
TKG?
TKG.
It's cute inside.
I'm watching while drinking tea.
I'm sure she's been watching all along.
It's a measure.
It's difficult.
Is it a measure?
Wow.
Did you get it right?
But you need a clue.
I don't have a clue.
I'm not sure.
I don't know.
I'm going to think about it.
It's not a problem.
It's not what I said.
I'm going to be minused.
I'm sad.
I'm scared.
Let's make up for it.
It's scary to be minused.
It's pretty hard.
What is the answer?
I don't know.
What's the problem?
I don't want to get minus 2 points.
I'm really scared.
It's been 5 years.
It's been 5 years?
It's 2015.
That's right.
It's been 5 years.
I don't remember at all.
I didn't want to say it.
A child came.
A child.
At the end, A-chan was trying to stop
the moving boy.
I think so.
I remember when I was a kid, I saw a lot
of kids playing with firecrackers.
I remember that.
It's a tie.
She still comes to the special event.
What? 2 points.
I couldn't answer that.
She's not crying anymore?
She's always smiling.
She's watching over her growth.
We're getting along.
So Aya-chan, minus one point?
Really?
This is bad.
To be continued...
I remember!
Did I wake up right after departure?
Place?
What should I do?
You went to play!
I went!
What happened to that?
I know the place!
I remembered the name!
It was pretty early in the morning.
I don't remember because it was early in
the morning.
It was early.
I was worried because there were so many
cars.
I can do this.
Ta-da!
Cosmo World!
I think it's a good one.
I remember the trunk door was open and I
heard a beep.
That's it!
The answer is...
The app was playing the song.
Mirei, you got it right!
I got it right?
I got 2 points!
I did it!
When I put the app in the app store,
the app wasn't closed.
But I kept saying PP.
I didn't know what to do.
I see.
I was panicking because everyone was on
it.
I see.
I'm scared of human's decadence.
Cosmo World is totally different from
the one above.
Minato Mirai is the best.
I thought it was Chugabai.
That's right.
It's right, but it's not.
Let's be careful about our memories.
It's amazing.
I'm scared of human's decadence.
What happens to the oldest child if the
youngest child is so old?
I'm so upset.
The oldest child is the youngest child.
I don't know.
We don't talk about this.
I think I've heard this before.
I was talking about this on the show.
I think it was during the tour.
I remember saying that at the end of the
show, but I don't know where.
What I just did was sumo matches.
Let's try fine stroke using ot slices
You don't get tired of teasing?
Hey!
I don't get tired of teasing.
You always lose.
You always play with me like that.
I only play with you.
If it's time like this, I won't wake up.
I'm here.
it was a cat
It was the last day of the solo tour.
The last day?
The answer is...
I'm worried
I see.
It's impossible.
It's difficult.
If I were in this situation, I wouldn't
know anything about baseball.
I don't know.
I wonder where you were happy.
It was Nagano.
I'm sorry.
The name of the store?
I was struck back.
I told you not to strike back.
I can't return it.
But
Riko and Hinata
You know, don't you?
I think we were together.
I wrote the name of the store.
Oh, my God.
It's amazing.
It's really
It's a dark history for me.
I don't remember anything else.
I'm so embarrassed.
This is difficult.
I don't know.
It's a very similar name.
It's true.
I'm scared.
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
It's difficult.
It's very elegant.
Let's go to Hokkaido next time.
I don't have a name that has a sense of
Hokkaido.
Let's go.
Let's go together next time we go to
Hokkaido.
Let's go.
We can eat it now.
Let's have it taken for making.
Let's do that.
We need to rewrite history.
It's a big story.
Let's do that.
Thank you very much!
What's that? Why did you say it was
100,000 yen?
I don't think everyone knows this.
I've never heard of it.
When did you say that?
Where did you say that?
I did a talk show alone at Singalong
Singason.
I told the fans for the first time at
that time, so they weren't there.
Oh, I see.
Thank you for buying it.
I bought it.
I bought a picture of the first time.
Thank you.
It's amazing that one of the people who
bought it is a member.
Thank you for watching.
Bye!
What? What do you mean?
I was wearing a school uniform for the
ring festival.
It was so cute.
I wanted a picture of an idol.
I wanted a picture of a cute girl.
I'm sorry.
And I bought it because I was told to
give me a new one.
I was told that I was right.
I was surprised.
It was a very rock-like feeling.
All the idols who were together were
playing the drums.
I was surprised just by passing by.
You were wearing a limousine to the
Budokan.
That's right.
I can't forget the face of Nogizaka at
that time.
I can't forget.