Shrimp Chuu Tastas has started!
This time, the people who add shrimp to
Chuu are Indians.
Then, what is the reaction of this
science?
It's delicious with a good feeling of
spiciness.
Chuu Tastas starts!
Which version did you use this time?
Now, do you want to participate in the
subscriber event?
If you're thinking about a 37-year-
oldIsn't there anything you like in the
world?
This program is sponsored by the sponsor
you are watching.
Are you okay with the camera?
Nice? Good?
Good?
Good!
This time, I, Kobayashi, will be the
host.
And...
I'm the reporter, Shinta Kiyoto.
I'm Jue.
I'm scared of the world, so I'll fly
away. Jue Jue Jue!
Please take care of us.
Kobayashi is the MC, but I'm worried.
That's right. Are you okay?
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm worried.
I borrowed a switch last time.
How was it?
It was fun.
There are many switches.
It's fun.
I can't go any further.
I'll give it to you.
Please subscribe to our channel.
What?
You just said you'd go back.
We don't have time to talk.
By the way, Kashiwagi is still in the
movie industry.
So, what are we going to do today?
By the way, what is the theme of this
time?
Today, we came to the park of
Nishikasai.
What is it?
I got it!
Matsuno!
There is a dinosaur, so it's a dinosaur,
isn't it?
There is a dinosaur in the back.
Riko, do you have a good idea?
Let's play tag with everyone.
People are playing tag!
This is a deja vu
I saw it the other day
That's right
What are we going to do today?
Let's play with the Onigakko
Onigakko?
Wait
No, no
Come back
Everyone is surprised
Chuu
Young members are increasing
Young members
Sorry
Bye
Can you go?
What are they going to do?
Please announce the theme
We are going to add Indians
We are Indians
Why are you adding Indians?
I don't know
Actually
West
West Sakai
Sakai
You didn't read it
Actually, West Sakai
Sakai
I don't know
West
In Japan
It's the city where the most Indians
live
That's right
You know it
In Edogawa
The city where the most Indians live
There are about 2000 Indians
In West Sakai
It's called Little India
If you look closely
There are many Indians in the park
Kobayashi
Please interview the Indians
I have an idea
Let's ask the Indians
Why are you becoming Kobayashi?
Kobayashi Kaho plus interview with
Indians
I'm going
Good luck
It's suspicious
Are you okay with the camera?
Are you okay?
What are you doing now?
We are talking about various things
Nice? Good?
Good
What are you talking about?
As you can see
They are using the microphone as a
microphone
They are brave
They are getting along
The interview is very hot
Is it near here?
I want you to do it quickly
It's a little long
The interview continues
It's different from Japanese culture
It's amazing
Wolf
It's a wolf
Please try it at Yasumoto Wolf
Kobayashi plus interview with Indians
It's a wolf
Is it over?
It's over
Welcome back
What?
Kobayashi Kaho plus interview with
Indians
Thank you for watching
So, the members came to this building
What is here?
Namaste
Sorry for the noisy kids
Great
I've never seen this before
Kobayashi came here after hearing from
Indians
This is Suwagat Indian Bazar which is a
restaurant that serves Indian daily
necessities and food
So, Kobayashi plus Ante is
There is a shop of Indian goods in
Nishikasai
Great
Coconut
I want this
I love coconut
What is this?
This is the one I was impressed
This is called Pan
Pan? I can't understand
Popcorn?
What is that?
This is rice flakes
Can I taste it?
It's good
Wow
What Kobayashi found is
A popular Indian dessert made by drying
rice
It's like a
It's like a volleyball
Wait a minute
Not yet
It's not yet
It's too early to wait
Don't drop it
Let's eat
Yes
It's good
It's the best
It tastes like Indian
It's good
Eat this
It's the best
I ate beans
Eat beans
I ate rice
Eat beans now
We didn't touch it
Shrimp Chuu Pass
Indian bean dessert is
Kobayashi, say it's good
It's good
It's salty
It's chewy
It's fragrant
It's good
How about Yatsumoto?
It's like a seed of a seed
It's soy
Yes, it's a bean
It's a bean
How about Nakayama?
Eat spicy food
Is it Nakayama?
It's not spicy
Is it spicy?
Shrimp Chuu Pass
Indian bean dessert is
How about Nakayama?
Eat spicy food
Mr. Placard became Nakayama
It's important to eat
It's not spicy until now
I want you to eat spicy food
I want you to eat sweet food after that
There are many things
She is very generous
I'm a big fan of it
Which do you want to eat, sweet or
spicy?
I want you to eat spicy food first and
then sweet food
I want you to eat sweet food first and
then spicy food
I want you to eat spicy food first and
then sweet food
I got it
So, they tasted the spicy snack
recommended by the store manager
I'm not good at spicy food
Ladies first
Ladies first?
So kind!
Why did you say that?
Because it's business
Egi-chuu Pass
What is the spicy Indian snack?
Let's eat
The smell is amazing
It comes later
It's spicy
What's wrong?
The pepper is here
It's not coming out
The pepper is working
What's wrong?
It's spicy
It's good
How about you, Nakayama?
Where are you from?
I'm from Tokyo
It's spicy
Egi-chuu Pass
What is the spicy Indian snack?
Nakayama?
The store manager was Nakayama
How about Nakayama?
It's spicy
Nakayama became a Kansai person
We have the image that Indians love
spicy food
Do Indians eat sweet food?
It's very sweet if it's sweet
Spicy food is very spicy and sweet food
is very sweet
There is no Chinese food
There is Chinese food
There are many things, but I like sweet
food
I will eat sweet food next time
What is this?
This is
Sorry
What is this?
This is called
Graja moon
Mix wheat flour and
cheese
and open
and add sugar and juice
Isn't this fruit?
It's not fruit
What is this?
Donuts
Donuts are made with sugar and juice
It's so sweet
After this, add Indian sweets to shrimp
It's very sweet
To try Indian sweets
Don't open it too fast
Be careful
I'm scared
I'm nervous
It's open
This is Indian sweets, GULAB JAMUN
The ball-shaped sweet donuts are soaked
in syrup
Shrimp Chou plus GULAB JAMUN
Please smell it
What is the smell?
It's a fruit
Fruit?
I don't know
It's hard
It's very sweet
It's not just sugar
I see
It smells like sugar
But there is something else
What is it?
It smells like a kitchen
What?
It depends on the family
It smells sweet
Okay
Please smell it
It smells like bread
Who?
I know
Did you smell it?
It's like sugar
But someone doesn't know
I have smelled it
Have you?
Can you tell me?
It smells like a good thing
It's very good
It's a good answer
It smells like a good thing
It's a good thing
It's a good answer
Hirota, what do you think?
There are some people who don't know
What do you mean?
Flowers or something
Good idea
The meaning of Grav is rose
Wow
The answer came out before Kobayashi
answered
Shrimp kiss plus Grav jam
It's a good smell
The comment went into the manager's pot
When he tried the sweet sweet sweet
Oh, it's sweet
How about Hirota?
It's sweet
How is it?
It's just right
It's sweet
I put 3 or 4 sugar in the tea
Mayama?
The manager recommended it, and the
sweet sweet is just right for Mayama
And the famous thing in India is
In India, there is a drink called Chai
Yes, Chai
I drink it 3 or 4 times a day
Really?
Do you know Chai?
No
I don't
Kobayashi, you don't know?
What do you think Chai is?
Chai?
What is it?
Chai is
What do you think?
Chai is a flower
A flower
Who doesn't know Chai?
Nakayama?
I know it
You know it?
Milk?
No
Then it's milk
Milk tea
It's Indian milk tea
Yes, it's called Chai
Kobayashi and Nakayama learned one
thing, and the tasting time is over
And MC Kobayashi will decide
Are there any places where Indians
gather?
Yes
There is a community hall, so Indians
gather there
Community hall?
Yes
Is that today?
Let's go
If you have time, please go
I want to go
Let's go
Thank you
And before that
Ebichu Game Quest
The game project is in progress!
The members of Ebichu have been chosen
to challenge various games for the game
project that was suddenly announced.
Last time, we showed a great game
project with Jenga and it was a success!
What is the quest this time?
I'll open it.
A letter.
Let's read it.
A letter has arrived.
Who is it?
Who could it be?
Experience the games of the world and
aim for a level up.
Today's game is a black beard game.
However,
What?
The losing team will get a ____________.
I see.
Okay, let's get started.
What is it this time?
What?
It's a beard dance.
This time, Ebichu will challenge a black
beard dance.
I'll do it.
Let's do it here.
But this is...
I'm scared.
I wonder if U-ma has it.
Wait, isn't it too soon?
No!
I'm not a good dancer.
einer!
I did it!
Liar!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, JeLiE, yeah, yeah,
yeah.
Thank you for watching!
I'm scared
Can you hurry up?
I'm going to chase the person who hurt
me
Eri-Chu Game Project
The dangerous adventure continues
Please look forward to the next episode
Is there a place where Indians gather?
There is a community hall, so Indians
gather there
Wow!
Let's go!
After saying goodbye to the generous
manager, they go to the community hall
where Indians gather
Then
Wow!
What's going on?
Wait a minute!
There are so many people here!
Why are you dancing?
Somehow he noticed
Wait, wait, he's dancing in the middle
What?
That person is...
I've never seen him before
I've been waiting for you all
What?
Everyone, today you've all come to a
party for me
Why?
The vocalist of the indie band Hiya,
Kaiki Ogata
He will continue to participate in the
location as a castas member
Everyone, are you excited?
Yes
Are you excited?
Is that okay?
How about it?
The people who were excited with the big
atmosphere were the Indians living in
Nishikasai.
So, first of all, this question.
Are there any celebrities in India that
are popular in this country?
I think there's only Sumo.
Sumo?
Sumo, Sumo.
Sumo.
Yes, yes, yes.
What did you say about Sumo?
Sumo.
By the way, are there any other
celebrities you like?
8.6 seconds bazooka.
Stop saying the same thing.
Stop saying the same thing in front of
us.
8.6 seconds bazooka is made by Kaiki and
Kobayashi.
Kobayashi plus Kaiki Ogata plus 8.6
seconds bazooka is...
You have to do it.
I can't do it.
Good.
I taught you the dance earlier.
Wait a minute, Mori-san.
What is this?
What is it?
It's a new buzzword.
Maybe...
You don't know?
8.6 seconds buzzword, you don't know?
This is a comedian, right?
Of course.
You don't know?
Do you want me to dig it up?
You know, right?
No.
Then, please try it.
Please dance.
What?
Do it quickly
ruler of drunken своих
to dance together
Ah
'll enter the Beast
Wait Please
Thank you for watching!
Hey, what is the last gorilla?
Yes, yes, I want to wait a little
I don't know this person
I don't know the last gorilla
So, if you add Indians to the shrimp
8.6 seconds bazooka
Both the shrimp and the Indians loved
the 8.6 seconds bazooka
It's a good opportunity
I rarely have this opportunity
I want to promote shrimp blood to
Indians
Next time, Ebichu will have a PR battle
with an Indian.
What will be the result of the heated
battle?
Moreover, a mysterious fortune-teller
appears.
Is it amazing?
The shocking future of Ebichu members is
revealed.
This program was provided by the sponsor
you are watching.