Good evening!
Hello, we are Kajibara.
Yes.
Today, we are going to play the emoji
gesture game.
Yeah!
Emoji.
We use various emojis, right?
We use it to contact people, blog, and
Instagram.
We use a lot of emojis.
We use gestures to recreate those
emojis.
And we ask them to guess the answer.
Isn't it difficult?
I know the answer to the question.
So, I'm a little scared that I don't
know the answer to the question.
I can't express it in words.
If you get the correct answer, you can
get a point.
That's right.
I see.
You have to guess how many emojis you
have in one minute.
You have to guess what emojis you are
expressing.
Then, you can get a point.
Okay.
Shall we decide the first one?
It's important, isn't it?
The order is important.
How many emojis are there?
Let's start with the loser.
Okay.
Rock, paper, scissors!
You are the loser.
Juri is the first.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Yori is the second.
The third.
The fourth.
The fifth.
The sixth.
Juri is the first.
The second one is Juri.
Let's do it!
Juri, are you ready?
Okay.
When you look back, there is a TV
monitor.
Look at it and make a gesture.
Are you ready?
Ready, go!
Heart?
Heart and ribbon
I don't know that
Star?
I know
I don't know that
What is this?
What?
This is cool.
What is this?
What?
Next mark, triangle.
Correct!
Sorry.
The answer is...
I don't know.
What was that?
I can't see the answer.
Correct.
Let's answer.
I've never seen this before.
I saw this on Twitter.
What is it?
This is difficult.
I don't know.
I'm scared.
What is it?
Piyo-chan, are you ready?
Yes, I'm ready.
Ready, start!
Snow!
Time!
Clock!
Next!
Milk!
Milk, pimpon!
Sushi!
Chiripa!
Bear!
No! Sheep!
No!
It's melting!
What is it?
Next!
Pass!
It's frozen!
It's cold!
A hat?
Ramen?
A bus?
Lip!
What is it?
A kiss?
Lip!
Time's up!
It's hard!
Wait!
It depends on the question!
It's amazing!
It's hard!
A kiss?
How many points?
6 points!
Amazing!
Thank you!
Is there a emoji?
You can choose now!
Next is Aki-chan's turn!
Aki-chan knows a lot of things.
But Rirako doesn't know much.
That's true.
Rirako doesn't know much.
Please show us your face.
OK.
Aki.
Ready, go!
Trash bin.
Correct!
Aki-chan's turn!
I don't know.
It's floating!
I don't know the name.
Red head.
Correct!
I don't know.
Stop it!
Next!
What is it?
Stop it!
Correct!
Please subscribe to my channel!
It's like a mask.
It's a pair of glasses and a beard.
Correct!
It's a match.
It's a table.
It's thinking.
It's like a telescope.
Correct!
I don't know how to describe it.
What is this?
It's a table.
Aki-chan got 6 points.
I'm the same age as Pio.
We're the same age.
It was cute.
Thank you for watching!
Next is Haachan!
How do you feel?
I'm not confident!
I'll do my best!
You can do it!
Ready, start!
Bird!
Angel!
Cupid!
Correct!
Sandman!
What is this?
Book?
It's difficult.
Pass!
Crying!
What is this?
Isn't that correct?
No.
Uru-uru.
Ah, I got it.
The pot is about to spill.
Water?
Air?
Correct!
What?
Uru-uru.
What is it?
It's a flower.
Uru-su.
What is it?
Correct!
Smile.
I was looking at you.
This is so correct.
Hurry up and answer.
It's like an air-lobby.
It's not an air-lobby.
It's not a flower?
It's a flower.
What is it?
8 points.
HANI got 8 points.
Yay!
You said you weren't confident.
I'm the first.
It's very easy.
Your smile was the best.
It was the last one.
I'm glad I got ramen in the spring.
Next, hitokai.
I'll do my best.
How are you ready?
OK.
How about me?
Nothing.
Let's go.
Ready?
This is a push.
This is a ball.
This is a bowling ball.
This is a bad luck.
This is a funny face.
This is a finger.
I want to see METTARucat's pose.
The Laughter feels them over and over.
I want to see the ribbon.
The head and eyes are full of laughter.
all didn't want to see their faces in
the video.
Thank you for watching!
I'm not sure.
How many questions are there?
How many questions?
I'm sorry.
Is this a game?
I don't think so.
I think the angel is a little wrong.
The answer is 9.
It looks difficult.
Please subscribe to my channel.
The last is KANABI.
I may be able to catch it.
I've seen five people.
I may get the highest score.
I'll do my best.
OK.
Ready, start!
Mousetrap.
Hamster.
Correct.
B.
Fried bread.
That's right.
Baseball.
umbrella.
That's right.
Crab.
Correct.
That's right.
Old man. Old lady. Tea. Tea.
Sashimi. Sashimi.
Next. Next.
Thank you. Next.
Next.
Strawberry. Strawberry.
It's a trick.
It's over.
10 questions.
I won.
It was good because everyone saw it.
The winner of the emoji game is KONAMI.
It's interesting. I've never seen this
emoji before.
Thank you for watching.
This way?
Let's go this way.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Please write emoji in the comments.
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
Please subscribe to my channel!