This time, I'm going to do what I want
to do as MC of Ebichu and Nakayama Riko
Ebichu and Nakayama Riko's special
edition
Nakayama Riko thought about a project
Then
etc.
reality of the
Silence, silent show
However
This time, they suddenly start running
Everything is in a hurry
The sequence of unexpected situations
Nagayama Tastasu Start!
What is it?
Add various things to private Ebisu
Middle School!
Ebisu Tastasu!
This program is provided by the sponsor
you see
It started! Ebisu Tastasu!
Thank you for watching!
Yay!
Today, I, Nakayama, will be the one to
do the daily work
Yes, I want to do my best
This time, Nakayama will do the daily
work
This is the second time
This is the second time since the second
barbecue
You didn't do anything during the
barbecue, right?
Yes, I didn't do anything
This time, I'm really worried
No, we are more worried
By the way, what are you going to do
today in this outfit?
This time, I'm going to do the shrimp-
chewing plus Nakayama Riko
Oh, I see
I'm going to do the daily work as the MC
I'm going to do the shrimp-chewing plus
It's a revolution
Yes, it's a revolution
It's a big adventure
If you don't do it properly as the MC,
you will be in trouble
Do your best
Do your best, Riko
I'm not doing my best
This time, we are going to do the
special episode that MC Nakayama really
thought about
What is Nakayama?
Nakayama, you will do the 1% of the
1% of the
Nakayama always exceeds our expectations
I'm sure a new plan will be born
What do you want to do first, Nakayama?
Something easy
Something easy?
What is that?
I'm not doing anything
For example, what should I do?
Just stand like this?
Yes
What a declaration that she is not doing
anything
This time, the staff had a meeting with
Nakayama in advance
What do you want to do if it was a show
that was only for Riko Nakayama?
I can't speak at all
Nakayama's plan started with a light
heart
I can't believe it's going to be like
this
Can I stand up like this?
I want to sit down too
Sit here
This is a good idea
The members will get along with it
Don't talk about anything
Rikuo wants to sit down first
You can sit down
Good night
Start
I can't speak
I spoke
This is not good
The TV reaction is definitely NG in
Nakayama's plan
You can't speak
Please do it again
Start
Thank you for watching.
Let's change the location
This is fun
Nakayama, is this okay?
It's okay, it's the next one
Is it okay?
It's over
It seems that the plan is over
The plan is over
Is this okay?
Is it okay for the treedaka?
I don't mind if you cut this part
Cut it?
It's cut?
It's time to be patient before the next
corner
Patience?
Why do you have a camera?
It's a story that you should do it at
the school
You just messed up your clothes
It's not something to do at the start
Let's go to the next one
Is there anything else you want to do?
I want to do it while running
While running?
Wait a minute
You want to do other program's songs
during the program?
I want to do it
Nakayama said this at the previous
meeting
I want to run in a big place
I want to do missions
It's not a program that Nakayama thought
of
It's something that she just wanted to
do
Nakayama Riko presents
Playing hide and seek while running
I want to decide the rules
Let's divide the teams
There are many people
You can divide as you like
Rika, Ai, Ai, Rina, Nankaho, one person
I see
Let's divide the teams
The one who said it just now is the one
in the back
Rika is over there
Mirei is over there
I see
Kabu is fast
Playing hide and seek during running is
divided into two teams
First, Mayama team
Second, Nakayama team
When everyone is caught, it's over
This is a half-time
There are 3 people in total
By the way, we have a mission
It's like running
Playing hide and seek during running is
this kindergarten
2 floors, 2 floors, and a close-up view
There are three areas in each area.
Each area has items that are necessary
for the mission clear.
These are the Nakayama stamps.
If you can find the stamps without being
caught by the hunter, you have cleared
the mission.
The time limit is 10 minutes.
The hunter will be released in 30
seconds.
If you can escape to the end or clear
the mission, you will get a luxurious
item.
Luxurious item?
Did you think about this?
Yes, I thought about it.
Is it cucumber?
Cucumber?
It's not decided yet.
Even if it's cucumber, it's only
cucumber.
What else is there?
The first is the Mayama team.
Ready!
No, no, no!
It's a 4-man battle.
I'm going to get caught in 10 minutes.
I'm going to get caught right away.
Stand up!
Oh, I'm scared.
Koba and Hirota move to the second floor
to hide
Mayama and Matsu run in the first floor
They don't catch up with the cameras in
the serious dash
Let's take a break here
We still have time
Now it's time for the hunter
Who will be the first to escape?
Oh no, what should I do?
The runners are screaming out of
excitement
The hunter has moved
I caught you
Why?
To be continued
Just one minute, without any chance,
Kobayashi is secured
The remaining three runners are still in
the game
Right next to Kobayashi
I'm going to get caught
Hirota escaped from the hunter
He disappeared
He's in danger
He's moving
I'm going to get caught
I'm sorry
They hide themselves in the warehouse
Let me rest for a while
I'll take some time
Is it a strategy or a big one?
They decided to hide until the time
comes
Good luck!
That was cool
I don't know that I'm caught
It's hard for the cameraman
Mayama is running there
At that time
Did you find it?
They are looking for the mission stamp
There
The mission stamp is hidden in the
warehouse
The hunter is sneaking
I found it
I can't do it
Please wait
On the second floor, Mayama's appearance
is also in the library
Found the mission's cry-stamp
But the hunter's evil hand
No!
Found it!
Don't come!
The hunter's evil hand
She managed to overcome it
Oh no, I'm scared
Mayama is scared of the hunter
It's about time
Nakayama-san, let's add a hunter
One more hunter, please
The hunter appears
The hunter has appeared from somewhere
The hunter is scared of the hunter
Now there are two hunters. Will the
remaining three escape?
At that time, in the gym...
I'm tired.
Mayama is trapped alone at the limit of
physical strength.
And...
Mayama. Mayama. Mayama.
Mayama.
What will Hirota do in the warehouse in
the back?
Don't worry. Just a little.
Don't go out now.
I won't help you.
He's TaKu bunched up by his creative
nature
Meanwhile, BANN to spend some 강아
Where is it?
How will grant them approval?
I found you!
Will he become a hunter's prey?
Can he escape?
Can he escape the hunter's pursuit?
Matsuno was the first one to get the
power
I'm stuck
How is it?
Two more
She's ready to go
I'm so tired
4 minutes left
Can the two runners escape?
Aika is caught
Hirotaro is not here
He can't run so he is hiding
I'm not good at running
I'm hiding from the distance
I see
Scary
Hoshina's prediction is correct
Abandon the mission and continue to
escape
Mayama is
Hoshina is
Mission's Yamastampu was discovered
Now he has two stamps
3 minutes left
The 3rd hunter is here
He's chasing the runner
I'm scared of the runner
I can't see him, so I'm chasing him
Hunter Ogata is in the atmosphere where
Mayama is spilling his guts
I can feel it
I can feel it very well
I found you!
He runs to the second floor, but...
Kayama, in great trouble
Stop!
...but to be Les Tian that seems to give
up,
Thanks for watching!
Mayama saves it clear
And
Mayama매amafatu
So he saves the camera
The decisive circle is less driving
Sikakki
Take the sword
slips
Again and again...
They were four at last there Six Rentai
The Blank m truly
Three hunters.
They are in a dangerous trap.
Two hunters are waiting for you
Hirota was the last one to escape
I won
The running record is 9 minutes 29
seconds
They couldn't escape
They escaped for 9 minutes
Amazing
Nagayama is coming
Nagayama
Amazing
Who did it?
In the middle of the war
Nagayama was collecting only two mission
stamps
Will they get the luxurious items?
This is not Nagayama
It's Nagayama
Look at this
Look at the inside
A bug
Really?
This is a bug
There is also a trap stamp
This is annoying
If you press the button, everyone will
die
It's like a monster
People react in a moment
They are like predators
They were excellent hunters
I will run again
You can do it
Nagayama team's challenge
Nagayama, you are next
I was looking forward to it
I was happy to see it
You are just a viewer
It's your turn
The second half starts
I'm going to be a hunter
While the hunters are coming out
The members are looking for a safe place
Nagayama team's challenge
The big guy is very scary.
He looks like a pervert.
The hunter is released.
Hoshina is looking for a safe place.
I don't know.
I don't know what to say.
Where are you hiding?
The idol is serious about the locker.
Who is the most likely to escape?
Mirei-chan
Mirei-chan seems to be tired
Hinata and Sebasikko
I think so
Hinata and Sebasikko are good at using
wisdom
One minute from the beginning
No one can be found yet
Hunter type
The one who is hiding right next to him
is
Scary
Run
The one who is hiding right next to him
is
Scary
The hunter's presence is not enough to
catch the eye.
At the moment, Yasumoto and Hoshina are
in the gym.
Kashiwagi is in the library.
And this time, Nakayama is in the second
floor hall.
The hunter is in the second floor hall.
Nakayama is in the second floor hall.
The big hunter is approaching.
I found you!
Don't come! Don't come!
I can't do it!
Let me taste the fun!
You can run away!
It's just the beginning!
I'll take you off!
I can't do it!
The first hunter to be attacked is...
Nakayama, worked as the chief Become
a想像者
7 minutes and 30 seconds remaining
Will the runners escape until the end?
Next episode, the finished of His Love
for Chinese
Next episode
Next time, end of Running in China
There is something unthinkable
You can watch the camera while expensive
Nakayama
The show is a project that you can only
watch.
It bloomed! It bloomed!
It's not coming out.
What is it? What is it?
Nakayama's project that you can only
laugh.
Look forward to it!
What is it? What is it?
This program was provided by the sponsor
you see.