Let's eat!
I'm sorry.
I was just looking around.
I'm a customer.
I'm so nervous.
You're nervous, aren't you?
You're here to deliver something cute,
aren't you?
I'll make it cute.
Have you ever done that before?
I'll make the title cute.
Customers say that, too.
Please make it cute.
I was in the second grade of elementary
school.
That's great.
I'm glad.
Yakan and Idol
Welcome to Viva Home! I'm Yakan, a
former classmate of Stardust.
Let's call our next guest!
This is the idol!
Hello everyone!
The one who will grab the crown of the
entertainment world is
MIA!
I'm Mita Ibuki from CrownPob!
Nice to meet you!
Ah, you're here!
Mita-san from CrownPob!
Yes, please!
You came to deliver something cute,
right?
Yes, I came to deliver something cute!
Your concept is cute, right?
This program's concept.
Mita-san, nice to meet you!
What are you saying?
Your voice is cute too, right?
I'm still nervous about this.
I'm always worried.
Yes, so this month is already December.
We're trying to end 2022.
In November,
I've worked with a lot of idols,
but what does it mean to have all
humanity live for free?
On December 20th, we're releasing our
second album, Live.
This time, we want to make it easier for
each and every one of our members to
meet each other.
I see.
We want our first audience to know more
about CrownPob.
So we're holding an event called All
Humanity for Free.
Just answer the questionnaire, and you
can get a screenshot of the event.
I see.
A lot of our first customers came.
People who didn't know about CrownPob
before?
Yes, and people who were curious.
And people who came because they had
time.
It was a weekday, but they came early to
work.
And people who were curious but couldn't
come to the live show.
They came to talk to us.
What do you do when you take a picture?
First, I ask if there's a pose I want to
do.
If there isn't, I say,
I'll do this.
You're like, I'll leave it to you.
I see.
Then, let's say you're a special guest.
I'm so nervous.
Are you sure you don't want to be
nervous?
I'm nervous.
You're like, nice to meet you, everyone.
I didn't think I'd be nervous.
I'm going to ask you to take a picture
with me.
Let's do that.
I don't know how to pose.
I'll leave it to you.
I see.
I'll do it with my left hand.
You do it with your right hand.
What do you mean?
I'll do it with my right hand.
I see.
One, two.
Like this.
Thank you.
I'm leaving it to you.
I'll just have to put up with it.
I don't want to show it to you.
I'll go see it by myself.
This program is brought to you by
Mamono-san
Mohi-san
Nori-san
Akkun-san
This video is brought to you by Moo-san.
Thank you everyone.
I look forward to working with you.