Night watch 아까 idol
Please subscribe to my channel!
3rd
The elements you're making are 2D and
3D.
The Holy Land Tour.
Yes, the Holy Land Tour.
I see.
What is this?
This is the Holy Land Tour, where you go
to the place that is based on the anime.
I see.
It's super fun.
It's like the scenery you saw in the
anime is there.
Do you go around in various places?
Like here in the anime?
I went around a lot.
The first Holy Land Tour I went to was a
work called Hibike Euphonium.
What?
It's a work of water science.
Uji is the original place.
Yes.
If you go to the city of Uji, it's
already full.
The scenery you saw in the anime.
The company that makes Hibike Euphonium
is Kyoto Animation.
Yes.
Kyoto Animation is really amazing.
You go there and take pictures and feel
the atmosphere.
It's the same even in the smallest
details.
I see.
So if you go there, you'll see the same
scenery as the anime.
It's the same even in the smallest
details.
It's super fun.
I'm sorry I don't have the vocabulary.
I know.
I want to go there.
I agree.
What other holy lands do you go to?
Just yesterday, I went to the Holy Land
of the work called Licorice Recoil.
Where did you go?
Around the Sky Tree.
I see.
The Oshia Station.
Yes, the Oshia Station.
Yes.
Tofu.
And the Asakusa area around there.
Yes.
And the anime artists draw the details.
That's nice.
Yes, it is.
I see.
I'm glad.
So you go there.
Yes, I go there a lot.
I see.
You can enjoy anime and manga at the
same time.
Yes, I can enjoy them even when I'm
outside.
I see.
I think it's an indoor place.
I think so.
But I love going there to have fun.
I want to go to many places.
Do you go there alone?
Yes, I go there alone.
I go with my mom.
With your mom?
Do you watch anime with your mom?
No, I go there with my mom.
You are friends with your mom?
Yes, I tell my mom to watch this anime
and that.
She watches it several times.
What is your favorite anime?
Violet Evergarden.
Wow, your mom is so smart.
I see.
So, you are going to make 2D.
Yes, I have to make 2D.
I see. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
コンスメは?
What is this?
You may think so.
Sorry. Sorry. Sorry.
Please give me power.
The practice has not started yet.
It hasn't started yet.
This program is
Hanari-san
Haster-san
Morning Koichi-san
何の4号さん
I sent it by Kepes's offer
Please continue to support me!