Thank you for watching!
Nogizaka, we'll go on!
We've been broadcasting the second game,
BATTLE, for two weeks.
I'm sorry.
In the battle between the juniors,
a new bond was born in the new
generation of Nogizaka.
Tonight, the only battle that didn't go
in, the battle of the last minute.
From the first round of the first round.
In the container with the liquid, each
person adds as much water as they like.
If you spill even a little,
the pair will be punished with a sharp
chair.
The battle of the last minute again.
Will Kaki and Inoue be able to protect
their seniors?
What is this? Can I drink this?
Is this a strong drug?
Is it a strong drug?
If you touch it, it will melt. Be
careful.
Why is that?
Wasn't there anything else other than a
strong drug?
The second round.
Seniors Nakamura and juniors Kaki.
How is it?
No.
What should I talk about?
I've had a stroke.
So I know the pain.
I see.
So I don't want to get hit.
I want to return it to you cleanly.
Nakamura, it's your first time, right?
It's my first time.
I have no choice but to leave it to you.
Good luck.
These two are good at drawing.
They are good at drawing watercolors.
They are good at drawing watercolors, so
they are not good at drawing surface
tension.
I did surface tension when I was in
elementary school.
That's a huge advantage.
What is free study?
I was doing something like floating or
sinking a 10-yen coin.
So you were controlling the surface
tension freely.
I know the degree of the tension.
I'm not a mythological person.
I'm a person who does that.
You are good at drawing and surface
tension.
I may be good at drawing.
You are good at drawing.
She is a semi-professional in surface
tension.
I'm good at drawing fine lines.
It's your first time drawing a line.
I don't know what it feels like.
I'm shaking.
These two are good at acting.
That's good.
I want you to play a game to see who
gets hit.
I will do that.
The first setting is changed in the
second round.
How much do you attack to drive the
opponent?
The last battle to determine the
boldness and caution begins.
The first battle is from Inoue who won
the rock-paper-scissors.
Let's start.
Your hands are shaking. Are you okay?
Yes.
She's good.
She's not good enough.
She studied about the surface tension.
She's good.
I couldn't get the prize.
She studied about the freedom of the
summer.
She's good.
What did she study?
She said, there is.
There is.
There is?
She studied about the freedom of the
summer.
Yes.
So, it's possible that she didn't get
the prize.
Well.
Let's start.
The surface tension.
Yes.
She's shaking.
Her eyes.
She's quite bold.
Her feet are not touching the ground.
Are you okay?
I'm slipping.
Can you still go?
I think I can.
I think so, too.
She's so energetic.
Yes, it's clear.
You've done a lot.
Let's go.
It's okay.
I feel like it's tea time.
What if you go with the feeling of tea
time?
I don't have to be nervous.
Let's go.
Start with the surface distance.
It's getting excited.
Oh!
Wow!
You're still going?
I'm going to stop.
Stop!
Clear!
You're doing pretty well.
Your decision was good.
It's time to start the game.
From here.
Yes.
Start.
I can't decide where to put my feet.
Wow.
Shoulder, knee, both knees.
That's it.
I want to see the surface.
Start.
It's stuck.
The tip of the stick.
It's okay.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I'm nervous.
The climax of the game.
The game starts.
Are you excited?
I'm excited.
Let's go.
I think I'm ready.
This is a dangerous place.
OK.
You cleared it.
This is amazing.
This is a big success.
This is more than before.
This is amazing.
This is exciting.
Do you see this?
KAKI, are you excited?
I'm excited.
Let's do this on the crane camera.
You have to be careful from now on.
I will go right away.
I will go to the surface.
Start.
Did it break?
I shook it.
I think it's broken.
It's okay.
It's amazing!
It's shaking!
The surface is shaking.
It's amazing!
It's already amazing!
Now, it's either the senior or the
junior.
It's scary!
Be careful of the top of your head.
Please do a surface landing.
It's getting excited.
Yay!
This is the world of Nanteki.
Let's do a little finger heart.
No way!
Points go to the Experts!
I thought it was OK, but it spilled.
I'm sorry.
You were quite aggressive.
I was shaking.
You were shaking and went.
You were aggressive.
You were good, Nakamura.
As expected, he is a great player.
Great.
I did research for today.
I'm glad you did research for
hypersensitivity.
I did.
That's right.
So.
Thank you.
The current goes to Lilia.
If you avoid this, then.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for your participation in the
analysis.
Go!
Why?
Ahhhhh!
It's a bomb!
It's cool!
It's an action movie!
What's with the rolling?
I thought you were just watching.
I'm scared.
There's a lot of people.
Are you okay?
I'm fine! I'm sorry!
Inoue did her best, but
because of what she did,
you got hit.
So, I'll keep this memory forever.
Promise me you'll be good friends with
me.
This is a good opportunity.
You're a great senpai.
Let's go to the next game.
Wow!
Are you okay?
Don!
It's started.
I'm Banana Man, your host.
Thank you for watching!
One, two, three.
To Manara's heart,
I love you.
That's good.
Now, Himura-san, please tell us about
today's project.
Let's go.
If you make Akimoto cry, you'll get a
reward.
Thank you.
What is this?
What do you mean?
What? What do you mean?
I'll explain. Listen to me.
Akimoto has sent a lot of members.
I've said this recently, but he cries
right away.
I see.
I just went to see him at a live
concert.
Thank you for coming.
No matter how much I try.
I announced my graduation.
I think he'll cry right away.
He'll cry. He really cries.
Cry.
I've never seen him cry like this.
So, this time,
I'm sorry to say this, but the junior
members have a mission to make Akimoto
cry.
I see.
It's a secret.
They've already done the recording in
advance.
I see.
So, Akimoto, there may have been
something strange.
There was.
There were so many meetings that didn't
work out.
One member came into the room.
This is it.
It's just a meeting that doesn't work
out.
I was so surprised.
I'd like to see it.
I hope it's a moving cry.
You cry.
Cry.
I don't like it.
I'm afraid.
Akimoto has seen all the members
graduate.
He's about to cry.
He's holding back his graduation this
month.
His tears are at their peak.
So, this time, the junior members will
challenge the project to make Akimoto
cry with their hands.
If Akimoto spills tears, it's a
delicious reward.
The top batter in the cry-plan is
Tamura.
We always play a joke on each other.
It's not easy to be serious and thank
you.
I'd be happy if he cried.
I don't know.
Tamura is talking about his enthusiasm,
but what about Akimoto?
He only knows that the other party will
cry this time.
He has a mission to make the junior
members cry and get a reward.
What is this?
There was a reverse mission.
Akimoto knows.
I'm in pain, too.
I'm so happy.
The cry-contest between the two members
begins.
I have a lot of opportunities to talk to
Mana-chan.
I thought it was hard to convey my
feelings seriously.
I asked him to make time for me today.
I'm nervous.
We always play a joke on each other.
I was called by Mana-chan at the live
show.
I thought the distance between us had
shortened.
I've been...
Mana-chan...
What?
I'm in pain.
Why?
I thought I could do well as a host.
What is this?
Akimoto knows.
I know.
Before the show started,
and when it ended,
I was called by Mana-chan.
I'm crying naturally.
But...
But what?
Akimoto is crying.
While talking about the memories of
crying,
Akimoto is overwhelmed with emotions.
Akimoto got a reward just by nodding.
I thought...
I didn't know that I could make him cry.
I thought I'd do my best if I was in
charge of it.
I'm usually told that I'm a high-powered
person, so I'm trying to talk to a lot
of people.
But Mana-chan, you've been kind to me,
too.
I'm sorry I've been cold to you on my
birthday.
I'm really happy about that.
I thought you'd like me to do that.
I thought we'd get along if we were in
the same school.
I thought so.
I was happy that he felt that way even
though I was separated from the first
and fourth graders.
I cried.
I thought I was a bad girl.
Akimoto endured so far, but she cried
because she couldn't stand Tamura's
honest words.
I was happy that I could be a senior and
be able to do bad things without feeling
guilty.
So I'm really sad that I'm graduating.
The first battle was a tearful battle.
The battle ended here.
I heard that you don't usually cry.
I thought that Mayu was crying and
telling me her feelings.
But it didn't work.
I thought it would be okay before the
battle started.
But when I talked to Mana-chan in front
of me, I felt overwhelmed.
I had tears, but I cried regardless.
The plan went bankrupt?
I cried a lot after that.
The next participants are Gokisei's
Inoue and Sugawara.
We've been with Gokisei for a year,
and we've received a lot of things.
We want to show our gratitude.
I hope we can show our gratitude as a
whole.
I'd be happy if you could cry.
Who will cry?
The second round of the tears battle
starts!
We have something to show you.
We've prepared a video.
A video?
I'd like you to watch the video first.
A video of a scene in the Nogizaka
factory.
I was very happy when Chi-chi, who was
rehearsed, talked to Manatsu.
I'm sad that Manatsu will be discharged.
Please look forward to the future of
Nogizaka 46.
I was very happy to celebrate my
birthday with Manatsu's national tour,
Sendai Park in 2022.
I'm sad that we can't spend our
birthdays together next year.
I'm rooting for Manatsu wherever she is.
I'm about to cry.
The message of the five students
prepared by the two of them.
What is the meaning of the words that
each of them has in their hearts?
I'm glad you were able to speak up
today.
during the MC.
I'm glad you told me not to hold my head
up when I go down the stairs.
1 minute 35 seconds from the start.
The third message is already full of
tears.
Furthermore,
When I first met you, I was nervous.
I've been relying on you, so I've been
able to support you.
The tears of Akimoto and the tears of
Sugawara are the key.
The tears of Akimoto and Sugawara are
the key.
I'll start with Gokisei.
I was surprised.
I don't want to.
Why are you all so good?
Both of them are overflowing with tears.
Inoue is aiming for a substitute for
tears with a monkey-like trick.
I was in the video, but I couldn't get
into the video.
I'm a little worried about the members.
I'm sorry.
I'm so happy that you told me that I can
bother you when I just joined.
I'm still graduating.
I'm going to show you my eyes.
I can't put it into words.
I drew a lot of Manatsu, my favorite
character.
Is this all Nogizaka?
I didn't know you could draw so
differently.
I'm so happy.
I think I was a little scared when I
first saw Nogizaka.
I'm surprised that they get angry behind
my back.
Especially, I felt that they were more
determined to move forward.
I taught them a lot of things.
I'm glad that they followed me.
Thank you.
The time of the election is over.
Are you still crying?
The next person is Iwamoto, born in the
3rd generation.
We are very close.
We go on a trip together in private.
We go to Manachi's house and cook.
Even if it's not a project, I cry with
the words I say.
I'm sure the recent類戦 is weak.
So I have confidence.
What is Iwamoto's strategy to be close
enough to go on a trip together in
private?
I like cameras.
So I made a slide show.
I also wrote a letter.
I want to read the letter together.
Iwamoto made a slide show with a photo
he chose from 100,000 photos on his
smartphone.
He read the letter with his feelings and
cried.
It's a wedding-like, bride-friendly
strategy.
I'm sure it's weak.
16 years?
When I first came in?
This is a letter with my favorite
picture of Manatsu.
This is my favorite picture.
I'll read it.
First of all, to Manatsu.
I still have a little time, but thank
you for everything you've done for me.
I think there have been so many painful
and painful things for about 11 years
that I can't even imagine.
Manatsu has been kind, warm, and
supportive since we met.
I'm sure you've heard a lot of people
say,
I've never met such a kind person.
So I'm always thinking about someone
else.
I cried so early.
The tears of Akimoto are crushed on the
way to the end of the two-way flow of
memories and letters.
I'm always thinking about someone else.
That's the nice thing about it.
I wonder when Manatsu will be selfish.
I wonder if I'll never say it until I
graduate.
I'm a little bit down.
And Manatsu, who is standing in front of
me as a captain, is the coolest person
in the world, no matter what anyone
says.
Akimoto, who had no chance of
counterattack due to the letter's
violent attack.
Thank you so much for listening to me
when I was in pain.
If Manatsu wasn't there, I might not
have been able to smile and act.
I don't know what it means to be in
Nagisaka.
I'm thinking about who I need.
I'm not thinking about anything.
I'm thinking about Manatsu.
I'm thinking about myself, who said
thank you for contacting me.
I thought about it and replied in a good
way.
With a letter of gratitude, Iwamoto is
overflowing with emotion.
Akimoto doesn't make a move and Iwamoto
drops tears here.
So, honestly, if Manatsu-san is not near
me, I don't know what to do.
I'm sad and I can't stop.
But I promise to contact Manatsu-san
when I'm in pain.
I love Manatsu-san's smile.
When everyone is laughing, I look at
Manatsu-san consciously wondering if he
is laughing.
If he is laughing there, I think from
the bottom of my heart that he is happy.
So, although it's a short period until
graduation, I pray that Manatsu-san can
spend every day with a smile.
I will burn Manatsu-san's cute eyes
until the end.
From Nenka.
Nenka cried.
Thank you.
You wrote a lot.
I couldn't write it at all.
Akimoto couldn't do anything just by
crying.
This battle was also a battle of tears.
Everyone is crying.
Akimoto is not doing anything.
Akimoto is crying.
They are both giving each other a
reward.
I'm crying too.
I think I'm going to cry again.
My wife and I are all crying.
We're the only ones laughing.
We're like crazy people.
The letter was really something.
I was going to write more than 5, so I
forced myself to write 5.
I was writing, and I was reading it and
I was definitely going to cry.
Thank you.
I like light one.
This one.
I'll sing a song to subscribe my
channel.
A song?
Please subscribe my channel.