Like videos of shrimp-chewed shrimp!
Yuno's hair!
Yay!
I'll ask you a lot of questions.
I'm Yuno's hair, who asks for the latest
information.
I see.
This is the Yuno version of Rikko's
hair.
I'm going to ask you a lot of questions
about the latest news.
Thank you.
You explained it twice.
What did you do today?
What did I do today?
Today is the day after the lesson.
So I woke up in the morning and didn't
do anything.
So yesterday...
Yesterday? I went to the sauna
yesterday.
What is the most recent anime or manga
you've seen?
The most recent anime or manga?
I'm into Paripi Koumei now.
I see.
Do you know Paripi Koumei?
I don't know.
I like biorelastic works.
So I don't know the genre at all.
I didn't know about biorelastic works.
I didn't know.
I like the kind of horror that is a
little different from horror.
I like it.
I got this from Mayama today.
Thank you.
I'm suddenly talking.
Where do you always buy clothes?
The clothes I gave to Yuno were candy
strippers.
I often buy clothes from the brands that
have stores in Harajuku.
Or I buy clothes from select shops.
Basically, I'm short.
So I think it looks more fashionable if
I wear a little bit of a
I like my favorite silhouette.
So I tend to choose a little bit of a
dress.
Most of the clothes I got were candy
strippers.
I thought it would go well with Yuno.
I chose it when I gave it to him.
What's the most fun song you've danced
to in Ebichu?
That's a good question.
What is it?
A fun song to dance to.
When I was asked to dance,
I didn't bite it in my mouth.
I've been biting it recently.
From Happy End
Something like this.
I've been doing a lot of things like
this.
I think the most fun thing to dance is
happy ending.
I see.
What do you like to say?
I like love rental.
Oh, really?
It's fun.
I like to go around.
You like to go around?
It's fun.
Oh, I see.
Certainly.
What's a fun song to sing?
A fun song to sing?
When I hear this song, I get excited.
I'm a mission survivor.
Oh, you're wearing a towel.
I grew up in Hall Rock, so I'm made by
Key Talk.
When I was a student, I listened to Key
Talk, Creeper Help, Aiko, Indie Grind,
and went to school every day.
I remember a lot of things from the
mission survivors.
I think it's the best song for summer
festivals, so it's fun to sing.
What do you like the most in the book?
I like Kotaro Isaka.
I still remember reading it when I was a
kid, and I feel like I'm going to read
it again.
I read a short book called The Fool of
the Week.
I like that book.
I'll read it.
Please.
Is there anything you want to talk
about?
Something I want to talk about?
What is it?
I think it's a good fit for Yuno.
But it's not surprising.
Even if you go to the deep side of the
reading genre,
I think it's a good fit for reading it
broadly.
What is it?
What did you eat recently that was
delicious?
Did you eat something delicious?
I ate the catering for the spring tour
at Hachioji.
I ate it for the first time, but it was
delicious.
You have a lot of favorite food.
It was delicious.
That's good.
Is Pakuchi a normal person?
I don't know if I've ever eaten Pakuchi.
That's right.
Pakuchi tastes shocking when you eat it
for the first time.
It's not the Pakuchi of shrimp.
It tastes like a really adult, unique,
and high-class taste.
Is it parsley?
It smells more Asian than parsley.
Is it MOLOHEYA?
MOLOHEYA is just sticky.
What is it?
I'm not good at mitsuba.
I may not be good at it.
But I was able to do it.
Fried onion.
Fried onion?
Something fried with onions.
The round one?
No, it's quite finely crushed.
The round one is crushed and fried.
I've been in a lot of them.
I like it in the four.
It was in there.
I didn't know.
You didn't know?
Yes.
I'm glad you were able to eat it.
Which brand of water do you usually buy
during the lesson?
I don't care.
I don't care at all.
For example, Irohasu or Tennen Sui.
Which one would you buy if you had those
two?
Suntory's Tennen Sui or Irohasu?
Yes.
I buy Suntory's Tennen Sui.
It's the same.
The same?
Yes.
You can tell the hardness of water,
right?
I don't know.
You don't know?
I bought it because the color was cute.
You choose the color?
Yes, it's light blue.
You like light blue?
Yes, I like blue.
I see.
You know, there's a jersey that Yuno
wears every spring tour.
It says light blue Ramune.
That's light blue.
What color do you like?
I liked red.
I don't know what color I like these
days.
What?
The color I often buy in clothes is
green.
I think so.
Is it because it's popular?
I find it cute when I find it.
It's like that.
Green is the easiest to match with
various things.
I have an impression that I can't get
green without thinking.
It's a mystery.
What color do you think you like?
What color do I like?
I think Yuno has more green colors since
the members' colors have been decided.
Do you have purple?
Purple.
I gave this to Yuno because it's purple.
I think purple is increasing.
When I first decided on purple, I didn't
like purple.
I wondered why it was such a plain
color.
But as a result, I like it because it's
increasing.
Oh, yeah.
My favorite color is purple.
If you were to dye your hair next, would
it be red?
Basically, I dyed it green only once.
But my face looked bad.
Basically, I keep adding red and pink.
I put it in brown.
It's not so flashy.
Basically, I don't do it.
So you don't want to make it red?
I don't think so.
I want to try it once.
I want to try a flashy hair color like
Hinata or Aya.
I want to try it with a flash of light.
I admire you.
I want to make my hair blonde.
I know. I want to try blonde.
I want to try blonde short hair.
I want to try it.
I want to try blonde with this length.
You want to try blonde with a little
longer hair.
I want to try blonde with a little
After I turn 20.
After you turn 20, you will be able to
do a lot of things.
I will be able to do a lot of things
when I turn 20.
But I think that you often wear red
clothes.
Certainly, I often wear clothes of the
members.
Like a red knit.
I think I'm not being teased by my
friends at school.
I have a purple shirt.
I don't have it at school now.
I'm teased.
I'm wearing purple.
I went to an exhibition and chose
clothes.
I was choosing purple unexpectedly.
I was asked if I would wear purple.
I was told that I should.
I chose a different color.
That's why I'm wearing more green.
I was told that if I wear a ponytail, my
friends will call me a mischievous girl.
What is that?
I was told that I was a mischievous girl
on a radio show.
You were told that.
I've been doing mischief for more than
10 years.
I think I said that on the radio once.
I forgot what I said.
I forgot.
I'm curious about your behavior.
What is your favorite thing about your
work?
What is my favorite thing about my work?
I'm close to you.
You don't have to be close to me.
Isn't it a live show?
Is it a spring tour?
Spring tour is going around.
The other day, we had a Hachioji
performance, right?
I thought that the heat of the
performance was different.
I thought that I could do more tasks.
I did the TDC Tokyo Dome City Hall and
the Osoda-shima river mouth.
We do it many times, but there are
people who can only come once.
I hope I can make memories with
everyone.
Thank you.
That was YUNO's room. Please look
forward to the next episode.
It's difficult.
Is it difficult?
When I talk, I get a lot of questions.
But when I ask, nothing comes out.
RICO, you didn't use the question that
you used.
Where is my favorite place?
That person runs away immediately.
This is a special question, so please
use it from the next episode.
Please ask RICO when you come.