Yasumoto & Kobayashi: Next Week is Already the Birthday Festival!
Yasumoto&Kobayashi Next Week is Already the Birthday Festival! As the spring tour is about to turn around, next week on June 13th (Mon.), we will hold a solo live for the birthday of Utao Kobayashi "Poland !!!!!!!", and on June 14th (Tue.), we will hold a solo live for the birthday of Ayaka Yasumoto "Singing and Singing". On June 13 (Mon.) and 14 (Tue.), Ayaka Yasumoto's birthday solo live "Singing, Dancing and Singing Show !!! Yasumoto's solo live will be held at KT Zepp Yokohama on Tuesday, March 14. We asked the two main performers about the highlights of this year's live! Ayaka Yasumoto's solo live will also be held in Osaka on Monday, June 27.
Po-Land 7!!!!!!!
Immigration Procedures
I think you have already gone through the immigration procedures.
It's not too late, so please come and join us!
We are looking forward to seeing you at !!!!
We are waiting for you!
Let's go for it!
Draw a picture of my enthusiasm!
drawing....
I made a mistake in expression.
Drawing.
I made a mistake in my facial expression.
"I'm up for the challenge!
I'm 22 years old and I'm going to do my best!
I drew this kind of picture.
About Po-land7!!!!!!!
Personally
I'm going to challenge myself.
I think it will be a birthday party like that.
Some songs will be a challenge.
or... or... or...
Or maybe it's a pororon
I'm going to challenge myself., so please come and join us!
But the atmosphere will be the same as usual.
like a dinner show
It's not a "let's get excited about the live" type of show.
You can relax.
People in today's society are very busy.
I thought it would be nice if people could relax a little bit.
That's the concept of this show.
About the costumes
It's like a docking.
I think you'll understand when you come.
I think you'll like it.
You seem to like this kind of thing.
About the goods
I would really like you to have a picture of me.
I've been working for a long time, and I've had
I've had a lot of good photos taken by professional photographers
I have many good photos, but this one is my favorite.
Please take a look at the photos.
I was able to take some live photos that are different from our usual live performances
I'd like to share them with you.
And the merchandise, too.
It's a perfect bowl or something.
It can also be used as a rice bowl or a small bowl.
I recommend it!
My birthday party is coming up soon.
I'm so excited and nervous right now.
I hope that this birthday party will make all the fans feel happy
I have a lot of plans for it.
I've been making my own original songs every year.
I'm planning to perform a lot of my new songs this year.
and various kinds of things that can cheer you up.
a lot of things happen, but we're going to have a good time every day
I've tried to write a song that will make you feel cheerful
I'm very excited to have you all listen to it.
If you would like to join us
I think you will enjoy it even more if you come and listen to the original songs I have performed and written by myself on YouTube.
I'll do my best. !!!!
I asked her about her points of interest.
I am turning 24 years old this year.
I think 24 is a full-fledged adulthood, so I wanted to make a song that is very mature for me.
I've prepared a song that I think is a very mature song for me.
I'm thinking of doing that as well.
I'm going to add a little bit of direction to it as well.
I hope you can come and see the adult Yasumoto
Our birthday party is just around the corner!
With our birthday just around the corner...
Today, we are talking to each other!
Thank you very much!
Please!
I never thought I'd be able to have a conversation with a master like this!
I didn't think you'd do it.
How many times have we done this?
Seven times!
This is the seventh time, isn't it?
Basically, Ayaka and I...
I'd say we're more...
I'm more of a laid-back type of girl.
If we split up, we'll probably end up in the same village.
If we split up, we'll probably be the same village.
It's a village!
It's a village! Completely!
The June group is the same village!
Yes, we are!
Everyone's live!
Like Mirei and Riko...
They are winter-borns...
I'd say they're more intense.
Or pop-oriented live performance.
They seem to be able to dance.
But this side of the country, during the rainy season and into the summer...
We are seem to be more laid back.
That's what we have in common!
I think it's a little bit different.
But if you divide it up, it's close!
I feel like we're close!
I feel like, you know, birthday festivals...
It's time to start getting ready for the birthday party.
Spring?
February or March at the earliest.
You know, people start to get nervous.
Around that time, I'm like.
"Wow, I want to do this! I want to do that!"
I want to do that!
But the period of time when you say, "I'm going to start in a month!
Isn't that the hardest part?
I'm not sure if this is the right thing to do.
or "Is this what I want?
I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to handle it.
Then again, in about two weeks...
And then, in about two weeks, you'll have something to look forward to again.
It's a busy time, isn't it?
I know, right?
We're touring right now.
I don't want to think about it as if I'm immersed in it.
I'm thinking about it in parallel.
I'm trying to think of the right things to do.
I'm so nervous.
So nervous!
I get nervous, nervous, nervous.
First time to talk about Yasumoto's original music.
The first time a song of Yasumoto's...
I was there from the rehearsal.
When I heard it, I thought, "That's a great song."
"Who is it? I thought, "Who is it?
I asked a staff member.
And the staff member said.
"What? It's an original song by Yasu." He said, "What?
"It's an original song by Yasu.
I think it's very comfortable and nice.
That's what I'm looking forward to!
I'm looking forward to it!
I don't know if it is or not!
Yes, I do!
Is there?
I'd like to hear about it!
I'll tell you a common thing at birthday festivals...
Kaho-chan is always at the back of the stage.
You have a seat for her during the show.
Why don't you watch from the front?
For example, next to the PA who plays the sound.
or the stage manager
You're always next to a staff member who's running around
You are always in mysterious positions, aren't you?
As for the recent past
For the past year, I've been saying.
"I don't need a seat.
I want as many people as possible to sit down
"No, I don't want a seat.
As long as you get permission to be in the sleeves.
Kaho is there as a staff member.
As an apprentice.
It's nice to feel close to them.
"I'm supporting this girl with her!" "I'm supporting her too!
"Yes!" That's how I feel.
It's not so much a customer thing.
It's more like...
"I want to cheer with you."
It's a different perspective.
That's part of the fun, isn't it?
It's part of the fun, isn't it?
"Where is Mr. Kobayashi today?"
It's a lot of fun to look for him.
I'll hang around.
I'll be hanging around.
Looking forward to our birthday party.
Please look forward to it!