Ebichu's video
So, this is the end of the 7th episode
of BORN OUT!
I think the second episode of BORN OUT!
is over
I'm still in the middle of it
I'm looking forward to the second
episode of BORN OUT!
I'm looking forward to it
Please watch this video too.
Look at the reaction at this girl.
Y visible
Trust your instinct.
Look at this girl.
Important scene
The head of the ball flies from outside
to inside.
This line Maximus is close at an angle.
I made a mistake with my facial
expression.
I said this earlier.
I will challenge myself.
I will do my best at the age of 22.
I drew this kind of picture.
This time, I will talk about Poland 7.
This time, I will challenge myself.
I think I will be a high-class singer.
I will challenge myself with songs.
I will challenge myself with songs like
Polon.
I'm looking forward to it.
But the atmosphere is the same as usual.
I want to have a good atmosphere.
I'm busy with the current society.
I want people to relax.
What is your costume?
My costume is a docking costume.
I think people will understand when they
see it.
I think I like it.
I think people will understand when they
see it.
What is your goal?
I want people to welcome me.
I have been active until now.
I have been taken by a professional
photographer.
I have a lot of good pictures.
I want people to see this picture.
I took a picture that is different from
the usual live.
I want people to see it.
I take a picture every day.
I take a picture of rice bowls.
Anyway, I recommend it.
It's almost time for the birthday party.
I'm so nervous right now.
We're planning to make the fans happy.
We're making our original songs every
year.
We're going to show you our new songs.
We're going to make you feel better.
We have a lot of things to do, but we're
going to have a lot of fun.
We're going to make a song that makes
you feel better.
I'm looking forward to it.
If you want to listen to my original
songs, please come to the concert.
You'll enjoy it even more.
Please listen to it.
I'll do my best.
We're going to make you feel better.
I'm 24 years old this year.
I think 24 years old is a real adult.
I'm going to make a song that makes you
feel like an adult.
I'm going to make a lot of songs.
Please come to see the adult Yasumoto.
Thank you for coming to see us.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I didn't expect you to come.
How many times have we said that?
It's the seventh time.
It's contexts I met Mr. Iga and me and
area institutes.
It's all in this village.
Mr. Iga61 and takai male
They are all warm.
It's pretty amazing player.
I feel like I can dance.
It's different.
In the summer, I feel like I can dance.
That's right.
I think it's a little different from the
usual.
It's similar when you divide it.
It's similar.
I heard that I was going to be in my 20s
soon.
It's about spring.
I was born early.
I was born in February and March.
It's going to start in a month.
That's the most difficult time.
I'm dying.
Is this okay?
What is this?
I'm worried about the radio.
I'm going to be a little more fun in
about two weeks.
I'm busy.
And the tour is over.
I'm thinking about it.
I'm so excited.
The first song I played.
I went to see it in real life.
When I heard it, I was wondering who the
song was.
I asked the staff.
The staff said it was Yasu's original
song.
I'm so comfortable.
I don't know if there are many.
There is.
There is a little.
I'm always in the front of the stage.
I'm always next to the staff.
I'm always in a strange position.
Recently, I don't need a seat anymore.
I want to be with the person who comes
to me.
I don't need a seat anymore.
I'm allowed to go to the arm.
You're going as a staff member.
I'm going as a member of the staff.
I'm happy to feel close to them.
I feel like I'm supporting my family.
It's not about the feelings of the
audience.
There are, but I want to believe in
them.
I think it's a little different.
I'm looking forward to this.
Where is Komaya today?
Let's do it together.
I'm looking forward to it.
Please look forward to the birthday
party.
I'm so happy.
See you next time. Bye!