Hello! I'm Orca!
Hello!
Where am I?
This is Yuzuki's room!
We're in Yuzuki's garden!
That's a lie!
Today, me, Hou-chan and a lot of my friends from Staples are going to have a special New Year's party in Yuzuki's room.
Yuzuki's Room New Year's Special.
This is in front of it!
We'll film afterwards!
Yuzuki's room has a really nice garden.
It's called...
Garden talk!
Oh no, garden talk doesn't really sound very interesting.
You're going to say that?
What's this?
It's a climbing thing.
Well, can I just...
Can I climb it?
You look really nice, Yuzuki.
Ooh!
Scary!
Wait, wait, just this bit!
That's all he says, he's scared.
I really can't go up high.
It's not high at all.
I really can't.
Yes, Yuzuki's room also has this.
Tell her if it's a self-portrait.
What?
There's a slide and a swing set.
I swung on this swing.
What's this?
Oh, my God! I've got it on!
Esuiken?
Aesiken.
Aesiken's gonna get drunk.
Are you serious?
Training.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Ahoy.
Oh, no.
Do it, Blanco.
Excuse me.
Oh, this is...
Is this one of the good ones?
It's pretty sturdy.
Oh!
Why do you whistle?
Why are you whistling?
Wow, Santa.
There's a lot of stuff here.
There's a slide here, too.
There's so many slides, so many slides.
Do you want a garden?
It's a bit of a hassle to clean.
Thank you for watching!
Wrap the transvestite...
Wrap it around...
A flat... a flat?
I'd prefer a house.
I want a house, but I don't want a garden.
But, Yuzuki...
I want a bed.
I think it would be better to have a garden.
I think so.
I want her to play.
But that's...
It might be the ultimate.
Oh, come on.
This could be the ultimate.
Okay, everyone, listen up.
Before we start this.
We're going to make the ultimate choice.
You know, the ultimate choice.
You know, the one we all have.
He said let's do that.
And now he's trying to make it work.
That's the ultimate choice.
So...
The ultimate choice for both of us.
Now.
I'm going to ask you the ultimate question.
Which is it?
A or B?
I love this kind of thing.
Okay, I'll get right to it.
Do I have to spend every day alone from now on?
Or do you have to play with your friends every day?
Which is it?
I'll be alone every day.
Friends every day.
Oh, that's... that's... that's... that's...
It's the ultimate, isn't it?
Here we go.
A is one person.
B is your friend.
Ready?
B.
I'm with you.
It's so lonely being alone.
Loneliness is the scariest thing of all.
That's right.
It makes you want to talk.
That's for sure.
I'll take that as a "1".
I wonder if there are any A's in this group.
There might be.
Friends all the time.
Friends are always distracting.
Maybe that's part of it.
Next.
A heavy one.
What would you like to eat at the end of your life?
A, a normal meal.
B, food from a very expensive restaurant
Yes, OK.
OK.
A, a meal at a restaurant
B.
Wow.
Okay, we're split.
Okay, let's dig a little deeper into this one.
Okay, let's start with A.
Usual cooking.
What I mean by everyday is...
It's the food my family, my mum, cooks for me, so...
It's good to be proud of it.
It's good to say it's tasty, but it's also good to say it's good.
I've always eaten it.
I wanted to eat the taste of my mother's cooking
I wanted to have it for the last time.
Yes, of course I love my mother's taste.
But...
I imagined that situation.
I feel like...
Tomorrow.
When you have to spend all your money.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Where to spend it.
You can't just buy clothes.
That's why I...
I spent it on food.
I see.
Which one were you?
In the comments.
Okay, next.
Let's try a love story.
Let's try this one.
Okay.
If you want to go out with someone...
The opposite sex that's nice to everyone.
A.
B. The opposite sex who is kind only to you.
That's pretty much the ultimate.
Ultimate.
I think this is pretty ultimate.
That's pretty bad.
This is pretty ultimate.
It's hard to know how much.
It's fine.
Because it's only kind to me.
If you want to collect other people...
That person.
But you're the only one who's special.
Special is nice.
It's nice to be special.
It's not like I'm not nice to other people.
Uh...
It's like...
It's not about being nice to your grandma or whatever.
It's not like you don't want to give up your seat.
Just, like, normal, but cool.
I don't get told I'm nice.
But you're really nice only to yourself.
Or someone who everyone tells you you're nice to.
Wow, that's pretty ultimate.
Oh, no.
I don't get it.
Wait a minute.
I don't know.
Well, which is it?
Which is it?
Uh, I don't know which way it is.
Okay, okay, okay.
OK, OK.
Okay, okay.
A.
Yes!
One.
That's good.
Yeah, first of all.
I don't think it's about going out with someone if you're not nice to them.
Yeah, sure.
I see.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Something like...
I'm...
I want someone who's kind to kids and stuff.
Yeah, yeah.
Both men and women.
Yeah.
Someone who makes me feel good.
Yeah, I want to feel kind when I see them.
I think it's good to feel special just for yourself.
Yeah.
But this was pretty ultimate.
I'm kind to myself too.
But I want you to be especially kind to yourself.
I'm begging you.
Please.
Everyone, everyone in Nafumi.
Please be especially kind to us.
Please.
Last then.
Wow, this is pretty ultimate.
Heh.
That's pretty ultimate.
Rast.
Yes, sir.
If you're going to spend an hour...
A.
Raiu outdoors.
Yes
B
Stinky indoor
Wow.
This is the ultimate.
Oh, my God.
How bad is the smell?
It's... it's... it's... it's...
The moment you walk in...
I'm like...
I'm like, "Oh, my God, what do I do?
It's been an hour, right?
This is the ultimate in last-minute entertainment.
What about Lai Woo?
Yeah, yeah.
No danger.
Do you have that umbrella?
No, I don't have an umbrella.
You don't? Is it cold?
Body temperature, body temperature, the temperature is just right.
There's no danger.
It's been rumbling all day, it's raining, I'm getting shot.
We're gonna get shot.
Oh, my God.
Eh, I don't know which one.
Depends on what you've got planned for the rest of the day.
Then there's nothing left.
Nothing, we're just going home.
All right. - All right.
Bye-bye. It's hard to say.
Okay, but maybe so, for sure.
Ready, A.
We're breaking up.
Right, so, A Honoka...
It's raining, so I thought it'd be okay.
Water, right? Yeah, it's not that hard.
Maybe it's because I used to do it. I'm not afraid of water.
If I don't have plans afterwards, I don't care about my hair or make-up.
I see. And B? Room B smells like B.
I don't like either one, but it's hard to tell.
But I thought if I put some stuffing up my nose, I'd be fine.
That's not fair, you'll have to endure it.
I can't stand it. Don't stuff your nose.
I thought if I stuffed my nose, it'd be okay.
But when I come out, it'll smell bad.
I'm in trouble. - You're in trouble?
It was the ultimate. Which one are you?
So, if you enjoyed this video.
If you enjoyed this video, please leave a comment and subscribe!
That's all for the shirt.