Thank you for your viewing.
D Mack
If you are practicing ETS, it would be
great.
I didn't think that there would be a
time when I sing all of my favorite
songs in Korean.
I was surprised when I was sent.
Korean!
But I have to deliver it.
Korean songs.
I'm sure you'll watch it.
It's still growing.
Music video and so on.
I'm sure you'll watch it.
We want to get 10 million views.
I can't wait.
It's cute.
It's good.
I'm so happy.
It would be great if we could have a
conversation.
Bye-bye!
OK!
Oh!
lol
Cha!
I did it!
Some ниил
NiziU members have TVXQ in theirbacks
words and actions after theIVE Rising
Star program.
Bye!
English version
Your eyebrows are pink.
I'm so happy.
The show will start soon.
Thank you.
Thank you for watching.
Please subscribe to my channel!
I did it!
I'm not sure if I can say it.
There are many words.
There are more letters than Japanese.
It's like a tongue twister.
That's the point!
Next, we dive in yogurt with brownie
shell and lemon and vão Devil.
Please subscribe to my channel!
What was it?
Bye~!
Everyone is blonde about 4 years
Everyone is going together, everyone
will meet
I did it.
You did it so well.
I could see it.
It was so good.
Thank you.
I'm looking forward to your support.
Thank you for your support with the song
you sang.
I'll do my best.
Please support me.
Bye.
Thank you for watching.
Please subscribe to our channel and
follow us on Twitter!
I wish you a miracle...
It's warm.
Thank you for your viewing.
It's a blue ribbon.
This one?
It's so cute.
Thank you for watching.
Shiruya ready?
Thank you!
Hello?
What? No way!
I think it's the same.
It hurts!
I'm not good at all.
My fingers are getting sick.
And the meat here is too thin.
I can't see the bones.
Thank you for watching.
Merry Changi Magenatic!
Daibutsuden
Thank you for watching!
You see me all the time, my love
It's hard to sing in English.
I got it.
I got the costume for the game.
You always get it there.
There are other costumes.
I got it.
Are you OK?
Hello, we are Joun!
Tokimeki Channel!
We are a 6 member girl group from Japan.
How are you?
Thank you so much for dancing to our
song, Suki.
Suki English version is this on January
30th.
Let's do it again.
It's totally different.
Suki English version.
Thank you!
Rock on your heart!
Please listen to it on streaming
service.
Please subscribe to our channel!
I'm looking forward to meeting you in
Korea!
What are you doing?
Good evening, everyone!
We are wearing an apron.
Today is the day of the cookpad live.
It's our first time to have a camera
here.
Let's do our best.
We are doing a live every month.
We are cooking together.
Today, we are going to make a rice
omelette.
I recommend it.
Do we have more meat?
We have to learn English.
You haven't learned it yet?
What's wrong?
I may have made a mistake.
Today, we are going to make a rice
omelette.
We are going to do our best.
We are going to rehearse.
Please watch us.
We are going to do our best. Please
watch us.
Don't be afraid.
Don't be afraid to jump.
It looks delicious.
I can make chicken rice.
I see.
It smells good.
I'm hungry.
Don't endure!!
So good.
Very good.
Delicious!
Our bento omelette rice is ready to eat.
Thank you for watching!
I'll always be waiting for you
Please subscribe to our channel and
follow us on Twitter!
You're not coming back here anymore, are
you?
I love you!
I could say I'll do my best
Stay with me a little longer
I love you
I'll never forget you
Under the sky with open windows
I love you
How was it, everyone?
How was it?
It was delicious
We learn a lot of cooking at Cafe
Patrive
We'll have a new app next month
Please download the app and try it
We also sell sweets
Financier
Financier is really delicious
It's really delicious
Please try it
Let's try it
Please try to make the recipe we made
today
Please make it
Thank you for watching
Byebecause
Thank you
Please subscribe to our channel!
Why is it that when I smile, the world
seems to shine?
I can turn my umbrella around and feel
better
If I don't, I can't walk
I'm sure someone is crying somewhere
I wonder if I'll get wet again somewhere
and not feel cold
There must be someone out there who is
crying
I want to share a little of my feelings
with you
There's still a view I've never seen
before
Come on, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye
Thank you for yesterday
The city after the rain is colored
On the canvas of my damaged heart
I'll draw a fragment of the future
I hope you can know somewhere
Now I can say it, the reason for my
tears
When I'm lost, I remember it right away
Even if it rains, I'll smile
Look, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city after the rain is sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day, the sound
of the rain drops
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city after the rain is sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day, the sound
of the rain drops
I wear a rainbow dress
Please subscribe to our channel!