UNKNOWN
Today, at Ichikawa City Cultural Center,
the graduation ceremony was held at the
Kashiwagi Hinata Produce Park
Many fans gathered
The new members, Yuna Nakamura and Yama
Sakurai, are at the venue
Thank you
They are visiting the live of the senior
members for the first time
And this time, they are showing the
special live of the members which is
filled with the feelings of Hinata
Kashiwagi
Thank you very much
The first performance of the group,
The first performance of the group, Riko
& Kaho & Hinata
What kind of live is it today?
Today, we are going to perform
Riko, Kaho and Hinata's
Hensei and GINNER's live
I want to learn from Suzu
They are working hard on their lessons
for their first live performance in a
month
As part of the lesson, they are going to
watch the live performance of their
seniors
4 hours before the live performance, the
rehearsal has started
The live performance today was produced
by Kashiwagi
Of course, the rehearsal continues as
Kashiwagi is in charge of the site
I wonder if I can do it
I want to be able to do it
The two people who watched the rehearsal
for an hour
How was it?
We have to do our best to not break that
atmosphere
I thought while watching them sing
It was very powerful
Everyone has been doing it for 8 or 10
years
We have to put in what we have done and
break it
I have to practice more and do my best
until February 17th
I want to do it
Finally, the venue is ready
While the seats are gradually filling
up, the two are also on standby
I'm nervous
But I'm so excited
And finally
Here they come, the Isokin Studio has
gathered
Everyone, please enjoy the show to the
end
I'm so excited for today
I'm so happy to see you all
I want to tell you how I feel
I want you to listen
Last night was so calm
I was so excited that I couldn't sleep
I want you to tell me how you feel
I wanted you to see
I want you to listen
to the memories of you
Let's all be happy and have fun diving
Your cheer and courage
will shine in this moment
I want to hold on to your feelings
Let's all be happy and have fun diving
Your cheer and courage
will reach out to you
Thank you for supporting me
Let's start the rhyme
Everyone, gather around
Yeah, yeah, let's do it
Go, go, say
In the middle of a shining future
What do we wish for?
Someday the rain that soaked into the
tobacco
will make someone cry
Say hello new world
The venue is heated up from the
beginning
In the middle of the shining future
What do we wish for?
The child we hold in our arms in the
distance
Tomorrow too
We might be able to change it
The blue, blue sky of the stars
What is it called the Earth?
The two stare at the stage with serious
eyes
What do you think?
Thank you!
I never thought that we could do a live
performance like this with Isokin
Thanks to everyone, we were able to have
a fun live performance
Thank you very much for today!
Thank you very much!
The live performance of Heisei Isokin
Trio has ended
And then...
Thank you for watching!
They will move to the stage and watch
the stage in front of them
From here, the surprise Kashiwagi has
prepared for this day
The six members gathered on the stage
What are their feelings?
The live performance with six members
It was not a break
The live performance with six members on
the stage
The last one was the mid-tone of 2020
Of course, we had been active as six
members since then
But it was surprisingly few
As six members, we were active
But the members who were visible to us
For example, five or four
We thought that we could not finish the
performance
As six members on the stage
But we didn't have a chance
So we decided to show the six members
this time
I thought we could do it, so we did it
The live performance was their wish, and
they have a particularity in the set
list
The first song we performed in the six
members' time was Sing along Sing a song
We will definitely perform that in the
first song
Sing a new song for the new song
Running, sliding, this parallel
I'm ready to go while being rushed
Now let's go
Let's not fall
Monday before the holiday
On the day off, I'm not in a hurry
I'm not in a hurry
I'm sure you're waiting for me ahead of
this road
Until I get there
I'll keep on fighting
No matter how many times I fall
Can't, can't, can't
It's okay to cry
No matter how many times I'm told to
continue to fight
Fiction, action, self-defense, sensation
Our fight of souls
I still have some selfieウォッチ
She's got the same heart as mine
I'm so jealous
Yeah
She's got the same heart as mine
I'm so jealous
Oh
She's got the same heart as mine
Translated by Releska
Thank you for watching!
The candles are growing every year
In my heart that's like an empty hole
While saying congratulations
Let's jump with excitement
Don't dream, catch it
Run through the storm
A fairy tale won't end
This is a heart drama
I first understood the pain of love
The sound of my heart beating
The door is locked
The door won't open
There's no place to go home
I'll spread my arms and fly
Happy birthday to you
I'll ring it, I'll ring it
Don't stop the really important things
I'll put love in the sky
I'll put love in again
This is the last song for today. Please
listen to it.
Thank you for watching!
We'll definitely meet again
One day
We'll definitely meet here
as always
Thank you for coming!
I'll be waiting here for you!
I'm really happy!
Even though we're apart, we're still
friends!
Thank you so much!
We'll definitely meet again!
I'll be with you forever
You are in my heart
Yes, we will definitely meet
Let's meet here someday
And so, the last 6 members' live show is
over
Thank you, it was fun!
Thank you!
Bye bye!
Thank you for watching!
After the live, Kashiwagi...
Good job
Thank you
I thought I was going to graduate from
high school
Is it the last course?
Yes
I'm really happy that I was able to
finish the live
And the two new members who saw the
special live that was held in front of
them
How was it?
It was overwhelming
And when I was sleeping with the six of
us, I could see the stage from a very
close distance
It was amazing
I want to work hard so that I can get
there as soon as possible
I want to practice a lot from the
members and the older members
I want to study a lot and practice so
that I can do it someday
I was really impressed by the fact that
I could feel the history
It was amazing
The graduation performance of Hinata
Kashiwagi and the performance of the new
student,
Please look forward to Makuhari 2 days
Next time
I like spicy food
What kind of food do you like?
I like red pepper
I like spicy food
I found it
So, we shot with these three people