The year-end fashion coordination battle
is held
Oh, I found it!
It's so cute!
I'll buy this
With the choice of clothes full of
private feeling
What should I do? I don't know
My mother is always drawing on my mother
It's cute and cute
6900 yen
Coordination with members
Transform
What kind of fashion is it?
DELICIOUS TASTASU START!
Add various things to private Ebisu
Middle School
Ebichu Tastas
This program is provided by the sponsor
Ebichu Tastas has started
Okay, the next topic is...
Today we are at Odaiba!
Odaiba is...
Everyone is...
What is that?
It's Fujitori Bi!
Let's shake hands with the people who
are working there
Yatsumoto, what is Fujitori Bi?
I'm not sure
So, what is today's topic?
Today's topic is Fashion Coordination
Battle!
Everyone said they wanted to do it
before
In the previous program, Nakayama...
Someday, I want to be a hair-style
I want to be a hair-style
I want to be chic
I want to be a member
I want to be a member of the group
I see, it's like transforming
So, the fashion coordination battle that
everyone wanted to do is going to be
held
The two will be paired and coordinate
each other's clothes
The pair that transforms the cutest will
be the winner
The pair that wins will be given a gift
Yay!
So, if you don't win, you won't get the
gift?
Only the winner will get the gift
It's all about the budget
Before the coordination battle, let's
check their fashion sense
Let's start with Kashiwagi
First?
First
Please
It's cute
It's different without the bangs
It's like an adult
I like this kind of hat
Is there a theme?
Simple
I see
It's not flashy
It's simple
It's calm
Next, let's check Yasumoto
Jump
It's cute
This is Mayama's glasses
Really?
Did you get it?
Yes
I got this from Mayu
It's a Nike shoes
It's cute
She's a balloon artist in the park
Balloon artist?
I like to have a variety of items for my
fashion
Items for your fashion?
Next, Mayama
I got this
It's cute
Is this Mayama's?
Yes
It's totally different
She's wearing a hairband
It's like a female actor's hat
I learned it from the staff
What?
The staff?
It's the same as how you wear a hat
You have to wear a hat to show your
fashion
I see
I wear a hat every day
Next, Matsuno
It's weird
Is it right?
No, it's not
Why do you wear black clothes in a black
bag?
I'm sleepy
I'm always monotone
I'm calm so I'm always like this
This is also mature
Next is Hoshina
I'm here
Why are you wearing white?
How far are you going to go?
I don't know
I'm not asking the location, I'm asking
why you are wearing white
I'm hiding from the wall
I like knits so I wear it a lot
Knit girls are cute
Who are you talking to?
I think it's popular among boys
Next is Hirota
What?
Where are you going?
Is this your home?
No, I have an event at my favorite shop
I'm going to dress up
You are going to dress up from home?
This is the lowest line of my clothes
Is it more flashy?
I think it's not enough
I feel sympathy
You two are going to buy
I think it's not strange even if you
stand there
I think it's good
Next is Nakayama
I have air purifier like Aiei has
Why?
It's not different
It's the entrance
I find the air purifier when I clean up
I think it matches with the hat
It's stylish
It's very balanced
You always carry it
You dress like that?
I wear this for 2 days
Next is Kobayashi
What's wrong?
Ready, go
Cute
She is a baron
She looks like a baron
She looks like a boy who is in the
forest
It's not a forest, it's a park
It's an antique
She looks like a baron who is in the
forest
It's an antique
In the battle, it is important to match
your sense with the role of model
And the battle stage is
DiverCity Tokyo Plaza's shopping floor
You can choose the shop, but the budget
is 30,000 yen for the pair
The time limit is 40 minutes
Now, who coordinates who
The pair decided in Fuji is as you see
A team is Hoshina and Hirota
B team is Mayama and Nakayama
C team is Matsuno and Kobayashi
And D team is Yasumoto and Kashiwagi
How to coordinate each other and
transform
First, these two teams are shopping
Please decide the theme of each fashion
Let's go to Hoshina
Me too
Let's go one by one
Adults cute love love
Cute is the same, but different feeling
I think it's better to wear something
that I don't usually wear
I'm looking forward to this
Hirotami is different
I see
What about Hirota?
I'm a square
Colorful Hoshina is the same
Mayama
Datsuten
This time, I decide with only my own
inspiration
Are you okay?
I don't rely on the staff
I said it
I'll do my best
Please don't ask the staff
Hey
It took time
Nakayama, let's go
This is small
It's like a
Cute like a
Like a
Because it's like an adult
I want to put Mayama that is different
from the image of the usual
Cute feeling
Fluffy
Then the time limit is 40 minutes
Fashion coordinate battle
Ready start
Please go
I'm sorry
To find the clothes according to the
theme
What the A team headed to
It's fun to run in a cloak
But it's cute
I'm going
Forever 21
Los Angeles
Fast fashion brand with a wide range of
generations
What kind of clothes will they choose
from the rich products?
Oh, it might be cute
Glittering
Oh, it's cute
Cute
It's nice, glittering
Let's find something like this, let's
squeeze it out
Hirota's theme is me
A straight line for super colorful
styling
It's 1700 yen, I'm wearing this
It's cute to wear it like this, but I'm
not wearing it
I've never seen it
Hirota imagines an adult cute and
chooses chic colors
I'm lost
It's so cute
I want to wear a kit
I wonder if it won't cut
It's cute
It's 6900 yen
I can close it if I don't have anything
I'll go like this
I found it
It's so cute
This is cute
I want this
It's popular this year
It's 6490 yen, it's expensive
It's fun
I've never been to Diver City, so it's
fun to see the shops
On the other hand, the two of Team B
Thank you
Cheapness is important
Riko-chan, it looks good on you
What should I do?
It definitely goes well with a large
skirt
It's fast
Mayama, who always leaves her body to
the staff, is also looking for
Nakayama's clothes
What is her sense?
Next, 6th floor?
It's already WIGO
It's faster to go from here
Team B is planning to check various
shops
Next is
Harajuku-style brand with unique and
reasonable items
We go
A hat
I want to wear it
It's a knit sweater, so I don't know
what it is
You can wear it
I see
Rika-chan
This is only for Yagami-san?
How much is it?
The bag
I'll take this one for free
The bag is fine
Rika-chan, Rika-chan
What about this?
I'll leave it to you
Yes
As the theme, Nakayama wants to make
Mayama fluffy
What kind of finish will it be?
Cute
It seems that this kind of thing is
popular now
I asked the shopkeeper the other day
It's a
I like it
I like the most
I don't want to go on an adventure
Adventure
It wasn't that cute
I don't want to do it
Meanwhile, the members of the second
half of the team
What?
This is beyond imagination
It's fashionable
Taking a break at a cafe
It's like a slurp
Yasumoto
It's hard
When Yasumoto was fighting with bread
The second half of the team also goes to
the Wigo where Mayama Nakayama is
I see
I wanted a hat
There are a lot of shoes
It's a
This kind of thing is popular this year
What kind of thing?
What?
Go over there
Why did you hide it?
What?
What to do?
It's only a coat
Really
On the other hand, Hirota
2009, this is good
It's really cute
It's really good
The budget is okay to draw the favorite
one after another?
Hiroto Pink
Don
Please subscribe to the channel
But I won't buy the one from before
I'm sorry, I wanted to buy it
Can I cancel it?
It's not right
She cancels the coat she just bought
and tries to increase the number of
items
2900 yen, that's good
3000 yen
How much is it going to be?
It's 9000 yen now, but it's still a
bit...
It's going to be over 15000 yen
It's going to go over 15000 yen
But it's being minuscule how many times
Both three internet players need to use
change to get more than 5000 yen
to grab her the amount that the
coatediche reads
Meanwhile, Team B
If I put this coat on, it's like they
are in good hands
Hang on
It's fluffy
What should I do with it.
It's a bit white,
but it's delicious with a little bit of
a trick.
They're starting to see their true
image.
At the cafe,
they expect to see Mayama shopping.
What kind of shopping do you do?
I think Mayama uses the staff.
I think so too.
I think we should ask the staff to do
something.
Did you say that?
You broke your promise.
Then you can say,
I'm going to leave the cafe.
I see.
Mayama's staff is saying that it's
impossible.
Mayama's
movement is cute.
This coat is cute.
Hello.
Mayama is calling the staff.
This is cute.
She's very reckless.
This coat is cute.
Hello.
Mayama is calling the staff.
This is cute.
At that time...
Mayama.
What are you talking about?
Hello.
This is a normal conversation.
Mayama is caught up in cheating.
Meanwhile, Nakayama is...
What should I do?
What should I do? Help me!
Nakayama is too busy to choose clothes
What should I do? I don't know. My mom
always tells me to change
She is struggling with the fluffy outfit
of her imagination
What should I do?
What should I do? Help me!
I'm sorry
This outfit is suitable for this outfit
It has a good look
Nakayama is helping the staff instead of
Mayama
It looks good on you
I agree
It's really cute
I'll choose this
I'll choose this. This is a skirt
While the time limit is approaching,
Team A is...
What if I buy a small bag?
I'll choose this one
I've decided
I also want a necklace
I want a necklace like this
Hoshina is attacking the budget
And Hirotama
It's really good
14,890 yen
Isn't it good?
I'm sure
So you've decided?
I've decided
For Team A, these two...
I haven't decided the price at all
Nakayama says that the budget was not in
her head
It's about 7,000 yen
But it looks good
I forgot
She forgot to buy
The budget is what she's worried about
The staff
With this
I'll buy this
The staff
With this
I'll buy a cheap one-piece
Nakayama is crying to the staff
Nakayama is looking at the budget
I feel like it's cheating
I can see a little
I think this is a 2-page
Can you go together?
30,000 yen
I think I can go
The total is 14,534 yen
Is it okay to be close?
So both teams finished shopping safely
without any budget
What kind of coordination did they
choose?
They are back
Welcome back
Hirota is like a model
What's wrong?
It's not enough
We don't have enough budget
I see
I don't have enough stamina
You don't have stamina?
But you bought a lot
We bought a lot
We bought a lot of things that look big
I'm looking forward to it
The neck in the whole progress is the
first half team called budget
How will the second half team face it?
Before that
Ebichu Game Quest
Ebichu Game Project launched this year
Finally, the game trial version is
completed
Another development tonight
I'm going to play
What's this?
This is really bad
This is Rina's
This is mine
What is this related to?
Actually, that's right
The character that Matsuno drew before,
Ebimaru-chan
I really adopted it
Actually, the character that Matsuno
presented before
This Ebimaru-chan
This was adopted into the game
Please see what it actually looks like
Cute
It's so cute
This Ebimaru-chan will appear as an item
that strengthens the member character
And
This time, I would like you to think of
a new item
That's it
There are a lot of weapons that are used
as a motif in the game, such as
stationery and other school items
I would like the members to think about
it
First, Mayama's weapon
This is a vending machine and a machine
that often appears in the society
I used this part as a motif and this is
a pretty cool weapon
That's right
Next, Hirota's weapon
In the song of Ebichu, there are songs
where members actually tie a broom and
dance like a guitar
So it seems interesting to have
something related to Ebichu songs
I see, this is good
Next, Matsuno's weapon
First, the black board can be erased by
taking an enemy's attack
This is a weapon that can be erased by
taking a round part like a yoyo
It's like a shooting
Finally, Kashiwagi's weapon
When you press the bow, it's like flying
a meter
It's like a direct shot of the bow
Will there be something that will be
adopted in this?
Ebichu Game Project, wait for the next
episode
Next episode of Ebichu Tastas is the
second half of the fashion coordination
battle
But this is good
The members transformed in the fashion
show
Will it be?
And the person who missed Ebichu Tastas
will be rewarded
On the school video distribution site
Stardust Channel, Ebichu Tastas is being
widely distributed
It's not over yet!
If you want to enjoy more like Nakayama,
you can get Ebichu Tastas for 400 yen a
month
In addition, there are many videos of
the unreleased
For more details, search Stardust
Channel
This program was provided by the sponsor
you see
What?
Amen.
Thank you for watching!