Belonchan
Hello!
We are CUB!
It's been a while since we all got
together.
Today, we are going to be our manager.
It's going to be hard, so please don't.
Please go home.
If we are going to be our manager, we
have to do the interview.
We have to do it.
We have to know a lot of things.
So, we are going to have an interview.
It's going to be fun.
9 vs 1 is too much pressure.
We are going to have an interview at 1
or 2.
It's like an audition.
We are going to have a fun promotion.
What kind of people do you need?
We have a lot of luggage.
We need a strong person.
We need a man.
We are from Tohoku, so we need Miyagi.
We don't know Miyagi.
We need someone who has a strong heart.
Someone who doesn't give up.
We need someone who can make takoyaki.
We need someone who can do catering.
I don't know who is going to be our
manager.
We are going to have an interview.
We are going to find a manager.
Please come in.
Thank you.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Are you nervous?
This is normal.
Please introduce yourself.
I'm Katsuya Hirano from UUUM.
Thank you for watching.
What is your motivation for applying?
I'm from Sendai and I'm a YouTuber.
I often watch your videos as an idol in
Sendai.
I want to be a YouTuber and manage my
channel.
Thank you.
Do you really think so?
I'm a YouTuber.
What is your specialty?
I said that men should be strong.
I can raise my legs.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Can I ask you your strengths?
My strengths are...
I'm kind.
You said it yourself.
It's important to have a self-awareness.
What are your weaknesses?
I'm a loud mouth.
I'm loud and smelly.
I'm a minus.
That's a little tough.
I'm not good at being loud.
I get angry.
Are you good at complimenting?
I'm not good at complimenting girls.
That's a minus.
I'm embarrassed.
Please compliment me.
You're cute.
Your hair looks good on you.
You have a big face.
You have a grain of rice on your face.
Your hair is smooth.
I don't think I can do this.
I've learned your name.
You don't have to learn my name.
I'm your manager.
I have to learn your name.
Date-san.
Hinata-san.
That's a minus.
Thank you.
I'm a good man.
Can I choose a favorite from these?
Soy sauce?
I like salt.
Who do you choose?
Hinano-san.
I don't know what she's talking about.
I like soy sauce.
Can I have a joke?
Sure.
Thank you for watching this video.
Please subscribe to this channel.
I think it's good.
I like the impression.
Is this good?
It's not good.
I can hear your voice.
Manager's voice is not good.
I think it's good.
I think so.
It's almost good.
I can see your bear.
It's not a bear.
It's your eyes.
It's a different character.
I was told that it's good.
I feel good.
It's good.
It's almost good.
I'll do my best.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Let's start the second census.
Thank you.
What is your personality like?
My personality?
I'm difficult to get along with.
Please tell us about your positive
personality.
I don't care about my personality.
Oh, I see. Thank you.
What do people around you call you?
I don't know why, but they call me a
weirdo.
I don't know why.
I just live my life normally.
They ask me if I'm kidding.
They ask me if I'm kidding even when I'm
serious.
I think you should ask what type of
person you like.
Oh, what do I look like?
Anything.
What do you like?
Someone who is fun to be with.
And?
Someone who is not quiet.
Someone who is noisy.
I think noisy is good.
Someone who is a little bit annoying.
I think I should be someone who is not
annoying.
I'm curious.
Do you have a girlfriend?
What?
I'm saying this in the video, but I
don't have one.
Congratulations!
Do you have a girlfriend?
I don't have one.
Thank you for watching! Please subscribe
to our channel!
I want a lot of them.
Thank you.
I can't say it.
By the way, can I ask you about your
annual income?
If you get a P,
I don't know how much I get.
I don't know.
I feel awkward.
I feel awkward, too.
But, I have many preferences.
You have a dream.
How about Takoyaki?
I can make Takoyaki at home.
I can't make Takoyaki at home.
I see.
By the way,
Takoyaki and YouTubers are prohibited.
I want you to quit YouTube.
How do you decide?
I quit YouTube.
I'll be a manager.
Is it a luxury?
Yes.
If you can work here, I'm happy.
I think it's good.
This is a video of the second screening.
Thank you for watching this video.
Now, we are going to do the final
screening.
Thank you for your cooperation.
The fifth question is,
What do you want to be when you are
reborn?
I want to be a cute girl when I am
reborn.
Why is that?
I thought school would be fun.
I see.
I think life from that point of view
would be fun.
I think my life is good now.
If you become an idol, what do you want
to be in charge of?
I want to be in charge of pink.
I see.
I want to be in charge of pink and be a
cute girl.
You mean Fushimi-chan?
Yes.
I see.
I want to be like Fushimi-chan.
I want to be like her.
You are white.
You can be white and white.
I see.
Thank you.
I have a question.
YUNA is 20 years old.
She invites you to drink.
But you have an important job tomorrow.
What do you say?
It's difficult.
You have to realize the relationship.
I have been doing my important job.
That's why I'm still drinking.
So, let's go drinking.
Are you going to go drinking?
I think it's good.
I think it's good that she goes drinking
no matter what happens tomorrow.
She drinks and does her next job.
I think so.
I think it's good.
I'm not going to drink.
On the day of the important live, Katsu-
san was late.
What do you say?
I brought 100 Gari-Gari-kun.
I said I saved the convenience store.
I wanted to give it to everyone, so I
sent it.
I see.
You bought 100 Gari-Gari-kun.
Yes, I bought them at the convenience
store.
Is that a sign of apology?
Yes, it is.
You bought them.
I bought them with my whole fortune.
You didn't buy them with your money.
I don't have 100 Gari-Gari-kun.
I have 100 Gari-Gari-kun.
Did you buy them at the store?
I don't know.
I thought I might have a chance to buy
them.
I thought it would be difficult to sell
them if I bought them at the store.
You're going to bring a sign of apology.
That's important.
I'm going to tell you to come as soon as
possible.
I agree.
I'll take your feelings.
I think it's important to show your
feelings in a form.
I see.
One member didn't come to the important
live.
But, you'll be there 30 minutes after
the live starts.
How do you fill the gap of one member?
I'll be there.
I'll say hello.
Do you have the courage to come out if
you're going to be there?
I'll be there if I'm there.
Can you dance?
I think improvisation is important for
idol.
Can you dance?
How do I do it?
It's good.
You're good at improvising.
You're good at arranging.
Can you introduce yourself to the
audience?
Hello.
I'm a YouTuber who came from FUWAFUWA.
I'm Katsuya.
I'm a crazy guy who came from KURUKURU.
I'm Katsuya Hirano.
You're good.
You've got a good personality.
What do you think is important when
you're a manager?
I think it's important to protect time.
I think it's important to be
considerate.
If you pass the audition, you'll be the
manager of TOHOKU.
How do you want to produce TOHOKU?
I think you can change your policy when
you can do anything.
I want to make a channel that can target
all countries while leaving the color of
TOHOKU.
I want you to do it.
I feel like I'm a very talented manager.
Lastly, please appeal to the camera.
Thank you.
Please subscribe to our channel.
I will announce the results based on the
selection of judges.
Katsu-san is the manager of the In Night
Talk.
Congratulations!
Yes!
I did it!
Now, I can be a member of Ikezaki Talk!
Wow!
I'm so grateful.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Hey!
I'm a member of Ikezaki Talk!
Yay!
So, we collaborated with Katsu this
time!
Thank you so much!
Thank you so much, Hondo-kun!
I'm acting like a kid.
There aren't many idols who are active
in Sendai.
I'm a little...
I got it.
I thought there were a lot of younger
sisters.
I felt like I was talking to my sister.
That's great.
I'm talking to an interesting brother.
I see.
That's great.
Thank you so much.
Can I say something?
I'm a leader.
I've been thinking about it a lot.
Everyone is betting their lives on Talk!
I don't know what to say.
If there's someone who thinks of us as
younger sisters,
I thought I might be anxious about the
future.
What do you think?
I'm going to blow a new wind.
I see.
The leader will announce the results.
Thank you for your kind judgment.
I'm going to choose Yu-go-kan.
What should I say?
I think she is a good person.
I hope you can get along with her.
I'm not imitating you.
I'm happy to collaborate with you.
Thank you!
Please continue to support us!
This was Tomoko Ikinari. Thank you!
Thank you!
Thank you for watching! Please subscribe
to our channel!