Thank you for watching!
Please subscribe to my channel!
Hello!
Hold on a second.
Will the archive stay?
What?
There'll be a connection?
There's one!
Is there a live stream?
Hello?
Live stream...
We can't connect.
Hello.
You're being interviewed.
Hello to hell.
Sorry.
Thank goodness.
Thank you.
I'm Shirite, Ebisu Shark, Shizuki number
12, Kayamariko.
Nico-chan.
Hello.
I saw you.
I send you a video every week, but this
week I'm going to teach you a game.
You all have a game and you've been
practicing for a week.
I'm going to play Top Batter, but I'll
be playing Top Batter because everyone
will come out one by one.
I'm going to cut an egg omelet in the
middle and make it beautiful.
Yes.
What is it?
You said you were going to make an
omelet, right?
Yes.
I'm going to make an omelet.
I sent a message to the principal that I
was going to make an omelet.
I don't know what to do with the omelet
and the omelet.
Are you okay?
I've been worried about it for a week.
I'm worried about it for a week.
I made an omelet rice, so I'm going to
make an omelet rice this time.
The most important thing is to make an
omelet.
Look at this.
I made it with tofu, not rice.
It's tofu.
It's amazing.
I made it with tofu.
It's good for women's health.
I'm not introducing this.
I'm scared.
Let's cook.
I'm going to break the egg.
What do you make fluffy when you break
the egg?
Do you make tofu fluffy?
I'm scared.
Do your best.
It's amazing to break the egg.
My hands are very dirty.
Do your best.
Hoshina said it was amazing to break the
egg.
It's normal.
Hoshina is on a cooking show.
I'm breaking eggs.
It's the same as the last time.
I'm not breaking eggs.
I'm going to make a frying pan for you.
I'm going to make it.
You're in a hurry.
I was going to take a frying pan out of
my bag.
I laughed a lot.
It seems that it takes about 10 minutes
for one person to make it.
I think I know that Saibashi.
We often have it at home.
I think so.
Do you have it at home?
I don't know.
It's a good condition.
What do you put in it?
I put milk.
It's a high-calorie food.
Is it salt?
It's salt, isn't it?
Are you okay?
The staff of this project is kind.
It seems that other people will be more
than me.
AsuAsu was strict.
I didn't do that.
I know that.
I can see it.
I can see it by looking at it.
Butter.
I want to eat butter.
I like butter.
It's going well.
I like square butter.
I can eat only what I can eat socially.
I'm glad.
Good luck.
Don't cut your hand.
I can't cut my hand with this.
Are you okay?
I'm shaking.
Put it down.
Thank you for watching.
How is everyone?
I'm scared.
It's fun to talk with everyone.
I agree.
I want to eat butter.
I was told to be quiet.
I was told again.
Meanwhile, fire.
Thank you for watching.
How many times did you practice this?
I did 30 eggs.
I lived an egg life.
The egg consumption in Japan is the same
every year.
I still have a long way to go.
I'm on high heat.
Too much?
It's shaking.
Riko-chan, you're shaking.
Like a crab.
My hands are shaking.
It's done.
Wait a minute.
I'll warm up the frying pan.
I'll start.
Finally.
It's gone.
Don't do that.
It's hard to control the fire.
It smells good.
Mix it.
It's soft.
Do your best.
It's good.
Oh!
I'm going to cut it.
Isn't it amazing?
Is it okay to do it here?
I'm shaking.
I'm shaking a lot.
This is different.
Where is the middle?
But, but, but.
I'm going to make some corrections.
Hello.
From this side.
I'm shaking a lot.
Here you go.
What's going to happen?
I love you.
Wow, this is amazing.
I feel like I'm seeing a fan.
I'm going to show the camera.
I'm going to show the fans.
It's shaking a lot.
Isn't it fluffy?
There's a little hole.
It's so fluffy.
It looks delicious.
It's shaking a lot.
It's like, uh?
Why?
You'll know when you see it.
I see.
I want to see the floating function.
It's not hidden.
But it's a flash.
I want to practice hiding it.
Let's try it.
OK.
We'll decide it again at the food
report.
Let's eat.
Everyone looks good.
Isn't it amazing?
It's soft.
Please subscribe to this channel.
It looks very soft.
I'm shaking.
It looks delicious.
Let's eat.
I'm hungry.
Is it good?
I want to eat. It looks delicious.
It's delicious. Is it sausage?
It's not an egg.
How about the egg?
Please subscribe to this channel.
It's fluffy.
Isn't it a success?
How is it?
It's really good.
It's a bit laggy.
It went well.
I don't know if it went well.
It was terrible last week.
If you watch the video we watched
yesterday,
Let's judge by comments.
Please.
Everyone's voice decides.
Success!
Great success!
There are many people who say success.
Success! Passed!
So what?
There are many people who say it's a
success.
Congratulations!
It's a big success.
I can see that you are excited through
the screen.
Really?
It's a success.
It's a success because it's the first
one.
It's amazing.
I'm surprised myself.
I'm confused.
It smells good.
It smells really good.
I've only been able to do it because
it's very hard and soft.
The result of practice.
Do you want to eat it?
We want to eat it.
I want to eat it.
It's amazing.
I'll hold myself back.
When are you going to make it?
I'll make it when I get better.
It's not good for shrimp.
I want you to make tofu.
It's going to be tofu.
Next.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Thank you so much.
We got the results of our practice.
It was worth using 30.
I was confused.
It was my turn.
Next, baton touch.
This is the first time I've seen a VTOL.
I'm not sure if it's a normal VTOL or a
special VTOL.
I can't tell.
It's a VTOL.
I'm not sure if it's a special VTOL or a
special VTOL.
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
Hello, I'm Hoshino Mirei.
Hello.
Riko just ate a fluffy omelet.
Omelet?
I think I'll do my best.
I'm not good at juggling.
I'm not good at playing ball.
I don't know the distance from the ball.
I started with one ball.
I practiced like this and passed it to
the other person.
I practiced like this.
I did it.
Isn't it amazing?
It took two days to do this.
When I finally got three, I couldn't do
it.
I dropped the ball and the cat in the
house misunderstood it and chased me.
It's hard to practice.
I'm nervous.
How many times can I do this?
For the time being.
If I say no, I'll stop.
I'm making a stupid face.
I'll do it.
Oh!
Please be careful of the camera.
I'm afraid the popcorn will break.
The audience will be surprised.
Wow, that's great.
This is a practice scene.
Is this the real thing?
How many times should I do this?
I don't know.
Five times.
What is five times?
Seven times!
It's Lucky Seven.
Seven times.
Seven times!
How are you supposed to count?
Like, ho ho ho ho.
Like, count 2, 3 times.
We are switching places.
Waaahhh!
Is that a picture?
I can't see it.
Oh!
I wonder if she's playing with Moca.
Is Moca here today?
Oh!
It's like a step.
Like a step.
Step.
I want you to show me your whole body.
It's really cute.
Oh!
I want you to show me your legs.
I want to see your legs.
I can't show my legs.
But you can practice.
You're running around with your neck.
You're like a seal.
You're cute.
I can't.
Step.
5 times is the best.
Really?
You did it 5 times?
Isn't it amazing?
The one who counts.
This is...
Suddenly, I look like Hanasaka-jiisan.
I look like that.
Hanasaka-jiisan.
How about your neck?
Oh.
Hahaha!
Bye!
The position of the hand is going up.
What?
Is it a pro?
It's a good advice.
Jagling's pro.
If you don't understand,
I'll send you a Jagling's manual.
It's like an Instagram account.
I'm glad you sent it to me.
Great.
I thought you were kind.
You're kind.
Oh!
You guys are pretty good!
You know, just now,
you gave me advice that my hand was
getting higher.
You want to make it lower, right?
You want to stabilize it, right?
It's not a practice video.
You're practicing with everyone.
Look, another professional came.
I think you should throw it a little
more outward.
Are you practicing juggling?
I'm being mislead.
Someone said something.
I heard something.
I'm not a teacher.
I'm raising you all.
Oh!
How many times did you do it?
I think I did it.
You're still practicing, right?
It's a practice.
Judgment?
Let's see the real thing.
The real thing?
Wait.
It's a capture.
I'm sorry.
I think I've done it 7 times.
I think so.
So,
Wait a minute.
I think she's motivated.
I'll do it again.
One more time.
So, we'll try to do it 7 times.
We'll try again.
We'll do it 7 times.
We still have time.
How many times?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
Oh, it's the last one.
We got a new sound.
What about this?
No good!
Okay, Mi-chan, can you say your line and
we can start over?
I'll do it for the last time!
How many times will it be?
I wonder if it's the last time.
Only one thing is left until last.
Do you want to finish it as the last
time?
No heating!
Aircon!
lmao
Card game
Ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
So, what's this?
If you don't drop it, it's a finish.
What?
One ball?
Don't drop it even once.
So, as the last one,
I'll do it without dropping it.
So, as the last one, I'll do it without
dropping it.
It was a surprise, right?
It was.
There were more than before.
Miria-chan did her best.
I did my best.
You passed.
I passed.
Really?
It's good.
Everyone said, wow.
Let's end it soon.
It's a good thing.
Thank you.
Please watch again.
Thank you for watching.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Hello!
I don't know what I'm saying.
So,
It's like a lunch wide show.
So, it's Yasumoto's turn.
I'm going to learn a lot from Ebichu's
video.
Yasumoto was going to play the role of
Cinderella in Harmonica.
What?
This harmonica is not a key that
Cinderella, the temporary key player,
can play.
What?
Our principal, Mr. Fujii, sent me a
harmonica by mistake.
He's the principal.
So,
It seems that blues harp has a deep
meaning.
It seems that there are many things.
I'm not good at studying.
What kind of sound is it?
It's a sound of a pick.
It's a sharp sound.
It's a flat sound.
It's a difficult sound.
So,
I'm going to play a sparkling star
instead of a harmonica.
I happened to have a book of harmonica
at home.
Why?
Did you get it?
No, I didn't.
Did you happen to have a book of
harmonica?
Did you say, Mom?
Did you have a book of harmonica?
I have a book in my butt.
My hair is brown and I'm old.
I think someone in my family played it.
So,
I'm going to play it.
Yasumoto's sparkling star challenge,
start!
Ready?
Thank you for watching!
Wow!
Is this a success?
Yes!
So, everyone, what do you think?
Please tell us in the comments if it was
a success or not.
Everyone said it was nice and amazing.
It's a success!
Thank you very much.
By the way, why did you choose the
sparkling star?
It's the most popular song in this book.
It has a lot of things like Michael
Corleone.
Everyone, please read this book.
I was really drawn to this book.
Please read it.
I think we succeeded in this project.
It's an encore.
You guys are so eager.
What's going to disappear?
Can you do it?
I'll try to play the song, Koge wo
Maikeru.
Can you do it?
I'll try.
I don't know this song at all.
I don't know this song.
I'll try.
You're laughing, aren't you?
I don't know the song.
Sorry.
I don't know the original song.
Good work.
This is a success.
I can't read the music.
I don't know the timing, but I tried.
It's an original song.
How do you like it?
It's good.
It's a success.
Do you want to play the song?
I want to play it.
Can you play it?
I'll play the sound that doesn't come
out.
I'll practice a little.
I'll play a little.
What song is this?
I've never heard this phrase before.
The chorus part.
Can you play it again?
I'll play the first part.
I don't know this song.
Sorry, but we have to stop.
We have to stop.
What?
That's it.
Let's say goodbye with a nice sound.
Please listen to the last song.
Don't listen to it.
Let's play the last song.
Thank you.
It's a great sense of stability.
We also played songs we didn't know.
It was a mini concert.
How was the mini concert of YASUMOTO
AYAKA?
It was a great surprise.
Did you enjoy it?
It was YASUMOTO AYAKA's challenge.
Thank you very much.
New Episode Coming Wed. 1700 JST
Thank you for watching.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Hello!
I'm the host, Mayumi Rika.
So, what was the name of the show?
It's not Ichige, it's Ichige.
It's Ichige?
It's not Ichige?
It's Ippatsuge.
Ippatsuge.
Ippatsuge is a great name.
I'm going to learn Ichige.
So, I'm going to start with Mirei-chan,
no, Rittan.
Rittan, Mirei-chan, Aya-chan, and now
it's my turn.
I'm going to challenge myself to go
around Japan with a kendama.
You want to go around Japan?
Yes, I do.
I want to go around Japan.
I'm going to do something like stabbing
a small plate, a large plate, or a
sword.
Can I start now?
Yes.
Go for it!
Everyone's energy is so strong.
It's fun.
What?
Isn't it amazing?
It's unexpected.
Yesterday, I did it once. Suddenly, at
midnight.
At that time, God Town was broadcast. I
was watching Tanaka-san of I-World on
the screen.
Then I did it. I want to do it with
Tanaka-san in mind.
I couldn't do it.
I didn't get hired.
I was talking in the middle.
This is it.
Focus.
I want to do it.
This is not good.
You brought a bad one.
I learned that I can do it if I do this.
I can do it up to here.
I can do it normally.
Let's see.
Is that Hokkaido?
Yes, it is.
We have to put Hokkaido at the end.
It goes up from the bottom?
Yes, from the bottom.
Okinawa, Tokyo, Hokkaido?
Yes.
This is Okinawa.
Kyushu.
Wow!
What about this?
Honshu.
Wow!
Hokkaido.
Hokkaido is Dekkaido!
Dekkaido!
But earlier, you said it's better not to
raise the ball too much.
You're a pro again!
A kendama pro.
There's 10 minutes.
In 10 minutes, once...
Ho! Ho!
Oh, no!
Hokkaido is...
Hokkaido is quite...
It's amazing.
Hokkaido!
I did it!
Wow!
I did it! I did it! I did it!
It might be a fluke.
Wait!
We just became friends.
I'm scared.
A fluke?
I imagined it.
I imagined you.
Thank you.
And...
Oh!
Hokkaido.
Hokkaido!
I'm scared!
It's really bouncy.
It's like...
Leave it to me!
It's easy to do.
It was a mess.
The finishing touch.
It's amazing.
You're so good at the rhythm.
It's a big mess.
It's difficult.
Go for it!
Are you with me?
So close!
It's so fast.
Hokkaido!
Amazing!
It's a draw!
See?
I told you!
I told you to do it earlier.
Be honest.
It's a draw!
Isn't it amazing?
It's purple.
The principal chose this purple one.
It's cute.
Then, there is one person who thinks
it's harmonica.
Then, it's harmonica.
I'm laughing, but I can't think of the
principal.
It's coming.
Thank you for watching! Please subscribe
to our channel!
This is good, right?
This is good.
So, the Kendama Challenge is a success.
Wow.
Thank you very much.
That's all for me.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Hello everyone!
Hello!
So far, everyone has succeeded.
This time I will challenge the 5-stage
Trump Tower.
Wow!
First of all, this is not a problem of
practice.
This is luck.
I would like to do it.
I may go to a place of nothing for a
while.
Do your best!
Do you have to speak a lot?
No, it's okay.
I think it's okay.
I would like to do it.
I was able to do it when I was
practicing at home.
The time zone was decided.
It is possible from 17.30 to 19.00.
The time is decided.
It's fast.
This is difficult.
I'm shaking.
Let's concentrate.
I have been a teacher for a while.
There is a professional.
I'm mixing alone.
I'm experiencing everything.
I think I was practicing earlier, and I
was able to do it.
My hand muscles are very...
You're shaking, right?
I can hear the principal's laughter from
a very far away place.
What are you laughing at?
I think it's because it's broken.
Oh, you're watching the video.
Is it easier to do it with two pieces?
If you make it two, the strength will
increase.
Even if the top is broken, the bottom is
strong, so it's hard to break.
It's a problem.
Make sure you breathe steadily.
It's a matter of time.
Is it a breathing tool?
You can't do it that far.
That's amazing.
That's fast.
I can do it well while listening to such
a speech.
Wait, I have to cheer for you with a
sparkling star.
Wow, that's great.
I'll do my best.
That's fast.
By the way, did you practice?
I practiced.
You are very good.
I heard you were drinking water during
the practice.
I didn't say that.
You are like a god.
I'll beat you.
Watch the original work.
I can't sing.
I remember the first time I sang this
song in elementary school.
I know.
Isn't it too fast?
Wow.
Trump's breath.
All focus.
The best.
Heart's ace.
Stop it.
Only Kaho can do this.
I can't do this.
Wait, can I fix this?
Do you need to fix it?
It's too narrow.
It's not uniform.
I'm scared.
Your eyes are weird.
I'm scared. I'm going to stop.
I want to stop fixing it.
I can't breathe.
Hang in there!
It's good.
Sometimes you need to shut up.
We're too noisy.
We've done two.
Three more.
Three more?
It's beautiful.
How do they support each other?
Amazing.
The tip of the hand is clean.
I was surprised.
I'm sorry.
It's good to have two at this time.
I see.
I'm taking a video of the concert.
Please support her in the comments.
The audience must be nervous.
They must be.
Will she finish in 10 minutes?
I'm scared.
It's scary.
Is it suddenly harder?
The third stage?
Yes, if it's hard from here,
it's over.
But there's still time, right?
It's okay.
I'm going to do whatever I have to do.
I'm not going to go this far.
I'm really...
I'm nervous.
This side is nervous.
This is it.
Ah!
This is...
I'm getting dizzy.
How many times do I have to say it to
you to understand?
Although the truth is that it's not easy
to win the lottery.
What?
Should we make a vow?
If you get angry, the lamp will go out
again.
I see.
It's difficult.
Let's try it in the room with air
conditioner.
Come back!
Let's turn off the air conditioner.
Is it OK?
Yes, it's OK.
I'll ignore the time limit.
It's OK.
Let's start with someone next to you.
It's fun to watch.
This is bad.
Everyone is like, ah!
Even in the comments.
It's a little beautiful when it falls.
It's better to turn off the air
conditioner.
The wind has an effect.
Thank you very much.
The wind is strong.
Good luck.
Your manicure is beautiful.
It's beautiful.
Good luck.
Blue.
I'm going to change my mood with
harmonica.
I'll do that.
The focus is off.
It's so fast.
I wish you success.
I wish.
I'm sorry.
I'm wrong, but it's fast.
It's fast.
It's amazing.
It's a word police.
Because I work with a word police.
It's really fast here.
It's stable.
You!
You're the king.
You're the king, so you're a little
selfish.
U-pidonk semi.
The foundation is cleaner than before.
Thank you.
There are professionals.
There are professionals in all fields.
I thought it was clean before, but it's
better.
Have you ever played Trump in Ebichu?
I have played Uno.
I don't have Trump.
I want to play Trump.
Why don't you have Trump?
Because we are Uno generation.
Do you have SD?
No.
We have more than you.
But it's amazing.
Great. I will do my best.
It looks difficult.
It's beautiful.
It's really beautiful.
It's well-balanced.
I didn't know there was such a building.
I want Kaho to build it.
I'm sorry.
Please do your best.
You're amazing.
Please, please.
You're not good at this.
You look better than before.
Really?
You're a pro.
A pro.
I'm nervous.
You said it.
Lord?
Lord!?
Lord,
You told to jump Airport strip, right?
Aaaah
Thank you.
tramp tramp tramping
Wow!
It's coming!
Two more steps!
This is amazing!
I can't do this.
Can we go up two steps from here?
Thank you!
Oh my god!
Wow!
I'm so nervous.
She's in trouble.
Her manager is in trouble.
She looks worried.
I'm so nervous.
You're amazing!
Are you sure you're okay?
We'll cheer for you.
There's a card for YOSHI-HASHI.
It's not a good match.
It seems to be rooted here.
I took it.
So, this is...
This is a success.
Great.
This is something you can use for
thumbnails.
Great.
I'm done.
Thank you for turning off the air
conditioner.
I did it!
Wow!
Ah!
It was a little bit close.
It was fleeting.
I did it!
Thank you very much.
The last one.
What is that?
So, hello!
Hello!
Oh, it's Ime-chan!
It's Ime-chan!
Oh, oh!
The comments are going crazy!
Everyone's faces are turning red!
It's embarrassing!
So, I've dyed my hair!
That's nice!
I've dyed my hair!
It's cute! It's like beige!
It's nice! It's a pretty color!
It's like beige!
Thank you!
Sorry to those who like black hair!
It was really black before, so it's
fine!
That's true!
It's fresh!
It's like an adult!
It's dyed black!
Somayama was impressed by that!
It's amazing!
This is a cute ubuge!
So, I want to do a Rurikku Cube!
You want to do it?
I want to do it, but...
When I come to the office,
I can't get it together!
Please subscribe to our channel!
This is a problem.
Until then, we were all together.
At home?
We were all together.
We did it for a week.
We were all together in the office.
What happened?
Did we have to dye our hair?
No, we didn't.
It's okay. We're on air.
Let's do it.
We did it in 3 minutes.
We did it in 3 minutes at home.
3 minutes is hard.
Is there a trick?
There is.
If you remember the trick, you can do
it.
Please subscribe to our channel!
It's going to be a mess.
Yeah.
Do your best!
I can't do it here, but everyone is
doing well.
I'm a little suspicious.
Suspicious?
Everyone is doing well.
Thank you.
I'll do my best.
I'll try it for 3 minutes.
If it's impossible, I'll do it without
this.
I'll do it with this.
I'm scared.
I can't see it.
It's a mess.
We're gonna cry today!
kusuda The
Yay!
I'm going to set the timer to 3 minutes.
Are you ready?
Ready, go!
Did you press it?
Yes, I did.
It's started.
It's live!
How was it, Isamu-san?
The challenge of Kachigiri-gata.
It seems that the practice time went
well.
I was not in good condition when I
landed in Tokyo.
It's a matter of environment.
How was it, Nakayama-san?
You are a professional at spinning.
You are doing great.
How many fingers are you using?
I'm using 10 fingers.
I'm not sure if I'm doing it right or
wrong.
You are amazing.
You are getting used to it.
You are fast.
You are getting used to the green.
You are getting used to the yellow.
This is amazing.
Yes, it is.
Your ant, to.
Thank you.
This is Masashi's Kashiwagi Senshu.
I've heard of Kashiwagi Senshu before,
but now I've heard of Kashiwagi Senshu.
What is it about?
As a semi-pro.
It's better to put your hips in and put
an angle.
Do you need to put your hips in?
I don't need it now.
I think it's better to put your hips in.
You're going this far, but you're going
to go crazy from here.
I don't know that.
I can't sympathize with you.
I'm sure there are no more pros in the
comments.
I've heard a lot of things.
Each pro.
It's pretty difficult.
Halfway through.
There's one minute left.
It's weird.
Hang in there.
Calm down and hang in there.
There's one minute left.
I know.
It's like a sudden challenge.
It's a serious feeling.
It's a sudden challenge from around
Kaho.
It's a serious feeling.
Shiro has been here all along.
It's getting more messy than before.
It's amazing.
I can do it at home, but why can't I do
it here?
The Rubik's Cube is not supposed to be
turned.
I turned it and it popped.
I was surprised.
It's impossible.
It's different.
It's messed up.
Today's guest is a mess.
It's a mess.
I can't do it.
6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1
It's over.
What's this?
It's suddenly serious.
It's like a sunset chime.
Wait a minute.
Why?
Let's move this.
Wait a minute.
This is...
From now on, we will challenge without
time limit.
Why?
A professional of Rubik's Cube.
Is there anyone?
Is there a professional of Rubik's Cube
in this?
Me too.
I think it was good until the second
row.
I agree.
I can go to the second row.
Is there a second row?
Why?
It's amazing.
But it's half aligned.
The second row is a good way to say.
Why?
You are ready to study, right?
It's aligned.
I came here and tried to align the
yellow.
I couldn't draw it well.
I can't do it.
Please look! I did it!
Amazing, Nodoka-chan!
I did it!
Sorry, sorry.
No dinner for you, Niko-chan.
I'll make you tofu rice.
Why?
One corner is off.
One is off?
Aren't there three?
A pro at Mimic Game?
Wait a minute.
Welcome.
The color...
The top is yellow.
The color of the side and the corner...
The three are in the right size.
But it doesn't match.
Why?
If you mess it up again, it will be more
confusing.
It says it's correct.
It's correct.
Let's try it again.
The corners are off and it doesn't fit.
The corners are off and it doesn't fit?
What do you mean?
It says it's great if you turn it twice.
There are a lot of pros.
It's yellow.
I think there are more pseudo-pros.
It's amazing.
Everyone...
I wonder why we can do so much at home.
It's scary.
It's because we're relaxed.
The environment is different.
The environment?
No, I don't think so.
Why? Really?
I see. It's because people do it
differently.
I see.
It's different.
I wonder why.
It's like a pro.
It's because we're relaxed.
Wow.
It's amazing that we can do it so fast.
We can't break it after buying it.
I should have stopped.
Why?
It's like a decoration.
It is.
I think it's better to hit the floor
once.
I want to hit it.
I want to say that I succeeded.
That's amazing.
It's good to have a big hand.
What?
Why?
It doesn't change even if you do it
once?
I messed up and put it back.
Put it back?
And it's back to the original position.
I've been able to do this as usual.
Why?
Isn't it amazing?
What?
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
What should we do?
Does anyone know what to do?
We can't do anything.
We can't do anything but we can't give
advice.
What should we do?
The top part is a yellow cross.
A yellow cross?
Let's read the manual.
It's difficult.
Isn't it amazing?
I saw the live streaming of the Rubik's
Cube.
The cube at the top is off.
What?
The one you brought?
Yes.
But it's all right.
That's why it's not all right.
Isn't that a surprise?
The color of the cube at the corner is
not all right.
What?
I'm scared.
What's going on?
Rubik's Cube's corner can't be moved.
What?
Who did that?
I didn't do it.
It's not the same.
The cube is not all right.
What's wrong?
I don't think it's right.
Really?
But you did it at home.
I twisted it once.
The blue corner is not all right.
You should ask the suspect.
Who is the suspect?
That's why it's not all right.
Did you do it outside of the house?
Who?
I did it outside of your house.
What's wrong?
Is this the original?
What should I do?
Is it all right?
It's all right.
You didn't take it off, did you?
I can't take it off.
What's wrong?
Who did it?
It's not me.
I'm not the same.
I don't have the power to take it off.
I twisted it once.
Can you do it?
Wait a minute.
Is this really a Rubik's Cube video?
I twisted it once.
Can you do it?
If you can do it, let me challenge it
for 3 minutes.
That's right.
Wait a minute.
Is this a Rubik's Cube video?
I'm scared.
You can't twist it.
I can't do that.
I think I twisted it too much.
That's not possible.
That's true.
Wait a minute.
That's not possible.
You've learned.
You can twist the Rubik's Cube.
Wait a minute.
No, wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
I'm taking too much time.
It's the last one.
I feel like I'm challenging.
I want to know the answer.
What happened?
What happened to my Rubik's Cube?
I'm scared.
From tomorrow...
To be continued...
This is the suspect's private service
job.
There's a comment that says you should
listen to the left.
Why are you all...
Wait, I don't know.
But I've been practicing for a week with
this, so...
I don't think that's true.
I'm serious.
That's good. I'm surprised.
I'm sorry.
Because I've been doing this for a week.
See?
That's amazing.
You came to the office and it's weird.
I'm not weird.
Who?
Hey! Who are you?
I'm not weird.
I'm not weird at all.
Is that possible?
I think there was a blonde hair in the
last Rubik's Cube.
What?
I think so.
I'm not sure.
I can't say it easily.
It's difficult.
I don't know anything.
It would be great if you could solve it
with this.
You can do it with a cube.
I heard it again.
I can't think about it together.
No.
Maybe it's just me.
I think she's just thinking about it.
I wonder why.
She can't give advice.
She can do that much, but she can't do
it here.
That's right. It's strange.
Rita, you're not talking much, so it's
suspicious.
I can see it.
I'm a viewer.
I'm a little scared to participate in
that drama.
Right away.
I don't want to get hurt.
Riko, you're a big success.
How should I twist it?
I twisted it in the wrong place.
Did I make a mistake in twisting it?
Wait a minute.
I don't understand if you twist it.
It's a long-term entry fee.
I'll cheer you on.
I'll do my best.
You want to buy a new one, don't you?
That's right.
I want to buy it.
I don't know how much it costs.
Wow.
Wait a minute.
I'm going to ask for help from the
customers.
I'll stop you.
It says that we should make a yellow
cross.
It says so, doesn't it?
The real people have finally appeared.
Yellow cross.
This is the yellow cross.
It's amazing.
Thank you for watching until the end.
It's perfect so far.
I see. That's where it doesn't work.
That's right. If you do it as usual, it
will never be aligned.
What do you mean?
For the time being, the corners are
aligned.
It's in a state where it's not aligned.
It's a Rubik's Cube that never aligns.
Please twist the Rubik's Cube in the
right direction once.
What should I do? What's the right
answer?
Come here.
Do you want to call?
Wait a minute. I'll make a cross with
the corners aligned.
Can you do that?
What is that?
I want to align it.
I'm not doing it.
So I made all four corners in a diagonal
line.
What should I do?
On the contrary, the person who twisted
this is a professional.
I don't know where I twisted it.
It doesn't match.
The yellow on the outside...
It's okay to twist it, but I can't do it
now.
I'm sorry.
I've never seen you twist it.
I can't twist it.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
I didn't know you can do that.
Thank you for this.
I don't know what you mean.
I'll put it on.
It's already done.
It's done.
It's fast.
Thank you for watching.
I don't understand at all.
Wait a minute.
I'm going to mess up.
Do it again.
I'll try to do it slowly.
If it's really all together, let's do it
for 3 minutes.
It took a long time.
I'm sorry.
I was able to repair the booming
keyboard.
It's a repair video.
That's why I'm here.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you.
That's what it is.
Thank you everyone.
Great.
I'm so happy.
What's going on?
Everyone was successful.
I was so nervous that I almost cried.
I'm so sorry for my failure.
I'm glad.
It's all thanks to everyone.
I'm glad I had a function.
I'm glad it's messed up.
It's messed up.
It's okay. It's not twisted.
It's not twisted.
It's okay.
Let's start from the beginning.
Let's try it once.
Don't we have to measure the time?
It's 3 minutes.
Do you want to do it for 3 minutes?
Wait a minute.
Let's do it together.
Let's do it together and check it in 3
minutes.
Let's check it.
It's twisted again.
I know how to twist it.
That's how it is.
It's a nose-up ball.
It's a super power.
I see.
That's great.
I don't know the principle at all.
I'm glad.
If you buy a Rubik's Cube and it's
messed up, you can twist it.
That's how it changes.
That's great.
It's been more than 10 minutes.
I'm sorry, everyone.
It's okay.
Thank you.
That's great.
Especially the Rubik's Cube's shape.
It's maintenance.
First class.
That's great.
It's so quick.
That's why it's so difficult.
I was told that I can't get it right.
I was so scared.
I thought I couldn't get it right.
Isn't it amazing?
Please subscribe to our channel.
Wow, you've been explaining for a long
time.
You can rotate the corners in three sets
in the same direction, but you can't
rotate one corner.
If one corner of something is rotated,
it will never be completed.
I see.
Isn't it good to turn too much?
Maybe I turned it too much.
You can turn it without turning it.
It's coming.
Isn't it strong?
No matter how much you mess it up, it's
going to be fine.
It's coming.
It's okay. It's fixed.
Miyatan's expression is...
It's back.
Thank you for watching.
I'm cured! I'm cured!
Don't fight!
I'm glad!
I'm cured!
I almost cried until now.
I'm so happy!
I'm cured!
Thank you for watching!
Thank you everyone!
So, we're going to do the 3rd challenge.
We're going to mess it up.
I'm going to do it.
I'm nervous.
I'm glad!
I'm so glad!
I'm so happy!
I wonder if it's mixed.
I wonder why.
I think I twisted it too much.
It's going to be soft.
Maybe I did it too much.
Thank you.
It's messed up.
Kaho messed it up like this.
Let's do it again.
I'm nervous.
I'm scared.
Can I see it?
Let's see it together.
I'm nervous.
I didn't expect it.
I'm starting to fix it.
We are Ebichu.
We are, but you're going to do it.
Are you ready?
Please subscribe to our channel.
I can talk now.
I can see you.
Thanks to everyone,
everyone is waiting for me.
Thank you.
It started again. 3 minutes challenge.
Yes.
It's a live broadcast.
I didn't say anything.
You're so fast.
It's not that smooth.
It's not smooth, but it's close.
I know.
Isn't it fast?
It's getting there.
It's fast.
Wait.
Two minutes.
No, no.
It's been 2 minutes.
It's not fast at all.
Stop it.
Isn't it great?
It's my first time to do it.
It's like the yellow cross we talked
about.
I can see the yellow.
I can see it.
I'm not sure if I'm doing it right.
It's okay.
I'm getting the sense of harmony.
I'll put it on later.
You're so fast.
1 minute and 30 seconds.
You can do it.
I'm getting the sense of harmony.
1 minute 20 seconds.
So, you did it in 1 minute and 40
seconds.
That's right.
I'm glad.
Wow!
You did it in 2 minutes.
I'm glad.
It's a success.
We did it.
It's a big success.
It was a surprise.
It's all thanks to you.
I couldn't get it right.
Everyone taught me how to do it.
I was able to do it in 1 minute and 40
seconds.
You did it in 2 minutes.
I did it in 2 minutes.
Is this the latest record?
The latest record is 1 minute and 26
seconds.
But I did it in 2 minutes to do it in 3
minutes.
That's a big record for me.
It's a big record.
I'm glad.
I'm really glad.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad you did it, Hina.
It was like a touching finale.
Thank you very much.
We all learned a lesson.
It was a great success.
The video of Ebichu from tomorrow will
be a Q&A.
If you tweet the question, we will
answer it on the day you tweet.
We will post the details on Twitter at
night, so please check it out.
Thank you for watching the live stream.
Please subscribe to our channel.
We are waiting for your questions.
Thank you for watching.
Please subscribe to our channel.