We had a fight.
What did you fight about?
About this.
We didn't tell each other the secret.
It
I pretended not to see you
I pretended to understand you
I cried
I'll be the interviewer
Yes, interviewer
First self-introduction
I'm Coco from Gang Parade.
Hello.
I'm listening to the story of Ayano
Toyotoshi and Tsuki Haruna.
I talked about something deep.
I heard that she will be happy even if
she says something bad.
So you should talk about it more deeply.
I was worried about Tsuki and Haruna's
appearance.
I was surprised that they were in the
same group.
I was worried that it would be
interesting.
There were 13 people in the group.
At that time, there were 9 people in the
group.
I was worried about that.
But I was more excited than that.
I think there were people who resisted
the increase in the number of people.
Everyone has an allergic reaction at
first.
But it ended soon.
So I think they were the children who
were wanted.
We were wanted.
I was jealous.
We were only three people.
There were various practice periods
before the show.
Tsuki and Haruna were the two opposite.
I was worried.
Haruna was like a jumping tool.
Tsuki was serious.
I was worried.
After the performance, the movement is
slow.
It's slow and always wrong.
The first practice is over.
I was nervous.
I was most worried about Haruna's
performance.
I was worried about the performance.
Tsuki and Haruna were in the group.
The first practice was ZEP Diver.
In the
second practice,앙
BIO was
very effective
to meDon't forget
that my
perfection was
very good
while I remember
Heil
Maps
I'm not giving up on this morning
I'm not giving up on this day
I'm going to die, no matter how long
Let's talk about Tiff
P2M 6 consecutive
Yes, it's a timing point
Yes, yes, yes
Maika was in a very bad condition at
that time
I was hot
I was hot, my face was dead
After the end, everyone was crazy in ZEP
Everyone was like
I was like
Maika was down
Really in the hallway
I was like, is it okay?
At that time, the staff who called us at
that time
I happen to be watching that live
Our best performance
I watched it in a crowd
Maika was lying down
We made our major debut
That day was our beginning
At Kawasaki Club Chitta
I played the video and made my major
debut
It wasn't just a major debut
announcement
It's a little bit of a habit
I can't say that
I'm going to say it
It's okay because you don't have to use
it
It's okay
I don't need that at all
I don't need it
I really don't need it
I'm a black
I'll say it including that
What?
I don't need it at all
I don't need it
I really don't need it
I'm okay
There are many things I have to talk
about
Can I talk about the audition for
Narahagi?
Yes, you can talk about it
I was surprised that I had been doing it
with confidence in the job
I didn't pay much attention to Narahagi
in the training camp
There was also a dissolution of the BIS,
so I was conscious of it
I was also affected by the dissolution
of the BIS
I was a classmate
The BIS of the second generation was
very different from the BIS of the third
generation
I had a lot of memories, so I didn't
feel lonely
I had a lot of feelings of inferiority
I was inspired by the dissolution of the
BIS and I realized that I had come this
far
I can't answer
How is it? What level is it?
I'll talk about everything
How can I pull out the story that I
haven't talked about before?
It was a project
If you could make a proper introduction
that reminds you of the episode, I think
you could talk about it at all
There is no such thing at this time
There is a lot of after that
So, Haruno's...
The moon is already bright.
Haruna will quit.
What is this?
Suddenly...
I pretended not to hear you, even though
I could hear you
I pretended to be stupid and gave up
I pretended not to see you