Thank you for watching.
Protect your seniors, second game battle.
Yes!!!
To avoid punishment for the senior members.
The second half of the second game battle in which paired juniors face off in various competitions.
So far, four third-term seniors have been defeated by four juniors in an ejinky to make them chatter.
A battle of juniors who absolutely cannot be beaten The first showdown of the night is
The one-man challenge.
Soak Dash when you press the camera's self-timer.
If you can get your face in the frame and take a photo within 3 seconds of the shutter release, you've cleared the challenge.
Each time you increase the distance, and if a junior fails, the punishment for the senior is...
A pie in the face.
This is the nostalgic one that changed from this.
I miss it.
Suzuki.
Yes, sir.
I don't want to eat the pie if I can help it.
I'd rather go home with a clean face.
This is my second pie.
At the corps competition.
Mr. Shirara cut the string for fun and I ate the pie.
I'm not playing, I'm doing it for work.
I don't want to do it.
That's right.
He's a senior... with a pie in his face.
Of course, Ayane's face is a national treasure, and she's a legend.
I won't let you pie me.
I won't let you.
That's why even if one of us wins, only one of us can go home clean.
I see.
And now the older Umezawa wins out.
I'll never let you pie the beautiful Umezawa in the face.
I'll run for my life.
I used to be a karate fighter, so I'm afraid I'll get pummeled later.
Scary.
Ume.
Yes, I'm afraid.
I wish you good luck.
I saved Shiraishi-san with this.
I see.
I don't mind if you get your juniors dirty at all.
I'd rather focus on your attitude than your success or failure.
That's the most pressure.
What do you mean, what do you mean?
That's good.
It's totally fine to fail and eat it.
But to take it seriously, that's different.
I see.
Your attitude towards this game.
That's right.
Next senior Kubo, junior Hayakawa...
Yes.
You're a great actress, aren't you?
No, you can't put that kind of cream on a big-girl actress.
No way.
I'll never get this job.
It's a game you can win if you work hard.
That's right.
I'm used to this sort of thing.
Really.
Just the other day, when I went on a trip with Shiori...
I left it there.
We made hearts together.
But one concern is that we're too close.
It's not like she's just going to give up.
It's better to eat them.
Attitude is important.
Attitude is important too.
How about you, senpai Yoda, junior Iki?
Yes, I'll stand up for myself and not let my senpai stand up for himself.
I see.
I just imitated Masami Nagasawa.
Indeed.
You're right.
We haven't talked like that at night either.
I've talked about it a bit.
You know, even at night it's the scariest thing in the world.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I want you to do your best.
You can do it, Iki.
Basically, I'm scared of the third term.
Third term's been through this before.
I'm scared.
Like this.
The result of rock-paper-scissors-scissors.
The order is chosen by the winners.
The first one up is Iki, a fellow student.
I started with Ioki, but he's at 5 metres now.
I have to move at least one square at the beginning.
4 memory
Suddenly...
Oh, my God.
It's all right.
Four out of nowhere.
It's 60 centimetres down.
And I'll be here to support you if you go over the edge.
I'll be careful.
Let's go.
Here we go.
Try your hand at the selfie challenge.
You've got time!
I've got plenty of time.
I've got time.
Photo's up.
Oh, you can afford it.
She's cute.
It's totally fine.
If you want, we could go right past it.
Hey...
Next is fourth-year student Sato's challenge.
Are you slow?
I'm slow, probably.
I'm about third or fourth from the bottom out of all of you.
Oh, no. Suzuki's in trouble.
But I believe in you. I'll be fine.
I'll be fine.
You'll be fine.
I'm fine.
Until the third eye.
There's plenty of room.
Hirasato, try 45 cm lower.
Shall we?
Okay, then.
Last-minute selfie challenge!
[Hajime Shacho's ending]
I've got too much leeway, I'm coming out too fast.
Aaah!
I'm so embarrassed that I'm in the picture.
I wonder if fishing all the time will not slip away...
て
Aaah!
I can afford it!
It's difficult, isn't it?
Yamashita came out in plenty of time, too.
I'm sure they'll come out more and more.
They'll come out more and more.
The last of the first round is the late Sugawara. Go ahead, attack or wait and see.
But if you really go for it, you'll be fine.
Four by 47 meters, 25 centimeters, 7 meters and 25 inches... that's a hell of a long way.
さあねはい気をつけてくださいこの辺でボンミスで落とすってありえないですから
It's impossible, fate is watching our stance.
Let's go for the last-minute selfie challenge.
Ha-ha-ha.
It's not sticking out now, it's coming out.
Let's take a look at the photo.
It's hiding the whole rock. Yamashita's come out all right.
After this, all the members who carefully tried to bowl the second lap with strength and distance were successful!
そして勝負は10メートル越えの3巡目に突入
Fifth-year student Iki's choice...
What should we do?
Attack or defend?
Defend?
Frazee, but that's a weak statement.
Defend.
Let's go on the offensive.
Four.
Ten metres, 70 centimetres.
That's pretty good.
Yoshihiko Ioki, take a selfie challenge.
No, thank you. It's getting pretty close.
It's getting good. Let's see the photos.
That's pretty close.
Oh, it's from around here.
I'm pretty close to the edge, as far as I'm concerned.
The timing is faster than I thought it would be.
Well, this is where it starts.
Here they come!
Next, Sato, who's not sure about his leg strength, chose the 30 cm plus for protection.
Let's check the photos.
I managed to get it in the frame, just in time.
This is how it's going to be.
Hayakawa's fast.
Why Hayakawa?
Because he's fast.
You're so fast, Hayakawa!
Try it with plus one memory.
Succeed without fail.
Put pressure on the rest of the field.
Seriously.
And the third and final round is Sugawara.
Come on, Shogo, I'm nervous.
I really want to attack, but...
To save Umezawa-san's face.
But I don't know...
Maybe they'll think you're trying to be aggressive.
Even if it doesn't work, it's okay.
Can I ask your opinion?
You don't have to ask me for my opinion.
I'm scared.
I see what you mean.
But that's...
It's in anticipation of what's to come.
I've been hungry since I sat here.
I'm going to start my fifth term.
They'll think for themselves.
They'll act for Nogizaka on their own.
I'm not here to listen to my seniors' opinions.
I'm going with my own opinion.
Yes, sir.
Second place.
Let's go for second place.
11 metres, 45 centimetres.
That's great.
Here we go.
Here you go.
That's fast.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I think I'm good.
I think it looks good.
Let's see some pictures.
Oh, lee.
In the middle.
That's amazing.
But it's not good if it doesn't show up when you run in like this.
You have to go in like this.
It's the face side, so it won't go in there.
That's right.
Maybe...
I'll set a world record in the short distance.
Right here.
I'll find myself doing 50 metres or something.
Send it into the rainy season..."
The selfie challenge has already attracted 40 participants
Iyoki added 2 memory 30 cm.
11 metres and 75 centimetres.
Sato was just barely there earlier.
Sato, wanting to hang on, tries an extra 1 memory.
Let's go! 11 metres, 90 centimetres!
Let's go for the last-minute selfie challenge!
He's so cute!
Go for it! I can do it, I can do it, I can do it.
How's it going!
No, you got it!
What's Sato's result?
Let's check the photos.
Wow!
There it is!
This one's not in.
It's not in!
Wow!
So that's a pie in senior Suzuki's face.
Just say something to Suzuki.
I'm sorry, sir.
Not at all.
Let's go... to Suzuki.
Three seconds.
Three, two, one.
Strong.
Harder.
Not too hard?
No, it's fine.
Look at you, you're so beautiful.
Who's that?
Not too hard?
I thought I'd lose my nose.
Punch it.
I got hit a little hard, didn't I?
But you've already done your best.
Only one of the juniors survived, so they might be a bit scared now, the pies are getting more powerful too.
Only three left, one senior to be saved, and here we go.
Aaaaaaah! Cleared some 12 metres and 5 centimetres.
What about Sugawara?
How's Sugawara?
He's improved his record by 15 centimetres!
Amazing! Daikichi!
Great luck!
50 metres from here.
Iyoki is on the offensive, plus two memories.
You'd better screw your face in at the end.
I think it's that game now.
Here's your last-minute one-man challenge.
Go for it.
Whoa!
Oh!
Oh, oh, good, it's not in yet.
No, the face, the one you just put in, it's not in there.
That was a second ago.
It was a while ago, but I don't know if it's in there.
I don't know.
It's in, it's in, it's in, it's in, it's in, it's in, it's in.
Oh, my God!
It's just about to go in.
Bravo!
Bravo, bravo, bravo!
I think we've put a bit of pressure on the last two.
Suzuki's having fun.
Yes, it is.
Why is it fun?
What do we do, Hayakawa?
First place.
I guess it's a toss-up.
Even first place could be bad... this time.
Here's your last-minute selfie challenge!
Go for it, go for it!
Shut up. Hey.
How's it going? That was close.
Is it in? I think it's gone.
If not, I'm gonna eat a Kubo.
Is it in my face?
It's in!
Oh, my God!
That's great.
It's really close.
That's not good.
If you get it in next time, you win!
That's amazing.
To attack or not to attack?
One or two questions won't make much difference.
Amazing!
Utsu and Uiran were so scary!
Sugawara, under pressure from Umezawa, chose the plus two scale of victory.
Use your own timing!
Last-minute selfie challenge!
Sugawara, go ahead.
Go for it, go for it!
I can do it, I can do it, I can do it.
Can you do it?
Maybe a little too subtle.
Let's see the photos.
Is it in?
Sugawara's ready for a fight.
Can he save his senior, Umezawa?
Is it in?
Oh, no!
It's not in!
I'm chattering like a baby!
You're out.
Come on, Ume, you're gonna get your pie.
Let's do it.
Just one last thing, senpai.
I'm sorry.
Get down on your knees.
That was cool.
That was cool. Ume, it's all right.
It's all right.
Come on, let's go.
Pie, three, two, one, go ahead.
Wow.
Yoo-hoo!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Ooooh, that hurt!
It's painful. Let me take it off for you.
Hey, then...
Haaaa...
[All] Huh?
[All] Wow!
Oh, my God, they're all buried in the beauty.
Oh, my gosh.
That's a lot of swooning.
Yes, it's like we're doing a variety show.
I feel like I'm doing a variety show.
That's cool.
Now that's a great comment.
That's great.
Finally, a fight.
Who can defend their seniors?
It's all down to the wire from here.
Ioki's going for 12 metres 80.
Come on, Ioki.
Go for it!
Last-minute selfie challenge
Take your own timing!
Here you go.
Go, go, go!
That was quick.
No, no, no, not fast enough.
You did it once.
It's not safe.
From my vantage point, it looks like you've got plenty of time.
You look comfortable.
How do you feel about it? Do you feel like you're ready?
I don't know.
If this is out, Kubo is safe.
I wonder if it was in there.
Let's take a look at the photos.
Wow!
Out!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Thank you for making it this far.
I'd better close my eyes, but I don't want to keep them open.
It's the first time I've ever done this... and I'm a senior now... but the sun is shining, so I'll have to get rid of Pichler.
Now then, Brother Peeser, one back.
Oh, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha...
My tummy's full of pies.
It's gone a bit high up.
Take it off for him.
Look, look...
It's like this at the bottom.
Right here, below the face.
It's beautiful.
It's totally visible.
It's all right. It's all right.
How's she looking?
You're making a funny face, but I don't know, I want to take a picture of it.
いねそして久保
Safety!
I told you she's a Tiger actress... like that...
Let's continue with the game.
Oh, yeah...
The junior members are on a mission to save Akimoto, who's trapped in a giant balloon box.
If they can get the balloons into the bucket three metres away without dropping them with the wind from the hairdryer, they'll be airborne for a moment.
トップ
If the giant balloon doesn't break by the end of the four members' challenge, Akimoto will be rescued!
挑戦するのはこちらの4人
Will you work together to complete the mission?
ということで真夏さんを風船の餌食にしちゃあまずいですよ
He's the captain's senior, and he's sacrificed his life for us. We won't let it break.
Please... and Hayashi... we'll all work together... and just now... it was a battle... but... we'll also be working together.
もチームワークして
I'd like Manatsu-san to witness the bond between the fourth term students.
Don't worry, Kuromi's here.
Kuromi's in trouble, if she fails, leave it to Manatsu-san.
Will she be all right?
Protect the captain from the giant balloon.
さあそれじゃいきましょう1人目柴田チャレンジスタート
I can do it, I can do it, I can do it...
Go for it!
Go, go, go!
Uraa, I can't get in!
Akimoto's balloon's getting bigger and bigger.
Oh, no!
It's in!
It's stopped!
It's pretty inflated.
It's stopped now.
It's inflating quite a bit, isn't it?
That's pretty fast.
A little slow.
It's hard to fine-tune.
Yes, it is.
I can't get it in.
It's too slow.
You've done a lot of work on the balloons.
I'm so scared.
Yeah, very scary.
Holiday!
I'm scared... that's Holiday!
Now let's see if we can recover the Yakubo.
Let the challenge begin!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
Good, good, good.
Oh!
Huihui.
That's great.
Kick it
Wow, you dropped it!
That's a time-loss.
Oh, no, no, no!
It's pretty inflated.
The balloon's in trouble.
Come on!
The fallout's pretty bad.
It's okay, it's okay.
In, in, in, in, in, in, in, in.
I'm in, I'm in, I'm in.
Oh, man, I thought it was going in pretty good, but it came off.
I can't believe how panicky he gets when he takes it off.
When he came to get it, he was like a cartoon.
That's amazing.
Do you guys know how bad this is?
Surprisingly, when everyone's playing the game, they're so focused.
The third in a last-ditch fight is Kuromi.
Kuromi's really working hard.
I'm good at this.
Don't worry, I'll take care of it.
You're so determined.
Leave it to me.
Let's start the third.
Go, go, go, go!
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
You, you, you, you.
Quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick. Good job, good job.
Good, good, good.
Amazing.
You survived, Akimoto.
You're going to live!
It might...
Come on, we're moving too fast.
We don't have much time.
It's getting cold.
Why don't you use a hairdryer to warm it up?
Can the giant balloon save Akimoto?
I can do it! I can do it!
The Anka Hayashi Challenge is about to begin!
Go, go, go!
I'm here, I'm here, I'm cracking, I'm cracking!
I'm down, I'm down, I'm down, I'm down, I'm down, I'm down!
Oh no, oh no, it's cracking already!
The fall is already halfway full
It's too big!
You scared me!
That's too big!
Wow!
Oh, my God.
Ew! Ew!
That's too big.
Explosion sound too big.
Explosion sound.
How many times have you dropped the forest?
What are you doing?
Hayashi, you're not very good at this!
I'm just doing it right. I'm really serious.
I'm not doing it!
It's amazing how everyone seems to be against you.
You're so bad at this!
Now you're the one who got Akimoto killed.
Akimoto was high, wasn't he?
I'm sorry.
Fifty-five.
But look, no, no, no, Hayashi's here now.
No, no, no.
He's only stopped because he's cracked.
Why are these four funny?
They're funny.
They're the four of them.
And they don't really feel sorry for Akimoto.
It's true.
No one feels sorry.
No one is sorry.
It's true that in other games, everyone said they were sorry.
It's true.
They were four good guys.
That was so scary.
You should all come backstage later.
Maybe that's it, just say thank you for making it so good, and give me a bit of pocket money.
Thank you for your hard work.
Sword bullet.
Something happened, didn't it?
Here we go.
One more time, one more time.
Oh! Please subscribe to our channel.
Okay, I'm Kelly, Weiter.