Gekko-tto! Idol!
The second part of the story
What makes you like sweet potatoes?
Nature!
I grew up in Fukuoka
I grew up in a place where nature is
abundant
I went to the mountains and the sea when
I went to play
There is also a sea?
Yes, both
Even now, when I want to refresh, I go
to the sea and listen to the sound of
the waves
I'm having a good time
When you go right away, you can see the
sea from a nearby house
Yes, I go by car
The sea is very beautiful
The stars are also very beautiful
There is no light around, so when the
weather is good at night, you can see
the beautiful stars more than the
planetarium
I saw three shooting stars
I saw it
In that case, it's still a local place
Yes, it's still a local place
Do you have a driving license?
I already have
I see
You drive yourself
Yes, I go alone
Nature makes you
It's important to go to such places and
change your mood
Yes, it's important
The third story
I heard that you are a fishmonger
Yes, I was on a program that supports
fishing in Kyushu
I learned the history of the Oita
family's fish
I learned the good things
Fish Ham?
I learned the deliciousness of fish ham
for the first time
What is the original dance?
I learned the original dance
There is a dance that was created to
convey the taste of fish ham
I ate it and tried to express the taste
with my body
I see
I moved like a fish ham
I want to ask the professional
I want to see the viewers who are
watching
Can I see the fish ham dance?
Now?
I ate fish ham
It's delicious
Fish ham
Thank you
How did you feel when you saw the fish
ham dance?
It's intense
I have sharp teeth
I bite people so hard that it hurts
Really?
I express it
It was a white fish, right?
It's delicious
I'm glad I met you today
Please eat a lot
Thank you
I went to the sauna alone
There are many people who like saunas in
Japan