Now, the shrimp-chewed TASTA has
started!
How are you all doing?
This is the member of TASTA, Oga
Takayuki!
It's still early in the morning...
You two!
It's been a while since I've held this
mic!
It's been a while, right?
What are you doing here?
We were waiting for you two!
We were waiting for you?
We were in Kyushu, right?
We had a solo live in Kyushu yesterday
And today we're free
And tomorrow we're going to Tokyo for a
solo live
We're free for a day, right?
So let's go to the fan meeting!
OK!
This is it!
As you all know, I don't have much
stamina
What are you talking about?
Please keep up with this tension!
I can't do it because I have such a
heavy thing!
You don't have to do that!
What is it?
Let's go!
The fan meeting is not going to wait for
us!
Let's go!
This time, it's the special edition of
Eri Chu TASTA!
Fan meeting special!
It's another big event that is sent by
three men!
Start the speed race!
Here we go!
Start!
This program is brought to you by the
sponsors
Fan meeting!
I'm going to call the girls with
overflowing talent!
If you have anything to say to me, say
it!
It's just a memory!
It's a memory!
We are going to the fan meeting
Chuhei-san is going to go
As we said, it's a big event
We have a live show tomorrow
We have a big show in Tokyo
You did it alone yesterday too
It's impossible to go home
It's just a little bit
What did you say?
I said it's just a little bit
You can do it
It's just a little bit
This program is about the schedule
It started with Chuhei's selfishness of
wanting to see the fan meeting
What is a family end?
What do you think it is?
You are asking me the opposite
It's a big live show
Family concert
Family concert, family end
You want to have a concert together
It's a night
Family end in the shrimp, which has
become a summer custom
Nightly one man concert with a theme of
speed
This is the third time
This year, they will perform live in the
Echigo Park in Niigata Prefecture
They will be in Haneda for about 3 hours
and 40 minutes
They have a tight schedule
It's a one-man event every year
The moment when Ebichu is in the mood,
we have to meet as TASTAS members
Ebichu is waiting for us
Ebichu doesn't know we are coming
What?
They don't know that they are going to
the concert
They are rehearsing
Let's move on
Next, Jony
They are watching us
Sakurai Bees are also at the venue
They are coming to support Niigata
They are going to the concert today
This is their first time to meet
I'm looking forward to it
Sakurai Bees help them with the goods
They are going to the concert
What are they doing?
We are going to surprise them
Let's do a prank and ask them to come
We are going to have fun
Don't bother us
They are going to the concert
Why do we have to go to see your live?
We are going to have fun
Let's go
Can I?
What are you going to do?
We want to make the venue more lively
I want to do call and response
I think it's impossible to do live
Thank you for watching
I think it's impossible.
I was thinking that I could go out.
It's too much.
The stage is very tight.
It's closed.
Let's negotiate.
At that time, at the venue.
To schedule the fan meeting,
It's still in a tight mood.
Members were taking pictures on the
stage.
On the other hand, the three of them
have a big announcement from the show
staff.
I have big news for everyone.
What is it?
I got a message last week.
After September, the Ebichu Tastas will
continue.
The Tastas members are here.
It's a big news.
I did it.
It's great.
I'm so happy.
I will continue as a member of Tastas.
I don't know.
Can I do it?
It's the first time we've heard it.
We're okay, right?
I'm glad.
I want to hear it again.
I can go as a member of Tastas.
Taiki.
Thank you.
Wait.
Please stop.
Stop it.
You're making me emotional.
I'm just asking you what you're going to
do.
What?
He's asking you.
He's asking himself.
It's funny.
He's hesitating.
You shouldn't ask yourself.
For example,
you're on the stage.
Yes.
You should ask your fans.
You should ask them if they want to
continue.
They need to.
That's great.
Thank you.
I see.
I'll call you on Twitter.
No, you can't.
We're going to do it secretly.
Why? You'll find out.
Suddenly, the view is getting narrow.
It takes 2.5 hours to leave the station.
The three are taking a break in the
service area of Akagi Park.
They haven't had lunch yet.
What should we do?
Should we order it as it is?
Yes, I think so.
Actually, I'm making a lunch box.
What?
You're making a lunch box?
It's tough.
Who said that?
I did.
I'm a
good chef.
Thank you.
It's really delicious.
It's delicious.
It's good, isn't it?
It's good
Even in Niigata, the members who finally
got together
They were enjoying the barbecue time
Sakura Ebi is mixed with shrimp
They are enjoying the barbecue time
The members and staff got together and
had a special time
It's good
On the other hand, the 3 people with the
scampi are leaving the service area
It's about an hour and a half from here
It's still not over yet
Let's wait
Let's enjoy the barbecue together
It's not one yet.
It's a lot.
They were in a rush, but it's already
past 3 o'clock.
The fans are finally entering the venue.
It will be open at 4.30, but will they
be able to make it in time for the live?
40 minutes before the live, they finally
arrive at the venue.
Let's go.
It's almost time.
Only 10 minutes left.
10 minutes left.
What will happen to the three members?
And finally, the fan meeting begins.
The three people who arrived at the
venue at the last minute of the live.
It's wide.
It's the manager.
They found the manager, Kojo Fuji.
They immediately made that request.
Manager, we are actually a member of
TASSAS.
I know.
You're filming the camera.
We will make the fan meeting as exciting
as possible.
If you don't mind, can you come on the
stage?
I can't.
I'm in trouble if you suddenly ask me.
We will do anything.
We will start in 30 minutes.
Of course.
You have to say something.
Please say something.
I should ask him.
I'll ask him.
Excuse me.
You're very mature.
I'm very selfish.
I agree.
Will they appear in a meeting just
before this?
It's a grilled
It was surprisingly fast.
I don't know how fast it is yet.
I'll stop the car.
It's a big car.
I'm scared.
I'm scared of it.
I did it!
It was surprisingly fast
I think it was just a little bit
It was totally fast
I think that's good
Thank you very much
Thank you
Thanks to the manager's effort
9000 fans gathered on the stage
Thank you
Thank you very much
Just 3 minutes
They will meet the members who are just
before the show
We are here to meet you
We are here
You can be surprised
How are you?
We are here suddenly
We are here to see your performance
We are here to see you
Who are you?
I didn't know
We are here to cheer you up
It doesn't matter
We are here to enjoy
You are great
Kaiki-san, you are here
There is no wall from here
I didn't expect you to come
What do you mean?
I expected it
You always buy goods
Will you buy goods this year?
This year?
This year
We can buy goods from there
Please don't recommend goods when you
come
Thank you
We are looking forward to your
performance
Bye
Buy goods
You are doing it right
We will have a meeting here
Don't recommend goods
Good luck
Let's move to the opening act of FAMIEN
FAMIEN 2019 is finally opening
After the opening act, the three members
were left to
introduce themselves
We will introduce ourselves
And
Kaiki-san
I'm the one
I'm going
It's time for the three members
We are going to the opening act
FAMIEN 2015
The supporters who are watching the
program
I would like to give a message to the
shooting stars
Hello
Hello everyone
Amazing
Thank you
Everyone is getting excited!
This is amazing.
The reason we are here today is because
we have a show called Ebichu Tastas.
Do you know about it?
That's great.
Actually, there's an important
announcement about Ebichu Tastas.
It hasn't been decided since September.
We will continue the show.
We will continue the show!
Thank you for your support!
Thank you!
But we still don't know what to do with
Kaiki.
That's right.
So what should we do?
Yeah.
Well, then...
From now on...
Hey, thank you.
You've worked hard.
I can hear you.
Kaiki...
Everyone is getting excited.
It might be an interesting announcement,
but we will decide it by everyone's
opinion.
That's right.
Kaiki, please say something.
Yes.
I appeared on Ebichu Tastas
and got a lot of experience from there.
And from here...
It was so long that it was surprising.
But what's the conclusion?
Kaiki, I think this is enough.
If you think this is the end,
please raise your hand!
Is that all?
You said it.
You said you were so nervous.
I said it.
So, let's hear it.
Kaiki, please tell us if you want to
continue.
Oh!
Amazing! Thank you, everyone.
You've worked hard.
So, Ebichu Tastas will continue as it is
now.
Thank you.
OK, everyone.
Let's get excited!
The three have managed to warm up the
venue.
And finally...
We wish them an enjoyable component!
Also, we have Sakuradi, watching over R
Rank!
Thank you for watching!
They start with들이
However, not everyone is good at singing
Everyone won
What I can do isn't our precious
Everyone number is a 속
At this high point, we have no chance
After listening to the pitch
Thank you for watching!
The sun is setting, and the live
performance is in a fantastic mood.
The live performance is in a fantastic
mood.
The live show that lasted for two and a
half hours ended.
This is the first time I've seen
fireworks.
This is my first time seeing fireworks.
Everyone, this is my first time seeing
fireworks.
Matsuno is crying while looking at the
What's wrong?
fireworks.
And these three people also started this
project with loyalty to the central
government
After reaching the end, the overwhelming
stage of Ebichu
With the flowers of the
big forest floating in the night sky,
the other round was gently closed
Next time
We will open the Tastatsu court from now
on
Ebichu trial is closed
It is a trial
Ebichu members are judged one by one
In addition
This is quite negative
It is a development
The heated legal battle
Guilty or not, which is it?
The first round of the trial is closed
This program was provided by the sponsor
you see
What are you doing?
Do you have anything to say?
I'm going to
I look like I'm going to
Isn't the talk of Kenji Takiue
interesting or not?
Not interesting
Good