Tonight's Ebichu Tastasu will continue
to look for a property for Mayama who
wants to live alone.
They approach a super-expensive property
of admiration
Ebichu is very excited
Who?
And
There is something
Moemo is in a pinch
Ebichu Tastasu Start
It's a contract
Ebichu Tastasu
Thank you for watching!
What should I do with the heart of a
crazy person?
Monotrium, Monotrium, Monotrium, Junior
High School
Add various things to private Ebisu
Junior High School!
Ebisu Justice!
beautiful
I saw it on TV.
For Mayama who wants to live alone, a
real estate agent introduces her
favorite property.
The first one is a super open designer's
mansion.
Although it was a factory, Mayama...
I'm sorry.
Next, Mayama's favorite, a dreamlike
property where she can live in a ramen
shop.
But...
I don't think I can live there.
Mayama is so selfish.
Can she find her favorite property this
time?
Next, the property that the real estate
agent introduces is...
A really big five-star mansion.
Mayama's dream mansion.
This is an property that the real estate
agent was confident in.
By the way, where is that property?
That property is behind you.
This is our mansion.
How is it, Ms Mayama? It's nice.
It's nice.
Ms Mayama's face is shining.
Let's go then.
Okay.
This way.
That way?
They go to a different direction from
the apartment.
It's a smooth ride.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
It's been a while.
Who is that?
Ruke-Heon from Godzilla.
This is Mr. Kameda of Roomcore.
Is this a real estate agency?
Group.
You two look like a real estate agency.
Let's go.
We are guided by Mr. Kameda.
This is a 49-story super luxury
apartment in Shibaura.
I will introduce the top floor room.
It's a room with five stars.
Mr. Kameda, let's go.
I'll let Mr. Mayama touch this.
Thank you.
No, I can't.
What do we do?
Wow!
It's amazing.
It's so nice.
You can stand up in the middle of the
fight.
Really?
Even the camera can do that.
Wow.
Mayama, you're the first one to go.
You're the first one.
Thank you.
You're ready.
Okay, take off your shoes.
Thank you.
Please show us the way to the living
room.
It's a little soft.
Mayama-san, you go first.
I'm getting excited.
Oh my god!
Wow!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
What is this?
This is the perfect trimmed Salami.
Wow!
This is the 26.1-square-meter living
room.
Wow!
Look outside!
Skytree!
Tokyo Tower is in the back.
Wow!
You can see Mt. Fuji over there without
clouds.
Wow!
How is it?
It's great!
This is good!
Everyone's mouth is getting bigger.
That's right!
Hurry up and push it!
How is it, Mama-sama?
It's great! It's really spacious and the
scenery is great!
It's great, right?
Then, let's go to the seal.
Thank you!
It's going to be more interesting.
Of course, it's going to be more
interesting.
It's going to be more interesting.
First, they are going to have a spacious
living dining room.
There is only the top floor, and of
course, the view is also great.
If it's this big, what do you do?
What do you do when you come to play?
Dance practice.
Dance!
Dance practice is good.
Do you want to try dance practice?
Let's dance!
What song are you dancing?
Wait a minute. Why do you use the edge
of the room?
I think we can use this as a mirror.
Oh, really?
You are amazing, Matsuno-sama.
Let's try it from that side.
You can only see the back of the dance
in the shrimp.
You can do this with your hands.
Hide and seek!
I like this, too.
Let's do it!
So, the demon is Kaneda-san.
Here we go.
Ready, go.
Daruma-san fell down.
Oh, good.
One more time.
Daruma-san fell down.
The last one.
Yay, you got it.
You get a half price.
Daruma-san fell down.
Is this how you decide the winner?
I want to show you the next room.
Let's go to the kitchen.
The kitchen is important.
Here we go.
Come on.
I've seen this on TV.
There are four.
Wow.
There is a refrigerator.
Yes, it's perfect.
It's a system kitchen.
The kitchen is a system kitchen made in
Germany that celebrities love.
On the same floor, there is a modern
Japanese-style room with a dragon-shaped
tatami mat.
So, Mayama-sama, do you want to make a
contract?
Let's do it!
I want to come to the living room!
I feel like I've been to the living room
twice.
What should I do?
I feel like it's a waste to decide here.
I see.
What a mesonet type!
When you go to the second floor...
I was curious about this staircase.
Wow!
Awesome!
Wow, it's like a fashionable beach
Where is the beach?
Wow
Yes, this is the beach
Wow, it's huge
You've been making noise since a while
ago
Please look behind you
I was curious about this
This is
Waking club
What did you say?
You pronounced it too much
Waking club
One more time
Wow
Please go inside.
This is the walk-in closet.
This is amazing!
This is a room.
So, Mayama-sama, how was it?
I thought there was something more
important.
What is it?
Bath.
It's different from the bath.
Bath?
Yes, the one with the steamer.
It might be a unit bath.
I see.
What is Mayama-sama's bath?
Excuse me.
What?
The view is amazing!
I can't see anything!
Hurry up!
The view is amazing!
Excuse me!
Wow!
It's so white!
How is it?
Everyone can go in!
Let's watch TV together!
Mayama-sama, if you go in the bath while
looking at this view,
you'll think you've won!
We're the winning team!
That's right!
So, is this decided?
It's decided!
I can't imagine myself living in such a
nice house because it's too good.
Then, let's go to the room below and
talk to everyone.
Then, everyone, please leave.
It'll take some time.
It's an ideal property that goes far
beyond Mayama's conditions.
Will Mayama sign the contract? Or not?
But, the most important thing is the
rent.
It's so good, so why is it so cheap?
By the way, how much is it for everyone?
For example, Kobayashi?
I think it's over 100,000 yen.
That's true.
But, I think it doesn't matter how much
it costs.
Because Mayama was so satisfied.
It's not 10,000 yen.
You can press the button and see.
No, no, no.
I'm a little curious.
Kamen Rider, I want to know the answer.
Can I see the answer of Yachi?
Yes, I understand.
This is Yachi's answer.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
It's wrong.
It's 42.
Congratulations.
It's a lie.
Hanko! Hanko!
Hanko!
Do you push it or not?
Please!
What will happen?
Please! Please! Please!
I'm sorry!
I can't pay this much
You can do it
I can't
Ok, so the third one was also a no
I don't know if you didn't get this one
I think it's good
I think it's a little expensive
Yeah, I'm a middle school student
I see, then I'll introduce you to a
reasonable property that even middle
school students can afford
The next property is this
Vintage Mansion recommended for
entertainers
Vintage Mansion is also popular
It's popular now
What is Vintage Mansion?
It's really recommended for entertainers
Let's go to the property
Yes
They move to Sasazuka, which is close to
Shinjuku
Mayama-sama, the next property is a
vintage mansion recommended for
entertainers
I'm curious about vintage mansions
The next property is over there
Is it in the back?
Yes, it is
It's big
It's like a normal Japanese house
It's a vintage mansion, so it's been
around for 40 years
40 years?
It's a vintage mansion that reminds you
of the old days
It's a pretty vintage mansion
It's a popular vintage mansion that you
can easily access in Tokyo
There are already celebrities living
here
For security reasons, I and Mayama-sama
will be the only ones to go
Please wait here
It's cold
Mayama and Chuu-ei will leave Takeue and
the other members behind to see the
property
It's nice. How is it?
Whose shoes are these?
It's nice. It's all vintage
Mayama-san, this is the room you want to
show us
Can you open it?
What will happen to Mayama?
Mayama came to a vintage apartment that
is recommended for celebrities.
It's a vintage apartment.
Mayama, this is the room you want to
introduce.
May I open the door?
May I come in?
Who is it?
What's wrong?
There's someone here.
It's Nammei.
Who is it?
It's my...
There's someone here.
Let's go in.
Please come in.
Is it okay to go in?
It's around here.
Is there a door?
It's a little far from here.
Is that so?
The person in the room is a junior
comedian from Chu-way.
Who is Gold George?
They are leaving this room, which is one
floor above the ground floor.
They are looking for a new tenant.
This is a trendy vintage house.
I'm confused by the word vintage.
Vintage is a place like this.
I haven't seen a dirt wall in a long
time.
It's a dirt wall.
I like this dirt wall.
It's rough when you touch it.
It's rough.
Why are you leaving?
I'm having a hard time with the rent.
I see.
I'm trying not to work part-time.
If I don't work, I can't afford the
rent.
How much is the rent?
20,000 yen.
How is it?
Do you want to sell it?
I'll sit down.
I don't want to give you anything.
What is it?
It's a great property.
Do you leave the refrigerator?
I leave the refrigerator.
Do you want water?
Thank you.
Do you want a potato?
I've never seen such a colored water.
Is this water that no one has ever
drunk?
That's right.
It's a crime.
I want to hear more points.
I see.
Please subscribe to my channel.
He shows his innocadoence even here.
The diving ins when he actually lives
Nise Know Negative
There are two toilets
I see
Because you are a girl
I think it's better to have separate
bathroom and toilet
Separate?
It's quite far away
Really?
It's very different
How is it?
Do you want to eat it?
No, I'm fine
I'm not sure
Nami is the ultimate appeal point for
Mayama
I forgot to tell you this
What?
I think I have something
The owner is a very nice person
I'm relieved to have an owner
I'm relieved
And I don't charge a single yen for food
What?
What do you mean?
All three meals have rice
Why?
The owner made it for me
What?
I'm surprised
Really?
Sorry, I didn't mean to.
Only the chosen one can use the
bathroom.
It's not here, but I said it's separate.
What do you mean by chosen one?
If the owner likes it?
Yes, if the owner likes it.
This is a deal.
Is it?
This is the best property I've ever
seen.
This is a little expensive in Tokyo.
It's quite reasonable.
Do you have any questions?
In this place.
Kitchen?
The owner has already made it.
Can I make it myself?
The owner's kitchen is very large.
I see.
I'm curious about the owner.
One more step to the contract.
She will introduce the owner who lives
in the room.
Someone is here.
Excuse me.
There are many people.
No, no, no.
Excuse me.
What?
There is someone.
Nice to meet you.
We were shot by the camera.
Sorry.
Actually.
It's cold, so come inside.
Hello.
The owner who noticed the person who was
outside was inviting us to his house.
Thank you for having us.
Come and eat anytime.
Thank you for the meal.
By the way,
this idol group called BABYCHU,
is one of the members.
I'm sorry, my name is Mayama.
I'm a grandmother from Kitazan, so nice
to meet you.
I think she's decided.
She's going to be accepted.
She's really into it.
By the way, do you have girls living
here?
No, we don't have any girls.
You don't have any?
Is it just one?
Yes, just one.
The owner is very kind to the tenant.
But only men live here.
Why is that?
I have two daughters and two
granddaughters.
I don't have any children.
I didn't have any children.
I only have my own siblings.
Anyway, the owner is kind to the tenant.
It's a miracle.
But if the owner doesn't accept her,
it's difficult to get in.
Will Mayama like it?
So, if Mayama lives here,
can I borrow her bathroom?
I'll lend it to you.
That's rare.
Basically, women are not allowed.
That's right.
It's a very rare thing.
That's surprising.
By the way,
can you make three meals for Mayama?
I can make anything.
Wow.
I'm glad.
You're the best.
Can you say, grandma?
I love kids.
Really?
How many can you say?
I can.
You're too small.
I thought you were going to quit, but
you're so happy.
This is no good.
This is a game, right?
You don't have to live in Mayama
anymore.
It's a game, right?
Oya-san, Oya-san, Oya-san
Who?
Who? Why? Why are you doing that?
Who are you?
What do you think, Mayama-sama?
There's no other place where you can eat
this much
That's right
Right?
What should I do?
How about the other members?
Come here and try it
It's really delicious
I'm happy
That's right
I'm going to eat it
At this timing
It's delicious
It's delicious, right?
I can eat this all the time
That's good
Mayama couldn't hide her confusion when
she saw the room of the slug
But she met a wonderful Oya-san
Her heart moved at once to realize
living alone
Will it finally be a contract?
Mayama-sama, please give us a half-
boiled egg, a sugar, and a salad
I'll do it
Will she?
To be continued
Case closed!
I'm selfish.
You don't have to borrow it, so come and
play.
Let's go.
Everyone is leaving.
This is...
I'm nervous.
We will continue to look for Mayama's
property at the Chuei Budo.
This is the first step.
Until we find the property you want.
We only eat rice.
I'm doing it now.
We are more peaceful here.
Let's go find it.
Mayama, let's go.
Let's go to Part 2.
Let's go to find Mayama.
Where do you want to go?
Can you say, see you next week?
See you next week?
Say it in front of the camera.
See you next week.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Next episode
Finally
Ebichu Tastasu 100th episode
Ebichu Tastasu 100th episode special
30 minutes of fun
Obanburumai Goka Shouhin Renpatsu
I'm not listening!