YAKANT IDOL!
It's a fast ending!
Please let us know!
The Rino-kuni Thank You Festival, which
was held in Akita, Chiritsu, Ebisu, and
Akita branch, will be held on November
26th at the Akita Art Theater Miruhasu
Daihou.
And there are more.
There will be two days of live
performances at the Makuhari Messe event
hall.
On December 16th, there will be a
graduation ceremony for Hina Hashiaki
and Smile for You.
And on December 17th, there will be a
new style university art festival, Learn
in Our Ebisu Family.
And on January 14th, 2023, we will be
performing at the TsutaPla Idol Festival
in Yokohama Arena.
There will be a lot of live
performances, so please come and have
fun!
I see.
How many years has it been since you
last went to Akita?
I wonder why we went there.
It's amazing.
The people of Akita are very happy.
Maybe Akita is more famous than Tokyo.
That's not true.
It's weird to say that's not true.
Akita's station is very famous for
shrimp chou.
That's right.
It's famous for its view.
So when I go to Akita for a location,
people say,
Oh, shrimp chou!
But in Tokyo, it's not like that.
That's not true.
When did you become so self-centered?
But people of Akita are really happy.
Thank you very much.
They said they were happy to see us
every time.
So please look forward to it.
And finally, there's the graduation
ceremony for KASHIHAGI.
Do you have any memories of graduation?
I'm sad.
I talked about it in detail.
Did you?
I ate grilled meat and French fries
while saying,
Why do you quit?
That's nice.
With all the big sister groups.
We've been together since we were
little.
No, no, no.
This is probably a new shape from the
next day.
Is that what it means?
I graduated from KASHIHAGI and became a
shrimp chou for 10 people.
And next year, January 14th,
It's called the Star Pla Idol Fest.
I got to do it with the Japanese prince
at Star Pla.
Maybe this time, the group.
The group's victory.
Was it better not to tell you now?
You're announcing it, aren't you?
I've been hearing a lot from Rika.
Oh, really?
It's like a sports day.
You can't eat spicy food.
You should have a competition for Mirei.
Oh, should I have her compete?
It's a quick victory.
I don't know.
Reni-chan, Reni-chan.
This is a fake, Takagi-san.
You can do it.
You can still do that.
What else is Mirei good at?
I wonder...
I think she's good at running.
I think so too.
She's good at running.
Yes, she's fast.
I want to do a race.
I'm making a race between a race and
spicy food.
I'm going to run in the middle and eat
Nakamoto.
Nakamoto, with all your strength.
I want you to come.
Let's go.
By all means.
I'm looking forward to it.
Now, I'm going to pray for your success.
I'd like to give you a cup of tea that
will cheer you up.
Is that okay?
Yes.
You're an artist after all.
A blend that will cheer up your throat.
Herb tea bag.
Do you usually drink tea?
I love tea.
Really?
Yes.
Then I'll do it.
Will it make you feel better?
Yes, it will cheer up your throat.
I'm having a blend today.
Thank you for your cooperation.
It's delicious.
I'm glad.
I thought you were going to make a
bitter taste.
No, no.
I've been in Stardust for too long, so
it's getting weird.
I was surprised. I thought it would be
delicious at first, but it's delicious
later.
Thank you very much.
It was good.
Stardust was kind.
That's right.
Thank you very much for today.
Thank you very much.
It was good.
It was fun.
I was happy to see different sides of
you. Thank you very much.
Finally, can I ask you one more thing?
Could you say something cute to the
camera and close it?
Let's go eat spicy food from the drama.
Thank you very much.
This program was brought to you by...
Dark-san
Taka-san
Hacchan-san
Kahikahihiko-san
and Tatsu-san.
Thank you very much.