Ebichu's videos
Ebichu Table Tennis Tournament!
The winner is...
Number 3, Mayuma Rika.
Number 5, Asumoto Ayaka.
Congratulations!
Please watch.
I'm nervous.
This is difficult.
Which one is better?
After the game, Misaki finished quickly.
You should make Ayaka bounce.
I can't tell if you are focusing on me.
See you next time!
Pink team Win
Round2
Result
I'm most fortunate, by milk
Yes
Unlucky, by hate
Let's start
Seana, one mini Lose
Champion candidate
Koshirani
Black team Taikyo
We win
Oh my god!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'll start.
You're good at it.
You're good.
It was like a table tennis.
I couldn't break it.
You can do it.
Thank you for watching.
Wait a minute, even in this challenging
situation if I surpassed you, I wouldn't
have been able to do it.
I wish they have these nuclear combo or
this kind of shape
The result
I'm Kobayashi Kaku, the 11th.
I'm Nagayama Riko, the 12th.
I'm the 2nd.
The 2nd is Nagayama Riko.
The 3rd is Nagayama Riko.
It's not a bad thing.
You don't have to take that.
Riko is also a good girl.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Here I go.
Wow!
Imakei wins!
Another go?
What!?
Ah, yikes!
Aaaah!
Thank you for watching!
To be continued
Why are you sneaky?
On another day…
I irritate.
That's confusing.
Are you talking about my serve?
That's team Karma.
CSMarusive from Team South America.
We never receive angry calls from our
viewers.
To be honourable,
she lost a set.
I lost twice!
I am upset.
Please subscribe to my channel!
To be continued
I can't see...
Say cheese!
Thank you for watching!
Oh!
You're out of pose!
I'm sorry.
Ha!
Oh!
You're not good at it.
Ha!
Oh!
Isn't it over?
Thank you very much.
Match point.
!
Shopping
Bye bye!
If you're a slow starter, you can't win.
Yes!
Oh!
Which one?
Yes!
I'm scared!
Ah!
Yes!
Oh!
I'm scared.
I can't breathe.
My right eye...
Oh!
I'm scared.
I can't do it.
Thank you.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Please try
I'm sorry.
What's the point?
Thank you for watching.
Calm down!
I am calm!
I will do it with a punch.
Let's do it twice.
OK.
I want to do it with a punch.
Punch!
I will do it with a punch.
I made a mistake.
I hit the ball first.
I finally hit the ball.
I didn't hit the ball.
I'm sorry.
I will do it with a punch.
I hit the ball.
I didn't hit the ball.
To be continued.
Let's start.
I don't need your YATTA~!
Hana-chan, 1 point!
No need to stop the clock!
Really??
Fill in the blanks!
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
I'm going to do my best.
Please subscribe to my channel.
stabilize
Oh no!
I'm going to die!
Both of them looked like they're at full
profile.
OMGłe
Thank you for watching!
Ainu, your turn!
Wait!
Hi!
Oh goes the bucket too!
Ready?
I'm not good at this.
You are doing it with the same hand.
You are good at this.
I'm not good at this.
Please subscribe to this channel.
γ
To be continued
Oh, wow!
Like this?
Oh!
Oh, I see.
I see.
1, 2, 3!
Oh!
Oh, no!
3, 4!
Ha!
Oh!
Oh, no!
Ah!
Far traditions from the present,
сор actually have many traditional
thoughts too,
and seems the way not to do the
traditional directions is just a tired,
they might feel to do even harder than
Local culture and the point is
My name is...
Nooooooooo
My name is...
Thank you so much!
Let's see how well they do!
Oh!
I'll do it!
Okay, so if I'm not pounding on here
like this.
What's gonna happen?
Go to the next one!
LMAO
MODERN HANDS
So they will regret.
A win shop is...
Please subscribe!