Ebichu's video
Kawaii Kono Oogiri-chi training
What was the last thing you did?
Ebichu Tastas
I often do Oogiri
At that time, I was playing together
with the picture
I was born in the year of the dog
I was really heavy
I was really tired
What was the last thing you did?
Mayama today is fake.
Yes.
Why do you think so?
Mayama in the past is different from
now.
Because I dressed up.
Mayama now is like Bob.
It's similar.
Wait, wait.
It may be the same as high school
students.
Mayama in the past is different from
now.
It's like this.
Let's change it.
Yes.
How is it?
Why is it fake?
Mayama is 180cm tall.
It's like a high school student's boot.
Mayama is Rika.
Shin-san is Rika.
It's fake.
What is this?
Wait.
What are you trying to write?
The next question.
What is the next question?
What is it?
Is it true?
It's your father.
You laughed at the same time.
No.
I laughed at the same time.
Shoryu.
You are good at it.
I don't want to do it anymore.
Let's go to the next question.
What is the next question?
What?
What is this?
Which one?
What is it?
Foundation.
I'm scared.
I'm still going to do it.
What is it?
Pink.
You're using a lot of paper.
What do you have?
I'm sorry.
Is your house pink too?
You're laughing at me.
I'm scared.
I'm not confident.
Is it Hina's Twitter?
What are you whispering?
I'm whispering.
I don't know.
I'm scared of the live ham.
What do you think?
What is the number of times you have
been on a date?
I have been on a date 13 times.
I'm scared.
I'm not going to reveal it.
I'm going to reveal it to myself.
I'm going to be a serious解釈者.
I'm scared to buy a hamster.
I can still do it.
I'm already tired.
I can't run away.
I'm thinking.
What's this?
This is not delicious.
cut
I'm sorry.
I made a small hamster.
I was born with it.
What is your favorite food?
Think about it yourself.
Kazumi?
It's not a cucumber.
It's a suggestion.
What? Original Gyoza?
Original Gyoza?
Is it a seed?
Seeds are a seed.
Gyoza that makes you insincere.
She's very serious.
She's a little insincere.
I'm a little different from what I
thought.
Let's crush the seeds with a stick.
Let's put it in a jar and crush it with
a stick.
Let's put it in the oil at the end.
She's very serious.
It's a suggestion.
Two more questions.
Is that all?
Five more questions.
Let's go.
What is your favorite food?
It's a zombie.
But she's an idol.
It's a suggestion.
Zombie.
The pose of her appearance is a zombie.
This is it.
What about the idol?
You are an idol.
You are a good idol.
I'm scared of her face, but her legs are
very beautiful.
She is very beautiful.
Thank you for watching.
This is when Kashiwagi-san was at home.
He brought a cell phone instead of a
mid-term tent.
I think so.
The person who uses the construction
site.
That's Ryosuke.
Kiro-chan, Kiro-chan.
The person who is the most surprised.
I'll ask you if I can scare you.
I thought the same thing.
I'm really sorry after I scare you.
He's a really kind person.
He's a good person.
He's not a scary person.
The person who is the most surprised.
I don't know.
The tail of a shrimp.
What?
What are you doing?
The sense of
I don't know.
I forgot the feeling.
Don't forget.
I don't know what's in the ceiling.
I'm wrong.
I'll read it.
Kashiwagi-san's shoes.
It's a component.
The second-class of the factory.
The person who is the most surprised.
What are you not saying?
What Nakayama-san doesn't say?
Choriiiis.
This year's goal is to be sexy.
Don't say it.
I'm scared to slip for a week.
That's the scariest thing.
It's only two minutes, right?
I'm scared of sliding for two minutes.
And then on Sunday, I'm going to be...
No, no, no!
That's YouTube!
I'm scared!
Really.
Like, PANTAWO!
Yeah, like that.
I don't know if it's America or
something,
but I've heard it in foreign comedy
dramas.
Like, oh!
PANTAWO!
I'm sure you've heard it a lot.
I've heard it a lot.
Let's hear it.
I'm sure you've heard it a lot.
Oh!
Let's hear it.
That's the funniest thing.
That's the best answer I've heard so
far.
What's the best answer you've heard so
far?
I don't know.
I want you to point it out.
Let me point it out.
I think there are people who can answer
other people's questions.
I think it's okay.
I think the members are the first time.
Maybe the second time.
I think so.
I don't know if there are.
Please look forward to the second
episode!