Happy New Year!
We are Shiritori Bishuaku.
Please watch the video of the shrimp in
2022.
The first video of the new year is...
What do you think we will do?
What?
We will do KARTATOMI.
We are the first-class shrimp in 2020.
The first video of the new year is...
I'm KASAMI YANAKA, number 55.
I draw.
I'm a rapper.
I'm HIKACHAN.
Thank you for always.
What?
Who?
I draw.
I'm HIKACHAN.
Thank you for always.
I draw.
I drew.
It's difficult to draw because it's hard
to see.
I'm done.
I draw.
I'm a shrimp that shines more and more
on the 10th anniversary.
I will show you the age of the nine
shrimp that has evolved more since the
age of the six shrimp.
I'm done.
What is your number?
I'm number 14, KUBO INO.
I draw.
I'll draw a card.
The first one.
The yaki udon is delicious.
I like yaki udon with a lot of cabbage.
The illustration is complete.
The letter is complete.
It's Y.
It's Yuno.
I can't say it.
The baby of Wanko is Kee.
It's Woka.
White is different from anything.
I'm done.
I made it special.
This is the illustration of all members.
It's done.
I'm Sakura Yoko.
I'll draw a card.
The yaki udon is delicious.
I like to eat yaki udon, but I'm not
good at drawing pictures.
I'll do my best while watching the yaki
udon.
I'll draw a card.
It's delicious.
Let's eat delicious food.
What is delicious food?
It's rice balls.
It's delicious.
Thank you for your viewing.
Next, I draw eyes.
What is this?
It looks like Jin-chan.
This is a
eye-catching eye.
I did it.
I'm Kayamoniko, number 12.
I'm going to change.
I'm a tooth fairy.
First, teeth.
I have a tooth paste on my chin.
It's itchy.
It's the story from before.
What should I do?
Left ear? No, right ear.
Is this okay?
Something grew.
It's swollen.
Nakayama's nose is swollen.
Help me.
Is it okay?
It's okay.
I don't give presents to fans.
I was bad at it.
Last, Hoshina-san.
Hoshina-san, you are cute.
I drew it.
I'm YOSHIKO FU, number 51.
I draw a picture of my family.
I'm NAGYO.
I draw from NA.
I draw from BUN.
I haven't used a lipstick in a long
time.
Next, the other side.
Amazing.
I'm sorry.
No
What is No?
I finished drawing NANINUNE.
I'm the 10th member of the group.
I draw this.
I'm going to draw a fish.
I draw a fish.
I'm done!
My number is lucky 7 star Nami Rei.
I will draw a card.
This is a work.
I draw a picture.
I made a mistake.
I couldn't draw a picture of this code.
I can't draw Nakano-san's picture.
Small
How small
I think so
What about the last day?
Correct
All correct
OK
I did
I finished
I'm YASUMO TAYAKA, the 5th seat number
I'm going to write
I don't know the mic
OK, I'll write
I'm not feeling good
My memory of KARUTA
When I was in elementary school, I was
in the top 100
I was different from KARUTA
I had to check and memorize
I had to remember hard
I completely forgot
It's a waste
I remembered
I think there are many schools like that
Everyone said
Like this
I don't know
I only wrote something that didn't make
sense, but it's okay.
I really feel like there is a culture
like this.
Yes, it's done.
I'm Marika, number 30,000.
I will write.
I'll write the name of the sea first.
I'm worried about how much I drink.
It's dangerous.
I see Yua's feet there.
I'm worried about how much I drink.
I'm worried about my friend.
I'm worried about my girlfriend.
I made it.
While I was working hard on Ebichu, I
made a picture that was conscious of the
composition.
It's a masterpiece.
I'll draw Mirei's legs neatly.
I'm always watching.
Oh, it's dangerous. Mirei's legs are
there.
What is the most dangerous thing about
Ebichu's school? Mirei's legs are too
long.
I have to jump over it.
I greet you with a loud voice.
It's done.
This is my super-powerful work.
I hope the members will take this.
Please look forward to the next.
This is unique.
We drew our own characters.
I think I know who drew what.
Hoshina's shoulders are wide.
I think so.
You can draw one shoulder.
What does San do?
San?
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm curious.
I'll try.
You don't have to draw one more.
You remember it.
I remember.
I'll draw one more.
This is serious.
What is the prize?
The person who gets the most will get
something.
I know.
Let's start.
Ready?
Let's start!