What was the worst thing?
The worst thing was...
When I said I was sorry to him.
I'm really sorry about that time.
I'm sorry.
I pretended not to see it, but I did.
I pretended to understand and cried.
The first time I met her was at the
audition.
Kano Sei, please.
Sei passed the back-to-back audition in
2022.
Every day is a new experience.
I'm motivated every day.
That's good.
Before the audition,
did you work with other idols?
Yes, I did.
How long did you work with them?
I think I worked with them for about a
year.
I did other activities, too.
How was the training camp for WAKKU in
2022?
It was harder than I thought.
Was there anything difficult?
I had to work with the candidates
from the beginning.
I had to work on the performance.
I had to work on things that didn't fit.
What was the hardest time for you?
The hardest time was...
the fourth day?
I didn't know what to do.
I had to work with NEO and Tsuyogari.
The ranking was falling.
I thought I might not make it.
I had to change, but I couldn't.
I was worried about my performance.
What was the hardest time for you?
I'm Tantan.
I'm Yua Okita.
I'm Leo Tres.
I'm Bernardo.
Thank you for watching!
When you were about to take the training
camp,
you said you quit your previous agency.
Is there something like that?
I had the feeling that I would do
anything.
So I think I took a step forward
to something I had never done before.
As soon as you joined,
you released your new song, Signal.
It was your first time writing lyrics
for all of your songs.
Was it hard?
It was hard.
I had never written lyrics before,
so I didn't know what to write.
When I first released it,
I thought it was different.
I remember I was like,
I'm sorry.
You joined WAKKA and became very busy.
I think your life has changed a lot.
Is there anything you're not satisfied
with?
Not satisfied?
I'm not that satisfied.
Not really.
I was really busy in August.
Did you go out to play?
Sometimes.
I went out to play.
You went there.
Why did you go there?
What?
I don't know.
What is this?
I'm busy and I think it's a waste to
sleep.
You are a energetic type.
I want to go to a little gap.
I can't go to all the places.
I didn't know that.
Did you go to the toilet?
I went with my friend.
How was it?
I want to throw up a little more.
No, I've thrown up enough.
I don't use it, do I?
That would be great.
The interview was a lie.
Is that so?
It's a prank.
Prank?
Yes.
I'm surprised. What do you mean?
I'm wondering how many P's I can earn.
I was surprised that you would ask such
a question.
I was surprised.
You said something that I would ask.
I had to answer all the questions.
The channel that shows that peak is
amazing.
Certainly.
I'm surprised by your smile.
I pretended not to hear, even though I
did
I pretended to be stupid and gave up
I pretended not to see