This was our response to the video.
Ayaka, Hinata, Kaho, Riko, Mirei, Rika
100 times of the original
The first song of the day
The second song of the day
This time, I will show you the secret of
singing during the debut
The secret of singing during the debut
Please look forward to the next.
Let's start the first week of the debut.
What is the lesson for this day?
I explained yesterday.
The part where the voice is made.
There is a part called the biron biron
here.
What was it called?
Voice training by Nishiyama Emiko, who
also participated in the audition
training of the new members.
This is the vocal cords.
When you breathe, you open it like this.
When you exhale, you blow air into the
vocal cords.
So, remember the system that you must
not stick to the vocal cords unless you
blow air.
Ms. Emiko has been in charge of the
singing and dancing of Ebichu since 7
years ago when Kahoriko joined.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
She is a very fun and funky lady.
With a method with both theoretical and
scientific background,
she has supported Ebichu's singing from
the shadows.
The tone of the voice, the sound of the
voice.
What kind of voice do you remember?
Real voice.
Yes, real voice.
What is the kanji?
The voice of the green.
Yes, that's right.
The voice with the green in real life.
Ready, go.
For the three new members,
she is carefully guiding them from how
to make the voice.
The relationship between the voice and
the voice.
You just said, huh?
What was the expression for the voice?
H, A.
Which is the character of the voice?
H.
What was the role of the voice?
The voice is air.
If you don't make the air, the voice
won't be good.
It won't be real.
Let's practice singing the C.
Let's practice.
One, two, three, go.
Ready, go.
A, ya, hi, na, ka, ho, ri, ko, ri, re,
ri, ka.
Do you understand?
Without the C, the words won't be
connected.
A, ya, hi, na, ka, ho, ri, ka.
Ri, ko, mi, re, i, ri, ka.
100 times faster.
1, 2, 3, 4.
A, ya, ka, hi, na, ka, ho, ri, ko, mi,
re, i, ri, ka.
One more time.
Looking at the island.
1, 2, 3.
A, ya, ka, hi, na, ka, ho, ri, ko, mi,
re, i, ri, ka.
To make a voice, they move their bodies.
Everyone, let's have fun!
Let's go!
Aya, ka, bisante! Bye!
This is the end of the warm-up.
After the warm-up, they check the
iper andelyantysport show.
And then, yesterday, we talked about
making a face, but our faces are
different.
No, not our faces. Our mouths are small,
so we can't look like we're singing.
We have to open our mouths more, so we
can't look like we're singing.
Of course, the singing voice is
important.
In the debut, they are an idol group.
They have to be aware of how they look
on stage.
And then...
That's right
You're too bright
What are you looking at, Yuno?
You're not looking there
You're looking here
When Yuno sings,
Am casting that prelude, we notice
calling him 가냥 나
Majura Yeseba, absolutely editor
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for your hard work
Nono, please bring the mic
During the audition training camp
Nono's voice is amazing
She can sing
Nono's senior member praised her singing
voice
She struggled a little here
I don't want to reveal the true nature
of everyone
But everyone
I'm not doing this with the microphone
I think I have to bring the microphone
here
1,2,3,4
But everyone is really
I'm not doing this with the microphone
Let's do it a little bit more.
I'll do it completely.
I'll put everything on my feet.
She can sing beautifully,
but she doesn't have the desire to do
so.
She's not good enough to show her
accent.
I'll do it again.
I'll do it like this.
Thank you.
And
I heard that there is a singing test, so
I don't sing
I was talking about the fact that I was
not good at singing at the camp.
そうだね。で、こう。
そうで、もっと。で、こう。
とか、いい。もっと歌ってみよう。
それぐらい。
ケイのシーンが出ると、めっちゃ歌ってエモーションに聞こえてくるのね。
から、
特に、木とかめっちゃ出してるし、
地下付きたいよりも。
地下付きたいってなると、なんか大人っぽい歌い方になるっていうか、アーティスティッ
クで歌えるようになるから、
地下付きたいよりも。
つかづきたいぐらい。めっちゃ新出した。
それぐらい。
こうでさ、この
ここで歌い終わるまでずっと顔をつくって、ずっと顔を残していて。
I want to get closer to you
That's right, like this
That's about right
I'll start from the middle of the first
line
The teachers are conscious of the parts
they pointed out and once again
The first line is the most beautiful
Please teach me
I want to get closer to you
That's right. You can leave it like
that.
You can leave it completely.
Leave it like that.
Then, you can make a loud voice.
That's good.
As they continue their lessons,
they are able to see the challenges of
the three of them for their first live
performance.
Okay, now set your stage.
Have a set of officer's
Then add to all your practice.
Make S feature the whole song.
Make a set of officer's
Then add to all your practice.
So, you know something will happen.
Make a S feature bottle-like one.
You can't change the eye looks.
Otherwise, you can't be famous with your
songs.
You will get nervous,
and you'll never change because of eye
looks.
You can practice and work.
You can lift this part a little more
If you don't lift this part, the back of
your mouth won't open
Because your voice is here, it will
become a cute voice
So practice opening your mouth wide
That's what you should do at home
Thank you for your help
After the lesson, the three of them
I can't see
I don't know where I'm looking at
I'm nervous
It's difficult
I can't sing well
T, K and S
I'll do my best
Kokona, who pointed out the way of
singing like a child
I was a baby
I can't stand up
I can't do the same thing as a cat
It's difficult to do it like this
I want to raise the number of songs that
are called by Ms. Emiko Masa and sing it
like an adult
Next time, continuing the lesson every
day like this
I want to seduce you
First time to infiltrate the recording
studio
Next time, I will do it like this
I want to seduce you