I have the feeling that I can do
anything.
I have never done anything before, so I
think I took a step forward.
I pretended to understand and cried.
Today, I'm going to look back on the
BAKURO interview with the 12th year
members who finished the interview.
First of all, Yuki.
I went to the factory after working
part-time at a chicken restaurant.
I opened frozen food and packed it in
various ways.
I was doing a daytime bike for frozen
food.
I knew it.
I was doing it like that.
What kind of day was it?
We all got together at 8 o'clock in the
morning and we all went to the bus
together.
Since then, I've only had the least
contact with the people around me.
I often stay at the side of the music
room.
I've been Miki since then.
That's right.
I see.
Who did you interview next?
I interviewed Yua of YUME.
I was filmed by a camera in the MV of
PRETTY PRETTY GOOD.
There was an incident while I was
moving.
I lost contact with the people around
me.
I was too high up to tell anyone.
I lost contact with the people around me
in the music video of PPG.
I'm sorry.
You were talking about your part-time
job, right?
Yes, I was.
I was working normally.
Were you involved with people around
you?
Yes, I was.
I thought you were not a person who
likes to be involved with people.
I thought you were a friendly person.
I don't hate it.
I was scared of you at first.
But now I'm scared because you're coming
to me.
But even if I go to the gym, I don't
touch you.
I choose you.
I'm still in the gym.
At that time, I thought it was
impossible for me to be involved with
MAIKA.
What kind of character was MAIKA when
she was in the game?
What kind of character was it?
She was a cat.
She was wearing about 500 cats.
In the past video, she had long bangs.
That's exactly what I thought.
She had long bangs and had black hair.
I thought I might be sexy in a few
years.
That's impossible.
I've been in a lot of groups since then.
We had a lot of fights.
We fought.
What did you fight about?
With her.
We fought at arm's length.
No, I cried and came out.
You didn't cry.
You were crying.
I cried in the bathroom.
I cried.
I was a sweet character.
I cried in the middle of the room.
I had a lot of such scenes.
What is MAIKA's personality?
I can't tell you that.
I'm going to get a cramp.
You don't have to tell me.
It's okay.
I don't need to tell you that.
Please tell me.
I really don't need to tell you.
I have black hair.
Please tell me that.
What?
I don't know.
I was scared when I saw your interview.
I'm not hiding it.
I happened to be the most.
I'm not that loud.
I'm not.
I've only been hiding and taxing.
I've only been taxing.
I've been taxing a lot.
I've been using it a lot.
I don't have any savings.
I don't think your interview is funny.
I'm honest.
I've been in a taxi a lot.
I can't help it.
I'm not in a taxi anymore.
I don't want to be in a taxi anymore.
I was told by a man to show me around.
I was told to show you around.
I talked to him.
I thought he was a little bit of a
pervert.
I was told that I was a little bit of a
I think I've been working with you for a
week.
I like you.
I'm always like that.
I'm sorry.
I'm often told that.
You're the type of person who's allowed
to like me.
I'm not allowed to like you.
We have a switch.
What is it?
It's hot, isn't it?
That's...
It's hard.
That's a little...
How should I put it?
That's the reality.
I think it's more poisonous than me.
Certainly.
I'll tell you what's left to see.
My favorite scene on the first episode
of the interview is...
That's the current music video.
I was like, was that a
strong one?
When I heard that, I was like, what is
this guy?
I don't think it's strong.
That music video was very strong.
Everyone was so tired that they didn't
scratch.
I didn't think it was that strong in the
first place.
I don't know what it is.
I don't think it's strong.
I don't use it with anyone.
It's my privacy.
I don't think I can use this part.
Really.
No, I can't.
I was asked by DOKU what she was talking
about.
I was surprised.
I was surprised, too.
I didn't know because I was DOKUSON.
I'm always crazy.
I was curious about one thing.
She was a good girl at school.
I don't get along with anyone.
But I have a good group photo.
I'm sure you have a good group photo.
I'm sure you're in the middle of a cute
girl group.
I was always scared of DOKUSON.
I'm sure.
I'm scared of YUA.
I was scared, but she was kind.
I heard that there was no member who was
bad at getting along with her.
I was wondering what to do because she
wasn't there.
I was wondering how she was scared.
She was worried about me.
I was worried about her because she was
in a good mood.
She is the most scary member.
I don't have a favorite member, but I
don't want to be an enemy.
That's right.
I think the finger pointing is real.
I'm very strong-minded when I'm on the
side.
It's okay. We're all on the side.
That's right.
I was told I could do whatever I wanted.
I thought I'd try something different.
This is the only time.
If you're in an interview, you don't ask
an idol about their love.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Non was a little bit of a P, but she
said you were good at interviews.
I was told that I was really good at it.
How was it for you?
I think I can take this.
Non was a little bit of a P, but she
said you were good at it.
How was it for you?
I was told that I was really good at it.
I learned a lot.
How was it?
I want to do better.
You're already good at it.
You don't use it, do you?
Bye.
Please subscribe to my channel.
The answer is almost P.
I thought I had to answer this.
I thought this was a wack.
I thought so.
I was asked a lot of questions.
I was told to say everything.
I had to say it.
It was like a opening.
We've been looking back at a long
history.
We've been looking back at a lot of
things.
We're going to have a gang parade on
January 1st.
Did that have anything to do with this
interview?
There is.
Why?
We're going to have a gang parade
memorial live on January 1st.
We've been looking back at the history
of the gang parade.
It was a song from the past.
It's a recent song.
We're going to have a live that will
lead to the future of the gang parade.
Oh, that's what it was like.
How can we do that?
That's a good question.
This is the priority of the gang parade
major force single released on November
16th.
What is it?
This is a priority ticket.
Priority ticket?
Wait, I didn't have this in the one I
bought.
Me too.
This is a random priority ticket for
those who got this CD.
What can you do with that?
What?
I can do it.
Is there a good thing?
I don't know.
What is the priority ticket?
Is it a song?
If you have this priority ticket, you
can participate in the lottery of the
gang parade on January 1st.
You can enter the QR code of this
priority ticket and win the lottery.
You can participate in the gang parade
on January 1st.
If you win the lottery, you can get
200,000 yen.
I can't afford it.
If you win the lottery, you can
participate in the gang parade on
January 1st.
What?
You can enter the gang parade on January
1st.
I think it's a good thing.
It's easy.
It's a random priority ticket, but it's
a 5-hour song.
It's a 5-hour song.
The history of the gang parade is not
short.
We want to make a live with future
players while looking back on the
history of the gang parade.
From the past songs to the latest songs,
and maybe new songs.
But there are only three people.
That's right.
We will hold a gang parade memorial live
on January 1st.
That's great.
I was invited to the gang parade on
January 1st.
Thank you.
Please get this priority ticket and
apply.
Thank you for waiting.