Ebichu Lucky Girl Grand Prix
This week's Ebichu Tastas is the second
half of the Un-Dame Championship, where
the members will be chosen by luck.
However,
It tastes just like it smells.
After eating a strong-characterized
dish,
A baby is born to the members.
What is this?
Why?
I can't stay still
100 times more frustrating emotions
I'm so crazy about you
What should I do with my heart?
Moratorium Moratorium Moratorium
Middle school student
Add various things to private Ebisu
middle school
Ebisu middle school
What is this?
This program is provided by the sponsor
you are watching
Well, the name is
Saori-chan
Who will be the luckiest person in
Ebichu?
In the second half, you will play
various games that only rely on luck.
And in the end, you will compete in
survival mode to see who survives.
Tonight, the number one luck will be
decided!
Unbekastore Ebichu Lucky Girl Grand
Prix!
You can do it if you are like this
We will have you do various luck tests
If you are unlucky, you will be
eliminated
The person who is left in the end will
be the luckiest
And will be the winner
It's an elimination method
So everyone, please look over there
There is sushi
So the first round is
Who can't eat sushi?
Is it a food sample?
What do you think?
But what I want you to look at is
There are 8 people
Why?
Everyone, please sit in your favorite
seats
Is it okay?
It's luck from here
Without knowing what will happen
The luck test starts quietly
That's right
Please sit
Then I'll sit here
What?
It's luck
Is it okay?
Why did everyone sit in that seat?
The chair was beautiful
It's a good thing
The feeling of standing up
I think it's the most difficult
It's the most difficult
On the contrary, there was a reason why
you sat here
Oh, Nakayama, what's wrong?
I always believe in this position at the
end
Believe in this
That's good
That's true
I have an image of the end
So
What? I'm scared
What?
What do you mean you can't eat?
Well, that's
Let's go
You can understand if you do it
Everyone, please eat
Thank you for the meal
I was hungry
I got it
It's broken
Wait a minute
What's wrong with Kobayashi?
What's wrong?
Kobayashi, please eat
Please eat
It's not broken
It's a joke
There was one person who couldn't break
the chopstick
Kobayashi is eliminated
It's a pity
To be continued
Only one person can't laugh
Kobayashi's luck is bad
In just 5 minutes after the program
started, Kobayashi was unlucky and
dropped out
7 people left
So Kobayashi-san, your turn is over for
today's show
You're going to be disqualified
It's a regular show
It's not a regular show, it's not a
graduation show
Your turn is over for today
By the way, teacher, what can I do to
make my luck better?
Is there anything?
Is there?
In Kobayashi-san's case, do you have a
guarantee that your luck will improve if
you appeal to the common people?
The common people
You're appealing to the common people
More, more
Really?
If I appeal to the common people, my
luck will improve
Really?
Kobayashi-san, since you're here, please
appeal to the common people
I had my favorite shoes, but I wore them
until the hole opened
You're a common person
If I wear them in the rain, I'll be
soaked
I see, a nice common person
The second round of the Lucky Girl Grand
Prix
You might have noticed, but this sushi
is just regular sushi
I knew it
Let's go to the second round
Russian Wasabi Sushi Battle
Actually, there is only one sushi with a
lot of wasabi
Who will be the unlucky member?
Please eat
How is it?
Delicious
Don't you eat?
I don't eat
The tension is dropping
Don't eat
What should I do?
I think she's the only one
Let's go
Ready
Thank you for watching. Please
subscribe.
It's so good that I can't help but
laugh.
Hey, catering staff, come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
You can't move.
So, Hoshida is out of here.
Yay!
The end of the show.
Hoshida, come here.
Thank you for your hard work.
They were unlucky and got wasabi sushi.
They were eliminated.
6 members are left.
After this, the members will face a more
difficult test of luck.
The third round.
Pull your luck and have a gourmet
fortune-telling contest.
Go, go, go!
Sorry, the person in the middle.
I'll be in the frame.
So far, there are 6 people left.
But, we'll split them in half.
Is that how it is?
That's how it is.
Please look over there.
There are 6 boxes.
Inside, there are various ingredients.
I want to eat them.
You want to eat them, right?
Do you want to eat them, Matsuno-san?
But, 3 of them are correct.
And the remaining 3 are wrong.
How many are there?
At the end of the string, there are 3
ingredients that are delicious as a
lucky draw and 3 ingredients that are
hard to eat as a wrong answer.
If you can eat all of them, you'll pass
the test.
Then, Chu-A noticed something.
Something is sticking out.
It's sticking out.
What is it?
Something is sticking out.
Look at this. It's sticking out.
What is it?
I'm scared.
I don't know. It's sticking out.
Look at this.
Is it a squid?
It looks like a squid.
Let's wait.
It's not a squid.
It's a squid.
So, I'll start.
I'll go in order.
Who wants to go first?
I'm scared.
I'm not going to do it.
I don't want to do it.
I feel like I can do anything.
First, a lucky draw from Hirota.
Which one do you want to do?
I'll do the longest one.
I see.
The length is a little different.
Then, please draw.
I'll start.
Hirota has successfully avoided the
suspicious box.
However, there are three failures.
What is inside the box?
I got it.
Please open it.
Thank you.
This is a fail.
It's a Hachinoko and Mitsubachi
Oyakodon.
Let's check with the staff.
What's wrong?
Hirota has eaten the wrong food.
But if he eats this, he will clear the
game.
I will go.
Are you going?
If you eat this, you will be safe.
If you eat this, you will clear the
game.
It's like a tea.
Chew it well.
He finished eating.
Hirota cleared the game.
How was the taste?
Please subscribe to our channel.
Who wants to go next?
You were like, oh!
I'll wait a little longer
Next, Mayama will try
Mayama, please
Oh, I picked up something
OK!
I picked up a cake.
You are lucky!
This is a big one.
This is what Mayama picked up.
Ta-da! It's Taiyaki!
You are lucky!
It was sunny yesterday
Let's move on
Next is Matsuno
I'm waiting for the third one
I see
Are you OK, Matsuno?
My heart hurts
Next, Matsuno will try to be lucky
There are two more chances
Will she be lucky?
Matsuno, please pull
It's the first one
How did it happen?
This is it
I see
Matsuno pulled a black box with a
suspicious atmosphere
What's inside?
I did it
This is the perfect one
Thank you very much
Please subscribe to my channel
Konpeito is a kind of sweet dish
Please eat
So, you got it right
There is one more correct answer
Who is it?
The remaining 3 people will challenge
the game while leaving a suspicious box
Shall we go with the 3 people?
Yes
Let's see
What should I do?
One of the three is correct
Who will be the lucky one?
Wait, wait, wait
It's the same
Are you OK?
I'll leave it to you
First, Yasumoto, please pull
Yes
Oh, it's close
It's close
Wait, is this correct?
Yes
I don't know if it's correct or not
Kashiwagi, please draw
Here you go
Nakayama-san, just in case, just in case
So, this is Kashiwagi-san
I don't know yet
You don't know yet?
Maybe this is correct too
Yes, this is correct too
First, let's check the contents of the
box that Yasumoto drew
Here it is
It looks delicious, it's a jelly
It looks delicious
What is it?
This is a puzzle
It's a jelly with a fun texture that
pops
Wow!
So, Kashiwagi-san, let's move on
It's a manju
So, Nakayama-san, you're up last
I'm nervous
Open it
After a long time, the inside of the box
is revealed
Let's go, Nakayama-san
Are you ready?
It won't come out, right?
It's a food, it won't come out
Please open it
Hello
Yes, it's a Takame
Please take a look
Hello
Can you hear me?
It's a Takame made from a high quality
of Thai that smells like La France
It smells like a Japanese cat
It smells amazing
What kind of smell is it?
Oh my god
It's La France
It smells like a high quality of fish
Yasumoto and Nakayama are out of luck
But if they can eat all of them, they
can clear the mission
The possibility of it being delicious
depends on luck
Yasumoto-san, let's go
Let's see how it goes
Please judge if you can eat it or not
Please
Let's eat
Oh, I can do it
Oh, you can do it
I didn't expect that
It's not bad
What is it?
It's like a salmon roe
What's wrong?
The aftertaste is bad
It's better to eat it all at once
Jelly
All of them are tough
If you can't do it, please apologize
here
I'm sorry
Yasumoto couldn't eat the jelly
She is eliminated
Next is Nakayama
If she can eat a whole boiled turtle,
she will be cleared
Nakayama
Let's eat
I'm interested
I'm sorry
No!
It's hard!
It's cute!
It's like a chair!
What is this?
It's like a monster.
It's just the taste of the smell.
That's enough.
What are you going to do?
I'm sorry.
Don't eat it yet.
I can't eat it yet.
Why are you eating it when I said I'm
sorry?
My teeth can't win.
You can't win.
Yasumoto and Nakayama are disqualified.
There are 4 people left.
The next is the final round.
Who is the luckiest girl in the show?
The final round is about to begin.
The next is the baby, come on!
The last test of luck is to compete with
a simple rule that if a baby comes near,
it's a victory.
Only luck can decide the outcome.
How do you feel about this project?
I don't know if I'm close to him, but we
get along well.
I think we're the same age.
I don't know, but we get along well.
Do you get licked?
No, I don't.
I was the one who got scolded.
So, let's get started.
Here you are, baby.
Baby.
Cute.
You have strong bangs.
This baby is the child of the director
of Shirakawa.
What does that mean?
Wife.
This is the main topic of this program.
So, who will Saori-chan choose to hold
the key to the fate of the members?
The final round is about to start!
Well, well, well, Saku-san.
Saku-san, in the middle.
Let's put it in the white spot.
In the white spot?
Well, let's start.
Baby, come here, come here, the battle
has started!
It has started!
I'm crying!
You cried when you lost your friend,
didn't you?
Why?
I'm crying!
Saori is a little bit scared.
She is scared.
She is tired.
Saori is a little bit scared.
So, Kobayashi-mama is going to help her.
10 minutes later
The baby is crying
You all have sweets, right?
Who will get the sweets?
The person who gets the sweets will be
the winner
By the way, this is your favorite sweets
Everyone
Ready, start
Who will get the sweets?
Senpai, please
Senpai, I will eat
Who's turn is it?
I'm watching
I want to give it to you
This
I'm opening my hand
She's opening her hand
She's ready to grab it
Grab it
She can't grab it
She's coming
She's grabbing it
She's taking it out
It's Kaori-chan
She's good
Kaori-chan is good
As expected of the director's child
She knows how to have fun
Then
She's giving the rice cracker to
Hirotano again
I'm opening it
So the winner is Hiroto!
I'm so happy!
Amazing!
I'm glad for now
I don't know if she was lucky or not,
but the lucky girl is Aika Hirota.
Finally, for the luck of all the Ebichu,
they received a prayer at the shrine.
And a word from the Japanese director,
Mayama.
Mayama-san, what are you doing here?
I've done a lot of things up to now, but
from now on, it's an emergency special
project.
Takebe Shinichiro's first childbirth,
before becoming a father, let's give a
baby a name!
Peace, peace, peace.
Yeah!
Wait a minute.
I didn't hear anything.
Wow!
So, Friaris, you're going to write your
name on this flipbook.
Wait a minute.
I'm serious.
This is not a flipbook.
This is a real one.
Can I use this as a shrine?
So, we asked Friaris,
who is thinking about the name,
to make a life decision.
By the way,
is the name you chose really your name?
I don't know.
By the way, everyone, it's a girl.
A girl.
Let's take a look at each of them.
Yes.
Here it is.
Dora.
No, no, no.
I see.
It's a proverb.
I thought it was Ryuko or Tatsuko, but
it's Dora.
It's so cool and looks strong.
It's too strong.
It's a strong word to call a girl Tatsu.
And it's the worst to call her Dora.
OK.
I'll keep it for now.
Why?
Next, Matsuno.
Kirara.
Cute.
It's cute.
Takiumi, Kirara is good.
It's like a starfish.
I see.
It's the first time to hear it.
It's the first time.
I thought I could do it.
I can't do manzai with a child.
Here are the names each member came up
with.
Among them, Nakayama has a unique name.
So that I can say thank you a lot, Miku-
chan.
What's that?
Numbers?
Numbers.
It says thank you.
Here, it's here.
Oh no.
Miku, just the sound is good.
If you write thank you, it's a game
name.
The sound is good.
I can say thank you a lot.
I see. You're going to be famous.
I thought of one too.
Really?
I want you to raise a strong child.
Lastly, the names each member seriously
thought of.
High school classmates, as best friends,
what did they come up with?
So, this is it!
Taki, Ue, Ue, Shita, Shita, Hidari,
Migi, Hidari, Migi, Bie.
This is like Famicom's invincible
command.
This command is strong.
I'm sure I'll be bullied.
I want you to be strong.
This is the worst.
How about this?
It's not how about this.
There are two good ones.
There are?
Not Dora-ko?
Dora-ko and...
One is this.
This is it?
Wow!
Really?
The number of strokes is good.
The number of strokes is good?
It's a child who is loved by many
people.
That's good.
No, no, no.
It's a child who is loved and teased.
Another good one is Kirara.
That's really good.
Really?
This is a child who can cope with
anything.
Taki, Ue will choose the last one, θ
bearing the fortune's result in mind.
Won't the photo booster be decided?
No, no, no.
GO Ball
You should report to your wife.
He said, it's settled.
No, no, no.
ONE OF THE PHOTOS TO apparently conclude
Your cloud was covered with several
greenhouse gases, already deformed and
jungled.
Hello?
Well, the name of the child...
I've decided on a name.
What? Why?
It's Kirara.
Why?
It's just a flow.
Can you say, I'm fine with Kirara?
It's weird.
Ready, go!
I'm fine with Kirara.
Never!
I don't know yet.
Congratulations!
I'm not sure.
Kirara-chan!
Please come back to the game TV!
I don't know yet.
I'm not Kirara, probably.
Next time, in the heavy rain,
Ebichu is split into two teams and walks
around a certain town.
Everything is going well!
It's very hot, so let's all do a
coordination battle.
Oh, I'm looking forward to it!
Go ahead!
I'm going to win!
This program was brought to you by the
following sponsors.