comes from locations outside Sh rushing
Sea,
Jessie Copen
In airing tomorrow Jervis
And other contracts
I'm Riko Nakayama, the 12th member of
the Shiritsu Ebisu Group.
This is my favorite item.
It's a highlight of my milk makeup.
This is the first cosmetic brand in the
U.S.
I got this from my senior at the agency,
Momokuro-chan.
Thank you so much.
When I got my makeup done by a makeup
artist,
this was used as a highlight.
I really wanted this because the color
is so cute.
I couldn't find this in Japan.
I was planning to buy this when I go to
the US.
Momokuro gave me this.
I've been using this since the day I got
this.
Thank you so much.
I'll introduce this.
First of all, this is a bag.
It's really cute from the package.
It's clear.
It's in a transparent case.
It says Milk Makeup.
It's a mini size.
So it doesn't get bulky even in a makeup
bag.
It's cute from the package.
I'm excited just to have it.
It's the best.
I'd like you to see the color.
I'll put on a little more.
So that you can see the color easily.
Can you see it?
It's a blue-ish purple.
It's more purple-ish and glossy.
I think it's a little flashy when I look
at it like this, but it's really good to
get used to it when I put it on my face.
I'll put it on.
I'll put it on my head.
Can you see it?
I put a little more on.
How can I tell?
It's transparent.
The transparency...
It's easier to tell with my arms.
The transparency is getting used to my
skin.
It's so cute.
I talk too much.
I'm going to do a monkey pose.
I'm going to put it on my lips and chin.
It's cute.
It's a really cute item that you can
definitely ask me what the highlight is.
I've always wanted to introduce this.
That's all for my one-piece.
Bye bye.
This is my favorite item.
It's Etuse's mascara base.
I've been using this since I was in
junior high school.
I use it as a mascara, not as a base.
This product is before renewal.
I use it in the store.
I think the one in the store is a little
more powerful.
Anyway, this mascara base is really
good.
I like it.
There are three points I want to
introduce.
The first is curl keeping power.
I use it when I do my own makeup.
I don't know if it's because of the
mascara liquid, but it's easy to remove
the curl.
But this doesn't have that problem.
It makes your eyelashes look more
natural.
If you have a problem with curls, please
try it.
The second point is...
You can make beautiful separate
eyelashes.
This product has a lot of black fibers,
so it's a product that stretches the
eyelashes by adhering the fibers to the
eyelashes.
Anyway, it stretches.
I think the lower eyelashes are
particularly easy to understand.
It's like a doll's eyes.
I like it very much.
And the third is natural.
This liquid is not just black, but clear
black.
It's a clear black liquid.
No matter how much you apply, it won't
be a ball.
I don't want to overdo it.
No matter how much you apply, it will be
natural.
I'm only doing lip makeup right now.
I'm going to apply brown mascara to my
lower eyelashes.
It doesn't look like I'm wearing eye
makeup, but my eyes look bigger.
I think it's good for no makeup look.
If you want to make it look more
natural, you can use this mascara as a
base.
I think you can make beautiful and cute
eyelashes.
Please try this mascara.
Let's match it.
I'm Kobayashi Kaho, 11th.
This is my favorite mascara.
Ta-da!
Eyebrow mascara.
This is a color called Fumii Multi
Mascara Red Brown.
I want to recommend this color.
As you can see, my eyebrows are very
thick and obvious color.
So without mascara my eyebrows show like
they are higher than before.
Eyebrows with...
I don't like to have my eyebrows drawn.
When I was shooting, I was told that my
eyebrows were a little too much.
I used to apply mascara many times to
suppress my eyebrows.
I thought my eyebrows were too much when
I put on makeup.
I looked up what I should do.
What I had used for the style of this
color was
I have as the color,
which fits if the person using blonde
voice use it.
So I have applied the color that
you focus on if you are close to blonde-
looking girl.
And I have applied the color,
you will see the golden eyebrows.
I thought that was wrong.
I found this one.
It's a baby brown.
When I bought this,
I saw that it's easy to get used to this
color.
But it says that it's easy to get red.
So I can get red even with eyebrows.
I wanted to show my eyebrows even though
I was 10 meters away.
I thought this is the best.
So I introduced this.
I think many people have thin eyebrows.
I use eyebrow mascara to make my
eyebrows look smaller.
If you want to make your eyebrows look
smaller, I recommend this.
It's easy to use because it's a baby.
It's easy to use because it's a color
that people of all ages can get used to.