The third one is Red Bull.
Red Bull?
You came here for a limited time.
You are famous among your fans.
Yes, I am.
I am grateful.
When I want to cheer up,
I come here.
I will come here.
You always go to the stage to drink.
No way.
You drink Red Bull, too?
You?
You are performing live.
Yes.
That's amazing.
You are so hot.
You don't move much and stick your
mouth.
I saw a video of a Queen.
I see.
I saw it and thought it was a good idea
to drink coke.
I thought it was a good idea to drink
coke.
I wanted to play Red Bull.
I see.
I think you want to play Red Bull.
I love your performances.
When you are in a bad mood,
I drink Red Bull.
I want to show this to you.
I don't know what to do.
I think Red Bull will like something
extreme.
Something extreme.
Maybe we should do a live show with
energy.
Red Bull will be happy.
We'll talk about it.
Talk about it?
You like Red Bull, right?
I think I sponsored it the other day.
Like coming down from the space.
What should I do?
I think Red Bull will like something
challenging.
I think it would be nice if the bolt was
sponsored like that.
I think it would be nice if it was an
extreme group.
Next, Naito's...
There's one more.
Sorry.
Naito's...
Is there one more?
I can't hold it down.
There's one more.
It's 3.5.
What do you like about Red Bull?
I like it when it sparkles.
What do you mean?
My dream is to be a celebrity.
I've always liked glittering things.
It's something I can't live without.
You want to be a celebrity?
Yes.
Why?
I've liked it since I was little.
I see.
I think it's really fun.
It's fun, right?
I love it.
I'll be like that in the future.
I think Red Bull will come to that
point.
I think so.
I don't think Paris Hilton is ready yet.
I see.
I like it.
I haven't seen anyone like that lately.
I think everyone's into it.
I think it's good to have everyone like
that.
I want to be the last Paris Hilton.
I'm not saying Paris Hilton.
I want everyone to spread their
reputation.
I want to be the glittering me.
What is the reason for Red Bull?
The reason for Red Bull is that they
want to be Paris Hilton.
I think so.