The first episode of Nobizaka TV
Nobizaka TV
Tonight, to train the wide-spread acting
skills of the members
They will challenge various acting
techniques
First, they will check the ad-lib acting
skills
with a short-time topic
Pinpoint Acting Test
Tonight, the first member of the team is
The eye-contact acting when they touch
each other to buy the same book
I think something is going to start from
here
It's a play that makes you feel like
it's going to start
This is the beginning of the story
First, Endo challenges
What kind of encounter will she play?
Endo is right
Ready, start!
Endo's first attempt at acting
Endo's second attempt at acting
Please.
She got it.
I see.
She's cute.
It was a good match.
This world is like the end.
I was nervous, but I did my best.
It was good to be fresh.
The same age. What is Suzuki's acting
plan?
Are you a book lover?
Yes.
Ready, start!
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Cut!
I see.
What is the meaning of SUZUKI?
It's a little scary.
It was scary at first.
SUZUKI's world.
Do I have a world?
There were many.
The next question is.
When you wave your hand to a friend from
the front, you are cheating.
There is such a scene.
This scene is cute.
This is a challenge for YODA, which is
active in movies and dramas.
YODA is also doing it.
YODA is doing it.
Start!
and that's it!
It's hot!
You've already decided on a light one.
I've done this a lot.
What does this mean?
I had a bad eye, so I looked at it from
a distance and thought it was my friend.
When I did it, it was different. It's
hot.
You really did it.
It was good.
Change the subject again.
A play that hit the corner of the chance
with a little finger.
This may be there.
It's a family-like play.
It's like a hurry.
Can Kanagawa show his natural acting?
Ready, start!
Why did you do that?
Ouch!
Cut!
Something flew.
It was a normal staff.
I caught it.
I see.
I'm surprised that I didn't even plan
it.
That's right.
I lost all my memories of what I just
did.
That's right.
But eat the half-dough.
I want to eat it.
Thank you.
The next pin-point setting is
The expression of when the material that
was completed with this was broken in
front of you.
I see.
I'm impressed.
That was also there.
In Hanzawa.
It was exactly there.
In front of you.
In this situation, how will Umezawa
express it?
Ready, start!
I don't think that's possible.
Thank you.
That's good.
Even if you're a boss, I think that's
the worst.
I thought it was a little bit of a low-
key, so I thought I could get angry.
That's right.
That's good.
Announcing the following settings.
It's a wink performance to tell you that
it's a secret between the two of you.
It's a way to make people nervous so
that they don't know.
That's right.
What was Iwamoto's wink that was highly
rated last time?
You were good earlier.
Let's start.
Start.
I'm not dating anyone.
I'm sorry.
You are very good.
I was nervous.
Yamato, you are good.
I'm not dating anyone.
I'm 180 degrees different from my usual
self.
I'm nervous.
You are doing it.
I will never do it.
I love anime.
I have a lot of reference materials.
You are a good actress.
I did my best.
Next.
A play where a monster holds one hand
and clings to his neck.
I'm sorry.
Some people may find it easy to play.
The 4th generation Tsutui will challenge
the tricky challenge.
I don't think Tsutui will hold hands.
What kind of performance will you show
us?
Let's get started.
Did you do it on your phone?
Oh?
It moved.
That's scary.
Oh!
Damn...!
Poro Fight!
I was thinking about going somewhere
It's a very difficult movie
It was good at first, but it started to
move slowly
It was good, right?
Good good
The last pin point announcement
It's a comical garbage box crash play
This is a little irregular
When we went to the location
I was surprised that it was a comical
comedy
What kind of comical play will Kamura
show?
Kamura looks good.
How is it?
Let's start.
Be careful.
It's cute.
It was good.
Really?
Be careful.
Who did it before? Higuchi and Kubo?
You couldn't do it at all?
I couldn't do it at all.
It's the coolest when you take off the
shell.
Next, how will the 5th generation Ikeda
fight?
Ikeda!
Oh no, Ikeda is dangerous.
Is Ikeda okay?
Ikeda is dangerous.
Ikeda!
Ready, start!
Thank you for watching! Please subscribe
to our channel!
That's terrible!
I'm sorry!
It's different from the plan.
The trash can was supposed to be a big
one.
Yes.
Do you want to do it again?
Let's go again!
What kind of plan will she show us?
Ready, set, go!
What is she doing?
She's just like a bulldozer
What are you doing?
I lost a little bit
I'm strong
What are you doing?
Thank you for watching!
Fantasy School Championship!
From now on, we will be checking out a
little bit of school drama.
But how will the members respond to the
quite crazy fantasy setting?
I love you.
You love me.
Yes, that's right.
I knew it.
I can see everything.
Let's get married and live happily ever
after.
That's cute.
I'm sorry.
How will Natsuni androids play this
game?
Tempo 120
Tempo 125
Tempo 140
The chance of success is 90%
Please date with me
The next topic is the toilet that she
ran into because she was scared
Then the sound of knocking the living
room gets closer
Finally, her own room is knocked and she
looks up at the door
The girl who doesn't need any
explanation, Riria Ito's challenge
It's possible.
If you run into the bathroom, it's over.
Why do you run into this?
Don't mess with me.
She's good
What will the 4th generation Hayashi
find?
Uemura-san?
The huge safety element was its own!
That was scary.
How should answer that?
It's because of this cheer.
I'm wearing 30 cm shoes.
Please don't make them angry later.
Next,
Zonbi approaching to its new Czech
friend from school.
Zonbi runs into a classroom which was
empty.
But he was bitten by a zombie.
So...
First, Nakamura. This is a one-shot shot
of the camera.
Cut!
I see.
The camera is dead.
I was bitten.
Why?
What should I do?
You're good.
I understand.
I'll be a dance.
So,
I hope you live.
You're good.
I'm sure.
You're not crying.
Really? Thank you.
I'm back.
She's going to dance.
YUNEKI is serious about dancing.
huh?
sorry
I...
I think I was bit.
Good.
Oh no.
You did it.
Until now.
Why did you put it in?
Thank you.
You put it in.
I did it.
You can put it in and continue.
I see.
You are good.
I was good, right?
You were not good.
I was not good.
You were not good until the end.
You can continue well.
I thought about it for 3 days and I made
it.
You made it.
You are good at it.
You are good at Android.
Really?
I want you to continue.
Blast Serif!
Always say as many lines as you can
What will Inoue say?
Who do you think is eating with whose
money?
Inoue probably didn't say that.
I don't know who said that.
Please.
Who do you think is eating with whose
money?
You got it right.
Inoue, do you think you are eating with
someone's money?
I didn't say that.
You didn't say that?
I thought you were used to saying that.
I think it's because I'm a girl.
Did you say that to your wife?
No.
That's good.
Inoue is good at this.
Boxing.
Is boxing good?
Boxing is good.
It's good.
Akimoto is going to challenge.
This is the last chance.
Akimoto will say this.
You are a dirty rat.
This is different from your answer.
I may have never said this before.
There are such lines.
Please remember the lines.
Akimoto's line.
You are a dirty rat.
This is different from your answer.
I'm sorry.
I'm frustrated.
This is difficult.
I will do it again.
I bit it.
I often do this.
I can't help it if I bite it.
You are a dirty rat.
I'm a dirty rat.
Please think of someone.
What are you looking at?
I will say it without biting it.
You are a dirty rat.
This is different from your answer.
What are you saying?
I overcame the line.
You are a dirty rat.
Next, ICHINOSUKE will say the line.
Next, which finger should I remove?
She's a psychopath.
If she can do it, it's scary.
ICHINOSUKE's line.
Next, which finger should I remove?
Which finger should I remove?
She's scared.
I want nails.
You want nails?
Yes. I want Aya's nails.
You want Aokawa's nails?
What do you mean?
She's scared.
Because Aokawa is cute?
I want to remove her nails.
I want to take her nails home.
What is that?
Kaki will challenge.
Can she say a strong line?
This is a match between a man and a
woman.
I see.
Is this a Kansai dialect?
I want you to say it in a loud voice.
I will do my best.
I want to take her nails home.
That's great.
Why do you say that?
I want to take her nails home.
That's the main character's line.
That's great.
She's the main character.
Asuka, you were good.
I was good.
I was closed.
You were closed.
Really?
After all the performances, the first
winner is Yamashita.
Yamashita.
I gave you 95 points.
Thank you.
You have a lot of points.
Kaki and Iwamoto are good.
I have a lot of points.
I thought it was Riria Ito.
Riria Ito was good.
Riria Ito is like Riria Ito's special
prize.
Riria Ito's special prize.
Today, we will announce the selected
members of the 31st single of
NOGISAKA46.
With the release of the new single,
NOGISAKA46 will select members who
perform the song.
This is the formation.
There are only one member from the
previous song. 18 members will be
formed.
The first is the third row.
Yuumiki Nao.
Shiba Tai Yuna.
The next is the name.
Hayashi Luna.
The first selection of the 4th grade
Hayashi
I'm not sure if there was a part of me
that I was happy to jump through,
but I think there are parts of me that I
could grow through doing live
performances under the stage.
I hope that I can show my best and grow
more
through my performance under the stage.
The third row, Iwamoto Renka,
Hayakawa Seira,
and the next person to be called is...
Tamami Sakaguchi.
Sankisu and Sakaguchi are the first to
be selected for the first time.
I came here to be selected.
I came here every time.
I thought it would be no good this time.
I was wondering what I should do more
than this.
But I was preparing to go anytime.
I'm very happy.
Do you remember that I did skydiving?
I'll do my best.
Minami Umezawa
Yuki Yoda
Haruka Kaki
Mizuki Yamashita
Sakura Endo
And the center of the 31st single.
Saito Asuka
Asuka Saito, who announced her
graduation, is in the 5th center.
I feel better than I thought.
I don't have a twisted feeling.
Anyway, I'm a Chikuichi fan.
I feel like I was playing the role of
telling the fans to change.
I'm out of the change.
I hope that I can change.
I want to be a wonderful star.
I don't want to be sent out so much.
I want to show everyone that I'm having
fun.
That's what I want.
Saito Asuka, who has supported the
history of Rokizaka to the Undercut
Center.
What kind of outstanding beauty will she
show us?
I'll do my best to shoot Asadora.
Asadora is really fun.
Lastly, Yamashita, please jump and say
your thoughts in the test room.
This bald snake, you dare to jump?
But successful!
We will do our best.
Start mobile first
Preview of the full-fledged video will
be released in the full-fledged version
Ta-da!
Kendama!
I'll put the kendama here in one shot
from now on
Let's go!
Please subscribe to my channel!
Thank you for watching.