These videos during Ebi-Chu!
Rookie Talk Hoshino Mirie
Today's theme is
A little outdate
The points of coordinestably
Sweat pants are attenuated
Also i think it's important to bring
such a bag
I dressed up as an adult and dressed
casually
I'm wearing it when I go to a cafe with
my friends
It's not like I'm going out, but I'm
wearing it when I go somewhere
What is the image of the city?
The image of the city is...
I don't know
Daikanyama
If I wear sneakers, I think I'll be
casual
I think I can go to a fashionable city
because I matched a jumpsuit
I'm Mirie, the 7th star of the lucky 7.
This is my second day of the day.
The theme of this outfit is to go to a
place where I don't usually go.
I'm going to a place that looks like a
museum.
The theme is difficult.
The point of this outfit is...
The top is a sweet blouse-like dress.
The shoes are a little hard.
I like this feeling, not too sweet.
I don't make it sweet.
That's what I always do when I wear
something fluffy.
This ribbon...
What was it? There are many fashionable
ways to say it.
I like the one-piece dress with a ribbon
on the chest.
I always buy it.
I like the same clothes, so I'm worried
about buying the same clothes.
But MAYAMA always stops me.
I'm a little worried about buying the
same clothes.
I buy a lot of clothes for CHI-KU, so I
save it and buy clothes for each other.
I want to go to the museum or the movie
theater when I want to stretch my back.
I don't know where the city is.
I think I can go to Harajuku.
I don't know, but it changed suddenly.
I don't know, but I want to be like an
adult, but I want to go to a place where
I can play with my friends.
I'm Mirie Hoshino, the number one lucky
seven.
This is my outfit for Wednesday.
The theme is a holiday for an office
worker.
I'm dressed like a woman who is about to
start working.
I don't wear a lot of jumpsuits, but I
bought a jumpsuit this year.
I think it's good because it's cool to
wear even one piece.
The length is very long, so I was
wondering how to wear it.
I wear it like today, and I fold the hem
a little.
I sew it when I have time to sew it.
I sew it a little, and I always wear it
with a safety pin.
I usually wear a high neck top.
When I do that, I make sure to put my
hair together.
When my neck is tight, I always put my
hair together so that it looks
refreshing.
I'm Mirei Hoshino, the 4th member of
Lucky 7.
This is my Thursday's outfit.
I'm wearing casual clothes.
I'm wearing a skirt even though I'm in
my 20s.
I'm wearing a light-colored skirt.
I like short tops.
I can see my style well.
I often buy short tops.
I also cut short tops that I haven't
worn for a long time.
I wear a short skirt and a high-waisted
bottom.
I wear a skirt and a top to improve my
style.
I'm aiming for a style-up effect.
I bought this skirt three years ago.
I'm wearing a skirt and a top.
I wear a skirt and a top with a
combination of old clothes.
I'm wearing a skirt and a top.
I think some of you are wondering where
I got this.
I got a lot of new ones.
I'm wearing the same one from 5 years
ago.
I wore this on the second day of the
shoot.
It's my first time wearing this.
I wore this on the second day of the
shoot.
I matched it with this today.
I wore it in a feminine way last time.
But this time, I wore it in a casual
way.
I coordinated it.
My hat is fluffy and warm.
I'm M essentials, Eun kimchi, from
Shizuoka эти durable, clean, gorgeous
cosmetics stand for Beauty Essences.
Today is the fifth day.
This is my Friday outfit.
I look like an adult.
I really like black.
The point of this fashion is...
It's a bit British.
I matched it with a knit vest and a
dress.
I made it a little elegant.
I wore these pants on the first day.
I changed the top.
I think the atmosphere has changed.
I'm wearing the short boots I wore when
I was wearing a jumpsuit.
These are square-toe boots.
It's a trend.
I'm wearing black, but I'm wearing a
blouse with a luxurious feeling.
I'm wearing boots with enamel.
I'm enjoying black with a different
color and material.
I'm Mirie Hoshino, the lucky seven.
This is my Saturday outfit.
I'm wearing a mustard-colored skirt and
a top I wore two days ago.
I regret that I should have worn it on a
different day.
But I'm not wearing it because I woke up
all day, so don't worry.
I dressed up like an adult today.
I'm wearing a chain, but I'm not wearing
it this time.
I'm wearing a clutch bag.
I wore this outfit two days ago, but I
feel like it's going to change the
atmosphere.
I have a hoodie like this.
I'm wearing it with a dress.
I think it's an item that can change the
atmosphere.
MR.HASHI
I'm Mirei Hoshino, the number one lucky
7.
This is the last day of the week.
I dressed up like this for the 7th day.
It's a different style from the previous
one.
I dressed up like autumn.
The point of this dress is...
This knitwear, vest and dress were sold
as a set.
This dress is cute and has a beautiful
shape.
It's fluffy.
I chose this dress because it's a battle
suit.
I chose this dress because it's good for
the last day.
I don't wear colorful clothes.
I wear a blouse-like dress.
It's cute because it's fluffy when I
run.
I put a scarf on my hair.
I wear a ponytail and hide my hair with
a scarf.
How was it?
I thought I would wear different items.
I coordinated the items I like and use.
I chose a ribbon that looks good on me.
I coordinate the items with the balance
of the total.
I use the same color.
I coordinate with 3 colors.
I have a favorite item.
I like elegant coordination this year.
I haven't worn a skirt and a trainer for
a long time.
I have a checkered pattern, but I don't
wear it much.
I think I have a lot of monotone
coordination.
I don't have the same combination, but I
often have items that I actually had.
But recently I've been feeling a little
bit more chic, so I don't feel like I'm
wearing the same clothes as everyone
else.
What's farther than me?
I think it's the fashion of 4.
It's like a forest girl.
4 is also 4, and it has a lot of unique
items.
For the time being, there are a lot of
animals.
I don't wear much patterns, so I think
it's the farthest.