This week's Ebichu Tastas is the sport
of the sport
Ebichu Tastas Sports Festival
I think it will be opened with high
tension
It's not small
What is it?
Ebichu Tastas Start
Add various things to private Ebisu
Middle School!
Ebisu Justice!
This program is brought to you by the
sponsor.
1, 2, 3, 4!
We look forward to your continued
support!
Today, I, Yasumoto, will be the one to
work on the day job
I'll do my best today as well
I'm glad
Speaking of autumn, what is it?
Speaking of autumn
Autumn of appetite
Autumn of reading
Autumn of sleep
This is it
This
Autumn of music
Autumn and chestnut
You already know
Autumn is the season of sports
Yes
I see
Autumn of sports
Today, we'll have a
Ebi-kyu
Magi-undoukai
Yay
Well, well, well
What is it?
It's a sports day
Magi-undoukai
You can't understand the meaning unless
you watch it
This staff's sense is amazing
It's getting deeper and deeper
Amazing
Magi-undoukai
Yes, Magi-undoukai
In the class of Ebichu and Tsutasa
When I did a test for my academic
ability
Please stay still
Here it is
Napoleon of the dream
I don't know the word
I've never heard it
In this simple and common subject
Yasumoto's answer is
Yasumoto
Really?
The character is amazing
Good job
You're handsome
No, no
It's not
It's a real Terame
Super Kyodo
It's not written in any dictionary
So
The title of the sports day is
Yasumoto's personal opinion
I wonder if everyone is going to the
sports day in the temple
And
What?
Behind us
It's noisy
Scary
Magi-undoukai has started
I'm going to win the first prize
Are you ready?
I'm motivated
I'm ready
You were moving too much and dropped the
microphone
I was too much
But it's okay if you don't participate
That's right
You don't have to go out
I thought you were mistaken
But you came to the academy and told us
Nagareboshi san, what position should I
go?
Your position is the same
You shouldn't show your position
Amazing
So this time, we will have a serious
sports day
First, we asked the members' memories of
the sports day
I have one
You do?
What?
I won the first place in the Swedish
relay
Swedish relay?
It's not a normal relay
For example
Half a lap, the second person goes for
one lap, the third person goes for two
laps
It's increasing
Swedish relay?
Yes, it ran 320 meters
It was chosen as the fourth place
So it's fast
It's faster
I'm sorry, but Swedish relay is still in
my head
What about you, Hiroto?
I've been a cheerleader
You look like you're in a cheerleading
club
You look like you're in a school
I've been a cheerleader since I was in
3rd grade
I wanted to be a cheerleader since I was
in 6th grade
I've been trying hard
But I entered the student council in 6th
grade
So I couldn't be a cheerleader
So you can't be a cheerleader in the
student council?
No
If you were a cheerleader, how would you
do it?
I don't want to
Play, play, ABQ
Don't say such sad things
So the cheerleading club, Hirota's
cheerleading club
Play
I'm sorry, I was more serious than I
thought
I thought it would end with this
I was serious
You were serious
By the way, I was a cheerleader in
elementary school
That's amazing
How did you do it?
I want to see it
The cheerleader experience, Takiue is a
cheerleader
The one I adults have used.
Fl water, water!
Red light!
Skinny
What?
Wait, are you sweating?
That's what I thought!
He was singing, but his voice sounded
strange,
making me sing.
You're state of SQL.
graduate
Though he's in his total ass,
Resources just to be super
Just a joke, but
Lacrosse
there are even celebrities who make
idols SEOìŒ!
Oh no
And here is Kobayashi
I was also a cheerleader
Cheerleader?
What is a cheerleader?
What is it?
Do you say it like that recently?
I hold a
It's totally different from the image
It's cute
Do it again
I feel like I'm not doing it
I won the game of Yautja in elementary
school
Yautja?
Is it okay to say that?
I couldn't win the game of the losing
team
I have
You have been doing it since the
beginning
What is that?
You have never won a game of Yautja,
right?
I have never won a game of Yautja from
the first grade to the third grade
You have been in a team that has been in
the hell?
Seriously?
You have been in a team that has been in
the hell?
The team where Kobayashi is is a team
that is sure to lose
Yes
Now it's time to announce the team
Kobayashi with a lot of trouble and
Hirota and Akagumi with Mayama
The opposing white team is Yasumoto,
Hoshina, Matsuno, Nakayama
They will be divided into two teams and
aim to win the game
And the center is the president of the
tournament
The top and the bottom will be the
judges
The winning team of the serious sports
event will be given a luxurious autumn
set
The member who is the most active is the
super luxurious MVP, Shoma
It's a bit different
There are people who haven't won in
years
That's right
I lost in the competition
Listen, it's a serious sports event
There is no such competition
Let's win for the first time
Look at our team and see if we can rely
on this team
Do you think we can rely on this team?
We can rely on
Akagumi is Mayama
It's a bit of a narrow road
And the four white teams
Who will be active?
Oh, that's true.
Hoshina is also like that.
Is Hoshina Nakayama?
Nakayama is the same.
Because he has a lot of luck.
Oh, luck?
I thought it was a sportsmanship.
If you were to say no to Nakayama now,
No luck.
I was embarrassed today.
It's not physical strength or anything.
It's luck.
Are you going to wait?
Me?
Don't say.
I'm not motivated today.
You can't say that as a professional.
Why are you saying that?
I don't want to run.
Don't say you don't want to run in front
of the sports car.
Why don't you want to run today?
I feel good.
I don't know if I can win.
I don't know, but maybe when it's time
to run,
I'll feel better and want to run.
Well, today, do your best.
I'll do my best.
Let's do our best.
Please decide the leaders of each team.
Please talk to each other.
First, the leaders who pull the team.
Who is the leader who decides the
direction of the game?
Please announce.
First, the leader of the red team is
I am.
I'm surprised.
Why did this happen?
Yaocho.
Yaocho? What does that mean?
Chao?
Chao is the
Chao is the boss.
It means that you are the boss.
And the leader of the white team is
Masa Kano.
What is this?
I don't feel like running today.
I thought I would feel like running if I
became the leader.
I see.
That's great.
The leader is decided by these two.
Will Kobayashi win the first victory of
the sports festival?
Will Matsuno, who was motivated, take
it?
A serious battle begins.
The opening of the Ebi-chu sports
festival.
Entering last week.
Program No. 1. Entering last week.
First, the entrance from the red team.
I'm just walking.
What is this?
It's a strange entrance.
The tension is going up and down.
The members of the red team are
Mayama Rika, Hiroba Aika,
Kashiwagi Hinata,
Kobayashi Kao.
This is the most attractive place.
It's a free place.
While you're saying that.
That's right.
The white team has also entered.
Chiyo, please tell us about the members
of the white team.
The members of the white team are
Yasumoto Ayaka,
Hoshina Mirei,
Matsuno Rina,
and Nakaama Riko.
Matsuno is in a low tension today.
He doesn't want to run.
But it's going up.
It looks like a burning smell.
It's in the front and back, so it's
forced to move.
It's getting very slow for the white
team to choose that way of running.
That's right.
It's going up a lot.
It's the most tiring.
The white team is using their physical
strength.
Are you okay, White?
You are in the car a lot
I can't do it anymore
Matsuno is in danger
Why did you choose the way to enter?
It looks fun
Matsuno decided
You are excited even though you said you
don't want to do it
Matsuno, raise your head
It's burning inside
It's good
Next, program 2, sensei
The representative of the red team and
white team will come forward
The representative of the red team,
Kobayashi
I want to do it
And the representative of the white
team, Matsuno
Sensei, please
The leader of the red team, Kobayashi
and Kobayashi sensei
Sensei, we are
What is interesting?
We will use the Yaucho skill
No, no
You can't use the Yaucho skill
We will use the Yaucho skill
It's good
We don't have Yaucho today
Next, the leader of the white team,
Matsuno
Sensei
Sensei, we
We will ride the sportsmanship
We will run with all our might
You said you don't want to run
You look sleepy
Sensei
Thank you
Please come back
You are serious
Next, rock sensei
The representative of rock, Ogata sensei
Rock...
Is it okay?
Are you surprised?
There is such a thing
Since there is no place to stand, we
will add a rock roller Ogata
Rock sensei
Yes
Sensei
I, rock star Ogata
I will ride with high tension today
Ride?
Since it was not rock, we will add a
rock
Let's drink
Next, Program 3
Next, the greeting of the goods
This time, Akiyama-sama, the director of
the Hachioji Tourism Association, will
say a word
Akiyama-sama, please
Everyone, that Akiyama-sama
This time, the Ebi-Chu Magi-Undo-Kai is
recorded by borrowing the Grand of the
school in Hachioji
The sports festival held in Hachioji and
Akiyama-san, the director of the local
tourism association,
He rushed to the support of the Magi-
Undo-Kai
On behalf of the tourism association,
Akiyama-sama from Ebi-Chu, a very
beautiful word
Good morning everyone
Good morning
How are you all?
Yes
Do you know that there is a Takao in
Hachioji?
Yes
Have you ever climbed?
There are a lot of Takao in Hachioji
In a year, there are 2.5 million to 3
million people
If you haven't gone, please go
I would like you to cheer up Hachioji
with your power
Can you promise?
Yes
Thank you
I would like to send you a cheer
There is a white flag here, so I will
send a cheer from the white flag
Yes
Ebi-Chu White Flag A-A-O
Thank you
Next, Red Team Ebi-Chu Red Team A-A-O
Let's do A-A-O together
A-A-O
Let's do it together
Thank you
Thank you Akiyama
Today is the first day
Please watch it
Everyone, do your best
After everyone became one with Akiyama-
sama's ALE
The magic sports event has started
Everyone, let's go
Before that, what is Yasumoto's original
sportswear?
It's not 1, 2
ALE from Akiyama-sama of Hachioji
Tourism Association
After getting into the spirit, they are
getting ready for the event
This is Yasumoto, who is in charge of
daily work
Then, let's open the event
1, 2, 3
It's like that
The opening is different
Think about the distance
First, from the cushion
1, 2
It's normal to go up to 3, 4
It's so easy
5, 6
It's so small
You can open it more
It's good to wear Yasumoto's original
sportswear
Really?
The one that can relax your body
The one you usually wear
First, the first edition, Oenori
sportswear
Everyone, let's go
It's one-to-one
What is this?
Everyone is doing it naturally
I can't question it
What is this space?
I think everyone does it
Maybe before the live
They don't use the fan anymore
Next, the swing competition
Do we do it one by one?
Yes
Let's do it with the teacher
The teacher will get down
The teacher will get up
Next, the members will do the swing
competition
1, 2
I see
It's good
Why are you so good?
I think I'm still good
Are you confident?
This is a new one.
I don't know.
This is a thigh stretch.
This is like a water sword.
This is it.
Let's go.
I feel a sense of unity.
It's like a proper exercise.
I feel like the exercise has started.
Go!
It's serious.
OK, it's over.
It's a small size.
It was a serious exercise than I
expected.
The scheduled time is quite late.
The preparation is over.
Let's start the series of Ebisu Chigaku
serious exercise.
The serious exercise of Ebichu has
finally begun.
We will compete for the best score with
five items.
The first competition is the standard of
the sports event, Hamaide.
The first competition is the defense
match, Majitamaire.
At first, it's a ball-in, but it's not a
simple ball-in.
Here are the rules of Majitamaire.
Red, white, team match.
The one who has more balls in the basket
within the time limit wins.
In addition, there are special rules.
The defender will use a special board to
throw the ball back.
The table tennis player and the big
player will be the defenders.
First, we will decide which team will
defend which team.
Which team will defend which team?
I think the one who is not good at
defense is better.
But I'm worried because Kaiki is
serious.
Kaiki is not mature.
I think I'll play Brikko.
I agree.
I think Brikko is better.
Which team will defend which team?
The time of fate
Ready, go!
Burikko!
Don't say it's Burikko!
Red is Kaiki-san and white is Burikko
It's a waterfall
So the first move is red
The defender is Kaiki Ozata
What will happen?
Red team will start now, 1 minute limit
Ready
Let's go
I won't let you get in so easily
It's going in
Let's cross the wall
There's a lot of time for broadcasting
We'll show you a lot of the real sports
event
Next episode will be the second episode
of Ebichutas Sports Event
It's a waterfall
The waterfall is accelerating
The competition is going on
A fierce battle awaits
It's a fight between Kao and Shingo
It's a battle between Kao and Shingo
A battle between idols
Which team will win? Red or white?
If you missed Ebichutas, please check it
out
On the Star Dust channel, Ebichutas is
on air
I'm going to go somewhere
I don't think you'll come close
That machine is free of charge for 400
yen a month
There are also a lot of exclusive videos
that are not on air
For more information, please search on
the Star Dust channel
This program was provided by the sponsor
It's a battle between Firebat and
Yatsumoto
This is dangerous
It's going in