This week's Ebichu-tastas is the last
week's Ebichu-tasu University
Last time, they aimed to become the
university they wanted to be in and took
the entrance exam for Shiri-tsu Ebisu
University
Shiri-tsu Ebisu University
They passed the exam
The best of the Ebichu students
The first part of the interview
This time, the university student will
be the one to do the part-time job
interview
The interviewer of the core is in front
of her
Welcome to Happy Cafe
The way she waits is strange
The soloist, Koyama
I don't want to do it anymore
What's wrong, Nakayama?
I don't like the way you're acting
Ebichu Tastas, start!
Add various things to your private Ebisu
junior high school!
Ebisu Justice!
Welcome to Angel Reacts Cafe!
This program is brought to you by these
sponsors.
Please visit us at
www.angelreactscafe.com!
She's awake.
She's fine. She's doing her job well.
Today, we're going to have an interview
with her at her part-time job.
She said she'll be working part-time
when she gets a big discount.
Everyone in Ebichu wants to work part-
time.
I want to try it.
What kind of part-time job do you want
to try?
What about Yasumoto?
A crepe shop or a restaurant?
I want to try it.
A crepe shop?
The crepe shop owner is cute, so I want
to try it.
It's also in Harajuku.
The second part is called a secret job.
Why did you try to let her go?
I want to be the one who can get the
most money.
That's right.
I can't even think of a secret job.
What kind of secret job do you want?
A secret job that closes the bag.
It's like a secret job.
It's hard to get one for one yen.
One is about 5,000 yen.
I want to try it.
As an experience.
I want to earn money.
If you see this, you'll want to work
part-time.
What about a towel in Ebichu?
That's a good idea.
I don't need a house.
Please do it if you like.
Then the main subject.
Ebichu plus interview.
Challenge the interview of a part-time
job.
Members are divided into four groups and
have a group interview with a part-time
job of a popular girl student.
The waiting is a fake interviewer.
The shooting star in the room secretly
gives instructions.
Let's start the interview with a part-
time job.
Here they are.
Yasuno Hoshino, Nakayama Matsuno.
They look quite nervous.
Please introduce yourself and promote
yourself.
Please introduce yourself, Ms. Hoshina.
I'm Mirei Hoshina. I'm 17 years old.
I'm always cheerful and smiley.
I think I have the power to cheer up
people around me.
Thank you.
She's very confident.
Ms. Yasumoto.
I'm Ayaka Yasumoto. I'm 16 years old.
I'm very shy.
But when I started working in a cafe, I
got over it.
I want to be a person who can be active.
Thank you.
She's not ready yet.
It's an interview.
I'm Rina Matsuno. I'm 16 years old.
I think I'm cheerful and smiley.
Thank you.
I'm Mariko Nakayama. I'm 14 years old.
I'm a person who can eat delicious food.
I work hard to make delicious food when
I get a job.
Thank you.
She said she was going to eat delicious
food.
I thought she was talking about her job.
Please take your seat.
Thank you.
If I were the manager, I would have
dropped this clothes when I came here.
I would have thought she was joking.
Please tell me your shortcomings.
Ms. Hoshiga.
I have a little bit of a mischievous
side.
I learned to fix that part.
I learned it at a cafe. I want to be
able to fix it with a calm feeling.
Are you nervous?
I'm nervous.
Are you a little different from usual?
I'm a little different.
Let's do our best as usual today.
Thank you.
Did you ask if she was sleepy?
Is she sleepy?
She is.
I'm often asked this question.
But I'm awake and doing my job.
I see.
Could you tell us the shortcomings?
When I fail,
I immediately start to reflect on
myself.
But I think I can reflect on myself
immediately.
You suddenly talk about shortcomings.
You were talking about shortcomings.
I think I can reflect on myself
immediately.
I'm positive.
That's good.
Let's start with Matsuno-san.
My shortcoming is that I'm too positive
and I'm not good at talking.
This is my first part-time job, so I
want to fix it.
She has only eye power.
Nakayama-san. My shortcoming is that I
can't communicate well with people.
I think that the communication with
customers is important for cafe staff.
I want to do my best.
Are you sleepy?
I'm awake. I'm okay. I'll do my job
properly.
Please think about the store name.
Are you ready?
Please look forward to the next episode.
To show the individuality of the cafe,
we will ask the person who will think
about the cafe's name.
Please show me from Hoshina.
I am Angel Relax Cafe.
What does it mean?
If you can make a guest with a smile
like an angel, you can relax.
If you see someone's smile, you feel
calm and happy.
I named it with that meaning.
Ms Yasumoto, would you like to try?
A little bit.
What is this?
I think a cafe with easy access is good.
I want to drink a little bit of coffee.
I want to make a cafe like that.
Is there a specialty menu?
I want to add a little chocolate.
What is a little chocolate?
I want to add a little chocolate to the
tea.
I'm confused.
Please calm down.
I understand.
Matsuno.
I want to open a happy cafe.
I want to make a cafe that people can
drink and eat happily.
I want to open a happy cafe.
Are you happy with your costume?
I'm happy.
I think it's good.
Nakayama's idea of a cafe is a smile
cafe.
Everyone's answer is ready.
Please tell me your name.
Yes.
He will actually train customers.
First of all, I want to train customers.
Welcome to Angel Relax Cafe.
Thank you.
Yasumoto.
Yes.
I'm going.
Can Yasumoto appeal to the interviewer?
Welcome to Choco Choco Cafe.
I can't meet her.
She is so curious.
What is she waiting for?
Welcome to Happy Cafe.
I want to make it more festive.
I'll do my best.
Welcome to Happy Cafe.
Happy Cafe is crazy.
That's all for the interview. Thank you
very much.
Excuse me.
I want you to appeal to them.
Good luck.
What's wrong?
Excuse me.
Can you show me your ID?
Yes, I'm fine.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Please show me.
Welcome to Smile Cafe
That's all for the interview
Thank you
The interview is over
What will the members say?
Wait a minute, everyone is coming one by
one
I hate it
What happened?
What happened to Nakayama?
I hate it
I hate that guy
I don't want to go to that cafe
What's wrong with you, Nakayama?
I'm still a virgin
I don't want to go to that cafe
What's wrong?
We're going to start another group of
interviews, but the interview has
changed a little.
Yes, it's more powerful than this.
It's scary.
I don't think I'll be the manager of
such a cafe.
Maybe it's like a cafe soul.
I'm doing something in the cafe.
Now, the interview of B group starts.
Excuse me.
I'm sure you're like, is this person?
Then sit down.
Excuse me.
First of all, like A group, if you ask
your own shortcomings.
My shortcomings are that I say what I
think right away.
I say words without thinking, so I
sometimes hurt people.
I try to be careful from time to time.
Then look at me and say what you think.
I thought the skinhead was a good fit.
correct
My shortcomings are that I am not calm
and I am shy
Are you okay with being shy and being a
guest?
But I will do my best
Good
My character is a weak child
When I was a child, I was a strong child
I cry easily
I have a character like that
I can interact with customers
I can overcome that
I chose this character
Is it a strong word?
My strong word is
For example
I don't have to do it anymore
I have a place I don't like to lose
I think it is easy to be hurt when I
hear the words that break my pride
That's right
Correct
Hiroto-san's face
My shortcomings are that I'm short-
tempered
I'm not good at acting
What's interesting about Kashiwagi?
You just laughed, right?
What's funny?
Nothing is wrong
Correct
You keep saying correct
Everyone will laugh at this
Think of the name of this cafe
I'm going to be the manager
I want you to have that image
What kind of name will come up when you
imagine the manager of the skinhead?
Mayama
Yes, I'm the manager of the skinhead
I want to use natural ingredients
And the manager has a nice head
You were pulled to the luxury
Mayama's answer makes the interview more
interesting
Kashiwagi
It's simple, but Tokimeki Cafe
Where is my nuance?
Tokimeki
Correct
Hirota
How about Uru-Tsuru Tsuru?
I'm screwed
Thank you
Kobayashi
I'm a cheerful person
You should read the characters
I'm sorry
Next, B team is also training the
customer
What kind of greeting will come out from
this store?
First, from Mayama
Thank you again
Welcome to the Meichan cafe
This is the one
Thank you
Kashiwagi
Welcome to Tokimeku Cafe
This is the boss' trick
Do I do that too?
Yes
Can I do it too?
Yes, please
Let's do it together
Welcome
Welcome to Tokimeki Cafe
Thank you
Ok, next, Hirota
Welcome to Furutsurutsura
It's pretty good.
OK, let's get started.
Yes.
Welcome to the cheerful and calm cafe.
This is the calm part.
It's calm.
I understand that you're cheerful, but
what does calm mean?
It means you're calm.
You mean my face?
No, I mean your heart.
I'm glad.
Thank you.
Here's an additional question from the
interviewer to Kobayashi.
What kind of food do you want to make in
this cafe?
I want to make dumplings.
Are you saying that to me?
No, I'm not.
Do you like it?
Dumplings.
That's correct.
Thank you.
The interview for the B team is over.
After this, we will announce the
candidates for the interview.
It's Nakayama Gokyu again!
I don't want to remember it.
So, we had a interview with everyone.
We had the A and B teams split into two.
First, we'd like to announce the people
who will be the candidates for the cafe
where the manager is.
By the way, how many people will be the
candidates?
Two people.
Then, please announce the first person.
Who will be the A team?
The first person to be announced is
Hoshina-san!
Why is this?
I think she is great at answering
questions
She laughed
Please announce the next person
Nakayama
Congratulations
What happened?
I'm not happy
Why?
I'm happy but I don't want to cry
You were crying
You were crying because you were scared
I was scared
Let's do our best with the manager
With the manager
Why are you crying?
I don't want to remember
Something terrible happened
Next is the manager of B store
There are 2 people who are working here
Please announce the next person
Who will be chosen as the B team?
Hidata Kashiwagi
Kashiwagi
Why did you choose this?
Tokimeki Cafe
This is it
You said you wanted to be the manager
I was surprised
It was good
Please announce the next person
Kobayashi
Why did you choose this?
I chose this because it's a new menu
Cafe with dumplings
Nakayama suddenly exploded
I was left behind at the end, I don't
like it anymore
It's the last one, it's an original
I did it, I said it
You didn't sell it, you didn't sell it
That's what the boss checks
So, if you add a university to Ebichu
I don't like it anymore
What happened?
What happened to Nakayama?
I don't need it anymore, I can't go to
the bank anymore
Nakayama Riko 14 years old, she decided
not to go to the cafe anymore
Sakura Ebi is on the front line
Auditions are held all over the country
From about 10,000 applicants
Ebichu Research Unit
Four members of Sakura Ebi are decided
Such girls
The first job is coming
It is the Tokyo Idol Festival 2015 where
more than 100 idols gather
Thank you very much
Sakuraibis is starting to work towards
the first appearance of the festival
And then
I'm going to take a picture of Aisha
after this, but before that I'll
introduce you to the new members
Let's go
I'm Akane Sora, I'm a first-year student
in middle school, nice to meet you
A new member has joined
Nice to meet you
Suddenly, no reaction
These 5 members will be participating in
the Tokyo Idol Festival
Let's have a lesson
If you feel like you fit in, you can
come in
I'm fine
I'm just in the mood
I'm in the mood
Then, nice to meet you
Nice to meet you
A fresh 1st year middle school student,
Sora Akane has joined
Sakura Beads will finally show their
true colors
In the program, Sakura Ebis who started
to move towards the Tokyo Idol Festival
in August
I will continue to follow them
Next time on Ebichu Sastas
Ebichu enjoys summer vacation
And the scary experience is
There is a doll
Ebichu's big panic
Wow!
Here is the announcement!
The main movie of Hinata Kashiwagi,
The Raging Girl,
will be shown nationwide from July 25th!
That's too cruel!
Don't miss it!
Furthermore,
The first photo book of Hinata Kashiwagi
will be released!
This program was provided by the sponsor
you are watching.
Please put down your weapon and get your
weapon!
If you don't give me 100 billion yen and
a car, I'll shoot you!
Where is that place?
The place where the memories accepted
Brian began!