I ate half of it, but I wanted to eat
more, so I'll take another one.
I ate two.
I'm happy.
I ate one.
You can still eat more.
Yes.
I ate one more.
You ate one more.
Good morning.
Today is the day of the festival.
Thank you for watching.
It's a little cold, but I made a mistake
in the season.
It's a little cold, so please make
yourself warm.
It's over, but...
How are you doing? Aren't you tired?
I'm tired of the live show, but I'm glad
I could do it.
Good job at work.
Good luck tomorrow.
See you in Osaka on Saturday.
Bye.
See you next time!
Good morning.
I got my hair and makeup done for the
first time today.
I'm all done.
I got my hair and makeup done for the
first time today.
I knew that I had to make this tour
longer.
I'm wearing a swimsuit right now.
I'm still doing it.
I cut my hair short.
I've been looking forward to this.
I'm going to eat this.
I'm shocked.
There's a whole one.
There's a half-up one.
I'm going to bring a comment and a go-
go.
Bye bye.
Good morning.
Today, a cat is out.
It was heavy.
How is it?
My eyelashes are curled up.
These are the lashes that are curled up
singly.
It was so hot this morning, but my mom
told me that it's cold in Shinkansen at
night.
I went to Shinkansen because it was hot,
but it was cold inside.
When I came to Osaka, it was so cold
that I thanked my mom.
I'm already sweating from the clothes.
There's something.
I think I should eat them everyday!
They Someone told me that I would look
cute if I put in weight
Sketch sunflower seeds
che echoes
custard
Thank you for your viewing.
I want to eat sweet chocolate milk.
What should I do?
I want to eat delicious food when I come
to Osaka.
By the way, I ate salad and soy milk in
the morning.
I ate salad and soy milk and decided to
go to the roadside station.
If I have such a thing, I will
definitely eat it.
Thank you for giving me something
delicious.
I will take a picture with Piyo.
The noodles are often made and
the soup has a great flavor
It was very tasty
Delicious
料理- Ninja
I made my nails shiny.
Oh, the focus is on our faces.
How is it?
Today, we are all together.
We are two.
I'm so happy.
Are you ready?
Yes, I am.
I'm a little different from HYOPOKU.
I think someone did it.
This is a very popular brand.
Baked Magic
Wow, it's cream cheese!
And raw chocolate mix!
Rich custard!
And this is raw chocolate!
Yay!
This is rare paper!
Bye bye!
Osaka!
I did very much like I was Haoko from
now on.
Nail
Yay! I ate it all!
Good morning!
I did my makeup!
Look!
Tada!
New hair arrangement!
This is probably my first time...
My first time in my life...
braiding...
How is it?
It's a little rare.
But today, everyone is taking pictures,
so I'm going to do my best to make it
look cute.
Then I would like to eat 551 again.
I ate 551.
Second time.
Oh!
Shoe cream!
Nail...
Sparkling!
It's cute, isn't it?
Isn't it rare?
I didn't put it down much.
Cute.
Is there a ribbon here?
Yes.
It's so cute!
Where is the
I don't think it's going to stick, so
I'll stop it.
Cute.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for yesterday.
Today is Tuesday, right?
Tomorrow is Tokimaro, Wednesday is
Tokimaro day.
Everyone is looking at the back.
Friday, again VLOG.
Oh, it's a VLOG.
Our VLOG.
Last year, I was on YouTube.
In the sales video..
We filmed a video in Sao Koka, so we
have a lot of videos of our dates.
Ah, Hitoka!
Hi!
Hitoka is going to show her forehead
today.
Oh, Hitoka is over there.
What? Which one?
Pasta or...
Pasta?
Then, this one.
Chocolate.
Milk choux.
Pasta?
You eat it properly.
I ate the golden one too.
Did you eat well?
I ate well.
Thank you for watching.
I don't want to eat it.
I'm waiting for Rikuro.
Kamen Rider Kamen Rider
Oh my god!
You came to see me?
What is that?
It's a canelé.
I'm so happy.
I like canelé.
I ate 1.5 canelé of 551 and cream puff.
You ate 1.5 canelé.
I'm eating a bento.
I can't eat it.
You can't eat it.
You came to see me.
I feel like an adult.
Where?
It's scary.
Look.
It's a canelé.
It's scary.
I'm scared of it.
I'm scared.
I'm back!
I got a little bit of a sprain.
I got a little sprain on my upper body.
I'm going to sleep.
I love Canelé.
I went to many convenience stores and
many other stores.
I'm very grateful to Canelé.
I'm a bit shy.
This is my new hairstyle.
I got a muffin the other day.
It's on Hiyori's story.
There was a chocolate-shaped lip.
And Hiyori's lips are two
It's like that chocolate.
It's like a way to make a mouth.
I put on lipstick.
I'm going to start.
Please say hello to the viewers.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
Hello, everyone.
We are Chou! Hikinichi TV.
Thank you for coming.
I'm Kano.
By cream to serve
So, let's go further
I'm sorry for not being able to see you
I don't need a fan anymore
1, 2, 3, 4!
Thank you for the rehearsal.
Thank you for the performance.
The rehearsal is over.
Checking the camera.
We went to Osaka!
I'm shocked!
What is this?
Matcha!
This is the last sweet potato.
Thank you for watching!
I'm not eating it because I'm on a diet.
I just collected the breath that I
forgot to take.
I'm sorry.
Yay!
No, not now!
Not now!
You did it!
Stop before the performance!
No!
No way!
Really?
Thank you very much.
It's been a month.
I'm looking forward to it.
I think there are many people who are
looking forward to it.
I'll do my best to answer.
Thank you very much.
Let's meet on July 22nd.
Let's do our best.
See you.
I can't take a picture of my friends.
Thank you for watching.
I didn't get to film it.
I'm so happy.
Yay!
I'm so excited.
Makuhari Messe, let's do our best!
Let's do our best!
Thank you for watching.
I'm ready to go home.
I'm more relaxed than others.
I got a candy.
Hitomi is ready.
It's not ready. It's in my mouth.
It's in your mouth.
It's a smell.
It's a terrible smell.
Calm down.
I'm going to dance to the first verse.
The first verse.
Today, we have a guest on the show.
Thank you for coming to the show.
I'm Hitomi from the show.
Hello.
I'm sorry to be late.
Everyone in Osaka and everyone watching
the show, I want to have a hot live.
Let's make wonderful memories together!
Please wait a little longer!
This is the end of the video.
Super idol.
I'm going to sing a super idol song.
Please sing.
Kanami, Julia, Toa, Haruko, Aki, Hiyori,
Chou, Tsukumi, Kisen, Ren.
Rock on!
Let's do our best!
Good luck, Kokuchi.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you.
Please wait for me.
See you later.
I'll do my best.
Bye bye. I'll do my best.
See you later.
I really like you.
Thank you.
I'll do my best even if I fail again.
Thank you for watching!
Thank you very much for the Osaka
concert!
Thank you for your hard work!
Thank you for your hard work.
After this, we will do live streaming.
After talk.
Thank you for your hard work.
Osaka Koe's Osaka Koe.
It was fun.
It was good to have a live in Osaka.
We also had a live streaming.
I was happy to have many people
watching.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
Thank you for watching.
I'm so happy to be here. Thank you so
much.
We have Sendai left. We'll do our best!
Touch, touch!
We want to deliver the biggest
excitement to as many people as
possible.
We want to be a good library that can
step up through this Macarie Mese.
We want to improve our performance so
that we don't lose to this company.
I'm really looking forward to seeing the
smiles of the young men.
I want to make a lot of memories.
I think it would be fun if the six of us
could go to various places.
On October 22nd, let's go to the Tokusen
Macarie!
I'm always crying
I wash away my dirty thoughts
Otherwise, I can't walk
Let's go anywhere
Goodbye goodbye to me yesterday
The cityscape after the rain is
sparkling
It's like my heart is clear
I'll play the piano of the rainbow with
the sound of the puddle
I wonder why? When I smile, it seems
like the world is shining
I can relax by turning the umbrella
Otherwise, I can't walk
Someone is crying somewhere
I'm getting wet somewhere again
Isn't it cold?
Someone is crying somewhere
I want to share my feelings with you
I'm still in front of you
I don't know the scenery 今は知らない景色
Let's go anywhere ほらどこまででも行こう
Goodbye, Goodbye, Thank you for
yesterday さよなら、グッバイ、昨日にありがとう
The cityscape after the rain is colored
雨上がりの街並みは色づいて
Hey, I'll draw a fragment of the future
on the canvas of my broken heart
Guiding me
I can say it now, even the reason for my
tears
When I get lost, I immediately remember
Even if it rains, I'll smile
Look, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye to me from yesterday
The cityscape after the rain is
sparkling
My heart is like a spring
I play the sound of the wind and play
the rainbow piano
Goodbye, goodbye
The town after the rain glitters on me
from yesterday
My heart is like a flower, covering the
clouds with tears
I wear a rainbow dress
Subscribe to our channel!