Yakan and idol!
And the second one is?
Music
What kind of genre is this?
I listen to Western music and pop music.
So you've been listening to music since
you were little?
Yes, I've been listening to music since
I was little.
Oh, really?
I used to drive a car when I was little.
I used to listen to music on DVDs and
radio.
I used to listen to it while I was
driving.
Your parents influenced you a lot.
I think so.
You made your own music in your car.
Is it the same at home?
Yes, I listen to music at home.
If I had a music that was important to
me, I would have been a singer.
I'm sorry.
That's the best part.
What is your life without music?
No music, no live.
I think so.
I've heard that.
That's it.
Stage drink
I drink stage drinks.
Really?
You drink stage drinks?
My dream is to be a famous singer.
I want to be a star since I was young.