Thank you for watching.
I'm a fan of your channel.
Oh, thank you.
I'm glad to hear that.
Thank you.
I'm happy to finish the manga.
I read the manga many times, so I don't
feel sad.
Thank you for watching.
It depends on the season. In summer, I
want to eat ice cream.
In winter, I want to eat ice cream with
a lot of milk.
I also eat ice cream with water.
I read the manga when I eat.
I didn't mean to be like that.
I didn't mean to be down-to-earth.
I was down-to-earth.
I like what I like.
But I don't like other things because I
like this.
I like it broadly.
I want to know more about it.
What does it mean to whom?
I think there are many things that will
come out.
I think it's Nao.
I think Nao has a lot of secrets.
She looks cool at first glance, but she
has a hot heart.
What is it?
I would like to hear more about Nao.
About her future, strategy, etc.
She is like a tricycle. She thinks about
various things about the group.
I would like to hear more about her.
What should I say?
I'm usually a person who doesn't talk
much to myself.
I can answer if I'm asked, but I'm shy.
I can talk to people with common themes
of conversation.
I like manga.
I like Shinju-chan from Paboku-san.
I like Shinju-chan's jump.
I heard that Kojima-Hana from
Anirakushin also likes One Piece.
I'd like to work with her.
Thank you for watching.
It was fun.
I was so happy to talk with Yakan and
Kanamin today.
I was laughing all the time.
I feel warm all the time.
I'm talking only about fun things.
I had a plan to go glamping before, but
I couldn't do it.
So I want to make it come true.
And I want to go to a hot spring because
I'm relaxed.
I like it.
When I have a trip, I go to a nearby hot
spring.
I do it with all the members including
the staff.
I went to Kumamoto with Sakura Nao and
Yufuin.
We stayed at the hotel again.
To be continued...
The day of the group's formation is
actually September, 2011.
It was when we were auditioning for the
Star Dust Nagoya group.
We were introduced to a group of girls
who were interested in becoming idols.
So we asked if they would be our idols
for a day.
That was the beginning of our group.
I think everyone knows that.
Yes.
We were asked to be our idols for a day.
We were asked to act as our idols.
Act as our idols?
Why would you try to hide it from us?
Right?
You should have told us.
We were originally idols of Momokuro-
chan.
But we joined the company when it was
not an idol agency.
So we were all models and actresses.
We were a group of people who didn't
even think of becoming idols.
I see.
But we tried it once and it was so much
fun.
And we wanted to continue it.
We were doing a 3B Junior annual
festival.
Yes, we were.
We announced that we wanted to continue
it as a team president.
I thought you were going to get in
trouble.
No, no.
We wanted to do it.
And we made our debut in Nagoya.
I see.
That was our first anniversary.
So April 12th is...
April 7th.
Oh, it's April 7th.
And then the 10th anniversary.
Yes, the 10th anniversary. It's from
2012.
The most popular manga for boys?
It's hard to say.
My favorite manga is...
Bible? I see.
Naruto.
Naruto?
I can't shake this feeling.
I'm here because of Naruto.
I see.
I was working hard, so I was able to do
my best.
I see.
By the way, what is the target age for
the jump?
Now?
The basic policy of boy's jump is...
There are about 6 levels.
There are 6 levels?
6 levels of difficulty.
That's right.
For example, you can't put in a gravure.
You can't put in a gravure.
The target age is from 2nd to 3rd grade.
I can't put in a gravure.
Of course, it's not a gravure now.
But there are more and more people who
are good at it.
But of course, the boy's jump is not out
yet.
The boys think it's interesting.
I think that the way to make a manga
that people think is interesting hasn't
changed.