Who will be the strongest?
Don't be tempted by the bonds between
the two.
Tonight, the first match of the Ebitune
Strongest Tag Tournament will begin!
slogan
Let's add various things to the private
Middle finger
The story of the Grande Mag tum
This program is with the support of the
sponsor
Thank you.
Good luck!
It has started! Ebichu Tastas!
This summer, I want to go to Hawaii. I
will be in charge of the two-man team.
Hawaii!
I want to go to Hawaii this summer.
Please go there without permission.
Today, I'm here at the practice room of
Pro Wrestling Noah in Rifa, Ariake.
There are some real rings.
I've never seen it so close.
It's big.
So, you are going to do Pro Wrestling
today?
What are you doing?
I haven't heard anything.
Pro Wrestling is scary.
There is no Shuei.
Where is he?
Uncle Akira?
What? What is this music?
Something came.
I'm hungry.
Uncle Akira.
There is nothing here.
Excuse me.
Who are you?
Aren't you Shuei?
I'm not Shuei.
You're not Shuei?
I'm Maiba Hachue.
Maiba Hachue?
Noah has a pro wrestler called Maiba
Hachue.
Everyone doesn't know about Pro
Wrestling.
Everyone knows.
The mysterious pro wrestler Maiba Hachue
will announce the theme.
Maiba Hachue, are you going to do pro
wrestling today?
No!
You're not?
You're not going to do pro wrestling?
Today's theme is the strongest team in
Ebitune.
The strongest team in Ebitune?
What does that mean?
The strongest team will be decided.
The strongest team?
This time, Ebitune Tastas is the
strongest team in Ebitune.
The four teams will compete to decide
the strongest team.
So, first, they will be divided into
their favorite team.
Let's announce the team.
Mayama Hoshino's team.
Yes, it's a tag team.
And Yasumoto Oshima's team.
And...
Hoshino Takashiro's team.
No, no, no!
It's not like that!
What?
There's no point in you guys sticking
together like that!
It's not like that!
It's because you're in the same team!
Isn't that right?
So, you two, who don't usually stick
together,
should be the strongest team.
Wait!
Why?
Then, why did you let them do it?
And so, the tag team that the host
decided on his own.
Okay, then!
Let's announce the tag team!
Okay, then, the first team.
What?
It's already decided.
First, Mayama Nakayama's team.
Oh!
That's true, I haven't seen them before.
But, they usually go home together.
You guys are just going to eat and go
home together, right?
Okay, then, the next team.
Yasumoto Kashiyaki's team.
That's quite common.
They often win together.
You guys have never been in a team
before, right?
That's right!
Next,
the next team is...
Hirono Matsuno's team.
That's right!
I'm happy.
But, I'm happy too.
And lastly,
Lastly,
Yes?
Kobayashi Hoshino's team.
That's really common!
He always walks like this.
To increase the connection between the
two teams,
this time,
the tag team that the host didn't see
them before
was decided on his own.
The top 2 teams that will have 3
preliminary matches in this tag team
will advance to the final match.
The two teams that have been the
strongest team in the first round of the
tournament
will receive the champion belt.
Now, let's see the first match of the
qualifier.
You're back to the center.
I was late today.
Congratulations.
I see.
Now, let's see the first match of the
qualifier.
This is the エビチュータッグ完全一致クイズ.
This match, there is a question.
You have to answer it.
You read the mind of the tag partner.
If the two answers are the same, you get
10 points.
That's the rule.
The first match of the qualifier is
完全一致クイズ.
If you get the answer of the tag
partner, you get a point.
The match is decided by how you read the
mind of the tag partner and get the
answer.
Now, let's see the first question.
Who is the most reliable among the
Ebityu members?
Wait, I'm lost.
Lost?
I haven't seen a girl who is so troubled
by the loan.
Because...
I don't know, but I'll write it anyway.
Wait, I wrote it.
Fast.
Good.
Hirota changed.
Are you ready?
I'll go.
3,2,1
Time's up.
It's okay, but the camera is shaking.
I can't see.
What is Matsuno's answer?
Let's see Matsuno's answer.
And...
Hirota's answer is...
Matsuno's answer is...
I can't think of anything!
That's true!
If you don't answer correctly, you'll be
so embarrassed!
That's right!
Let's continue!
Kashiwagi, please answer!
I changed it once, but...
Kashiwagi's answer is...
It's really complicated!
The answer is...
I wrote Hirota-chan
But if you think about the total, there
are many
So if you put them together, Hirota's is
more reliable than Hoshina's
I don't know
It's not Japanese at all
If Yasumoto wrote Hirota here, it would
be correct
Yasumoto, please
Correct!
I think Hinata is relying on Aiai-san
because she has a strong image of being
supported by Aiai-san
I think she is relying on Hinata the
most
That's a great answer!
As expected of Kobayashi-san
Of course, Yasumoto is the answer to
Kobayashi who is
Hoshina, can you see through her heart?
Hoshina, is the answer correct?
It's this one!
Ah, Hirota!
I see
I thought it was a question that suits
Aiai-san
It's like she knows everything
She said it
I see, it's just that she is the
teacher's
It's this one
As for Hoshina, Yasumoto, do you think
she can rely on her?
You think so, right?
That's right
What is that?
You're completely being pushed
And Mayama Nakayama's answer is also
incorrect
Next up is the second question
Who is the most selfish member during
the debut?
This is difficult
There are two people
Recently, there are two or three people
Everyone's face is on the screen
Let's go
Mayu, please
This is a little different
Wait
It's not selfish, but I can't do
anything by myself
I think that's what it means
Wait a minute, is the person next to you
dead?
It was good
The person next to you
I don't know what selfish means
Selfish?
It's hard to understand
That's right, but it's written
Please open it
It's not selfish
It's a win-win situation
Mayama Nakayama's team
Unfortunate and incorrect
Hoshina, open!
Riko-chan
Write your name and erase it
Erase my name
This is according to Kobayashi
Yes, so Kaho-chan
If it's not me, it's probably Riko-chan
I see
You're thinking well
As expected, Kobayashi-san, please
Hoshina-san?
Ah, too bad
Hoshina, you're wrong
And which one is the best for Hirono and
Matsu?
I don't know but it's the best for
Ebichu
Ebichu's selfish member, who is it?
And the one who is waiting is...
Kashiwagi!
Amazing!
Basically, Kashiwagi is selfish
There are things like being good at
being spoiled by adults
I'm stuck with my manager
I'm in trouble
What kind of trouble?
I'm worried because I'm like a child
The remaining members are the Kashiwagi
team
By the way, which team did you choose?
I chose Hinata
From the beginning
I'm sure Hinata will choose this team
I see
Then, Yasumoto, please
Kashiwagi
Kashiwagi, please
Amazing
This is amazing
Isn't it amazing?
Amazing
What is the strength of Yasumoto's game?
What?
Are you good at this?
I don't know
I thought I would play a game and write
I see
I thought I would be the type to write
I see. You read it that far
I see
Yasumoto read the character of Kashiwagi
She got 2 correct answers and took the
lead
Let's continue
It's fun
Nakayama-san
What did you say?
It's fun
Thank you
It's been a while since I heard
Nakayama's fun
I said I hate it when I sang Ebichu
I'm glad
The final question
If you get it right, you will get 30
points 3 times
Where do you want to go on a trip
abroad?
Let's go on a trip abroad
Matsuno was so cool just now
Match me
For some reason, Matsuno is full of
confidence
The reason is
This summer, I want to go to Hawaii
Matsuno will try to stay in Japan
Matsuno said she wanted to go to Hawaii
in the opening talk
This is
This is for us
This is...
Should we go with the safe one?
The safe one is better
Okay, I got it
I got it
I got the reason why I wanted to go
Ai-chan wrote it
Matsuno-san said, let me go
Matsuno, Hirota, Taku, let's go
Let's go together
Please
Hawaii, Hawaii
Correct
It's amazing
Matsuno said she wanted to go to Hawaii
Toshina and Goyashi team also went to
Hawaii
It's a wonderful world
The answer of Mayama Nakayama team who
said they got the reason why they wanted
to go is...
Who did you match this with? Riko-chan
You matched with Nakayama
Let's see this one too
Ready, go!
Canada! Canada!
Aurora!
I want to see Aurora! It's written here
It's true!
Did you say it often?
I said it a lot before but I don't think
I can do it anymore
You haven't given up yet?
If you give up at Nakayama's age, how
can we live?
Don't make us feel sad!
You still have a chance
I won't give up
You won't give up
It's been a long time
The answer of Yasumoto Kashiwagi team
who can read each other's mind is...
Let's open it together
Hawaii! Guam!
It's a shame
I want it!
I thought Hirata didn't want to go to
Hawaii.
If I say it's safe, it's either Guam or
I want to go to New York.
It's not a good match at all.
It's safe!
The last one didn't have a clue.
The Kashiwagi team missed 30 points in
the final question and fell to the
bottom.
After this, the second match will be
decided.
The second match of the preliminary
round is the tag team's team work speed
rescue match.
This match is a tag team match with one
eye blindfolded and the other one with
the hand on the ring.
The blindfolded team members will spin 5
times in the ring and the tag team
members will be guided by the
blindfolded team members.
The blindfolded team will take off the
hand and the blindfolded team will
compete for the time to spin 5 times in
the ring.
If ı get ı first place, 40 points.
Which ı will show ı strength of ı bond?
First, Mayama Nakayama vs Yasumoto
Kashiwagi
So, you are ready
You are blindfolded
Mayama-san, you are the one, right?
Thank you
And Yasumoto-san, please put on the
blindfold
I didn't put it on?
I did
You did, right?
Yes
It suits you so well
It suits me too well
I'm sorry
So, you will spin 5 times
1, 2, 3, 4, 5
So fast
Ready, start
Wait, wait, wait
Wait, wait
No, it's not that kind of game
So fast
Wait, wait, wait
You are almost there
Good
Take off your blindfold
Please take off your blindfold
Please
Calm down
Calm down and take off your blindfold
Don't take off your blindfold
I took off my blindfold
You did it
Please spin 5 times
1, 2, 3, 4, 5
One more time
Ready, start
You are almost there
1, 2, 3, 4, 5
One more time
You did it
1, 2, 3, 4, 5  Time is up
It was almost the same time
It was a good match
This kind of thing is fun and makes me
laugh
I'm glad that you enjoyed it
I'm glad
Next up is Hirota vs Hoshina Kobayashi
Are you ready?
Hoshina-san, are you angry?
Don't mess with me
You're really angry
Calm down
Matsuno-san, you're really serious today
Really serious
The first pose was definitely different
I was told to be serious so I thought it
was this
Her eyes are serious
So are you ready?
Let's start
1, 2, 3
4, 5
Ready, start
This is the relay
Mine-chan, this way
Fast, fast
Fast
It's hard
Take it off
It's off
In the middle
1, 2
Again
Ready, start
1, 2
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10
Time's up!
This side is shaking
Do your best
Why are you so slow?
I'm the slowest
Ready, set, go
You're almost there
Do your best
Ready, set, go
You're almost there
I don't know
I don't know the reason
Matsuno can't jump
Time up
Matsuno and Hirota's team is not going
to win
The game is over here
I'm looking forward to the result of the
game
I think I'm the winner
Shut up
Hirota and Matsuno's time is over
Of course they are the 4th place
Who is the winner?
This is difficult
The 3rd place is
Yasumoto and Kashiwagi's team
53.12 seconds
Let's go to the 2nd place
Mayama Nakayama's team, 52.56 seconds
By the way, what was the time of the 3rd
place?
The 3rd place is 53.12 seconds, so it's
about 1 second
It was close
And the 1st place is Hoshina Kobayashi's
team, congratulations
It's a close call, 35.75 seconds
After 2 rounds of qualifying, the winner
is as you can see
Will Yasumoto and Kashiwagi team be able
to turn the tables?
Which team will win the champion belt?
The next episode will be next week!
EDICHU Game Quest
EDICHU Game Project started last April
Tonight, we have a shocking announcement
Zero
Let's see
A letter
The game of Ebichu is finally completed
Really?
Really? It's finally done?
The members of the Ebi-Chu team have
also participated in the development of
the game project.
Finally, the game is complete!
The full picture is now available on the
Ebi-Chu website!
First, we will show you the title screen
of the game
The
Eh, it's cute!
Oh my, oh my, oh my
Oh, it's cute!
This is the home screen.
Yay!
It's me!
We will play a game that will be the
core of this game.
It's important!
There are many quests, so you can choose
from various things.
There is a screen called Skit here.
This is, for example,
If you play this game and become friends
with Hirota,
You can see Hirota's character here.
Everyone can do it!
This game is free to play by selecting 4
people from 8 Ebichu members.
You will play a pulling action game with
4 people you chose.
It's a little different from the
previous version.
You can put various shapes of balls.
Like this.
And put it on the top.
Oh, timing.
Yes, you have to put it in the middle.
I'm not good at it, so I took it off.
I beat it.
I won.
That's the flow of the game.
Amazing!
Next time, we'll reveal more game
information.
Breaking news! The game Ebitune is
finally releasing soon!
Currently, it's being pre-registered for
general users.
Depending on the number of pre-
registered players, the number of items
you can get will change.
For more information, search on the
Stardust channel.
Next time, we'll be more and more
excited! The strongest Ebitune tag team
championship!
I'll get my abs back! My skin is white!
Who will be the first team to beat the
mysterious battle and show the bond of
Ebitune?
Finally, the first Ebitune strongest
team is decided!
Please look forward to it!
This program was provided by the sponsor
you are watching.
Kashiwagi Taken!