It's night the daru
Do you have any announcements?
We are going to be doing a live stream
on YouTube every Monday at 8pm.
It's called Amahira Shaberi, and we're
going to be shooting it in the middle of
the night.
We're going to be doing it for the 100th
time.
I hope you'll be able to see us in a
more fun and linear way every Monday.
Please look forward to it.
What's next?
After talking about the rain, we're
going to be doing a radio show called
Oame Chuiho, which is a rain-related
news program.
You're doing a regular program on the
Inter-NUM, right?
That's right.
30 minutes every Monday.
Four of us?
We're doing it with four people.
I've been doing it with Shinagaki
Mainabi lately.
I've been doing it with a guest, and
I've been doing it with IME.
That's amazing.
That's right.
Are you wearing it properly?
Please stop looking at me like that.
I'm just kidding.
Who's next?
I'm going to be doing it with Ame-chan.
She's the one who makes NFT art.
Kojima Hana sold NFT art, so I asked her
to learn from the beginning.
It's a corner of the frame.
Before that, we talked about our daily
lives.
The time has changed to 9.30, but before
that, it was about 11 o'clock.
At that time, it was said that it was a
radio that couldn't sleep.
It's a bad radio that's uncomfortable to
sleep on.
That's nice.
What do you do in your free time?
It's not a comfortable radio that you
can sleep on before you go to bed.
I'm doing this on the radio.
I'm doing a shoulder-pulling.
If you mix this with this food, it'll be
like this.
What happens if you mix honey and
yogurt?
I'm doing that.
I'm doing things that I wouldn't do on
the radio.
Please listen to it.
Yes.
Finally, I'd like you to drink tea to
cheer you up.
I'm going to drink tea today.
Jasmine tea.
Is it okay?
I don't usually drink tea.
I don't usually drink green tea.
I don't usually drink it.
What's that image?
It's my own image.
I made it up.
But I don't usually drink it.
But I love Karada Square Kacha.
I drink it every day.
I'll have it.
Is it hot?
It's delicious.
Jasmine tea is not so tasty.
It's very delicious.
I don't drink tea, but I can eat Sadobu.
I see.
I eat sweets.
You eat sweets?
Yes.
Like a snack?
I was lost between Sadobu and Kadobu.
I lost to the answer to the question,
I can eat sweets in Sadobu.
I see.
Yes.
That's all.
Lastly, please close the camera.
Please come to see us at our live.
This is Amefurashi's one-time love.
Bye-bye.
Oh, you came? Nice to meet you!
I'm so happy!
Huh? Yeah.
Oh, I see. Thank you!
What pose should I do?
Anything is fine.
Ah, let's make a heart together.
Thank you.
Here I go.
Okay, cheese!
Thank you! What's your name?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, really? Thank you!
Second Idol!
This program is brought to you by...
Ghi-san
Yuzuki no Toshikatsu-san
Mana Cream-san
Itchy-san
I was able to deliver them all thanks to
Hiro-san's support.
Thank you for watching!