I'm so tired.
I'm like, I've been on a lot of taxis.
I'm pretty serious.
I use it a lot.
I'm so tired.
I pretended to be stupid and gave up
I can't see it, but I can see it
I pretended to understand and cried
So today is Kira Mei-chan
Why are you so nervous?
I don't know, but I don't have to be
asked by the members
After all, the interviewer
And I don't know
Since Mei-chan first entered WAKK?
After the show, until she passed the
training camp
If you calculate the shortest time, it's
probably about a month and a half
It's fast
You came to WAKK with Nass
I didn't put it out in the world, but I
started working as a paradise
Certainly
I started preparing
If Mei-chan or Ainas-chan is invited,
it's really amazing
I was really surprised because Mei-chan
was invited
Yes, it's Kira Mei
Thank you for a week
Because the limit is not beyond the
training camp
I will never set my own limits from now
on
I will always perform beyond the limits
I will think about it and do my best
Young Ballad
Kira Mei
Yes
Please stand up
I want to talk about the incident, but I
couldn't see the bra at that training
camp.
Can I say that?
I was scolded.
I think I was scolded by the staff.
I was angry at this moment.
I told the manager of WAG that it was a
live broadcast.
I still think this.
I changed my clothes.
I don't want to get angry at the
paradise.
Everyone is there and the entrance is
close.
I said that it was really bad because I
could see it from the outside.
I agree.
I will do my best with a smile.
Let's do our best.
Paradise sex.
Mei entered the training camp.
How was it?
I was very nervous.
I can't think of anything now.
I can talk lightly now.
I was like Tsukino-chan, good morning.
I was wearing a cat.
The audition was terrible.
I don't remember half of the audition.
I was thinking about what to do.
I felt like I was supporting rather than
pulling.
I want to do my best together.
I will announce the future of Paradise.
The song that will be the winner of
Paradise is...
I thought it was love.
But I was surprised by Uta-chan's
reaction.
I was worried about what would happen
next.
I was in a hurry to do something.
I was worried about what would happen
next.
It's difficult.
Mei is serious.
The story of the two of you is a little
thick.
How can the interviewer tell the story?
It was difficult.
Mei, do you have a boyfriend?
I'm not her boyfriend.
Really?
I don't have a boyfriend.
What about your boyfriend?
I had a crush on someone.
I was in a moving classroom.
I didn't know the way.
I asked the teacher for help.
I asked him where the computer room was.
He guided me all the way.
At the end, he let me go.
He told me to guide the boy.
He said, please give me a little help.
After that, I talked to him.
He said, I might be a little shy.
What are you doing?
I'm doing it!
I wasn't excited at all.
I was like,
Ah, it's the sea.
Ah, ah, ah, ah.
I didn't do anything.
So I didn't do anything more than that.
Be careful.
Don't get caught by a weird person.
I'm told by my friends and everyone.
They tell me to pinch myself once.
Pinch all 13 people at once.
I'm scared.
I'm scared. If I get caught by 13
people,
I'll be the fifth person to pinch a boy.
I'll be like,
Oh, it's okay.
We are working on a project to bring out
the back side of the story.
I think I'm pretty bad at it, I think
I'm pretty bad at it compared to
Tsukino-chan.
I pretended not to hear you, even though
I could hear you
I pretended to be stupid and gave up
I can't see the future