It's boooth time!
The third one is...
Idol!
I've been saying this for a long time.
The place where I was scouted was a live
performance of Momokoro-chan.
Oh, really?
She called me at the free event of Kaito
Shoujo.
I've been following idols since then.
If I keep following them, I'll be a
mini-moni.
I heard that you loved them when you
were a kid.
Your parents said so.
I heard so.
So you have a lot of memories.
I have a little memory.
It's too small to remember.
But my parents told me that
I danced to their songs no matter how
sick I was.
Wow!
That's great.
It's good to talk about things you don't
remember.
It seems that's where I lost my drop
singing.
I became an idol and went to see various
idols.
I've been getting more and more into it.
I see.
If you still want to sing and dance,
that's fine, right?
That's right.
Haruna is fine.
I'm doing it while thinking that.
I've been watching various idols.
I feel like the way I see idols has
changed since I graduated from
Takorizawa.
What do you mean?
When you were doing it yourself or in a
group?
I was away from the group and I was
attracted to idols' songs.
I also became very attracted to
songwriters.
I see.
I like the lyrics of the idol song.
I feel like I'm getting more and more
into that.
If you were to recommend an idol you
like,
what would it be?
Hello Pro...
I think it's Ochanoma-san.
Ochanoma-san?
He was announced as the new member of
the group.
He's the new member.
Ochanoma-san is a member of the Hello
Pro 9th generation.
He was one of the members of the group.
The song has a very old-fashioned Hello
Pro feel.
Like, this is how Hello Pro songs should
be.
Like, this is Hello Pro.
There are many songs with a very unique
feel.
There are a lot of lines in the song.
But it's catchy.
I think it's a group that reintroduces
that kind of thing.
I'm paying attention to it now.
In a new group.
I've seen it in a positive way.
That's what Hello Pro is about.
I watch idol videos.
I listen to the radio.
I also like dramas.
I watch about 25 shows every week.
I don't have enough time to consume
content.
I'm always on the lookout for the right
time.
Here it comes.
It's a modern feeling.
Life is about being on the lookout for
the right time.
I feel like I'm living the last week.
I'm about two weeks late.
When I'm getting ready in the morning, I
watch a drama.
I listen to the radio on the move.
I'm having fun while doing it.
I see.
Let's start the program!
Haruna Mai's...
This program is...
Hasta-san
Lutis-san
Okuyan-san
Satoma-san
This video is brought to you by Fuji-
san.
See you again!