I'm an idol.
The second song is Bonjiri.
This song has been said since middle
school.
I think people who support me are
thinking of me as Bonjiri.
I like Bonjiri so much that I used to
make bento from scratch.
I made two bento.
This is a part of the butt.
I want you to taste it.
I want to eat it.
I made it into one side.
I've never heard of Bonjiri bento.
I made it with AYA and NANO.
I've never eaten Bonjiri.
I ate the bento.
I ate the first Bonjiri of their lives.
What kind of reaction did you make?
I don't know if you paid attention, but
it was very delicious.
I said Chuu-chan's Bonjiri was the best.
How old are you?
I'm 7 years old.
I met Haruna Sakamoto from SHACHI in the
office a while ago.
There are few people who like Bonjiri.
Haruna really likes Bonjiri.
She said that she would take me to a
good Bonjiri shop next time.
I made a friend.
I'm sorry.
I'm looking forward to it.
Please do it a lot.
I'm going to drink it.
I can write strange letters.
What is that?
Recently...