It's cooking!
This week's Ebichu Tastas is the first
time in the history of Ebichu.
All the members are going to have a
cooking battle.
And then...
Wait a minute!
I'm not ready!
You just said, ALE, right?
A voice is echoing in the kitchen.
What kind of food will it be?
Be careful!
It's a stomach accident!
A bad feeling.
Ebichu Tastas Start!
In the middle of the school year,
I'll try to add a lot of things to my
private Ebisu middle school!
Ebichu Tastas
Moratorium, Moratorium, middle school
year
I'll try to add a lot of things to my
private Ebisu middle school!
Ebichu Tastas
This program is brought to you by the
following sponsors.
You're tough, so you can do it!
Thank you!
I'm not sure if I can do it
It's started, Ebi Chu Tastasu
Yeah, it's started
Recently, there are many foods that I'm
addicted to
I'm going to be the daily worker of
Matsuno Rinagai, who is always worried
What are you addicted to?
It's shaved ice, isn't it?
I'm addicted to it
I'm addicted to milk tea and fried rice
You're addicted to milk tea too
Are you addicted to drinks?
Today, Matsuno is the main character
What are you going to do today?
Tell us, Matsuno
I'm going to cook
What's that?
Cooking?
So, the first episode
We're going to cook
Please look forward to the next episode!
This is a competition between EBICHU and
the first EBICHU cooking competition.
Have they ever cooked?
First, let's check their cooking skills.
Who is good at cooking EBICHU?
Mayama and Aika.
Mayama and Hirota.
I see.
I asked everyone in advance about their
cooking skills.
Mayama is good at cooking.
She is a professional cook.
What is the Japanese food other than
fish?
You have to remove the fish.
It's difficult to remove the bones.
Did you make all the Japanese food
except for fish?
You can make it by looking at the
recipe.
YUBA?
YUBA is a soy milk.
I see.
Who are you?
You are good at making YUBA.
This is NAKAYAMA.
I didn't ask you about your cooking
skills.
I didn't ask you either.
This is a marble and egg-shaped dish.
This is the thickness of the word.
I want to know your cooking skills.
Aika?
Aiai is good at cooking.
I recently made ZAHATORT for my sister's
birthday.
ZAHATORT?
This is a chocolate cake.
This is a cake that makes the outside of
the cake smooth.
I have seen this.
The members except for HIROTA and MAYAMA
are not confident.
They have little cooking experience.
Children who don't know and challenge
will be surprised.
EBIchu Ryorio Ketteisen
Long Long
The first round is
Futomaki competition
So, the first round is
We will have a competition with Futomaki
We can do it
If this is it, what is your specialty?
I have one
10 years ago
By the way, what is the first time you
made Futomaki?
Who?
Yasumoto has one
I love Temakizushi
I have been to some events
I make Temakizushi with the one I roll
So, this is
It has a special part
I can be the first
I don't know yet
The first round is
Futomaki competition
The members will use their cooking
experience and sense
to make the original Futomaki
As you can see,
they will choose their favorite
ingredients
and make their own original Futomaki
Which one will be combined
will be decided by the members
So,
the first round is
Futomaki competition start!
20 minutes limit!
Ready, start!
Where are you going?
Kobayashi is like a zombie
I'm going to go too
Wow!
Everyone is moving separately
Everyone has their own way of doing it
What about Mayama?
Mayama sympathizes with Kyary Pamyu
Pamyu
You've got rid of the weird parts of the
fish, haven't you?
Yes, I have.
It looks cheap.
I'll start with rice.
You look like you're used to it.
I'm used to it.
I often make Tamaki-sushi, which you
know.
I'm going home early because it's
Tamaki-sushi for dinner.
Are you looking forward to Tamaki-sushi?
I love Tamaki-sushi.
This is a big advantage.
I don't know what Tamaki-sushi is.
I like Cheddar cheese.
I'll eat rice with Cheddar cheese.
I think it's good.
I like it.
What is Tamaki-sushi?
Hayama is doing it silently.
It's fine.
This is...
It's quite...
No, no, no.
It's too much for a meal.
What are you talking about?
It's enough for a meal.
Can I use this?
I think it's quite difficult to eat this
with vinegar.
Kobayashi has no sense of opening the
bowl.
But, it's fine.
You're not good at opening the bowl.
It was good at the atmosphere.
Yasuha is eating fast.
Is there a lot of ingredients?
Yes, there is.
Is this the point?
Yes, my father often makes this.
Is that so?
Mayonnaise is a lot.
My father likes a rich taste.
Mayama is good at cooking.
Why did you use tuna, avocado and natto?
I didn't make a mistake.
You didn't make a mistake.
Yasumoto has finished eating.
He is fast.
Please subscribe to this channel.
She is used to it.
She is just doing it at home.
Mayama, wait.
Mayama, are you going to do it?
You are too much.
Let's go.
Mayama, you can push it.
It's just right.
You can push it.
You can do it.
She is in a hurry.
This is it for this time.
That upsides down
What the?
I think it's over
Beautiful
Also some
Nice one
Wait a sec
Yasutomo and ella are almost done
Amazing! That was fast! Yasumoto is
done!
I'm done!
Hashiraki is done!
It's beautiful!
It's slanted.
I'm going to eat it.
I don't think it's going to taste bad.
It looks good.
Wait a minute.
The leftmost part of Kobayashi is going
to be weird.
It's going to be a mess.
You have one minute left. Hurry up.
You're not done yet?
Mayama is trying to destroy the
evidence.
The two who are done are sitting next to
me.
That's amazing.
I'm done!
Kobayashi is done.
And Mayama is...
Mayama is still trying to destroy the
evidence.
Destroying the evidence?
Mayama, this is not a segment where you
eat.
It's a success.
Mayama is done.
I'm done.
I'm not going to eat it.
Here are the four original futomaki.
They're somehow in shape, but what about
the taste?
It was fun.
Because you're already doing it.
It was so fast.
I love making futomaki.
It was already over in about half an
hour.
But the evaluation is the taste.
Is that so?
That's right. This is important.
Next, these four will try to make
original futomaki.
So, the second half team, start the
futomaki battle!
I'm nervous.
The time limit is 20 minutes.
But, since this is the first half, there
are a lot of hints.
That's right.
First, Hoshina will take the
ingredients.
Everyone except Hoshina will make sushi
rice.
Nagayama, have you ever made sushi rice?
No.
And, Hirota, you also went to get the
ingredients.
I'm cooking.
Oh, I see.
You're bringing all the seaweed.
Wait a minute.
Hoshina is bringing all the seaweed.
You can't do it alone.
It's for everyone.
That's right.
I'm going to put all the cucumbers.
Nagayama is going to use cucumbers.
Wait a minute.
The cucumbers are gone.
I like to eat it with rice.
You like to eat it with rice.
It's delicious.
Where are the chopsticks?
Hirota, you're mixing it.
I'm mixing everything.
Hoshina, are you okay?
Did you mix the vinegar and apple juice?
Are you okay?
I can put everything in.
Put everything in here.
He's making an arrangement.
You're just waiting for it to be done.
It doesn't taste like what I know.
Please make it taste like what you know.
I hope it tastes like what you know.
Please make it new.
How is it?
Is it too much vinegar or not?
It's not much.
But I think it's good.
But it's not a big deal.
She's putting rice on the seaweed.
That's right.
She's fixing it.
It's a rice ball.
She's making a rice ball.
She's cute.
Are you making a rice ball?
I'm making a rice ball.
Rice ball.
She said no.
Look, I can see sesame seeds.
You can see sesame seeds.
Because you put sesame seeds in it.
That's right.
What's this?
It looks like a tail.
It's coming.
Are you okay, Tako?
I made a mistake.
I think it's a little bit...
But it's looking good.
I see.
It's a bit too much.
It's too much.
Please subscribe to the channel.
Iketa's voice is so funny.
Did you hear Elmo?
You heard Elmo, right?
Don't laugh!
Did you hear Elmo?
Yes, I heard Elmo.
We made Ryota!
Ryota is done!
It's beautiful.
I'm ready.
You look so cute.
Hoshina is in the kitchen.
You made it.
Show me.
Here it is.
It's not done yet.
What's this?
What about Matsuno?
Matsuno, it's almost done.
Please subscribe to the channel.
5,4,3,2,1
Don't eat it!
I'm not eating it!
I'm just trying it!
Don't eat it!
What's that?
What's that mayonnaise game?
Does it go well with mayonnaise?
Please trust your tongue.
The time limit is over.
He went straight to the next one.
Ok, Maddo-san is done.
The second half of the team has a unique
design.
And the new design is also a
masterpiece.
The 8 original futomaki are all done.
In the first round, 4 people will be
eliminated.
The judging will now begin.
The judges will be very serious about
choosing the king of cooking.
They are familiar with various cooking
shows.
They will ask the chef Junko Takagi to
judge.
In addition.
I will ask another chef to judge more
seriously.
Please judge.
The judges are very serious.
I will judge seriously.
Please introduce yourself.
I'm Tomitoku Chu.
Tomitoku Chu is a gourmet.
He eats any cheap meat with wasabi.
First, I will judge the original
futomaki of Mayama.
Mayama chose tuna, avocado and natto as
his favorite ingredients.
What kind of taste is it?
Let's eat!
It's a little big
It's good
With one bite
What do you think, Sensei?
The natto is scattered, so I can only
taste the natto
The natto is scattered
It looks scattered, but it's scattered
in my mouth
It's scattered
The teachers are quite unique
Quite
A serious taste test
How will Yasumoto's self-made dish be
evaluated?
A salmon and beef mixed together
A futomaki full of originality
How will Yasumoto's secret taste be?
The salmon was in the way.
Is that so?
The fat of the meat and the freshness of
the cucumber.
After that, a mysterious slimy feeling
came.
It would have been nice if the cucumber
was in between.
If you cut it a little thinner, it will
be very harmonious.
Next, I will roll the hirotana, which I
am confident in cooking.
Mix shiso and sesame seeds in vinegar
rice.
The scent and appearance are beautiful.
What will the taste be?
Let's eat!
I'm scared of this.
I don't want to.
He's being seriously judged.
It's delicious.
He said it's delicious.
Did he say something?
He said it normally.
It's delicious.
The balance of the rice and the
ingredients is good.
Next is Hoshina's futomaki, which has a
novel design.
It's divided into three stages and you
can choose the amount you want to eat.
It's not a failure.
It's a failure.
I just cut the ingredients that I didn't
make.
It tastes good, but it's all messy.
It's all lumpy.
I think it was not enough to roll it
tightly.
What about you, Chuu?
It's big.
It's a matter of size.
I see.
Next, he put mayonnaise on the thick
roll of Matsuno.
He believed in his tongue.
How will the judges evaluate this?
The line is a little lost.
I'll calculate it.
How do you feel?
Mayonnaise is on the bottom when I eat
it first.
I feel like I can eat it with the
inside.
Next is the first time to make it, the
Kashiwagi Futo-maki.
That's why I chose the ingredients of
Odo for the first time, but did it taste
good?
It's the taste of Odo
So if you put it in the middle, it will
look like you only ate the ingredients
You're right
It's good to have them all together, so
putting it in the middle is the best
Next is the colorful Kobayashi's
Futomaki
It's a single Futomaki, but it looks
like it has a lot of variety
The inside is also a unique combination
of meat and cheese
This is more delicious than the one in
the store
It's delicious
I thought it would be delicious
But the real thing is a little thicker
Medium-rolled
There is no such word
The timing is also up to the time, but
at this time, this size is perfect
There is also a order
Finally, the character closes half of
the plate
Nakayama's thick roll
The contents are full of my favorite
cucumbers
What kind of taste did you make?
Cucumbers are surprisingly strong
Two cucumbers
It's strong, but the fish sausage makes
it soft
But the cucumber is strong
But I like cucumbers
All the tasting is over
This is difficult
It's difficult, isn't it?
The unexpected mixed battle
The results of the tasting are finally
announced
I would like to announce the rankings
from now on
The ranking from 1st to 4th is the 1st
place
Unfortunately, the other people will be
eliminated in the first round
First, I would like to announce the 1st
place
Please
The 1st place is
Who will take the lead in the fierce
battle?
Please announce the winner.
The winner is...
Hirota-san.
Congratulations!
The appearance was also very cute.
There was a cuteness that I haven't seen
much of until now.
And the taste was also well balanced.
After all, the appearance and the taste
were well balanced.
The balance was good.
Let's move on.
Please announce the second place.
The second place is Kobayashi-san.
It was a taste that exceeded the
appearance.
A taste that exceeds the appearance.
Great.
Please announce the third place.
The third place is Nakayama-san.
Wait a minute.
Why do you look so unpleasant?
Why is this?
This is a thick roll of Odo.
I think the balance of rice and
ingredients was good.
And it's Odo, but it's good to have a
sausage in it.
Wait a minute.
You are confident in cooking.
Your name is not called yet.
I like or hate natto.
That's right.
Yasumoto is good at making people lose.
I may be in the slippery situation.
Do you have a slippery situation today?
Who will be in the last place?
Please announce.
The fourth place is...
If you are not chosen here, you will be
eliminated.
Who will be the last person?
The fourth place is Kashiwagi-san.
Kashiwagi-san is in the fifth place.
Congratulations.
What kind of expression is this?
I'm happy, but I'm going to go to the
bathroom.
Because it's a thick roll of Odo.
If the theme is thick roll, it's Odo.
The combination of the two was good.
The third, fourth, and fifth places are
close.
Is the fifth place close?
By the way, who was in the fifth place?
The fifth place is Yasumoto.
I'm in the sixth place.
If it's a slippery situation, it's
Yasumoto.
If the person who was chosen gets sick,
he will be eliminated.
If he gets sick, he will be eliminated.
The results of the preliminary
examination.
Hirota, Kashiwagi, Kobayashi, and
Nakayama will advance to the second
round.
They will be tested in cooking.
A tough stage awaits them.
Next time is the second part of the
cooking competition.
I'm ready.
The members will show off their skills.
Hirota is amazing.
Who will win the first prize?
Emergency news.
Hoshina Mirei's first photo book will be
released next Wednesday.
The event will be held on November 10th
at Fukuya Bookstore.
This program was brought to you by the
following sponsors.