Yakan and Idol
The third one is sports.
Sports is... well, recently...
I like books that I can read.
Oh!
Yes.
I like Nagoya Grand Pass, which is a
soccer team.
And...
Nagoya Diamond Dolphins, which is a
basketball team.
I'm active in Aichi Prefecture, so I
feel the joy of supporting my local
team.
I'm glad.
I ran a full marathon, so I wrote
sports.
I ran a full marathon of women's
marathon in Aichi Prefecture.
It was my first time.
How long did you run?
I ran for 4 hours and 6 minutes.
You're fast.
I thought I could do my best.
Are you doing that alone?
I ran for 4 hours and 6 minutes.
I was wondering if I could run as an
influencer of Aichi Prefecture.
I don't run a marathon, so I wanted to
run it.
I was running for a month and a half,
but I ran every day because I wanted to
do it seriously.
I see.
You did swimming for 10 years. You must
have been very good at sports.
I wasn't very fast, but I like swimming.
That's good. You're a tiger athlete.
Do you want to try it?
I only swim and ride a motorcycle.
I only rode a motorcycle for 6 years.
I've climbed over 2 mountains.
I'm a girl, so I'll do my best not to
sweat.
But I'll talk about manga again.
I love the manga called Yomus Pedal.
It's a bicycle race manga.
The main character, Onoda, is good at
climbing.
I'm a girl, so I'll do my best not to
sweat.
I'm good at climbing, and I read it, and
I didn't like the mountain road, but
Onoda is climbing hard, so I'm going to
sing a flower and climb it.
I made sure I never got off.
The manga character is doing the insect
pedal.
There are many elements that manga can
close.
There are many.
I'm good at cycling.
I have a theory that you can save money
on your body.
Really?
Yes.
It's nice, Triathlon.
Let's do it together.
Really?
Yes!
It's not easy.
Yeah.
Oh, really?
But it's amazing.
Sorry, I'm going back to the story.
When you run 42.195km,
it's a completely different feeling.
It's a world you've never seen before.
At least, no one has done it before.
No one has.
No one has done a full marathon.
Our manager is a sportsman.
Oh, really?
They go to high school and participate
in national competitions.
So, we thought we could do a full
marathon.
You're kidding.
So, we thought we could announce the
next tour
right after I ran a full marathon.
If you don't do it, you can't announce
it.
Yeah, we're not allowed to announce it.
But you're a sportsman.
You ran a full marathon by yourself.
You're a great athlete.
I love it.
I'm a very serious athlete.
You have to carry the feelings of
others.
As a matter of fact, I decided to do it
right after I ran a marathon.
I was watching you.
You were watching me!
Do you know where I am running at the
moment?
What?
You mean, the players here?
Yes, the players here.
So, my fans know my number.
They know where I am running.
I couldn't cheer for you at the end of
the game.
You're smiling, but you must have been
under a lot of pressure.
You're not supposed to push me like
that.
We're a group that's got a super power.
I think it was just right.
Do you have a Santa Claus?
Santa Claus?
Santa Claus.
I'm sorry.
I'm just a guest.
I'll do it myself.
Thank you for watching. Please subscribe
to my channel.
Nishiro-san
Kagerou-san
I sent it to you with a supply
Let's play a game today!