We are BATTENSHO STUDIO!
I'm SAKURA SETO, a member of Miyazaki
Prefecture.
I'm YAMAI, a cameraman.
Nice to meet you.
Today, we came to Miyazaki!
We came to this building.
Miyazaki!
Can you see it?
This is it.
We came to Miyazaki.
I'll tell you why we came here.
The staff told us that we can go to the
bus tour.
We are going to the bus tour.
The bus tour is called GYAKU SEICHI
JUNREI TOUR.
GYAKU SEICHI JUNREI TOUR
Miyazaki prefecture is sunny and easy to
live in
I'm glad I walked a lot today
There is a post office in Hyuga Natsu
I took a picture just now
The place I found is Miyazaki
I found the place for the first time in
Hyuga Natsu
I hope I can eat today
Let's see the pictures I got
Thank you
Where is this?
It's beautiful
Is that the Scythe of the Demon?
I've never seen it in person
I've heard that there are many rocks in
the sea
It's beautiful
I want to see the big one
I want to go there
Is it a good place?
Is it a chicken number?
There are many pink and yellow
I've never seen it in person
There are many colors
I wonder if the taste is different
I'm curious
What else?
It's beautiful
I often see it
It's often on the pamphlet
I don't know the place
It's great
I want to do this
It's cool and the weather is good
What else?
I found something I wanted to eat
It's ice cream
I've never seen it in person
I've never seen it in Fukuoka
It looks delicious
I want to eat it
What else?
It's beautiful
It's a nice place
We can shoot a music video here
It's beautiful
I know the place
Do you know?
I know
It's called UNO Jingu
It's near the sea
There are many gods in Miyazaki
We're going to decide the destination
What should we do?
It's a nice place
We can have lunch here
This is just what we've been looking for
There are tons of vistable sights around
here
That's a cool place
The music video is about to make an
installment plan
It really is
Next time, we may actually be able to
shoot our music video right here
So, this is the classroom area
Our destination is here!
Here!
Ta-da!
We are going to walk around the city!
Please subscribe to our channel!
We have never been to Miyazaki-Ratano
before.
So, we are going to explore the area
around there.
I like shopping street.
I feel safe.
I think there are many shopping street
around here.
I think it is not the third time.
I want to eat the famous food such as
mangoes and chrysanthemums.
I want to eat them.
We have to ask the address of this shop.
We don't know if the name of this shop
is correct.
This is a shop of Kamauchi-Kan.
I wonder if I can see the top of the
mountain.
I wonder if there is a sweet potato
Excuse me
I'm shooting a video for YouTube
I'm a little worried about the store, so
I'd like to interview you
Are you okay?
Yes
Thank you very much
You said sweet potato
Do you usually sell sweet potatoes?
I'm in a bad situation right now
I started again around June 10th
If I had been a little late, I could
have bought sweet potatoes
Do you sell vegetables?
Yes
It looks delicious
Do you have any recommended vegetables?
I recommend mango
It is sold in Miyazaki
It looks delicious
Can I ask you something?
I'm looking for this place
Do you know?
Is it the same?
I think it's the same place
This is Udo Shrine on the south coast of
Japan
Udo Shrine
It is a shrine with a long history
It is a shrine
Here
What do you think?
It is called Undama
Undama
I bought it at a store
In the case of women, it is a woman's
right hand
From this place
There is a pot
Is this a pot?
If you put a pot in it, you will be
lucky
There is another place to use it
Do you want to go to the bathroom?
Is this the chicken nanban?
I think so
I don't know where it is
Thank you
I wanted to know
Udo Jingu
I thought it was Uno Jingu
How was it?
It seems to be a place called Udo Jingu
I've seen this before
Throwing?
I heard that if you throw it and get in
it, you're lucky
I've seen it on TV
Let's do this
I want to do it
My luck
I have to do my best
I didn't know the other one
It's difficult
I like women
I think it's best to ask women
I'll do my best
Wow!
What's that?
I found it!
Can you see it?
It's like a climbing wall.
There are many of them.
It's like a climbing wall in a shopping
district.
We took a picture.
We are going to a shop called Nambu
Pudding Town.
This shop was introduced by a member.
It looks delicious.
This is a limited edition of this month.
This is amazing. It's a blue pudding.
It's blue.
There are also dumplings.
There are also drinks.
It looks delicious.
There are also other items.
It's a limited edition.
There are many 100 yen vending machines
in Miyazaki.
I think so.
There are many.
I often see them.
I often see products that I don't
usually see.
It's interesting.
I saw a lot of them yesterday.
I saw a lot of self-portrait.
I saw them.
It's cold today, so I'm wearing a
jacket.
I've never seen a mentaiko vending
machine.
I've never seen it.
Is there?
I wonder if there is.
I think there is.
I think so, too. I'm going to eat
mentaiko.
I didn't notice it.
It's so fashionable.
I didn't know it was so fashionable.
It's here.
It's amazing.
Is it such a beautiful place?
I thought it was a clothing store.
I thought so, too.
I thought it was a shop.
It's 10cm in the middle.
It's easy to come here.
I often see live houses in the back.
I don't know if it's on the front.
I was curious about the live house.
I was surprised at the large size.
We went there together before.
We bought souvenirs.
We went there together during the live.
We went there once during the previous
tour.
We came early in the morning and
prepared.
We went there during that time.
I have a memory of going there with
everyone.
Cheese manju is also delicious.
It's delicious.
I like the moment when cheese is in it.
I like it.
There were many kind staffs.
We might know the reason.
If the material is OK.
We arrived.
Hidaka-san.
Hidaka-san of sweets.
What is it?
Let's ask if the material is OK.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad to meet you.
I've heard your name before.
We've been to eat sweets together.
Thank you.
This is a good photo.
I want to eat a watermelon.
Is it a bubble?
It's a watermelon.
It's black and white.
Is it white?
It's white.
It's nice.
There is sweet potato snack.
I bought it before.
Really?
My sister taught me.
Maybe there is.
I bought this.
It's a cookie.
It's cute.
It looks delicious.
What is this?
Cheese Manju
This is a souvenir shop
I want to buy a cheese Manju
Let's buy
Cheese Manju of Chizu
Cheese Manju of Shiro
I found this
Is this?
There are many
I'm so happy to eat this
I eat this often
Do you know this restaurant?
This is Clayton House.
Clayton House?
There are many sauces like this.
I see.
Do you want to go to a restaurant near
here?
I want to go to Kiyotake or Shigaia.
I want to go there.
This restaurant is delicious.
Really?
Yes.
There are many kinds of sauces.
There are many kinds of plums.
What is plum?
I think this is plum.
I see.
Let's go to a restaurant.
Thank you.
We came to a restaurant called Clayton
House.
I heard that women eat here.
This is called plum, isn't it?
I'm curious about this.
I've never eaten plum.
I've never eaten it.
I love plum so much that I can drink it.
I ate a lot yesterday.
I ate a lot.
So, I'm going to eat here.
Let's go.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Thank you for watching.
There are many kinds of food.
There are more kinds of food than I
thought.
For example, mentaiko.
Hello. I'm mentaiko.
Basil.
Basil?
It's green.
This plate.
There was a picture of this.
Yes, there was.
This is a normal one, and this is a plum
one.
This is a mustard one.
Mustard.
This is a chili mustard.
This is a chili cheese.
This must be delicious.
What should I eat?
I want to eat something other than
chicken nanban.
I think so, too.
Please subscribe to our channel.
I want to eat this.
It looks delicious.
I want to eat chicken nanban.
I'll choose this.
Do you?
I'm not sure, so I'll choose this.
It's good.
I'm full.
We have arrived at the restaurant.
We have arrived.
We ordered 4 kinds of sauce.
I ordered chicken nanban.
And rice and soup.
What about Ai-chan?
I ordered chicken nanban without tartar
sauce.
It looks delicious.
And bread.
I'm full.
Let's eat.
I'll eat from the top.
It's a rare one.
Let's eat.
It's so good.
It's soft.
It's fluffy.
It's like a chicken.
It's a combination of drumstick and
fish.
We got dessert.
It looks so good.
What's yours, Ai-chan?
It's strawberry tart and strawberry
yogurt.
Strawberry yogurt.
It looks good.
This is mango and orange tart and mango
juice.
It's good.
Miyazaki.
I came here.
I don't ask you.
You're right.
It's cute.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Thank you for the meal.
We ate Chicken No.1 of Great House.
It was so delicious.
I want to go there again.
I hope we can come here again when we
have a concert.
I hope so.
I'm glad that the staffs come here.
It's so big.
We can eat this and dessert.
And we can move and eat calories.
It's great.
I hope you can come here.
Where are we going now?
We are going to the final destination.
We were told that.
Udo Jingu.
Please subscribe to this channel.
We arrived at Udo Jingu.
The background is beautiful.
I want to drink Oiso.
We will go to find a place like Undama.
It's a very nice place.
It's beautiful.
It's nice.
The sky is beautiful, too.
It's true.
I'm glad we came here.
It's beautiful.
There are many people coming to see the
cherry blossoms.
Yes, there are many.
But the car number is
Oita or Fukuoka.
Oh, I see.
I want to come here.
Yes, I want to come here.
Can you see it?
The red and green are
so beautiful.
I like this atmosphere.
It's so beautiful.
It's so big.
What year was this?
It was the first year of the year of the
horse.
The first year of the year of the horse?
Yes.
I was so sad that I didn't see you.
I know.
Please subscribe to this channel.
It's so cute.
It's a perfect place for a photo.
I think so.
The sea breeze is so good.
It's so cool.
This is the place.
This is the place?
I think so.
This is the place.
The highest place.
I think so.
It's a little further.
How many?
One, two, four.
I can see four.
Is it around here?
Around here?
It's around here.
It's the same scenery.
It's here.
Is it more ahead?
Is it around here?
I think so.
It's the same.
I'll put it in.
Let's take a picture.
I think so.
Rabbit!
Rabbit's statue.
So many rabbits.
All of them are different.
This is beautiful.
Is that Emma?
Isn't that a rabbit?
It's Emma!
It's so cute!
She's writing with her hand.
It's true.
It's cute.
This?
It's a bit late.
We'll be there when we cross the bridge.
Yeah.
It's almost there.
Really?
Wait a minute.
I'll take a picture.
Please subscribe to my channel.
It's the same!
I've never seen the sea like this.
We don't see the sea from our house.
We don't.
And we can see the sea.
The sea is beautiful.
Can you see it?
It's like Emerald Green.
It's a delicious-looking color.
Is the sea deep?
It's deep, isn't it?
But the momentum is amazing.
It's beautiful.
It's really beautiful.
It feels good.
We found the second place.
It's a very beautiful place.
It's a little closer and we'll get off.
That's right.
Thank you for watching.
We're here!
Where is this?
This is...
Here?
Here!
I think it's around here.
Is it?
This way.
This is...
Ta-da!
There it is!
It's beautiful from the bottom.
It's beautiful.
It looks so high.
It's perfect.
It's complete.
It's good.
I'm curious about this one.
It's a cave.
A cave?
Inside of it...
There's a lot of water.
It's true.
Is it cool?
Yes.
Let's go inside.
It's cool.
It's amazing.
It's like a cave.
Is this the main shrine?
What does it mean?
Is it written as the main shrine?
It's the main shrine.
It's here.
We arrived.
It looks like a sacred place.
I can see the shrine.
We are going to the shrine.
Good luck.
It's difficult.
I'm going to the shrine.
Good luck.
Almost!
It looks difficult.
It's really difficult.
I'll do my best.
I'll do my best, too.
Right hand.
It's really difficult.
I'm doing good!
One more!
Ah!
But it seems like you can hit the ball
in the middle of the circle.
You did it!
I managed to hit it.
This is fun.
It is!
Please try it out.
The Kinlanpan was good too.
The Kinlanpan from Great Ones was good
too.
It was good.
You can eat a lot of different flavors.
I'm out of breath.
This is a good exercise.
It is.
We didn't do a live performance today,
so we should do this.
We should move a lot.
We should do this.
It was a beautiful place.
It was a serious place at the end.
I feel like I got a lot of power.
We have successfully completed the Udo
Jingu tour with the Udo Jingu we are at
now.
We did it!
We were able to go around safely.
The name of the place was Udo Jingu, but
we were able to go around safely.
We learned a lot.
We were able to go around safely.
We learned about Miyazaki.
We were able to shoot the video with the
local people who taught us.
Thank you.
The dinner was delicious.
We came to Miyazaki Park before the
tour.
We will eat a lot when we come to
Miyazaki again and do our best at the
live performance.
We will do our best.
Who will go to the next place?
I want to come to Miyazaki again.
I want to come again.
We can't go there in one day.
We will go to Miyazaki again.
Thank you for teaching us a lot about
the place.
If you find a good place, please let us
know with the hashtag.
Please let us know with the hashtag.
Miyazaki!
If you let us know, we might go there
again.
We will go there again.
Please look forward to the next member.
Please look forward to it.
Bye bye.