Thank you for watching.
This week's Ebi-Tutasas is the second
episode of the winter garden tour!
The members are challenging bungee
jumping
Then
Nakayama is crying
Then Hoshina is
The end of the touching ending
Ebichu Tastasu Start!
The first episode will be broadcast on
the TV channel.
The second episode will be broadcast on
We will add various things to private
Ebisu Middle School.
Ebisu Middle School
Good luck!
This program is brought to you by the
sponsor of the program.
My heart is beating.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
Last time, the members came to the
Mazaaboku Castle, the capital of winter
After the little pig race
It's time for the Jinguisukan BBQ
Lunch time for the members
I said it on the bus, but it's a revenge
BBQ
Please don't just eat it today
Last year, on the episode of Ebichutas
BBQ
I completely forgot that it was TV and
acted freely
The members who were punished for
copying the city of Fuji
So, in the bus heading to Mother's farm
to get revenge,
The public project is to liven up the
barbecue with a reflection point
It's Mizugoro-san
As a result, this time, a card with the
order of the member public project was
prepared
The selected members were chosen to
implement the contents of the card they
drew
The contents of the order that each
member thought of is here
Will they be able to get the revenge of
the previous time?
The revenge barbecue has finally begun!
Put the beef on the grill and grill it
It's about time
Let's draw the member cards
Let's do it
First, the member who will carry out the
order is decided
The chosen member is Yasumoto
The card Yasumoto drew is
Please read it
I'll imitate the six-year-old
Please enjoy the order by imitating the
six-year-old
Please
It's good
What should the animal do to make you
happy?
I'm going to make a
What should the animal do to make you
happy?
I want to be as gentle as possible
Let's start with the next one
Matsuno was chosen next
The next order is
Please eat vegetables
I'm going to eat it
It's my own
Matsuno chose the order he drew
Please express the deliciousness of the
Jinguis
Thank you for your viewing.
Woooow
Wow
I'm so excited
Calm down, Matsuo
Wait, can I try again?
One more time
Woooow
I'm worried about this
I'm worried
How can I make this animal happy?
How can I do it?
Like this
Like this?
You can be happy now
I'm scared
The mission card worked
The members had a great time without
getting tired
It's Lei physically and mentally
satisfied
But there was something that makes
everyone satisfied
But most importantly, it's fine with
just a baffling thirst
Everyone, you can see it now
What is that?
What did you say?
Bungee jumping, correct
The punishment game is bungee jumping
Ready, start
Hirota and Nakayama pair who were the
last to be the winner of the
last time's race
What is that?
What did you say?
Bungee jumping, correct
The punishment game is bungee jumping
Ready, start
The last time's race was the last time
Hirota and Nakayama pair who were the
last to be the winner of the
last time's race
The two will be
The one who will be waiting for the
punishment is
The scary punishment game, bungee
jumping
The one who will be jumping the bungee
jump of the punishment game is
one of the pair who lost
The two who will be jumping the
punishment game
Have you ever done bungee jumping?
Yes, I have
I have done bungee jumping earlier
Nakayama who has never done bungee
jumping
I was so motivated
Who?
Me
Nakayama
That's good
So the one who will be jumping the
bungee jump of the punishment game is
Nakayama who wanted to try bungee
jumping
Nakayama Riko's first try at bungee
This time Nakayama will try bungee
jumping from the roof of the 7th floor
building, 21m high
Ready to go with harness
I'm going to go with you
Not going
It's easy
Riko is fine
And finally to the jump platform
With the newbie Hirota, she climbs up
the stairs without any fear
Nakayama san is a little late
I'm tired
The stairs are very...
I'm tired, please help me
Hirota is scared
I'm scared
It's cold
Cold?
How is the wind?
I'm tired of the wind
You're tired of the wind?
It has nothing to do with the wind
I heard the wind
I'm tired of the wind
The wind
It looks fun
It's hair
Is the wind strong?
Like this
It's wavy
It's shaking
It's reporting with hair
Thank you for watching
But if you actually climb to the top,
you can see the height of the
surrounding body.
The members below are beans.
Bungee is scary.
Bungee, are you ready?
Can you do it?
I can do it!
Amazing!
Be careful
You can see the floor
I don't like that
Be careful, camera
It's cold
Go for it!
I can't do it
I'm scared of this
Nakayama has gone without hesitation so
far
Will he fly at once as it is?
I'm scared
How is it Nakayama?
I'm fine
Are you okay?
What happened?
I'm fine
Are you okay?
I'm scared
21 meters high
Nakayama shows her relaxed expression to
the height that makes her more scared
Finally, the first bungee jump
Nakayama, are you ready?
Yes
Let's do it together
5,4,3,2,1, Go!
What?
Again!
One, two, three, four, five, four,
three, two, one
I'm scared
I wanted that
You're scared, aren't you?
I'm ready
Are you scared?
Nakayama, are you scared?
What?
It's like a roller coaster
Takiya is staring at her
Cute
Bungee is scary when you wait
You have to go at once
What should I do? I'm scared
Are you scared?
It seemed easy, but when she was about
to jump, her determination was shaking
I was surprised
It was a punishment game
Bungee is scary
Shut up!
I'm sorry
I can hear you
You can hear me with this volume?
Why did you ignore me?
You were standing there and I crushed
you
You're like a hell
Thank you for watching! Please
subscribe!
The spider is fast too
Go, Nagayama!
Go, Chanriko!
You can do it!
One lap!
I'm scared of how she jumps
She's a little bit rough
She's saying she's rough
Shut up!
I said shut up!
What?
Don't forget that you are an idol
You are so bad at talking
What's wrong with you today?
You should fly like this
I'm so stupid
You shouldn't do that
Who were you talking to?
Turkey Ue is saying something that he
thinks is a person
Then, Nakayama is...
I want to see how it is
I wonder who will fly
I wonder
What did you say?
I feel like it's difficult to fly
I want to see it
You want to see the sample?
I want to see it once
You want to see it once?
I see
I wonder
No, no, no
It's the same
I'll decide now
No, no
10 yen
Okata, go home
Shinichiro Takiue
We are sorry
Everyone is a producer
He is a singer
I like Rikko Takiue
He is perfect
This is the worst
Shinichiro Takiue jumps to the top
He will be a star in Bungie for Nakayama
It's a moment!
You can refuse that
It's really scary
You can't protect her
Nakayama!
Nakayama, are you angry at Taki?
I'm really angry!
Riko-chan's mouth is shaking
I'm really angry
Yoshin is out
Countdown
No, no, no!
One moment! One moment!
One moment!
It's okay!
Nakayama!
Sorry for all the things I've done.
One by one.
Now, it's time for the showdown.
Let's go!
Ready, set, go!
5, 4, 3, 2, 1
I'm going!
Ah!
That video is lame!
It's lame!
Oh my god!
What are you doing?
You're drinking too much!
Oh my god!
One moment!
Wow, amazing!
It's like a shooting star!
Did you get scared?
I was scared because I was so thin.
You were so thin.
You are good at it.
I was scared.
Thank you for watching!
I'm sorry for being so excited
This is scary
You know how Nakayama feels right now
I'll leave the lead to you
You should really be quiet
You're so noisy
I told you to be quiet
I really thought so
Is he determined after seeing the
example?
Nakayama is ready to go!
Will they be able to fly next time?
When you can fly, say something to that
stupid man and fly
Rikko, say something to that stupid man
and fly
I got it
You can say it
I'm relieved if someone can fly
Please subscribe to my channel
I'm going to do it
Nakayama's challenge
Tonkotsu Taro, you must be faster when
you race
Nakayama's flying car
Nakayama's first bungee jump
Let's go!
Tonkotsu Taro!
When you race next time,
make sure to get on the bike fast!
Let's go!
Ouch!
It's scary!
I'm like a ghost
What's going on?
I was scolded by the staff
How was it, Takiie?
What do you think?
It was fun
I have to do it at my own timing
I can't hear you
You are a tonkotsu taro, aren't you?
Don't you have to say it?
I have to say it
I said it
I will do it
I will do my best
She can't take a step
Then
If you can prepare a bag, please go
there
To calm her down, she decided to go down
However
I don't want to
I'm sorry
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
You're sorry, right?
You're upset, right?
The tears can't stop from the unbearable
frustration and responsibility
But the staff decided that it's
impossible to continue here
Nakayama was trying to fly to the end,
but he retired without any thought
Nakayama-san did his best
sisters were the best
Was it scary?
Scary
But this is just a punishment game
I'm going to jump on the
Winner Hoshina
Everyone is an enemy
Hoshina makeseeeee meals
For the three of them
They are our blue team
Wait for us!
Coming!
Good luck, Oshira
It's cold
It's not cold
I want to get off
It's scary if you go to the front
They are ready after putting on the rope
Here it comes
It's fast
Oshira, how is the front?
It's high
It's high but it's cold so I'll do my
best to get off early
OK, let's go
I'm excited
If you feel good, you can count down
here
Then, let's do parkour
Parkour? OK
I'll say OK
OK? OK
OK
Now, it's time for the challenge of
Oshina
Let's go
Go
4, 3, 2, 1
Amazing!
Her legs are long!
Hoshina Hata!
Ichimagu!
She successfully jumped as the
representative of Ebichu!
She jumped!
Ayu-chan jumped!
Congratulations!
Ayu-chan is so good looking
I was so happy
Amazing!
She is so stylish
This is not good
You should not wait
She is so energetic
I was surprised
I want to fly
We were surprised
We were just surprised
Yassan is back
Bacchiiii
What did you say?
How was it, Nakayama?
It was amazing
Thank you
Amazing
Do you hate TASTA?
She is so fast
It was amazing
Thank you for watching
Ebichu Game Quest 4
The current Ebitube game project
We are making a pulling action game that
is a stage of an empty middle school
Ebitube members have been giving various
ideas such as items in the game so far
Some of them were actually adopted
So this time, we will think about items
related to school that are in the game
world
The items that the four of them thought
of are these
Among them, Nakayama Koan's item was the
one that was the most popular in the
game production
Usually, I use a eraser pencil, pencil
sharpener, and a pencil sharpener
And a school uniform that elementary
school students often wear on the land
cell
The items that Nakayama Koan's item was
the most popular in the game production
金着袋? 金着袋 is a type of 金着袋
合体して戦うときに 刃のような 刃尖が 飛んできます
上の部分が飛んで 敵に 被されて 見えなくして 動けなくします
システム的には 色々 繋がって いますが 金着袋が 飛んでいくだけです
金着袋じゃなくても 隠せたら 何でもいい ということですね
はい
果たして 中山のアイデアは 採用されるのか?
Emi-Chu Game Project 続報待て!
Next episode of Emi-Chu Tastas is...
Winter's End, Winter's End, finally the
climax!
The
I think it's amazing that the
Emi-Chu talks to each other in real life
This program was provided by the sponsor
you are watching
Where did you fall in love with me?