I love you
Good morning!
Today is the day of the school festival.
We are going to perform.
Can you hear the sound of the sound
outside?
Yes, I can hear it.
Oh my god.
It's so cute.
Are you sleeping?
The picture of the person who came out
of the water is half-frozen.
That's a human.
Are you okay?
What?
Are you saying that your face is not
good?
Your hair is weird.
I'm not good at it.
I'm tired.
Thank you.
2,3,4,5,6
Hello everyone.
We are MIXNINE.
Thank you.
Thank you for watching!
To be connected with you every day
Waaaa
I'm so excited.
I'm not sure how to say it.
We've finished the rehearsal.
I'll put on makeup and get my hair done.
We'll have a concert.
I thought,
I thought I was going to watch the
rehearsal.
I was wondering about it.
I hope you're looking forward to it.
Bye.
Here she comes.
Look at me.
Oh, really?
When we first met,
she was looking at me.
She was looking at me.
That's hard.
Look at me.
She's waving.
We're wearing a mask today.
Yes.
We're wearing yellow clothes.
So we're going to wear a mask.
Yes.
Let's do our best.
Is there a time limit?
Is there?
How many minutes?
Wait.
Ready...
Ramunano?
ettesu.
Ready...
Jupiter in love?
A song...
In the music video...
Ready...
KID STANDARD.
Yes.
Ready...
The Cider in July.
MC Asahi.
Ready...
I like you.
Wait, wait, wait...
Ready...
One of you will leave something behind.
What?
One, two, three...
I'm sorry.
What was the song?
It was this.
The song title is good.
Ko-chan.
Ka.
Sabe, Sabe, Sabe.
Katakata.
I thought it was a dog.
Isn't it a dog?
It's a dog, right?
Dog.
It's barking.
It's teeth are hard.
I'm going to have a hard time.
Na, Na, Na, Na, Na.
It's so cold.
It's so warm.
I feel so happy.
It's so nice.
It's like the warmth of the storm.
I feel like I'm flying.
I feel so happy.
I'm so happy.
I always did this when I was in
elementary school.
I was always doing this when I was in
I didn't do this.
Everyone was standing in front of the
stove.
I was in the air conditioner since
middle school.
You were in the air conditioner?
I was in the fan and heater.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's my first time to be on a school
festival.
Please look forward to it.
Thank you.
Nightала So bright
you made me happy
I wanted it
Same?
I'm sure it's the same
And then the next is the left
Win x2
Change one
I'm Haachan.
I'm OK.
OK.
Are you all OK?
Thank you.
Na Na
Just live and praise
I can't do it anytime.
I can't say it's the last time.
I can't feel it forever.
I'm sure I'm better than you.
I'm so used to such a song.
I got60powers點
I got60powers.
Let's do our best.
Enjoy it.
help me
lead
go
I was told that I'm cute. I'll do my
best.
Please right click on the video
And
Sh jindan
This is the actual first funfair
Please subscribe to my channel!
Thank you for watching!
Everyone who came to GENKAKU, we are the
super excited Senreibu who are locked on
to your heart.
The next song is, if you hear it, you'll
know this song.
I can dance this song very well.
I think there are people who can dance
perfectly.
It's our representative song.
Let's have fun together.
I can't stop this feeling.
I was there for you.
Say!
I can't stop this feeling.
It was fun!
Thank you!
It was the first time we had a school
festival, so I was happy to be invited.
Thank you!
It was really fun!
I was happy!
I'll do my best to invite you again!
Thank you very much!
It was fun!
Thank you!
I want to come again!
Why is it that when I smile, the world
seems to be shining?
I can relax by turning the umbrella,
otherwise I can't walk
I'm sure someone is crying somewhere,
I'm getting wet somewhere again, isn't
it cold?
I'm sure someone is crying somewhere, I
want to share my feelings with you
I don't know the scenery in front of me,
let's go anywhere
Goodbye Goodbye Thank you for yesterday
The cityscape after the rain is colored
I painted a fragment of the future on
the canvas of my broken heart
It will lead me
I can say it now, even the reason for my
tears
When I'm lost, I immediately remember
Even if it rains, I'll smile
Look, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye to me from yesterday
The cityscape after the rain is
sparkling
My heart is like a spring
Playing the sound of the rainbow
Playing the rainbow piano
Goodbye, goodbye to me from yesterday
The cityscape after the rain is
sparkling
My heart is like a spring
Drying the tears
I'll wear a rainbow dress
LaLaLa...