Nakano Idol
Wha?!
Now, let's move on to the ending.
Do you have any announcements?
Yes, we will be releasing our second
album, Live, on December 20th.
Thank you.
This second album, Live, has four new
songs added to the album,
and we also have a live video of it at
Toyosu Pit.
This time, we have five members, and...
this has been our path from the
perspective of the five of us.
What was the name of the song?
It's okay, you can just squeeze it out.
I want to capture your face right now.
So, this is what happened to Ayumi and
the five of us.
Yes, it's been a challenge and a
resolution since the five of us.
I think that the path we've taken has
become one with this album.
I hope you all get it.
So, what's next for this album?
We're going to be holding our first and
only transparent tour in 2023.
That's right, our first and only
transparent tour.
We're going back to Ebisu.
Tokyo, Nagoya, Osaka.
Is this your first time doing this?
It's my first time.
I've done a solo live in Nagoya before.
No, it's my first time doing a tour in
Nagoya and Osaka.
I see.
I'm going to have to go there if I'm a
fan.
Yes, please do.
So, we can't take our eyes off the club
next year.
But this is a special episode.
I'm a night watchman, so I'd like you to
drink tea from the night watchman.
Today, we're going to drink Shizuoka's
Makinohara tea.
It's green tea.
I think it's my first time drinking
Shizuoka's tea.
Oh, really?
Kaz, do you drink tea?
I usually drink water.
I'm not trying to make you laugh, but
that's great.
You're very particular about your tea.
Maybe I am.
Do you have a favorite water?
I'm not particularly particular about my
tea.
But I can tell that you're not good at
drinking water.
But I'm not particularly good at
I've tried a lot of different waters,
but I've never been good at drinking
water.
I've come to feel that way.
Then I'll try it.
Please drink it.
Thank you for your tea.
Oh, you're going to drink it?
I thought you were going to drink it.
I'm a little nervous because I'm eating
in front of people.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Thank you for the tea.
I'll try not to look.
Can I drink it?
Close your eyes.
Thank you for the tea.
Thank you.
Hmm.
How is it?
You always drink water, Mika.
Can I drink it again?
Yes.
It's good.
I'm glad.
It's smooth.
I thought this kind of tea was very
strong, but it's easy to drink.
Can I ask you one last thing?
What is it?
You're so cute.
You're so cute that you're closing this
show to the camera.
What? Everyone in the hotel is doing it.
You're so cute.
I'm going to do it.
Thank you for watching the video.
I'm Ibuki Mita.
I'm OK.
I'm burned.
This program is brought to you by
Zundare, Iseki Arinoshi, Yosshi, My
Monster, and Mitata Aoshi GTO.
Thank you for watching.
Christmas is coming soon, so I hope you
have a wonderful Christmas.