Yaka- expects work to be finished soon!
Yakan and Idol!
Now, let's get started with the news!
Here's Haruna's announcement!
Okay!
She's got it, so here it is.
Please show us your part!
Here's the BTR!
I'm going to be playing the role of
Hyoryuki, a 15-year-old girl.
She's an adventurer who meets various
conflicts and bonds
as she travels to the island of the
demon.
She's going to go back home to her
hometown.
She'll be in Tokyo from February 3rd to
6th.
And on February 23rd,
she'll be at the Yurigashi Bunka
Exhibition in Kanagawa Prefecture.
Please come and see her!
Before we start, we have a tea present
from Yakan!
Yay!
Today's tea is from Kagoshima,
Chirancha!
Chirancha! I've never heard of it.
Let's drink!
Okay!
How is it?
I feel relieved.
You feel relieved?
I talked a lot, so I feel relieved.
I heard that it's good for your throat.
I just warmed up my throat.
At the end, I'll do this.
It might be best to do it in the real
thing.
Can I get a new one?
I see.
That's what it looks like.
Which do you prefer, Cross or Muji or
Zero?
I'll choose the regular All Night
Nippon.
I see.
Let's go.
Let's start with the chorus.
Let's get started this week.
Spring is coming. All Night Nippon.
Great!
Let's do it.
I want to do it.
I want to see it.
I listen to it every week.
Today, we talked about Mai Haruna.
Lastly, please close the camera.
I hope you'll continue to watch us.
This was Mai Haruna.
Bye bye.
If you don't watch it, I'll be really
mad!
piccolo
This program is
Suspender
In the story
It's just to focus on the main topics
Please subscribe to my channel!
This was brought to you by Toshikazu-
san.
We'll be waiting for you on stage!