Please subscribe to this channel!
Hello!
Long time no see!
We're in the military!
It's been a while!
I haven't been out much.
I haven't seen you in a while.
I thought about it, but I don't have a
greeting.
I don't have a greeting.
Why don't you have one?
Why?
I'm not going to do it.
What would be good?
I've talked about it once.
I don't know how to do it.
I see.
I thought it would be different.
It's been a year since then.
I think it's okay to be a little bit.
Really?
Is it okay to be a little bit?
Should I be a soldier?
You're too understanding.
I think there are people who know me
from YouTube.
I'm being sent to Korea.
I'm having fun.
I think it's a little bit.
I'll ask you in the comments.
If there's anything good.
I'll go ahead and do it.
Today,
We're a little bit.
We're not wearing makeup today.
Hello.
I'm not wearing makeup today.
Around 2018.
Sendai Pit.
Suddenly, a big year-end party?
At the live show.
The girls who admired makeup.
I'm going to start this.
There's a song called Make Me.
I did makeup for the first time at that
time.
Now it's been banned.
It's been three years since it was
banned.
It's been three years.
It's been three years since the ban on
makeup.
I see.
I think it's improving.
I thought.
Today, I'm going to do makeup without a
mirror.
No mirror makeup.
I've never done makeup without a mirror
in my life.
I've never done it.
There's a rule.
What is it?
No mirror.
There's a rule about no mirror makeup.
Are you okay?
I can't speak at all.
I think it's because it's raining.
I'm not doing it.
I'll explain the rules.
I don't think it's fun to do no mirror
makeup for three minutes.
I see.
So while one person is doing makeup.
What?
While one person is doing makeup.
Raise your hand if you're the other
person.
Raise your hand.
You have to sing at that time.
The person who does makeup has to sing.
That's right.
There's a rule.
It's more fun to do that.
When I met you before, I did my own
part.
I'll recreate it.
This time, other people's parts may
come.
That's right.
I'm done.
I don't do makeup for three minutes.
It usually takes about two hours.
How many minutes?
I'm an hour.
That's right.
It's okay.
I'll sing for an hour.
I'll do my best.
Thank you for watching.
I'm ready.
Yes.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I'm going to drink water from Aqua
Chloro.
Are you ready?
I'm ready.
I'm going to put my bangs.
This is a gift from Tohoku.
Please buy it.
I really want you to buy it.
I'm determined.
I don't have a mirror anymore.
That's true.
It's an eyeball.
Please make it an eyeball.
It's okay.
Okay.
No!
I'm embarrassed.
Are you okay?
Start!
I'll apply the base.
Are you okay?
I'm scared!
It's still an intro, so you can say yes.
Do your best!
I'm back.
I'm applying it with a sponge.
I'm applying it to my face.
I'm listening to the story of our aim.
OK.
Do your best.
What's next?
Concealer.
I have such a day.
You're doing it yourself.
There is a mirror.
I'm looking for a place to sit while
looking in the mirror.
It's difficult.
I'm going to finish it.
Wait a minute.
Eyebrow.
I'm sorry.
Where is my eyebrow?
I want to try it. I will put it in my
makeup.
I'm sure it's not good.
I will go with the eye shadow.
Good luck!
Oh no!
Can you do this?
You can do it!
All the parts!
I got the lyrics wrong.
I'm gonna get scolded.
Oh no!
It's almost over.
I'm gonna sing.
I'm gonna do my best.
I'm doing the eyelash curler.
I gave up on the lower lashes.
I'm gonna do the lashes and do the
mascara.
I recommend this mascara.
I'm gonna do my best.
Eyeliner!
Lip! Lip!
The end.
I'm done.
I think it's amazing.
It's like natural makeup.
It was Kaya.
It was.
I'll do my best next time.
Please.
Please subscribe to the channel.
Miya-chan, don't do that.
I'm sorry.
OK, I'll do my best.
Can you do it?
I'm OK.
Miya-chan's no-mirror makeup.
Ready, start!
It's started.
Oh, that was close.
It was close.
Oh, the feeling.
Amazing.
Yes!
You're too calm.
How many years have you been an idol?
One year.
I'm not sure.
Is it okay?
Yes.
It's good.
Eyebrows.
I've been an idol for three years.
It's my first time.
I wanna challenge!
What?
That was the part?
I'm going to use my eyebrows.
Let's do the makeup!
I'm not good at this.
I'm going to use my eyebrow mascara.
Wow, that's a lot of mascara.
It's so pretty.
I'm going to use my eyeshadow.
I'm going to use this.
No, no.
Why?
I want to do it.
It's broken.
I'm going to use this.
I want to do it.
This is cute.
It's cute.
Next is eyeliner.
I want to try it.
You are not good at it.
It's good.
I will try eyeliner for the first time.
Good.
What is the most fashionable?
You are not good at it.
I can't see it.
It's the same color as the other one.
It's a doll.
I can be a doll.
スリーニー ジェオン サニー ニューデス
What's next?
Sharing.
スリーニー ジェオン サニー ニューデス
What is that?
If you look here, you can see the
mirror.
Here?
Yes, yes.
Highlight, highlight.
Thank you for watching.
kg
시면
Oh, it's a short story
It's put on a lip наш
ว
So cute!
We're done!
That was fun!
What's going on?
I think it went pretty well.
Finally, we're going to check our makeup
with a mirror.
Yay!
Here we go.
I'm scared.
It's scary.
3, 2, 1, go!
It's heavy.
I'm sorry.
It's really good.
It's really natural.
It's really cute.
It's hard, right?
It's really smudged.
Isn't it crazy?
It's really good.
I was a little too serious.
I'm sorry.
You were a little too serious.
Where?
Really?
I want to make my nose look higher with
the shadow.
I think this is better.
It's better for shooting.
Lighting is strong.
But now I think I look like I'm
barefaced.
I think this is just right.
There's glitter.
It's good.
I'll use this from now on.
Let's all do it together.
There's no school.
Please use the teleprompter.
Perfect.
After three years, we've improved a lot.
We've improved.
Is it okay to end?
I'll close it.
Is there anything you want to talk
about?
Is there anything I want to talk about?
Is there anything you want to talk
about?
Recently?
I've been cutting my bangs too much
lately.
I'll show you.
It's not bad, right?
I'll cut it a little more.
I'll cut it a little more and put it
back.
Thank you for watching.
If you liked it, please like it.
We're looking forward to your comments.
Bye bye.