I'm going to talk about the staff of the nightclub and idol.
I was told by the staff of the nightclub and idol to talk for 2 minutes.
Hello everyone, I'm Rika Mayama, the main character of Ciri TV.
Today is the Stapra Idol Festival.
I'm looking forward to the opportunity to gather with everyone every year.
This year, Neni is on vacation, so I'm the oldest member of the purple team.
I was really surprised.
I got a message from Reni yesterday.
I'm lonely. I wrote, so I'll do my best today.
I have a solo concert the day after tomorrow.
I'm going to Yokohama today.
I'm going to Yokohama again tomorrow.
I really wanted to stay.
I'm into saunas these days.
There is a famous sauna in Yokohama.
I wanted to go there.
I was wondering why I was going to stay for a day.
I'm looking forward to enjoying the festival once a year.
It's almost 2 minutes.
Please enjoy the nightclub and idol.
I'd like to have a conversation with you someday.