I was like, what was the most difficult
melody you've ever made?
You don't have to be the manager.
It's embarrassing to sing in front of
people.
Welcome. Welcome to Fukaboru.
Thank you. What brings you here today?
We have a lot to talk about. We don't
talk about music together.
We don't.
You're talking about music today?
Yes.
I see.
Thank you.
You're talking about music?
Orange
I don't care if it rains
I don't care if I'm late
I don't care if you laugh
I don't care if you don't know
You're a shrine maiden
Blooming in the wilderness
Don't mind me being lame
Don't mind my beard growing
Don't mind my back and front
Don't mind my diet
You're like the ocean
Like a distant horizon
You're like my mother
I might have realized it
The song called Moshimaro...
It sold pretty well among my songs.
It's always been on the market.
That song is super easy.
If you play it with a scooper, it's
never boring.
Just the melody?
Yes, the melody doesn't change.
It's simple.
It's a good song.
What does it mean?
You were surprised by it?
I was surprised.
I wondered what I had been working hard
to make these small melodies.
I wondered if this was okay.
And from that point on, it became like
this.
That's what it means.
That's the turning point.
So you discovered it in yourself?
I mean, I can do it many times.
I can make something simple again.
But when I think I made a good song,
it's usually not good.
So you think you made a good song, but
you have a different impression?
I guess I have a good timing.
I don't think about it too much.
Is there a moment when you feel
relieved?
Yes, that's a good thing.
When you were in Unicorn before you
became a solo artist, there were many
difficult songs.
Did you think it was easy to become a
solo artist while doing that?
I did a lot of cool stuff like that.
I was a little bored.
I thought it was a little simpler.
But I thought it was worth it.
I thought it was a good idea to not be a
manager.
It's an innovative song.
It's so simple.
The song doesn't have a lot of calories.
How does that work—
how long does it take to write lyrics
for a song?
It takes a while.
Really?
How long does it take?
How long does it take to write a song?
No, no, no.
It's like you just think about it and
then you come up with something.
I've forgotten why I wrote that song.
It's like...
It's been 2000 years.
2000 years?
Yes. It's been 22 years.
I've improved since 2000.
It's been 20 years since I've improved.
The Fly vs. Buddha
The Toy Xiaobao
Rock of Japan
assistant songwriter
wen Wales
I started a place called MASH to start
with.
Right.
It sounds sim מכ Spitz's music in a way.
You know more about that.
In Katakana.
Robinson, for example.
I see.
Robinson is the title of the show,
right?
So I decided to make it a marshmallow.
But it didn't say anything about
marshmallows.
So I added the word.
I just...
I just said no.
That's right.
I'm sorry.
I said I was a marshmallow, but he
didn't come out.
I said, I'm sorry.
I said, you're great, so Spitz didn't
apologize.
Robinson didn't come out, I said I'm
sorry.
That's the difference with me.
I'd like to ask you something
fundamental.
You're not a marshmallow.
That's right.
I wonder why. But you say it's a
marshmallow.
I was conscious of that.
I see.
Some people say that.
Wait, you're saying something so
fundamental now?
Marshmallow.
Yeah, it's not a marshmallow.
I know that.
I'm not mistaken.
The sound of a marshmallow.
That's what I thought was a bit of a
spit-spit.
I want to go back to the lyrics.
I thought the lyrics were great until
the last part, regardless of the
marshmallow.
Your skirt pattern, your wallpaper in
the room
No need to talk to you, just look at it
quietly
I'll keep trying every day to be with
you
I just wanted to say yo
Isn't this great?
Well, there's no one who would make a
skirt pattern into a wallpaper
I just changed my mind
I was thinking why a skirt?
I thought it was possible
Really?
Thank you for watching!
I'm writing the lyrics with a lot of
energy.
It's embarrassing to talk about lyrics.
That's right.
I'm sorry.
I'm embarrassed to say that it has
nothing to do with the end.
It's embarrassing.
It sounds like nonsense, but actually
there are different kinds of gift一点
vontade and energy is a lot of
物の心理がねいやいやあるかなそうなそういうところは結構
節々にあるのが聞いてるなぁと思うんですよね
まあだからその歌詞もようは
まあ気にしないとかって言ってるじゃないですかそれもそのさっき言ったようないろんな
ことを経てあまり気にしなくていいんじゃないかって思い
はじめてる頃の心の方が出てるんですよああそうかとかはい
It's not really for anything.
I think it wasn't made for that.
I see.
I just put one of these in the album and
that's it.
I don't have any pressure.
If I say I made it randomly, I'll get
scolded.
I'm really out of energy.
I think it was Tamiyo's invention that
made it cool.
There are a lot of songs like this in
the past.
But pop songs are all good.
I think there were songs that were not
like that that were popular in the past.
I think there was such a thought.
Sakurai and Kuwata-san make good
melodies, right?
Everyone admires them, and everyone does
it.
It's like, if you don't do it, you can't
do it.
In the wind, there's one melody.
There's one small detail.
I received it.
I see.
So you're not aware of the position in
the world, but...
But I do.
You're a counterpunch.
I think I'm a counterculture person.
I don't go with you when the world is
going this way.
I see.
I thought it would be unnoticeable if I
didn't do something different.
Of course, it's been like that since my
debut.
I guess that's how it is.
I want you to remember the time.
Do you remember the reaction when you
released Marshmallow?
It was a hit.
Reaction?
I don't think it was anything new or
strange.
It was normal.
There was no such thing as a large
audience.
It's different from now. There's no SNS.
That's right. We don't know.
Do you understand the audience's voice
now?
The audience's voice is echoing.
It was good back then.
You could have released it.
Yeah, you could have done it without
thinking.
And if it didn't sell well,
it would have been a problem if it
didn't come to the live.
Yeah, I guess.
I'm glad I didn't think about that much
in the past.
So it's not like it's going to be a big
hit,
or it's not going to sell at all.
It's a period like that.
I don't think I'll be able to sell like
Sazan anymore.
So I think I know where I stand.
You know where you stand.
But I think that's fine.
It's a great thing to be able to be
there.
It's such a great age, isn't it?
I don't think we need to think about
strategy.
I think the music video is unique and
interesting.
There was a commercial for that.
At the time, there was no more CBS-Sony
building.
It was called the Black Building in
Ichigaya.
There was a CBS-Sony logo on the roof of
the building.
That was cool.
It was a good commercial.
There was a logo on the back of the
single.
I admired that logo.
I was glad I could shoot right under it.
You were shooting from below, right?
Yes, I was shooting from here.
What was that?
What was that? Eyeball?
It was like a foot in an eyeball.
It's still the same as it was in the old
days.
I thought that was cool.
By the way, in the video, Maruyama-san
appeared in the epic of Sony.
It's nostalgic.
At the time, I had three Sony's.
The CBS Sony, Epic Sony, and Q Sony.
Do I have them now?
I was in the CBS Sony.
That was a scene where my boss was
getting angry.
I was standing on the bench, and Mr.
Amaru was doing this.
He didn't pick up the voice, so I didn't
need it.
But he was angry that I didn't come to
the picnic.
Are you really angry?
I don't care if he says that to me.
Mr. Watanabe Marina was there, too.
Yes, yes, yes. That's Marina and Azabu's
underwear.
That's where we shot.
It was a great atmosphere.
It was like a little play.
You call it a play.
We're doing a play that we don't usually
do.
Musicians tend to say that play on TV.
That's right. So it's okay to play.
That's right.
I hate it. It's embarrassing.
I'll do it if I have to.
There are musicians, actors, and both.
But I won't do it if I don't.
I'm interested in your embarrassment.
What? I'm embarrassed.
When are you embarrassed?
I'm basically embarrassed.
It's embarrassing to sing in front of
people.
Really?
It's embarrassing.
I'm always singing.
And it's embarrassing to make a song.
Really?
It's embarrassing.
I'm sure you'll send me a song that you
can sing right away.
I'm not embarrassed.
I mean...
I can't do that because I'm embarrassed.
I'm embarrassed because I can sing.
So I'm embarrassed.
How do you trick me?
I'm embarrassed.
I'm thinking about it.
That's why we've been talking about
marshmallows.
Thank you very much.
It's amazing that the show is coming to
life just with the marshmallows.
There are only two such melodies.
Thank you very much.
Now, we will hear a lot about the music
that Okuda-san was influenced by in Side
B.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.