Pl応 pearls
swords
Let's enjoy his bars.
Thank you!
We're Mayagoshi!
Nice!
Recently, I've been thinking about how
to make Ebichu more popular and more
popular.
I've been thinking about it for about 17
hours a day.
You've been thinking that much?
In a dark room.
Scary!
It's dangerous!
Are you okay?
I'll tell you my conclusion. We need to
know more about each other.
We know each other. We don't know each
other well.
We are good friends. We know each other
well.
Not enough.
Not enough to have a nursery school in
Tokyo.
Not enough at all.
Not enough?
Not enough.
We know each other well. We don't know
each other well.
Is that so?
Because...
We're both sold out!
What? Why?
Wait, can you say my full name?
Hoshino Mirei!
Wow! That's amazing!
Let's give her a hand!
No, no, no! Stop it!
I'm not making this up.
You're a genius.
What do you mean?
So you know about me?
You know my name, right?
Kobakaho?
Chan is Mayama!
No matter how you look at it, it's
Mayama!
Ah, it's Mayama!
Kobakaho or Mayama, it's a double-edged
sword!
What double-edged sword?
Sorry, sorry.
It's weird to have two swords.
I'm sorry.
Born on December 16, 1996, 22 years old,
A-type,
two brothers with three older brothers,
they played soccer in elementary school.
I'm right-sided and I'm Maya-maya.
You know a lot.
No, not everyone knows that much.
Oh, that's it.
I came to Stardust for the Kawasaki
audition in spring.
I've been doing it all the time.
I'm a youngster.
I'm Maya-maya.
I was auditioned for Kawasaki in spring.
I was asked to do a self-PR.
I was really into it at the time.
I said I would imitate Yukie Nakamura.
I said, you guys!
And I joined the agency.
If I say I'm a fetishist,
I was asked to do a psychological
analysis and be a queen.
That's Maya-maya.
I'm a youngster!
I'm Maya-maya.
So, um you know when people...
take deep breaths in the office they're
like
This person took a deep breath in the
office and literally felt embarrassed
Then the wall got felled and it was me.
... so then now
your abs are breaking apart
and your arms are gone
like BAM! BAM! BAM!
Scary!
That's the most Maya-like!
When I heard BAM! BAM! BAM!
The agency told me to stop training my
muscles.
So, you're saying that I talk weird and
move weird?
That's the little idiot.
You're the little idiot who talks weird
and moves weird.
So, you're saying that I'm Johnny the
cockroach?
That's the little idiot.
And I'm Maya.
Do you understand?
Yes, I do.
You don't know each other at all, do
you?
You're the only one!
Thank you very much.
Wonderful!
This is pretty...
The second team is the KASHIMAGI-
NAKAYAMA duo of Mr. Kimoto's team.
Thank you very much.
Keep it up, Yanpo.
What? A contract?
Ah, I'm so bored when I have time to
work as a telephone appointment.
Yes, thank you for calling.
This is the customer service center of
the Bonny's family restaurant.
Hello.
Yes, thank you for calling.
I went to that restaurant yesterday.
Did you have any problem at that
restaurant?
There were a lot of problems.
Could you tell me what kind of problems
you had?
I ate that.
Fresh cream pasta.
Yes.
What is that?
Did you have any problem with the fresh
cream pasta?
I'm not kidding.
What?
The cream was mixed with the pasta.
I put it in my mouth and I felt like I
didn't want to swallow it.
So, you mean it was delicious?
Shut up.
I'm not finished yet.
I'm sorry.
Do you have pizza?
Yes, I have.
What is that? I'm not kidding.
Did you use the cheese from the Swiss
cheese factory?
I brought the cheese from the Swiss
cheese factory.
What is that cheese?
How much does it melt?
It stretches a lot.
Did you mean the cheese was delicious?
The problem is the dough.
Did you have any problem with the dough?
What is that dough?
I'm not kidding.
You're finished.
Did you mean it was delicious?
That's not pizza.
It's pizza.
What is that?
Did you want to praise me?
I'm scared.
What is that?
Thank you for calling.
This is a family restaurant.
Hello.
You're the one who called me.
My mother saw a dog and said to me.
I'm a dog.
I saw a cat and said,
I'm a cat.
What's that?
It's not about the restaurant.
So what?
If you find a snake, you say,
I'm a snake.
What are you talking about?
What's the taste of salad?
It's just a good salt.
It's not about the restaurant.
I'm not a bad person.
What's wrong?
And...
You have too many front legs.
I'm fine.
Why do you have to use that part?
You don't say that.
I have nothing to say.
What time is it?
It's time to finish my part-time job.
Thank you for your company.
Thank you.
I'm a big fan of you.
Thank you very much.
I'm Yasumoto. I'm Kobayashi.
Together, we are Yasukoba.
Shortcut, concert!
Everyone, thank you so much for coming
today.
I'll do my best, so please support me.
Now, the first song is Dekadonden.
Ebichu, everyone, let's go!
Who are you? You're weird. Why?
Everyone thinks you're Ebichu.
Seriously, who are you? Seriously?
Seriously, who? Seriously, who?
You're too close, too close, too close.
Yes, Yasukawa!
Shortcut, handshake!
Thank you!
I've always liked you, Kaho-chan!
I'm so happy! Thank you!
Do you remember me?
We've met before, but...
Um, you're the girl who came to the
handshake event before, right?
No, I've never been to a handshake event
before.
Do you remember me?
Then you're the girl who comes to our
concerts often!
No, I've never been to a concert before.
You have!
Then you met me on the street and talked
to me?
No, the street was too funny.
It was a pot!
Sorry, I don't remember at all. Where
did we meet?
Where did we meet? What are you talking
about?
We've met for the first time!
You're a really weird person!
Yes, Yasukawa!
Shortcut, black peach!
Hey, Kaho-chan.
I'm into black peach these days.
Oh, really?
Black peach is so nice.
It's popular, isn't it?
Black peach is so cute!
It's cute, isn't it?
I've been watching a lot of videos of
black peach.
No, it's not black peach. It's black
peach.
No, it's black peach.
No, it's definitely not.
Everyone around me says black peach.
It's black peach because it's black
peach.
Black peach? What's that?
What? No!
What's black peach?
It's a insect that lives in Kyushu and
Hokkaido.
It's a black peach flower.
Black peach flower?
Yes, Yasukawa!
I made a mistake!
I'm sorry!
Thank you!
It's like a one-girl group.
Yasukawa-san is amazing!
It's cute!