It's morning time. We are Ebichu
University.
It's started.
Ebichu's new program, Ebichu Tastasuga.
Idol group, Ebichu University's new
program, Ebichu Tastasuga.
It starts next week.
Tonight's special is right before that.
berseker
World's Most Al pipeline
New P
This program is brought to you by these
sponsors.
A new program called Ebichu Pasta is a
variety of experiments that idols
collaborate with various things to
create scientific reactions.
The program is broadcast by the members
of Ebichu Junior High School and
supporters.
In addition, mysterious guests appear
every time.
What is the theme of the first time?
What do you add?
I add a switch.
I want to push it.
Let's push it.
I'm happy.
Is it okay if it doesn't stick to the
room?
The end.
What is the meaning of the Ebitu test
switch?
Before that, this time is a special
opportunity.
I asked the members what they want to
add to Ebitu in this program.
First of all, the number 6, Aika Hirota.
I am very interested in railways.
I like railways.
I am the only one who likes railways in
Ebitu.
I want to make the best of everyone.
I want to go to the factory of railways
with everyone.
Next is the number 11, Kobayashi Kahoa.
The reason why I wanted to add this is
because Nagariboshi-san always has a
funny laugh.
So I wanted to add a skit with him.
The reason why she wanted to add a skit
with Ebichu is...
I'm not used to variety shows, so I
always slip.
So if I have a chance to do a skit with
Nagariboshi-san, I want to be funny.
An idol with a comedian's gaze, will
Ebichu skit come true?
The number 12, the youngest, Riko
Nakayama...
I want to play a game with everyone.
I want to do a game where I can make a
face of the person who hit the dodge
ball.
I want to play anyway.
Next, the oldest member of the group,
Rika Mayama.
I want to cook.
I think it would be fun to have a
cooking battle.
I can eat.
If there is a reward, everyone will be
serious.
Mayama wants to cook.
Next, the two friends of the shrimp.
The number 7, Hoshina Mirei.
The number 9, Rina Matsuno.
I like to eat.
I want to have a barbecue.
I like nature, so I want to go hiking.
I like fruits.
I want to go to a strawberry bar with a
winer.
I want to eat other fruits.
I want to be healthy with a winer.
I think it would be fun.
The members who want to eat something
continue.
The 5th member, Ayaka Yasugoto, is
making a shocking statement.
I like comedians, so if I add comedians
other than Nagareboshi, I think everyone
will laugh.
She has been rejecting the cast of
Nagareboshi since the broadcast started.
Furthermore,
I have always admired Oriental Radio. I
like their rhythmical and good-tempo
comedy.
I want to show them.
Is there a casting change?
And I also asked Hinata Tashiwagi, who
was the first to see the movie.
Direct interview during the movie
shooting.
Good morning.
What does Hinata Tashiwagi want to show?
I want to hold a cultural festival.
Riko likes cotton candy, so I want to
eat cotton candy Riko makes.
Rina likes takoyaki.
I want to do what I want to do with all
the members.
I hope it will be a fun cultural
festival.
I heard a lot of things, but I want to
eat something.
This is the end of the show.
First of all, let me introduce the idol
group.
Please enjoy the video.
The concept of the group is to be an
eternal junior high school student.
The average age is 15.8 years old.
The formation was on August 4, 2009.
This is a picture of the early days of
Ebi-chuu.
Mayamato Yasumoto is a member from this
time.
Please see the very valuable live video
of the Indies era.
We are CJ Echigoku.
Thank you.
The
He continued his activities on his own
And after 3 years of being formed, their
activities are green and they made their
major debut
Oricon Daily Rank 2nd, Weekly Rank 7th,
and Cinderella who played the role of
Haruki made her debut single and won the
top prize.
Now, let's take a look at the single
songs of the Eri-Chu so far.
Eri-Chu Single History
Thank you for watching!
Ume's first daily ranking 1st place
This is the 5th single, the PV of the
unidentified junior high school student
X.
The director is Sekine Tsukomu.
The unidentified junior high school
student X.
Let's dance for the time being
Maybe I'm unidentified junior high
school student
The sixth single Butter Cry Effect
It became the first single in the
current member formation
When the wish comes true
A miracle of birth and death
I'm dying
I fell in love
The momentum of Ebichu never stops
The 7th single, Haikateki, is a big hit
Furthermore, Ebichu's biggest charm is
the live activities called Gakugeikai
After this, the live video will be
released
The new show of private Ebisu junior
high school, Ebichu Tastas
We will introduce their charm in the
next week's broadcast
The biggest attraction is the live
called Bakugoukaikko
In December 2013, the one-man live will
be held at Saitama Super Arena
It has been one year and seven months
since the major debut
At that time, the Japanese artist was
the fastest to perform at Saitama Super
Arena
He captured the attention at the cool
stage with a great performance
Furthermore, in 2014, they held a solo
concert at the Nippon Budokan and
attracted 10,000 people.
In summer, they held a solo outdoor live
with a theme of a long-distance trip.
During the show, they held a family
trip.
They performed with a lot of water and
fire.
The members ran through the outdoor live
with a group of fans.
At the end of the concert...
I wanted to see the fireworks.
The members are also impressed by this.
The special feature of the Ebichu
Gakugei is to enjoy the live with the
fans.
The event in the summer has been a great
success.
And in the fall, they will hold a one-
man live at Yokohama Arena.
And in January this year...
Ebichu has come to Taiwan!
This is Ebichu's first time going
overseas.
Please watch the special Taiwan version
of Cinderella, the hunting contract.
We'll do our best!
All the best!
1, 2, 3! We're
One, two, Three, four, Turn Turn,
fantastic!
This activity does not stop here!
The most popular shows in Eibichuu
Stadium is us.
según là sự chân ch否 Thank you for the
great show!
And, Mimcat is a baby that Aut Suppose
to be Fà Зем, alive and sure!
You say?
Yeah!
And this year's EbiTuber is also full of
energy!
The second album, Kimpachi, released in
January, was a huge hit on the Oricon
chart.
The third album, Kimpachi, was a huge
hit on the Oricon chart.
Please call us on a new journey
We are Golden Ace
Next is Shiritaya Bish Chukaku!
Shiritaya Ebichu Chukaku is challenging
again!
The new program Ebichu Tastas!
Finally, the next week starts!
This time, we will show you a little bit
of that!
This is the first time, so I will turn
on everyone's motivation switch!
I will turn on the switch!
Nakayama!
Don't run away!
Don't run away in the open!
Nakayama, press this switch and turn on
everyone's motivation!
If you press this, everyone will turn
on, right?
Yes!
The outcome is the power of НSR!
The opening character, the member's
maximum freedom!
AndみителもGigшь演出会社にて behavioural culture
問題の話
最新のスイッチに感動
何?どうして?
誰かピアノ弾ける?
誰かピアノ弾ける子
あ、かもかも
少しだけ弾けない
少しだけ弾けるのやってみなよ
何?
目が眩いちゃった
終了
エビ中にスイッチを足したら一体どうなる?
次回 新しいミニコーナーもお楽しみに
This January, the research student
recruitment of Ebi-Chu was announced.
The name is Sakura Ebiz.
Currently, auditions are going on in
various places.
In the program, the information about
the Sakura Ebiz audition will be
released one after another.
Furthermore, the new project of Ebi-Chu
will also be initiated.
There is a serious report for everyone.
The project to create a game of Ebi-Chu
is in progress in 2015.
What is the shock of Ebi-Chu game
development?
And finally, I asked the members of the
new program.
I think this is the only program that
can show the Ebitu-like feeling.
I think it would be Ebitu-like if we
could show a lot of free and loose
parts.
I want to make the Ebitu family and the
Hoshii family think it's interesting.
And I want to make the non-fans think
it's interesting.
I want to make it.
This time, I want to add something to
the show.
It's like a science ceremony.
And it's a location.
I want to be more active.
In the studio, I was often told that I
was passive.
So I want to do my best to show myself.
That's my one goal.
And this is a very relaxed program.
I want to show you how relaxed I am.
I hope you'll be surprised.
I think you can see the more powerful
me.
I appeared in the first episode.
But I'm more relaxed than before.
When we were planning for the Ebitu
Global,
at first we couldn't talk much,
and we were all like, wow, wow, wow,
as we were stacking up the times.
But this time, we're all like, wow, wow,
wow,
and we're going to add a lot of things,
and we're going to have fun.
Please watch it. Thank you.
We have a lot of friends in the group.
So we rarely get along with the people
we've worked with.
But we've loved Nagayoboshi-san since
before we started working together.
So when I heard that we could work
together, I was really happy.
And we talked to each other more and
more.
I think it's the first time we've gotten
along so well.
I'm so happy when I hear that we can do
a show together.
So, I hope we can make lots of memories
together this time as well.
And I hope we can grow further as a
group.
I hope Nagareboshi-san will teach us a
lot.
In the last Global Ka! Project, I always
relied on Nagareboshi-san.
But this time, I was able to do a show
with him.
I hope I can contribute to this.
And from Kashiwagi...
The program is about adding various
things.
Adding them and experiencing various
I hope I can grow up with this
experience.
And there is also a starfish.
I think it will be fun and interesting.
I hope it will be a lively program.
We are also the ones who are added to
the Ebitu.
Added to the Ebitu.
I think it would be nice if the Ebitu
explodes with a chemical change.
Please look forward to it.
Switch on!
The first episode of Ebichu Tastas is
Ebichu Tastas Switch.
Ebichu is pushing the switch.
Oh, it's coming!
It's shining!
Ebichu Tastas, target at 11 o'clock at
night.
This program was provided by the sponsor
you are watching.
Greek necessarily.
Will be launched in DEUTSCH package.