Ebichu no Douga Toka
I'm Kobayashi Kaho, the number 11.
Today's Ebichu no Douga Toka is...
Kaho-zake!
Yay!
I'm 20 years old now, so I'm going to
try Kaho-zake.
I'm wearing a men's outfit.
It's raining now.
It's been raining for a while, but I'm
going to go.
I'm going to try it.
This is Kojima-san's salmon.
I ate with all the members in Ebichu
before.
It was the 10th anniversary, so he made
a special 10th anniversary plate.
This time I want to go to Kojima-san's
salmon.
I'm often asked if I can eat salmon or
not.
So I want to feel salmon.
But this time I want to eat Kojima-san's
salmon.
No?
This is not Kojima-san's salmon.
I thought so.
This time...
I'm going to go to a salmon stand.
I'm going to enter the restaurant.
Hello.
Hello, I'm Kabayashi Kaho.
Today, I wanted to eat at a salmon
stand.
I'm going to eat at this restaurant.
I've never been to a place like this
before.
It's very relaxing.
I'm going to enjoy the place.
I'm going to order something.
I'm going to drink a sake that I heard
about.
Excuse me, I'd like a salmon sashimi,
please.
I heard that salmon sashimi is
delicious, so I ordered it.
By the way, do you know Ebichu?
He seems to know.
Ebi is a sea fish.
He is very kind.
I heard that you are Kobayashi-san.
Are you really Kobayashi-san?
Yes, I am Kobayashi-san.
Hello, I am Kobayashi-san.
I am Kobayashi-san, too.
Nice to meet you.
By the way, what was your nickname when
you were a student?
I was Kobachan.
Oh, Kobachan.
I was Kobaton.
I didn't know that there was a person
called Kobayashi-san.
I feel a little close to them.
They are my friends from the sea.
I feel relieved.
Thank you for waiting.
This is a salmon sashimi.
Can you see it?
It looks delicious.
I drink this for the first time.
I drink sake with a straw for the first
time.
I drink this.
May I eat it?
It's delicious!
This is the first time I have ever had a
plum wine with soy milk.
This is called shaki-hai.
I mixed it.
It's very delicious.
It's easy to drink.
If you come to this place, please try
shaki-hai.
Do you have any recommended snacks?
We have salmon and salmon roe.
I think I can order all of these.
We have fried shrimp.
This is raw salmon.
Is this raw?
Yes.
I'll have that.
Is it okay?
I'm good at eating salmon.
I can eat this time.
I'll eat this.
I made my debut as a stand-up comedian.
I think it's easy to enter.
The salmon stand is easy to enter even
for women.
I started to help with the meal.
I haven't cooked fish yet.
I'll watch the cooking video.
If I can cook salmon, I'll be hired.
I'm not good at it.
Thank you.
I eat this.
It looks like this.
I'm going to eat this.
Delicious!
It's so delicious!
It doesn't have a smell, so even if you
don't like salmon, you can eat it.
It's so delicious! The sauce is also
very delicious.
Is it sesame sauce?
It's sesame sauce.
It's very delicious.
I ate salmon sashimi for the first time
in a long time, but I ate such a
delicious salmon sashimi for the first
time.
Please try it!
Thank you for watching! Please subscribe
to my channel!
The cucumber is also crispy and
delicious.
Yummy!
It seems to be delicious for everyone to
drink alone.
Thank you for watching.
Some daughters are doing it in their
bed.
I think I know him.
A lot of people I know came to my house.
I'm surprised to see you here.
I'm a potter.
Thank you for your hard work.
I came here for the first time.
I'm surprised.
The first beer is beer.
It's good.
What's that?
This is a salmon pie.
Plum wine and soy milk.
I see.
The color of the salmon is good.
I mixed them, so they are separated.
Do you drink at home?
I do.
I drink.
I drink one cup a day.
I drink one cup a day, so my members
say,
I'm surprised that you drink so much.
It's okay. I drink one cup a day.
I drink. It's a fun time.
About five years ago,
I said I wanted to go to a ramen
restaurant on a program.
I said I didn't want to go.
I didn't expect to drink here.
I didn't expect to keep my promise here.
When I drink, I can talk to many people.
I can't talk to anyone when I'm drunk.
I only drink with my family.
I can talk to people around me.
You can communicate with people when you
go to a ramen restaurant.
I can communicate with many people.
I see.
I'm having a hard time now.
Excuse me.
I'd like a Kamaboko butter, please.
I eat salmon.
Is it good?
Yes.
It's easy to eat.
I've never been to a tachi-nami before.
I thought I could get in because I had
the image of a salaryman.
It depends on the place.
There are many young people in
Shinbashi.
I see.
It's easy to get in.
What do you want to drink next?
I think you want to drink beer.
Is it different from beer?
I should have made you drink a lot.
I drank up.
What should I do?
Or...
I see.
Excuse me.
I'd like a lemon sour, please.
How about the shrimp?
Is Hina the strongest?
I don't know. If I were to fight with
Kaho, I'd choose her.
Is this the first time?
Is this a raw squeeze?
It's the first time I've squeezed it
raw.
I'll do it for the camera.
I can't squeeze it.
It's like I can't squeeze it because I
don't have the power.
Is it on?
I can't squeeze it at all.
It's squeezed a lot, but I can't squeeze
it at all.
It's amazing.
This is the first time I've squeezed
lemon sour in my life.
I can't do it without squeezing it.
I've been told that.
Do you want me to squeeze it for you?
I'm not good at squeezing.
Will I be able to squeeze a lemon
someday?
This is not a straw.
That's a straw.
That's a muddler.
I'm sorry to say that I'm embarrassed.
I'll add more of this.
It's good.
It's good? Good.
It's good. It's full of lemon.
It's because you made it yourself.
I think it's good.
It doesn't matter.
I don't think so.
It's better to drink at a restaurant
than at home.
At a restaurant, you can get food right
away.
At a restaurant, it's the best.
It's the best.
How about a video of shrimp stew?
This is a challenging project.
I think it's important to try it and
keep doing it.
I'm sorry.
Park Oto.
Ham and egg?
Oh, someone I know is here again!
Someone you know?
Someone I know is here again!
What?
Are you two okay?
We're fine.
Are you okay?
I'm glad we kept our social distance for
this day.
Oh, really?
That's rude of me.
Private! Private!
This is private.
Oh, me too!
My name is Tewin Kobayashi,
and I'm wearing a suit for the show.
Oh, you're a special guest.
Yes, I am.
I didn't know.
What?
What a coincidence!
Special guest!
This is a special guest, Mayama-san.
I was in Shinjuku to go to the dentist,
and the knife came out suddenly.
That's a real story.
It's a serious story.
I just invited you normally.
That's why you came.
Thank you.
I made my debut in a standing drink in a
video during the show.
I've never made a standing drink before.
That's amazing.
It's easy for women to drink a standing
drink.
That's right.
I'm fine.
What did you drink?
I drank a salmon drink.
I'm drinking a lemon sour drink.
What is a salmon drink?
It was delicious.
It's a mix of plum wine and soy milk.
It's a mix of two colors.
It's a mix of salmon.
Do you have any beer?
Thank you.
How many glasses have you had?
I haven't had a drink yet.
I've had three glasses.
You're the best.
Thank you for watching.
Bye bye.
I'm sure you'll be able to eat it.
I've heard that before.
But now there's a lot more.
It's increasing.
I think you're getting more and more
like it.
It's better than before.
I can put it in my mouth for now.
You can't eat it.
It depends on the food.
I think I can eat it.
It's white meat or sashimi.
It's a good thing to eat.
Do you like it?
My family is...
The one who doesn't like it is
unfortunate.
That's how it's raised.
I didn't like eggplant when I was a kid.
I'm starting to eat eggplant.
That's right.
That's amazing.
It's gone.
How have you been lately?
Me?
There's a live show without an audience.
In August.
I'm going to warm up a little bit.
I started working out again at home.
I've only been doing it moderately
during the self-quarantine.
I've never had a drink before.
It's the first time we've been alone.
You look good in alcohol.
Really?
You look good in it.
I had a drink the other day.
I had a drink for two days.
You had a drink for two days?
My mom likes alcohol.
I drank with my mom.
I don't know the taste yet.
I'll drink it as delicious as I did.
Your mom is high-spirited.
That's right.
I didn't realize it until I drank it.
I thought I was drunk.
I was so drunk that I was blurry.
I thought so.
The next day, I drank a lot.
Isn't it too early?
How long has it been since you started
drinking?
About a month.
That's amazing.
I'm sorry to bother my brother and
sister.
I experienced it for a while.
I realized that this was the second day.
I've never seen you so drunk before.
How was it?
I was drunk with this extension.
I'm going to be more drunk.
I was so drunk.
I was watching a DVD of Sazan and
Torikawa, and I was crying while singing
together.
Sounds fun.
I'm going to do it.
I'm doing it with Aiko.
I'm going to cry.
Tears are coming out.
I'm sure you're sick.
I'm not drunk, but I'm sure I'm feeling
good.
It's refreshing to cry.
Have you ever tried drinking alcohol?
There are many.
I don't know yet.
I've never tried drinking alcohol.
I see.
It's my birthday.
What's your favorite drink?
I'm sorry.
I like plum soda.
What's your favorite drink?
I don't know.
I see.
I think I'll be fine if I drink this.
Does it depend on the store?
I introduced a bottle of beer.
When there is a red star in the bottle,
I think it's a bottle of beer.
When I drink that, I feel like I'm in
pain.
I think so, too.
I'm going to introduce a beer for women.
A beer for women?
It's called Wednesday beer.
It's a beer that I drink often at rest
stops.
It's a beer I drink often at rest stops.
It's a活بحれ Bowsan.
Is it
It's a beer that I drink often at rest
stops.
The bowl is cute too.
The bowl is cute.
The can is a bae.
It's a bae.
I see.
I think it's good for people who have a
resistance to beer.
I like dumplings.
It looks delicious.
Have you ever had dumplings and sake
together?
Yes.
Really?
I drank beer with dumplings.
It's great.
It's delicious.
I felt delicious.
I didn't have a problem drinking beer
alone.
But I thought it would be delicious to
drink with dumplings.
I thought it would be delicious.
What kind of sake do you drink now?
plum wine.
Do you drink plum wine?
I often drink plum wine.
What is the best food for plum wine?
I haven't eaten or drunk it yet.
You drink sake alone.
I don't know what goes well with plum
wine.
I only eat salami and chitaro.
What goes well with plum wine?
Plum wine is very sweet.
It's a appetizer.
You don't have to drink sake with plum
wine.
Is that so?
Beer has no taste.
I drink something that has a strong
taste.
Dumplings are better with beer.
This dumpling is very delicious.
It's delicious.
Did you go to drink with your friends?
I did.
I drank alone.
I went to a local restaurant.
I went there to drink.
I don't drink now.
I'm looking forward to the day when I
can find a place to go.
I don't think there is a place to go to.
Do you want to go drinking someday?
I want to go to a bar.
You can't go now.
I'm afraid.
I think I've grown up there.
I think so, too.
I used to eat at a bar.
I don't usually order alcohol.
I think I've grown up there.
I went to a restaurant that I often go
to.
I didn't order alcohol there.
I think we've grown up.
I'm looking forward to the day when I
can drink with my friends.
I want to see the day when I can drink
with my friends.
I'm looking forward to your birthday.
I think I can drink.
I think so, too.
I think RIKO is very interesting.
I hope I can talk to her.
I'm looking forward to the day when I
can drink with RIKO.
How was the video of the shrimp?
I think it's a video that shows the
personality of the shrimp.
If I hadn't made this video, I wouldn't
have done the trap tower.
I think it's interesting.
I want to get a kendama test.
Sounds fun.
I think it's fun.
I think you should try it.
What kind of video do you want to see?
I want to see KAO's hair.
I think it's good.
I want you to grow your hair.
I want you to grow your hair as much as
you can.
I'm going to grow my hair as long as I
can.
I think it's cute.
I'm going to grow my hair as long as I
can.
I'm not going to grow my hair as long as
I can, but I'm going to grow my hair as
long as I can.
Who said that?
KAO said that.
KAO said that when I was 20 years old.
I don't remember that.
What's your favorite drink?
plum wine.
There are various kinds of plum wine.
The plum wine I made at home was
delicious.
Is it sweet?
It's a little sweet.
It's not very sweet.
It's a little sweeter than sweet.
It's a little refreshing.