To be continued...
Happy New Year!
On the day of 2021, the year-end party
was announced.
The audition for the year-end party was
decided!
Shiritu Ebisu Middle School New Member
Audition Start!
The catch copy of the new member
audition is
More! More! More! Ebichu!
The catch copy is
Let's increase the number of members
that are like Ebichu
And the new member will be more powerful
And the new member will be more
wonderful
That's the catch copy
March 1st
The day after the audition is over
The first screening of the audition will
start!
The number of people who have gathered
is
About 7,000
The number of applicants is 7,000!
I think it's a good number
Because our new members told me
Thank you for watching!
Why not? 700?
Thank you very much
Yes
I'm looking for a man who's fit to be a
princess.
Prince, that's me.
Please make a contract with me.
K.A.I.
We're working hard!
We're working hard, working hard
Today, we're working hard for you
Since Kobayashi Kaho and Riko Nakayama,
it's been 7 years since they've been new
members
We managed to keep up with them!
I think we did the formation right.
And the first audition will decide the
members.
I think it will be interesting to see
who will be the first to enter the
shrimp house.
What about the members?
If we were to divide the shrimp house
into stories, the first and second
auditions will be when Natsuhiro and
Mizuki switch and the two of them join.
I think this audition will be the
beginning of the third round.
I'm looking forward to seeing what
changes will be made.
It's quite brave to be in an audition
for a group.
But I think the members who will be in
the audition will want to see the
beautiful scenery with us.
So I was more excited and excited when I
was told to be in the audition.
I didn't think I would be in the
audition.
It will be harder than when we were in
the audition.
There are so many songs.
Ayaka will be in the audition and Hinata
will be in the dance lesson.
I think I can support them.
And Hoshina is talking about her
decision.
I was able to hear the voices of the six
people who wanted to see the shrimp
house more.
I was able to hear the voices of the six
people who wanted to see the shrimp
house more.
I'm really grateful that they can say
that.
I hope that new members will be in the
audition and I hope that new members
will be able to accept the new beauty.
We are looking forward to seeing new
members.
Next time, we will continue to find out!