Thank you for watching.
Hello?
Who? Hello?
Hello? Hello? Me? Me?
it, please
I think
I Not
I I
...
me version y I
?
I don't know.
I'll make you get a cold.
What?
I'll make you get a grand.
Mr. Nakai?
Yes.
No!
Mr. Nakai!
Long time no see.
It's been a while.
I was surprised.
How are you?
I'm fine.
When was that?
It was around the end of August, right?
Yes, it was.
When was it?
It was around the end of August last
year.
Ah, at the Kyujyo.
Yes, I broadcasted at the Kyujyo.
It feels weird.
Was it your first time talking on the
phone?
It was your first time, right?
It was my first time.
You didn't have a phone, right?
Yes.
Your phone?
I have a strange feeling. I can't see
your face.
I've been looking at my face on the
remote lately, but I can't really call
you.
I don't have a phone.
You don't? Our generation used to have a
phone.
Don't you call your friends?
But I used to call my friends on the
remote.
When it was COVID-19.
You used to talk to your face.
It was easy to talk to.
I see.
You have a strange nervousness.
Did anything change?
I really enjoyed acting.
But I've been thinking about more
things.
I see.
I like you now.
I was surprised by the way you acted.
How can I say...
It's natural. You're very serious about
acting.
Really?
You're very thoughtful.
I don't want to lose in a good way.
The core is solid.
Your voice is unexpectedly...
It's an anime voice.
That's right.
But it's like the first oath.
It's like a student representative.
You talked.
I was a little surprised that the male
and female were together.
But Nakai-san was laughing at that time.
I was surprised that you made such a
loud voice.
I thought you were laughing a lot.
I thought it was amazing.
Did you laugh? Did you laugh?
I was surprised.
I was surprised that you made such a
loud voice.
I thought you were going to make a lot
of noise.
I was surprised. 意外だとかあるよね。
Really? 本当ですか?
But... でもあれ大変だった。最初じゃなかったっけ?
The last scene. ラストシーンっていうか。
With Sada-chan. サダちゃんとハーモニカのシーンですね。
You played the harmonica. ハーモニカ吹いて。
You shot the climax scene on the first
day. クライマックスのシーンを初日ぐらいに撮ってやる。
That's right. 初日か。
Almost. もうほとんど。
We got the pin and took it right away.
That's right.
We both started. アーモニカも吹かなきゃいけないし。
That's right. もう話してない時に。
I was doing it. やってました。
I was very nervous at that time. 緊張しました。
But the teacher of harmonica said that
it was good to be a teacher because I
was singing.
Really?
I'm glad. 嬉しい。
I'm also singing.
That's amazing.
You're also an voice actor, right?
Yes.
You're also a voice actor, right?
Yes, I am.
You're doing a lot of things, aren't
you?
Yes, I am.
I'm glad that you let me do a lot of
things.
But you never say that you can do this
much.
You're amazing.
No, no, no.
Do you think so?
I can do this much.
I don't think so.
You have a long career.
From a child's age.
I've been doing it since I was seven.
From the first day.
You've been doing this for over 15
years?
Yes.
I've been doing this for over 15 years.
But I really have to do it one by one
because I'm doing a lot of things.
Is that feeling of being relaxed at all?
Yes.
実は熱いよね。目が。
そうですね。体育会見なのが好きですね。みんなで頑張ろうって。
そうだよね。それこそさっきの腕立て伏せもこの間あのシーンでやったけど、軽く自慣で
やったもんね自分でね。
そうですね。
余裕で。
そうそうそういうのばかりです。 意外なことがすごいいっぱいあったなぁと思って。
嬉しい。 なんかあの昨日弱いちょっとお嬢さんで
えっと私できませんみたいな感じなのかなと思ったら真逆だったんでちょっとびっくりし
た。
嬉しい。
えー
すごい。でも なんかあの時表情の時は
大丈夫かなってずっと思ってました。
何が?
自信がなさすぎってというか、お芝居に対しても向き合えてるのかなみたいな。
アンコちゃん何が好きなの?って言って、そぼろですって言ったのを忘れられない。
そぼろって料理なのかな?まあいいんだけど。
そう、みんなに爆笑されました、あの時。
なんでこんなに笑うんだろうって思うぐらい。
あの、でも私、天然だと思ってないんだもんね、自分はね。
いや、違いますよ。
いやいや、かなり天然なことなんだけど。
いやいやいやいやいや、それはないです。
本当にそう思ってんの?
僕は天然な良いところだよなぁ。 だから。
嘘?ありました?そんなこと。 いやなんか結構その
意外になんか
これ今面白く本気でやってんだろうか、冗談でやってんだろうか、みたいなの結構あった
気がする。
ありましたっけ?あ、お芝居とかでですか? お芝居はね。
There was. I don't think there was a芝居.
I understand the芝居.
You understand? Were you able to do it?
But I'm trying my best to do it.
I'm glad I'm doing it because I think
it's okay.
I understand people who are doing
something that they can't take.
I think it's amazing that it doesn't
look like that.
It's true. It's true.
I think it's the opposite.
I want to hear about the acting.
But that's a special role. It's a role
that hasn't been done before.
That's right.
But really,
I understand it every time I go into
shooting.
I'm like, he seems like he's cut-throat
someone.
Haruka did it, so I played like her.
Really?
Yes. I took advantage of her.
No.
Yes, it's just like me.
I don't want to wait.
Really?
Ye official
Thank you for watching.
Is there anything else you want to do in
the future?
You're still doing drama, right?
Yes.
That's right.
Oh, you're watching it?
Actually, it's a little weird, but it's
like I'm going to ride it again.
Yes, it might be similar.
I want to do something.
I still have time to do many things.
I'm still young.
I want to do something.
I like family stuff.
I like family stories.
I want to see young people.
I want to do that.
I'm not a family. I'm a family. I'm a
child.
I want to be a mother.
I still want to be a child.
But it's a family. I like my family.
I can tell you what my family likes.
Really?
平穏無事じゃなくて、結構大人しめの役が多いし、気の弱いとか、見出せないとか、ちょ
っと真逆とかないの?
すっごい悪者とか、悪役とか。
でも、ヤンキーの役は、周りに絶対できないよって言われるから、やってみたいですね。
役だからね、できるかもしれないけどね。確かにできなそうだよね。
ちょっと。
ちょっとできるんだよって、やりたいです。
そう。
うん。一緒にやりたいです。中田さんと。
あら、そうなの?
え、やりたいです。
うん。
ありがたいわ。 いやいやいやいや。
なんかさ、今やっててこう、拒っていることとか、その、今後やりたいとか、そのお芝居
とかで、うんうん。
なんか考えることとか、ある? なんか。
うーん。
でもなんか、お芝居ってどうしたら、なんか、生のものっていうか。
I'm not talking about the technique, but
I'm thinking about how to make my heart
move more smoothly.
I think there are always people who
share the same thoughts. It depends on
the person.
I see.
I do a lot of things, but it's an analog
work, so I have to meet people.
I have to meet people and talk to them.
I wonder how people meet.
It really depends on the person.
I agree.
But at the scene...
Is it the right thing to do what you
felt at that time?
Well, that's right. Even if you think
about it, even if you think about it in
various ways,
It changes when you go to the scene. The
weather, the atmosphere, the opponent,
the staff, it changes.
It's a live show, but it's pretty raw.
I think we have to be very flexible when
we prepare for the show.
I don't know. We've been doing it for a
long time without knowing.
I think we might as well stop.
What? Please don't stop.
But now, there are people who are aiming
for that.
What do you want to be in the future?
What do you want to be as an actor in
the future?
I want to be more and more good at my
acting.
I want to impress my family.
I want to move people's hearts.
I want to do acting.
I want people to think about me.
I want people to think that I'm doing my
best.
I want to be able to change my life.
That's why I usually do my best.
I do things other than work.
Other than work...
But...
I do it every day.
Every day?
In private.
I see.
But...
I've been trying to be honest all the
time.
Oh, that's okay because you've already
done it.
I'm surprised you said that, but I'm
going for a drive.
I went shopping alone and went shopping
when I was a little messy.
What do you usually do? I can't see it
at all.
I'm surprised to see you alone.
What do you usually do?
I usually drive.
You drive?
I drive.
I also go to the gym.
You go to the gym?
I go.
I'm surprised to see you.
What?
I also go to the gym.
I'm a hair stylist, but I usually make
my hair very clean.
I may not be conscious of it.
My skin was beautiful.
The staff told me that my skin was the
best.
I'm glad.
I'm doing something.
Can I say this? I'm not imitating you.
Nakai-san is also fluffy.
I'm being careful.
But the lotion...
Food and lotion.
There's something like, this is it.
Eh? But, it's too late.
I don't eat snacks.
You're a child.
I see. That's about it.
I guess you live so that you don't get
stressed.
That's right.
I can get a pimple when I'm tired.
I see.
I'm glad.
What is Nakai-san doing?
What are you doing?
Like on a day off?
I'm not sure what day off I'm doing,
but...
What am I doing?
This summer, I'm working remotely.
I can't gather everyone, I can't go out,
and I'm busy with work.
I'm making cucumbers at my family
garden.
That's surprising!
That's more surprising.
That's surprising.
I heard that there are more people doing
things at home, and I thought I could
understand.
That's true. It's like something you can
do at home.
I want to go camping.
I want to go.
I want to call everyone.
That's right.
If we get together, we won't be able to
do the party properly, so we'll have to
do it together.
That's right.
I want to get together and do something
together.
I want to do it.
I have a lot of camping equipment.
You cook for me, don't you?
I do.
You cook for me every day.
I cook delicious food.
I see.
I want to go.
Do you ever think that you are strange
or something?
Eat as much as you eat.
自分では思わないのか? Don't you think so?
全く思わないです。 I don't think so at all.
全く思わない? いいや。 Then, don't you think so at
all? 自分の短所というか、弱いとこ。 I'm not sure. 弱いとこ?
I'm not sure. 変なとこって何だったら、例えばその弱点。 If
you're not strange, for example, your
weakness. でもあれですね。 But, I think 瞬発力が、
イメージが変わると、 人間の体力が変わる。 You can't change
your mind. 自分の短所というか、 人間の体力が変わる。 You
can't change your mind. 自分の短所というか、
人間の体力が変わる。 You can't change your mind.
自分の短所というか、 人間の体力が変わる。 If you're not
strange, for example, your weakness.
アイテムが変わると、 人間の体力が変わる。 You can't change
your mind. 自分の短所というか、 人間の体力が変わる。 You
can't change your mind. 自分の短所というか、
人間の体力が変わる。 You can't change your mind.
自分の短所というか、 人間の体力が変わる。
何か、ちょっとスロー。 slow.
理解するのとかは、ちょっと遅いなって感じます。 I think I'm a
little slow in understanding.
そのぐらいか。 That's about it.
あと、自信が持てないとか、緊張しちゃうとか。 I'm not
confident. I'm nervous. いっぱいあります。 There
are a lot.
なるほど。 I see.
いや、たかなか電話ご飯とお言いながら、とつで喋れなかったもんね。 I
didn't think I'd be able to talk on the
phone.
いや、嬉しかったです。本当に。 I was really happy.
ありがとうございました。またね。 Thank you. See you.
またお体に気をつけて。 Take care of your body.
いや、もうはるかちゃんもぜひ、がんばって。笑顔で頑張ってください。 Please
do your best with a smile.
はい。ありがとうございます。 Yes. Thank you.
では。 Bye.
じゃあね。また。 Bye.
ひつりしまーす。 Excuse me.
はい。バイバイ。 Bye.
ありがとうございます。 Thank you.
Bye.
Thank you for watching.