Ebichu's video!
Today is the 14th!
We're going to the rehearsal now!
It didn't rain.
Thank you for your continued support.
It's raining.
Hello.
I ran outside.
I slipped.
I'm Mariko Nakayama.
I'm Yuno Koguro.
I'm Kana Korimaya.
I'm Noibuko.
It's over.
I'm very nervous today.
I was nervous before rehearsal.
I'm more nervous after rehearsal.
I'm not talking.
I'm nervous.
I'm nervous and my voice is weak.
I'll practice.
I have a voice problem.
I have to be careful.
I'll do my best.
It's raining.
I made a turtle pose.
I'm sorry.
I'm under pressure to talk every time I
pass by here.
I'm always wearing a cover of CHU-YO.
I'm going to sing the song of Mika
Nakashima.
I had a co-host.
I'm going to cover the song of Mika
Nakashima.
I think I'll be a good accent.
I'll do my best.
It's really expensive.
It's expensive, but I'll do my best with
my voice.
I'll do my best.
I love it.
How is it?
I'm so hungry.
I'm full.
Did you eat?
I ate and did a 30-minute exercise.
I ate.
I'm nervous to sing alone.
Everyone sings first.
It was fun.
It's raining and it's cold.
I'm glad I came.
I'm practicing outside.
I came to the lesson and sang.
I was surprised to see a guard from
afar.
There is a guard pass.
I didn't lower my guard.
I was surprised to see a guard from
afar.
Why did I take a picture?
This is my stand.
I was surprised to see a guard from
afar.
I said, I'm a rabbit.
I said, I understand.
The staff around me said,
I like the little rabbits.
I said, I'm a little rabbit.
I'll crush it.
My stand suddenly appeared.
I'm a rabbit.
So I'm a rabbit.
It seems to have arrived.
Po-chan's...
What was it?
It's a rabbit from TETTLE BOYS.
Thank you.
I changed my clothes.
Look.
Why are you so excited?
Because I ate a shine muscat.
I got a lot of food.
I'll eat a lot.
I'm practicing on the road.
I'm a little sad.
The first day of the first part.
The first day...
What?
It's the first day.
Thank you for your hard work.
The circuit talk was smooth.
Bye-bye.
It's over.
The circuit is over.
It was fun.
Was it fun?
I was nervous.
I'm not in the picture.
I'm going to the picture.
No, no, no.
I can't stop you.
I'm a little nervous.
It was hard to understand.
I was nervous.
No, no, no.
I'm going to the picture.
Is it over?
It's over.
The first part is over.
The second part is over.
I'm going to the end.
It looks fun.
It was fun this year.
The person who came didn't show it.
I wanted to show it, but I was sad.
I'm going to the second part.
I'm a little nervous.
I have a promise.
You'll remember it.
The second part.
Day 1, Day 2.
I'll do my best for the next
performance.
I'll do my best to sing the song.
I sang Tomoya Harada's Dandenaiyan.
I'll do my best.
Go-de again.
Go-de, please.
Suddenly?
You came to do this?
Let's enjoy the performance.
Where are we?
Chuo!
We are ITZY!
Let's go to Japan!
Thank you for your hard work.
It's over.
It was over.
Day 1 is over.
The rain stopped at the end of the day.
I enjoyed it.
I'm glad I could see your faces.
It's over.
Good night.
Day 2.
Good morning.
I ate pho in Saitama prefecture this
morning.
It was very delicious.
But this is not Yamanashi prefecture.
I'm full.
Let's have a good day.
Day 3.
It was over.
Good morning.
Thank you for your hard work.
It's cold today but I'll do my best!
Please wait for me!
I'm going to sing a song.
Are you filming?
I'm filming.
Which one should I do?
What?
Everyone, please stand up.
What kind of ending is this?
Thank you very much.
It's the main show.
I finished my performance.
It's the end of the year.
I'll do my best for the next university
entrance exam.
Bye bye.
I said Fami-en.
I said Fami-en at the end of the
performance.
I said Fami-en in the middle.
Chuu-on Fami-en.
Let's say it's safe.
It's too beautiful.
I want to do it.
Thank you.
I'm glad you're not going to get hurt.
My favorite song is the last song.
The last earphone song was really fun.
Please listen to it when you get into a
fight with a CD.
Yellow light
It's a lot different from the usual
tempo.
It's a relaxing atmosphere with a nice
atmosphere.
I think that's the beauty of this place.
Please watch it.
The show is over.
Was it fun?
I had a lot of fun.
I hope you all feel free to enjoy the
show.
Please look forward to next year.
Bye!
I'm a ghost.
I was really worried about Kapila.
But she clapped in front of me.
I was so happy.
Thank you.
I hope the atmosphere of the team and
the sound of the music will be healed.
Thank you.
I was trying not to blink, but I was
surprised.
Thank you.
What are you thinking?
What are you doing?
Thank you for two days.
I was happy to be able to cheer for you.
I'm going to take a break.
I'm looking forward to seeing you again.
Let's meet with a smile.
Thank you.
I'm getting more people.
I was happy.