To be continued...
Please subscribe to us.
I'm already 18.
I know.
I think it's just before you're in your
20s.
Hello, everyone.
I'm 19 years old.
But, Miya...
I'm already 18.
But, you don't know what we're talking
about.
Right.
We're just talking on the phone.
Today is my birthday.
Yay!
I'm nervous.
I'm going to be Miya's fan.
And, I'm going to be 20 years old.
Right.
I'm nervous.
Yay!
The costumes are from different groups.
Actually, they made them for my
birthday.
The wings on the back are cute.
I think I can fly.
I'm holding wings because I'm drinking
something.
You don't have to do that.
I'm holding wings.
You're drinking something.
Right.
I can't show you everything because it's
a self-portrait.
Please watch our video.
Please watch it.
We'll do our best at the fan meeting.
We'll go.
Bye bye!