We are the three of us in cute costumes
Actually, on this day
We are the three of us
Please give us a good performance
The new members are close to the first
appearance on TV
So this time, Ebichu will appear
regularly
Kannai Devil and Zenmo Remix will have a
special collaboration
And
The three will enjoy the future of
Yokohama port
There is a meaning
On June 9th, the TV Kanagawa
headquarters in Yokohama
There is the name of the shrimp member
This is the day of recording the Kannai
Devil
The Kannai Devil, where Ebi-chu is on a
regular show, is one of the most popular
TV shows in Kanagawa.
Music variety shows are held every week
in the Kissa-ten in the Yoko-hama
Kannai.
The three new members will be on the
show.
This is the first time.
This is the first time to record a TV
program as a member of Ebichu.
I'm nervous.
I'm going to be excited.
Thank you.
The one who will appear with the new
member is...
Me?
Thank you.
The three reliable educational staff,
Boss Kashiwagi.
I'm a little responsible.
I wonder if I can do it. I hope the
three of us can talk.
I remember the questionnaire.
I don't know what I wrote. I can't talk.
Thank you.
The new member is...
This is Mirei.
She hasn't worn any costumes for the
show yet because she's a guest.
She's wearing her senior's costume.
But the size is perfect.
It's cute.
This is Mayama's costume.
Let's get them ready before shooting
their scenes.
Da Vinci!
You'll wear them after you work.
It's over.
I'm going to work hard.
I'll work hard.
Please take care of me.
And then
Excuse me, just one minute.
Meeting before recording
We're going to have a meeting with the
guests at the cafe.
And we're going to have a free talk.
So you can talk to the members.
And we're going to have a fan meeting
and a fan meeting LP.
We're going to have a fan meeting and an
LP.
Let's go.
Thank you.
Cheer up.
And let's work hard.
Thank you.
The staff is full of energy.
They're going to have a free talk
without a script.
Will they do it well?
We'll start live streaming.
Thank you.
Please open the credits.
Start the live streaming.
Please enjoy the video.
The third new member of Ebichu.
You don't say anything?
Please, please.
That's voice-out NG.
I'm sorry.
You can't speak.
You said it earlier.
I have to protect it.
What should we do?
Should we ask Shouya to introduce?
Yes.
The history book.
I think everyone will get it.
You may work here.
That's right.
You're already here.
It's too early.
I'm number 13.
My name is...
Kokona Sakuragi.
Is Kokona your real name?
Yes.
It's a very modern name.
I'm number 14.
I'm Yuno Kokobo.
Yuno?
That's your real name?
Yes.
I'm number 19. I'm number 15. I'm Kazami
Nanoka.
Nanoka?
That's your real name?
It's 21st century.
And the project called the job
interview.
Check the history book you wrote in
advance.
The picture.
Do you want to go, Ms. Sakuragi?
From Kokona.
This is the picture.
I'm not doing it properly.
Oh well.
The last one is the biggest problem.
Yuno Kokobo.
This one is the most
This is the most
You're a little too early.
You're too early.
Why did you get a forehead?
What are you doing?
It's a pretty forehead.
This and that.
Noroko?
Everyone wrote their own private private
school.
This is
When we saw it, we thought it was a
joke.
Yes.
Private Subie Middle School.
I'm doing it.
It's a little bit of a good thing.
The first TV appearance is a shocking
development.
Thank you very much.
But the MC leads the show, and the fun
recording ends.
Thank you for your hard work.
How was it?
It was fun.
I was talking a lot today, but I'm glad.
I was relieved.
I was able to talk.
I'm glad.
Thank you for your hard work.
The two MCs who usually perform with the
Ebi-Chuu members
Let us hear the impressions of the new
members.
The new members who are not in the Ebi-
Chuu team
You were shining.
I was fresh.
You were bright.
You have a lot of things that we don't
have.
You have a lot of things that I don't
I'll re-check what I lost.
You were really cute.
Everyone is cute.
I've been watching the audition video.
I'm glad I finally met you.
I was recording, and you were so cute.
I said it many times that I was cute.
It's a unique industry.
I'm glad to be able to work with people
who are so far away from the city.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'd like you to join the shift.
Thank you.
So, the three of them will appear in the
show.
Please check the show.
Before the show was recorded on this
day,
the three people who came to Yokohama
had a place they wanted to see.
Good morning.
We came to see the fan meeting at
Akarenga Park.
This is Akarenga Park, the venue of the
fan meeting 2021.
The venue of the fan meeting was
canceled last year.
And...
Thank you for waiting, Ebisu Junior High
School and the audience.
The music festival was held in memory of
the 10th anniversary of Ebisu Junior
High School.
The future of the people who shine
We always wish for it
The blue stars are now shining
Ebichu's most important place was chosen
for the debut live of the three new
members.
To find the stage location by hinting at
the photo of the music festival
The wind is strong
What is this?
There is a red one here
Isn't it around here?
Isn't it here?
It's around here
The wind is strong
Grandpa, please tell us the location
Here
It's here
It's more forward
We'll make a stage here so it might be
more forward
Here?
It's right here
We'll make a stage here
Here
There are people in the building
You mean they are in the farthest part
of the field?
Yes, to the farthest part of the field
Next month, the three of them will have
their debut live here
It's been over a month since they joined
the group, and what does she think?
It's so fast.
If it's been a month, we would have been
able to perform at the fan meeting.
It's crazy to have our first live
performance here.
I want to do my best to reach out to my
fans.
I want to practice hard with the voice.
I thought I had to do my best here.
I'm glad that the people who came here
and passed by me thought it was a good
idea.
It was a great success.
It was a success.
I'm happy that it was a success.
I still don't know because I don't have
a good feeling.
And, Kokona was a little worried.
I was worried that I would be okay if I
could say that there were customers in
the back of the stage.
I'm grateful that it was such a big
place. I'm very nervous.
When one of the managers shook his hand,
I realized that I was going to stay
here.
I'm getting closer to the fan meeting.
I'm very excited.
The three have made up their minds.
The fan meeting 2021 has been decided
and will be held in two days.
The hot summer for Ebi-Chu is about to
begin.