This week's Ebi-Chu Tastas is the second
half of the strongest tag team
competition
Short suits you
Soft skin
For some reason, they are complimenting
each other
I'm a little embarrassed to say anything
What kind of competition is this?
Which team will be the winner of the
title of the strongest team?
Moratorium, moratorium, moratorium,
junior high school student
We will add various things to the
private Ebisu junior high school student
Junior high school student
Ebichu Dance Class
Start
This program is provided by the sponsor
you are watching
You are beautiful
Your legs are so big
Your nose is so cute
Unni, I'm sorry
This week's Ebitu Tastas is the
strongest team contest in Ebitu!
The winner is...
The previous episode, the team that has
been competing in the preliminary round
to improve the team's teamwork...
The current score is...
Hoshina and Kobayashi team are leading
by one point.
The next match is...
The last match of the preliminary round.
Here it is.
The winner is Eri-Chill Yamanochi!
I will explain the rules
You have to put the good points of your
opponent on the rhythm of the game
You have to say the same thing and you
have to be able to follow the rhythm
The rhythm?
Yes, something like this
I see, so you have to match the rhythm
Yes, that's right
If you know the good points of your
opponent, you will have an advantage
The last game is the mountain pass game
The number of times you compliment each
other will determine the order
The referee will decide if you said the
right thing
First, the top team with the most
points, Hoshina Kobayashi team will
challenge
First, the Hoshina Kobayashi team
How confident are you?
No
I'm not confident
You are the first
What are you thinking?
How many points do you think you can
get?
How many points do normal people get?
I don't know
Let's start the game
Good drawing
Cute angel
Nice smile
Perfect eyes
Eat a lot
Ame-guchi
The end
It was fast
Nya nya
The rhythm was wrong
Nya nya, the end
This was not good
The end
No
Kobayashi failed to get into the rhythm
Out
What is it?
By the way, do you want to add the Nya
nya end?
Nya nya end is out
Out, that means
5 Nya nya ends
Thank you
By the way, you said you eat a lot, is
this a compliment?
The one who eats a lot is cute
Not only cute
I'm embarrassed
I brought the fact that the one who eats
a lot is cute
Is this okay?
The one who eats a lot is cute
My wife eats a lot too
Really?
Please wait for the result
The next one to challenge is the
Yasumoto Kashiwagi team
Let's start
Ebichu Yamashita game
Ready, start
Short looks good
Soft skin
Eyes are bright
Black eyes are big
Beautiful nose
Small hands are cute
Beautiful fingertips
Hair is smooth
Skin is white
Smile is wonderful
Clear collarbone
Eyes are black
Beautiful nose
Small hands are cute
Wait a minute
Someone said beautiful nose
I said it
I said the same thing
Out
It's difficult
Beautiful nose
Small hands are cute
Wait a minute
Kashiwagi team said the same thing twice
Out
Please judge properly.
This is a little difficult.
Also, there is a saying that the
collarbone is clear.
It's really beautiful.
Really? The collarbone is.
Is this good? The collarbone is clear.
Is the collarbone a beauty point?
Beauty point.
It was good.
Really beautiful.
The result is 12.
It was surprisingly good.
It was good.
Congratulations.
How was it?
I'm nervous.
Even if you have something to say.
I don't know what to say.
I don't remember what he said.
And you forget what you said.
I said it well.
It's beautiful.
It's not an impact.
What else did you try to praise?
Kashiwagi.
The singing voice is wonderful.
I also said that.
The dance is cool.
The MC is funny.
I'm not going to say anything because
I'm embarrassed.
I'm embarrassed when I see you.
The next challenge is the Mayama
Nakayama team.
Let's start.
Ebitu Yamase game.
Start.
Please give me a hand.
Please.
I'll do it again.
It's a point.
Let's go.
Ready, start.
The pony tail looks good on you.
The braids are cute.
The eyes are big.
The skin is like an egg.
The arms are thin.
Like a little sister.
The abs are thick.
The skin is white.
The legs are very thin.
The nose is cute.
Brother.
Can I have a moment?
The abs are thick.
And the nose is cute.
What did you say at the end?
Sister.
You should call her sister.
Can I have a moment?
She can't praise her sister.
Nakayama is out.
If you take out the sister, you get 10
points.
You got 10 points.
I'm sorry.
Don't jump.
But the first rhythm was good.
The one who prepared it was good.
I was caught.
The pony tail is beautiful and the
braids are beautiful.
Midami is cute.
The braids are beautiful.
But it's similar to the previous one.
To be honest,
this role is heavy.
That's true.
It's the most responsible role.
Let's all judge.
Yes.
Don't leave it to me.
It's heavy.
That's true.
It's like a bath.
I'm sweating.
The last one is Hirota and Matsuno.
Can they pass the 12 questions?
Let's start.
Ebitune Yamase game.
Start.
Black hair is beautiful.
Big eyes.
Can get along with anyone.
Has a sense.
Eat anything delicious.
Good at cooking.
Beautiful shoulder blades.
The nose is cute.
The nose is high.
The legs are long.
Gentle.
Didn't you get a gentle one?
I got it.
Wait a minute. Don't be silent until I
say it.
You got it.
Say it like you did before.
I didn't get it at all.
Chie is amazing.
I didn't get it either.
I thought you were really bad.
As expected.
Gentle.
Didn't you get a gentle one?
Since he got a gentle one twice, Matsuno
is out.
The result is 12 points if he gets a
gentle one.
He is the first one.
What should we do?
The result of the Yamanote game is as
you can see.
The match is extended since the Yamanote
team, Kashiwagi Yasumoto and Matsuno
Hirota, are tied.
Since the number of times we said the
same, we will start the extension match.
Each of the representatives will come
out.
And they will praise each other and if
they don't come out, they will lose.
I see.
This is a new thing. Praising the other
person.
They will compete while praising.
It's a very interesting game.
I'm very nervous.
Everyone is nervous.
The losing team is SADON.
SADON vs. DEATH MATCH.
Ebitu Yamase Game, ready, start!
Cute eckmo.
Great personality.
Beautiful bangs.
I hate losing.
A big heart.
A sweet child.
A lovely smile.
A good singer.
A good dancer.
Strong.
The winner is the Kashiwagi team!
I see, you got told just before.
I wanted to see the next one.
I was wearing the same clothes as the
first one.
That's not good.
You were quiet just now.
When I saw the first one, I was like,
I'm wearing the same clothes as the
first one.
The last Kashiwagi punch was
in Hirota's eyes.
I saw Hirota's eyes.
I was like,
What was that?
That was a nice match.
Thank you.
It's a nice game.
No one gets hurt.
It's good.
This game is good.
And so, all the preliminary matches are
over.
As you can see, the scores so far are
the scores of the Yamanote match.
The final decision is finally decided.
I will announce the result.
First, 4th place, Hoshina Kobayashi
team, 90 points.
3rd place, Mayama Nakayama team, 95
points.
2nd place, Yatsumoto Kashiwagi team, 100
1st place, Hirota Matsuno team, 105
points.
Yasumoto Kashikagi team and Hirota
Matsuno team, congratulations on the
final round!
It's like an old lady's team.
It's good, it's good for the TV.
When I saw the ranking, I thought it was
good.
This program is good.
The finalists of the Ebitu Strongest Tag
Team Championship are Hirota and
Matsuno, and Yasumoto and Kashiwagi.
Who will be the winner of the title of
the Strongest Tag Team?
The finalists of the Ebitu Strongest Tag
Team Championship are...
The winners are...
Wow!
It's cool!
Red corner!
Please!
Hirota-Matsuno tag!
Yashimotoashi vice Dinner by traffic
Buddy
Now, both teams, please give us your
enthusiasm.
First, the red corner, Hirota and
Matsuno's team.
We are always in the first place, so why
do we have to fight?
I see.
You are always in the first place.
That's right.
Why did we come out?
Thank you very much.
Please do it again!
The audience is happy too!
Now, we have a guest!
Yashimoto Kashiwagi's duck!
I'm sorry, but...
I'm the one who will be the first one.
I don't have the right to fight with
you.
I see. It was a bit hard to hear.
Anyway...
I'll fight with the teacher.
The interpreter is saying that.
That's right.
Thank you very much.
I'm looking forward to the final match!
Start!
After this, there will be a hot final
match!
But before that...
Don't miss it!
The game of Ebichu has finally been
completed!
And that is...
The first episode of the Ebichu Junior
High School Armed Forces Committee!
In addition to the last game we
introduced, there is another part in
this game.
Tonight, we will reveal that episode
part!
In the episode part, you will be talking
to the members of Ebichu one-on-one.
Choose the right conversation and aim to
clear it!
If you clear it, you can get various
useful items in the game!
Now, let's reveal one of the episodes of
Yasumoto!
It's like it's alive!
It's cute!
What?
You have to choose one of these.
Time is ticking.
You have to answer.
She laughed!
She's shy!
I'm shy too!
I don't want to see this face!
Are you nervous?
Please subscribe to this channel!
It's very well done!
You can get a present!
Yes, you can get a present if you clear
the stage.
I'm a little nervous.
I'm nervous!
In addition, a new function has been
added to this episode part.
You can change costumes.
Let's change costumes.
Cute!
It means that you can see the first time
you wear it on the virtual screen.
Yes!
I wonder if there is a new function.
Furthermore,
It's a real costume.
Are there more costumes?
Yes, there will be more.
I'm looking forward to it!
Will you be an anarchy one day?
Yes, I will be an anarchy one day.
Yes!
Great!
We will report the latest information.
Thank you for your cooperation.
After this, the final match of the
strongest tag team in Ebi-chuu will
begin.
Who will be the first champion?
Will it be the Dodo tag team?
The final match of the strongest tag
team in Ebi-chuu will begin.
It's the final match. It's cold.
I thought you would do the setting of
pro-wrestling and go outside.
Why?
It's so cold.
It's cold.
It's like a pasta place.
It's cold, so let's do it quickly.
The final match is the two-man tripod
marathon.
If you don't have the same breath, you
can't win.
We will decide the winner by the two-man
triangle.
The final is the two-man triangle
marathon.
The course is about 300 meters long
around the venue.
The two-man triangle will be a warning.
The team that scores the goal first will
get the best title.
Let's say a few words to each other.
Hirota and Matsuno's team.
I think we are a perfect match.
I see.
That's good.
You have already improved your match in
the battle.
That's right.
You have improved your match.
I see.
And Yasumoto and Gashagin's team.
I think I was able to catch up with
them.
What is that shaking?
I practiced to get the right rhythm.
All four of you synchronized.
You are in the center.
What kind of preparation exercise is
that?
Let's start.
Who will get the title of the strongest
team?
The two-man triangle marathon starts.
Ready, start.
Go for it.
You will lose if you start.
You can do it.
Go for it.
You are in the center.
The first pair is a little advantageous.
But they are catching up.
Gashagin is catching up with Yasumoto.
Go for it.
You can do it.
You are a little behind.
You are behind.
Gashagin is behind.
The tag is burnt.
Meanwhile, the Matsu-no-Hiroto team is
slowly heading to the goal.
What will happen?
Goal.
Matsu-no-Hiroto team wins.
Yasumoto-Kashiwagi team also aims for
the goal with their strength.
Go for it.
There was a girl like this in school.
The last one.
Don't give up.
Go for it.
It's no good.
What is this final teamwork?
Go for it.
The last one.
It took a long time.
We were stuck in the middle.
At the last corner.
What happened at the end?
We crossed and got stuck.
Crossed and got stuck.
It took a long time from there.
We laughed and got stuck.
It was fun.
You got stuck in a strange switch.
I was out of breath.
It's a little out of breath, but it's
not good.
This is not good.
The winner of the final round is...
Hirota Matsunotade.
The first team to be the strongest in
the first episode was Matsuno and
Hirota.
And as a proof of the champion, here is
the champion belt.
The champion belt should be there.
There is a person over there.
That's the name of the person.
It's interesting.
I said something.
It's Maiba, right?
Slowly.
Slowly?
Are you hurting your leg?
Where did you get injured?
Did you fight?
Congratulations.
Thank you.
You give it to her as much as you eat.
What is that movement?
Something is coming out of here.
From here.
Step on it.
And then?
Wipe your foot.
How was it?
We played various games today.
Did you get better at the game?
Yes.
It was fun.
Nakayama played the game with a smile.
It was really fun.
That's good.
That's really good.
Let's end with TENGYU.
It's a professional wrestling.
How was it?
It was delicious.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
Everyone worked hard.
Everyone is getting better.
Let's work hard together next week.
See you.
Bye bye.
Breaking news! The game called Ebichu is
about to be released!
Currently, it is being pre-registered
for general users!
The number of items you can get depends
on the number of pre-registered users!
For more information, search for it on
the Stardust channel!
Next time...
Are you happy?
Thank you for watching!
Thank you!
The members of EriChu are challenging
the broadcast reporters!
Are you curious? This is the first
episode!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Furthermore...
Who is the surprise guest in the middle
of the report?
This program was provided by the sponsor
you are watching.
I like the one with the cage.