What are you mostly afraid of?
Fear of top (*ing him on
I have always really liked them.
I went to the live concert of the band.
I was wondering if I could get a ticket,
and I happened to be at the front.
I was so close to the front, and it was
really cool.
And the band's live is completely
different from the idol's live.
I enjoyed the band's live while thinking
that it was so hot and fun.
Both.
But I don't know much about Western
music or K-pop.
I'm not good at languages.
So I always look up the lyrics.
I listen to all the songs I listen to.
I look at all the lyrics of the songs I
like.
I always listen to them thinking, what
kind of lyrics are these?
I think that's the reason why I like
Western music.
I take pictures of the sky.
So, I often go to Nami-e-machi with the
Namiye girls' shirt group.
The sky in Nami-e-machi is really
beautiful.
The sky is also beautiful.
I took a lot of pictures of the sky when
the orange and pink colors were mixed in
the evening.
I don't know when the sky is.
I am...
I don't really take selfies.
If I wasn't told, I would probably be
doing Instagram, blogging, and Twitter.
If I wasn't doing those, I wouldn't be
taking selfies at all.
But I take them.
I don't think I'm very good at it, but I
do post them sometimes.
I was born...
I was able to return to the closest
state when I was born.
I think that immediately after being
born,
there is no tiredness, worries, or
mental illness.
I think there is nothing.
I was just born.
And the moment I get the closest to
that,
I feel that my body is light and my mind
is empty.
Thank you for watching!
I want to ask Ayano-chan why she is so
tall.
Every time I meet her, I hear from the
staff and fans that I have grown taller.
I've been told that I've grown taller
every now and then, but I've never been
told that many times in the past two or
three years.
I'm most curious about it, but it's a
little embarrassing to ask directly.
I'll ask her here.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
Ebichu was on the show the other day.
I was impressed by idols who like
saunas.
I'm embarrassed to go to the sauna with
Ebichu, so I want to talk to her.
Hello
This summer, I set the theme of my goal
as a footwork.
Footwork? What is that?
It's like a light footwork.
I see.
So I went out a lot.
But if you look at my Instagram,
I'm like an out-of-the-world person.
I think a lot of people feel that way.
I don't wear light on my days off.
That's for work, right?
What?
For 25 years.
I don't wear sunlight.
I'm going to keep my skin white.
But I hate wearing sunscreen.
I'm sure you hate it.
What?
Really?
Makeup artists cry.
I don't want to wear it as much as
possible.
I'm sorry.
最近おすすめのサウナとか 最近おすすめのサウナとか?
ココよかったよとかあるんですか? 私がでもこの前、ちょっと前に
色んな特定される情報になっちゃったもんやん?
あ、じゃあ大きなくくりでお願いします。 静岡のサウナに行っても 大きな!
全然特定されてないから大丈夫だよ。 静岡に良いサウナある?
何がいいってお水が福寺さんの天然水に
すごい冷たくて、そこのサウナが。 あと、私が一番感動したポイントは
お水、飲む方のお水も美味しかったんですよ。
あー!
そこは私、すごい飲むお水がぬるいのが嫌で、飲むのも冷たいお水がいいんですよ。
そこはもともと飲める、その紙コップにザーって飲むやつが冷たくて、しかも福寺さんの
お水が美味しくて、それがすごく感動しました。
Do you also throw away red bull?
I don't throw it away.
Oh really?
I just drank red bull for the first
time.
Please subscribe to my channel.
After the first experience of Red Bull,
did you drink?
Yes, I did.
How was it?
I couldn't sleep.
I was drunk.
After the 3rd anniversary live, I was on
the radio.
I drank for the first time.
The next day, at 5 pm, I was on the
radio.
From Chii-chan.
Is it your first time to drink Red Bull?
Yes, it is.
I got a message about 5 o'clock.
Oh, really?
Well, I'm sure there's a caffeine and
something like that.
Oh, I see.
I guess you couldn't sleep.
I'm excited.
It might be a good stage for you to
drink before the stage.
Thank you for watching.
I sometimes feel a generation gap.
Even if the members above are excited,
I sometimes feel like,
What is this?