Ebichu's videos, etc.
Please subscribe to my channel!
I don't steal fruits
I'm not lying
I'm not really good at eating fruits
so I don't steal them
I do get them at the school cafeteria
but I don't eat them that much
I only eat pineapple and apple
I don't steal fruits
I'm not lying, I don't lie
even if I do, it's a small lie
like the April Fool's joke
I fought with my friends
I broke something
even if it's a small lie
like a lie to surprise a friend
I tell them that I'm with someone
I'm not lying, I'm not lying
my friend was surprised
and he surprised me
but it wasn't a person
it was a sign
that you see in the streets
like this
a sign for a boy who's about to jump out
of a car
that's what it was
I can only lie about that
I can't lie about
not stealing
I can't lie about that
I know who's the one who's about to eat
it
but
It's not me
I want you to believe me, please
First of all, the fruits that were
stolen
I don't know where they were stored
I'm not good at fruits
The last person who left the store?
Who is it?
It wasn't me who left last
When I left, there was a girl who said
bye bye
I'm still suspicious
Is it a lie? I'm not lying
I've been lying so far
When I was in elementary school, I told
a girl that the right angle is a two-
sided triangle
I'm still suspicious
I was going to tease her, but I really
believed it, and I was scolded by the
teacher.
I'm apologizing for that.
I've been told a lot of lies, but I
don't lie that often at this age.
I'm sorry.
I like fruits, but I don't think I'll
steal it because I'll probably eat it.
Isn't that the chief manager's
principal?
I don't think so.
No, I'm not.
I didn't steal it.
Is this a high-priced fruit?
I don't steal. Is there anyone who
steals such fruit?
I was watching it because I thought it
was kept carefully, but at that time I
was so hungry that I went out of the
dressing room to get some food.
I don't know if anyone was in the
dressing room during that time, but when
I came back, I wonder if there was.
I haven't seen it since then. I've been
in the dressing room since then. I was
looking at the origami.
I've been doing shuriken lately.
I've been into origami for a long time.
I eat fruits when I'm in the dressing
room, but I don't touch them at first.
I eat them when I think everyone is
starting to eat.
I eat them when I have my favorite.
Can I go home now?
I'm waiting for someone outside.
I'm waiting for Tokugawa Iyasu.
I'm afraid I'll be scolded if I keep
waiting for him.
Anyway, I'm not stealing anything.
Never.
To be continued.
I've heard rumors, but it's not me.
No, it's not me.
Really.
I don't lie much.
For example, if I ate Fujii's cooking,
I'd better show this to Fujii.
Well, yesterday I was eating Fujii's
cuisine...
I'm the type who can't lie.
I'm not kidding.
I don't lie that much.
Is it a suspicious person?
I was talking about this incident with
the members the other day.
Miria just avoids the story of it.
I'm not sure about the law of Fleming or
the law of Le Chatelier's parallel
movement.
That's about it.
I'm sorry. I don't have much information
that can help.
Thank you very much.
What? In the dressing room?
Are you a thief?
Hey, say no, monster! Your immortal is
important!
I'll tell you more and more, the crime
of teaching!
I don't know what kind of person you
are!
I'm not a mountain!
Do you know what song I was singing?
I was singing a song at the rent of
Ebichu's love.
I've been singing and talking about it
lately.
I'm addicted.
Don't be kidding me, talk to me!
Horiamen
That's what it is.
I'll talk to you.
Well, Mayama is...
I think I was eating at a catering.
Yeah, it's pretty late to eat, so I went
to a catering with everyone as usual,
but I ate and ate, and before I knew it,
everyone had gone home first, so I
didn't go into the dressing room in the
first place.
So I don't think it's me.
And after eating, I did half-naked
jumping and training, so I think it's
different. Can you guess the other one?
I really wanted to eat that.
And that's really expensive.
Right?
It's hard to say, but I ate too much in
the morning.
I'm really frustrated that I'm calling
myself a fruit monster.
I made a mistake in the morning when I
was in front of the fruit.
I'm sorry for my own fault.
I'm going to sing this frustration.
Can you listen to it?
I'm sorry.
If you listen to this song, you'll be
able to be sure that I'm not the
culprit.
I'm going to sing.
I'm sorry I couldn't eat the fruit.
I thought that the first line of the
national road that continues forever was
a dark dead end.
Curry and ramen gyudon from the morning.
I ate too much fruit monster.
It's like this, but I hope you'll
believe me.
I'm going to do my best.
My stay word was Tobidashi Boya.
My designated word was the right angle
two-sided triangle.
My designated word was Tokugawa Ieyasu.
Did you get it?
My designated word was Fujii's homemade
food.
Fujii's fried chicken is delicious.
My designated word was Heisei's monster.
Did you get it?
My designated word was the national road
1 line. Did you get it?
You put it on while walking A, B, C, D.
Open your mouth big!
Yes.
It's me.
Was my acting suspicious?
I don't think I would say the rule of
the parallel movement of Le Chatelier.
I don't think I would say it in my usual
way, and I didn't know this word.
But thanks to that, the probability of
correct answer of Yasumoto's designated
word was low.
This is my victory.
Thank you for watching.
Oh, my.
I'm sorry.
Did I do too much?
So, I'd like to apologize.
I'm thinking about what I can do for the
next project.