I cried for the first time at the
airport where I went to the training
camp
The two new members of Ebichu, Sakurai
Emma and Nakamura Yuna
will share their memories of the
training camp
with the unreleased video
The bond with the members they met at
the training camp
I was so happy to receive the message of
celebration at Chobun
The bond with the members they met at
the training camp
What kind of training camp was it for
you two?
The two who became new members during
their debut
have looked back on their memories of
the training camp
First, about the first day of training
camp
Good morning
In the interview right after arriving,
Yunao said
I was nervous yesterday, I slept and
woke up.
So I could only sleep for about 3 hours.
It's my first time staying at a training
camp for this long, so I'm nervous.
ーWhat does she think about this
situation?ー
I was really nervous before I joined the
camp, and I cried for the first time at
the airport.
I was so nervous, but I'm glad I could
overcome it.
Emma is right after arriving at the
camp.
Everyone is so cute, and I'm like, ーWhat
should I do?ー
I've come this far, so I hope I can do
my best to show my best.
ーHow did you feel about the event?ー
I've been to a school club once, and I
went to a camp.
I was singing Ebichu's song, 《Hand in
Hand》.
I didn't know that song at the time.
I knew Ebichu, and I heard the song, and
I thought, 《Hand in Hand》.
I thought, 《Hand in Hand》! I knew him
before.
I really wanted to be in the camp.
I was watching the camp last year, and I
thought, 《Hand in Hand》.
I thought it would be fun.
I've been wanting to be in the camp
since last year.
Really?
She was able to participate in the
audition she had been longing for.
She was very excited from the first day.
Good morning.
When she actually met the members at the
camp...
She was so thin and cute.
At first, she was thin.
I thought, there is a thin girl like
her.
I was strongly motivated to be like her.
I thought, the people who were in the
training camp a year ago would change so
much.
I decided to do my best.
Yuna was nervous and worked hard. She
finished her training.
Thank you for your hard work.
How was it?
I was very nervous until I got there.
But when I got there, everyone was kind.
The training was fun.
I'm more motivated to work hard than to
be nervous.
I want to work hard with everyone and
appeal myself.
Finally, she smiles.
When they hear that it was the most
difficult training camp, they both
answer the same.
Once again, the camp was the most...
What was the most difficult?
The camp was the most difficult.
It was the hardest to remember the
moves.
The third day was the most difficult.
Everyone was in a state of panic.
The atmosphere was different from the
first day.
We were so anxious that we couldn't
remember the moves.
It was really hard.
Thank you for watching.
Genero Ä McDonalds
The blue dress is too much for me
I want to be more and more happy in
front of you
I'm so happy
Ta ta ta ta ta ta ta ta
Can you see me?
Actually, they are quite pushed into the
song
I don't know why
I don't remember the choreography
I was thinking if I could sing more if I
put in more words
At that time, I was quite cornered
I was so frustrated that I couldn't do
it
I was crying all the time
I was glad I did my best
How was the final performance?
I want to praise myself for being calm
and dancing proudly.
Let's go!
Shall we dance?
The first performance of the second day
of the training camp
The heart beat of the girl who just
signed the contract
I can feel it from the hand that I held
I can't hide my feelings for you anymore
It's hard! We're running out of time!
We have to go back to the normal girl!
Please!
Please give me a smile!
Give me a smile!
The first day of the training camp
I made some mistakes
But I didn't feel like I was wrong
I'm glad I was able to dance proudly
Ah, God, please forgive me
Because I'm forgiven
Thank you very much
After overcoming the training camp, they
had a great time
Thank you for your hard work during the
training camp
Cheers!
Thank you.
I'll eat it.
I want you to eat it.
It's really delicious.
I can speak.
It's very delicious
Cute
Very delicious
Thank you for the meal
I recently got a 10th grade
Oh, no
High school entrance exam
After the training camp, the last thing
they talked about was
The last thing they talked about was
You did a great job for 4 days.
Thank you.
You finished everything.
Yes, I was a bit lonely.
I want to start over from the beginning.
You want to start over?
I feel like I'm done.
I was left with the final candidate for
the new member audition.
I had a chance to be a new member.
I don't want to go back to reality.
I don't want to go back to school after
summer vacation.
I'll do what I can do until the end
without running away.
That's what I want to learn.
If something bad happens, I'll quit.
Thank you.
I had to work hard to get to the top.
But I think that's the biggest thing I
gained from training.
If I could be like AB-TU, I'd like to
smile like the other members.
I want to smile like AB-TU and deliver
my smile to many people.
I think I did my best.
Thank you for your hard work.
How was your 4 days?
I think my 4 days were really short.
I think I woke up yesterday.
It was a really tough day.
I think it was such a day.
I think I worked hard until I was
satisfied.
I think I did my best for 4 days.
I think I grew up.
I didn't have to do anything more.
I made a lot of effort.
I want my parents to praise me when I go
home.
I met the members of L-CHU.
I announced it in front of the members
and the staff.
I'm having so much fun making my partner
happy.
I'm happy about it, too.
I want to be like Eriku and show my
personality.
I want to make everyone happy.
They all helped in creating this...
I think it was a great 4 days that
changed my life
I got to know more people and it changed
me
4 days that changed her life
And many more unforgettable encounters
And they became new members of the
private Ebisu Junior High School
After the live broadcast, Yuna had this
incident
Good job
Karen-chan sent me a congratulatory
message right after the live broadcast
Karen contacted Yuna who was in the same
unit as Yuna at the training camp
I was happy to work with the same team
for 4 days
I think Karen will be active in other
places
I want to support her
I didn't come here alone for the group
test
I want to do my best for the other 8
members
I want to be a person who can make the
other 8 members accept me
A new Xuc coloring starts to move
The two new members are close to their
first gravure photo