Please come in.
Thank you.
What do you think?
Yes, that's good.
I think it's a bag.
Please pose.
Thank you.
Hello everyone, I'm Sato Sakura, the
president of the Kyushu Cultural
Heritage Association of the Batten Book
Festival.
I was a little nervous because it was my
first time talking to a nightclub.
But I was able to talk about various
things.
I was able to talk about my three major
elements, so it was a lot of fun.
If you watch this, you will be able to
know more about yourself.
Good morning.
Are you sleepy?
I'm a little tired.
It's the best.
I'm tired.
I've loved Precure since I was a kid.
Precure is really cool, isn't it?
Usually, it's a little clumsy,
or it's a Precure that I usually spend
as a junior high school student or high
school student.
When I fight, I think that the
appearance of being very cool is also
inherent in idols.
My favorite character is Smile Precure's
Cure Peace.
I really like her.
At the end of the program, there was a
rock-paper-scissors corner called Pika
Pika Pika Rin Rock-paper-scissors.
I really liked that.
Thank you for watching.
I think it would be interesting to have
an interview with new members who know
more about Rirua and Miu.
I want to ask them what they like and
what they like. I think it's okay to ask
them anything.
I think there are people who don't know
much about the past and are interested
in it, so I would like to hear stories
from my childhood.
I can see the other side of this GoPro.
Amazing!
I'm shooting in Tokyo this time.
I only brought one T-shirt and one
T-shirt.
I'm glad I brought it.
I'm wearing a uniform.
I borrowed your shoes.
I thought it was a shooting with five
staff members.
There were so many staff members.
I didn't expect to be surrounded by so
many staff members.
I was nervous.
And there were many cute girls in the
other staff members.
Thank you for your cooperation.
I think Fukuoka is more sparkling than
Fukuoka.
Fukuoka is full of nature and I like the
feeling of the countryside.
It's a city, but compared to Tokyo,
Tokyo is more sparkling.
There are many people I want to talk to.
Mayama from Chiri Chibisu Junior High
School,
Sudaki from Chotto Kimeki, Date Kaya
from Iinari Talk, Tanaka from Kurako,
and many game lovers. I haven't talked
to them much, so I'm very happy if I
have a chance to talk about games and
anime together.
I used to make sweets on Valentine's
Day, but I don't make them often now.
I like meat, rice, and garlic more than
sweets.
I only make a lot of rice.
I don't make sweets very often.
Do you usually make rice?
I make rice when I'm not busy with work.
What are you good at?
I'm good at gratin.
My mother's recipe is very delicious.
I enjoy making it.
Did your mother teach you?
I make it at home and eat it.
What's in it?
Macaroni, scissors, and...
What should I say?
It's really simple.
There's not much in it.
It's a simple gratin.
What do you think about the president's
work?
I haven't introduced it yet.
But I think I'm eating a lot.
What is the most recent food culture in
Kyushu?
I introduced ramen the other day.
I have a lot of image of Fukuoka and
Hakata.
I introduced my favorite restaurant.
Do you do it on your own?
I do it on the stream and at the special
event.
Do you ask at the special event?
I ask the fans.
Do you have any food recommendations in
Kyushu?
I have a concert in Fukuoka.
I want to eat it.
What kind of food do you recommend?
I introduced ramen restaurants.
I introduced my favorite restaurant.
You don't have to explain one thing.
You want to explain it to me.
I want to eat a lot.
This is still the opening.
What is the best food in Kyushu?
When is this broadcast?
October?
What is the best food in Kyushu?
I think there is a good food in every
season.
I'm getting cold.
I think hot pot is good.
Motsunabe and Mizutaki are famous in
Fukuoka.
If you eat this, you will enjoy Hakata.
I want you to eat it.
There is no mistake in any restaurant.
I'm getting cold.
I like it.
Do you want to eat Mizutaki?
Yes.
Thank you for your viewing.
If you eat it, you can eat Hakata.
Thank you for watching.
I like strong flavors.
Strong flavors?
A little bit strong and sweet.
You're very friendly.
Really?
I made lunch boxes for my friends when I
was in high school.
You made lunch boxes yourself?
Yes, my mom made lunch boxes for me, but
I also made lunch boxes for myself.
Can you tell me what's inside?
It's fried eggs, and it's grilled with
pepper and bonito flakes soy sauce.
Grilled with pepper and bonito flakes
soy sauce?
That sounds good.
It's good. It goes well with rice.
I always add meat.
You always add meat?
Yes, I like pork, so I add ginger, and
mix it with sweet and spicy sauce.
I fry it and boil it, and I put it on
rice.
You made lunch boxes yourself?
You introduced lunch boxes like this?
You opened it yourself?
I'm sorry, but I have a twisted fan's
point of view.
It's a little twisted.
I'm sorry.
When I was in high school, Kyushu had a
zero hour class.
It's called Asakagai.
Zero hour?
Yes, class starts at one o'clock.
It's called Asakagai, which is in front
of Asano-kai.
Do you study?
Yes, I study.
How long does it take?
When I was in high school, it was from
seven o'clock.
From seven o'clock?
Yes, class starts at seven o'clock.
That's the zero hour class?
Yes, that's the zero hour class.
I don't want to be fooled.
Is that normal?
Yes, it's normal in Kyushu, especially
in Fukuoka.
Really?
If you look at Kyushu as a whole, is it
high-education?
No, it's not that.
It's not that?
But I want to do my best.
I see.
If you make a lunch box in the morning,
I'll give you my favorite food.
I see.
I'll open the lunch box before Asakagai
starts.
Before Asano-kai?
Yes.
The zero hour class is over.
Yes, the zero hour class is over.
That's it.
What are you eating?
Oh, it's a bento.
A bento?
A bento and onigiri.
Onigiri?
Yes.
I was like this when I was in high
school.
But it's good. I can tell by your
expression.
I usually ate rice. I brought rice balls
separately and soup.
I was sent a video of Sakura eating
rice.
I was impressed by NANO's ability to
move her body.
I'm a junior high school student, but I
was impressed by her ability.
I want to know more about her.
I was impressed by her catchphrase.
I can't lose to her.
I was impressed by her flexibility.
Is that okay?
I don't know if it's because of her
artistic feelings.