Me and Kannai Devil
Come on, Mayama!
Hey, Mayamaama, what's your favorite tower?
Of course it's the Tokyo Tower
What's your favorite tree? Master
Sky Tree.
What's your favorite banana? Mariko
Tokyo Banana
I was allowed to participate.
The principal said we were on the same wavelength.
The master and Ms. Kamunei
I was told that we are on the same wavelength.
I'm quite nervous.
I'm nervous.
Kannai Devil is the only one
Kannai Devil is the only show on TV where I don't get nervous
I can take on a challenge without being nervous.
I think it's a show where I can take on challenges.
I really think
I look forward to every episode of Kannai Devil
I look forward to it every time.
That's why it's a place I look forward to.
The master
"Hey, Mayamaama, why don't you sing with us?
He asked me to sing a song with him.
When the master sings...
I joined in a little bit as a chorus
I was able to join in as a chorus member.
That left a very strong impression on me.
That's when BFF started.
I've had the chance to cover songs...
When you are active in Ebichu
It's not so easy to get a chance to cover a song.
I'm very happy to be able to sing on the show
I'm very happy!
Kanagawa Prefecture
Kanagawa Prefecture?
It's like I'm really back in my hometown.
It's so warm.
The warmth of Kannai Deville
Every time I go there
I get a little nervous.
But when I actually enter the place
It's so warm
I feel at ease.
I enjoy the whole day of shooting.
I wrote a song about Kannai Devil
I was asked to write a song for a corner of the show.
I was able to show what I enjoy as a hobby
I was also very happy to be given a place to show what I enjoy as a hobby
I was very happy to have a place to show what I enjoy as a hobby.
I was also very happy to be given a chance to show what I enjoy as a hobby.
I think I like both of you a lot, and
I hope we can do more and more things in Kannai Devil
I hope we can do many more things in Kannai Devil
I hope we can do many more things in the future.
I would like to challenge myself in the future
I would like to challenge myself in the future.
I think!
Thank you very much.
You know what I think?
I think we have a similar style.
Hosina is the original gal.
Hanamichi is like a new type.
Heisei gal and 2025 gal?
My
Like my second
Like my second home
And
No matter how much freedom I have
They forgive me
It's like a big open field
Like a field.
That's the image I have.
DISH///'s
I was working as a stand-in for DISH//.
I was...
It was my first time to work at Kannai DeVille.
I was allowed to work for Kannai Devil.
I really didn't know what to expect at that time.
I really didn't know what I was doing.
But
what I wanted to do, what I wanted to try
I wanted to challenge myself
That kind of thing.
That's what I was trying to do.
And he accepted all of them.
That's what really impressed me the most.
But, I don't know...
The part-time job I did as a substitute
It was a part-time job that I did as a stand-in.
In this way, as a member of Ebichu
I was able to work as a part-timer with everyone.
I was able to do the part-time job with everyone.
I'm really glad that I was able to do this once.
I'm really glad that I was allowed to do it.
I'm really glad I got to do it.
It feels so good!
It's amazing!
Oh, man...
It's great...
I'll work a little harder for the show.
This is HINASIA
Yes... Thank you very much.
I really felt at home in this place.
I really felt that it is a homey place.
There is a lot of laughter when I go there.
and there is a lot of laughter.
Every time I go there
After every recording
I go home with the feeling that everything was fun.
I can go home with the feeling that everything was fun.
There was a jigsaw puzzle of the Kannai Devil
It's like a time attack puzzle.
I had to do a jigsaw puzzle
Kamunei was going to be the first place.
I had a plan.
But really...
I'm the one who can't read the atmosphere.
Kamune's record was surpassed.
But there was an incident...
I'll take care of it.
I got a Dyson hair dryer...
There was an incident...
I'm so sorry for being a savior at that time.
I'm sorry about that.
But I'm very grateful for it.
Yay.
Gal.
Gal
No gal
Like a coffee shop
A place like a coffee shop, or rather...
I mean, you know...
Because... really...
Various people come as guests
and you can hear their stories
I can listen to their stories in a fresh way every time.
I think everyone is saying this, but
It's a warm space.
The master, Kamune and all the staff
and all the staff
It's a really warm place
Because it's comfortable
Because it's comfortable, I feel at ease.
I enjoy recording here.
At the beginning.
With the Master
When I met the master for the first time
I wondered if he was...
I thought he was a difficult man.
I thought he was a bit of a difficult man.
He's extremely friendly and
He's funny.
He's a funny guy.
I felt like I got along with him right away.
Master, we talked about many things.
He knows so much!
I look forward to hearing his stories every time.
I'm not nervous or anything.
I'm free to be myself.
I can be myself.
It's a wonderful place!
I'm also going to do a corner called "Biocreation (Imagination) Corner".
I'm going to do it.
You hear the name of the creature and imagine it yourself
and draw an illustration.
I don't know.
I thought it wouldn't be right.
I thought it would be different, so I submitted it.
I thought it would be different, so I put it up on ....
I'm always so happy when people laugh at my work.
I'm always so happy.
If it was a variety show...
If it were a variety show, I wouldn't be able to say this because it wouldn't be funny.
I can't say it because it's not funny.
But with Kannai Devil, it's like...
If you say it, it's like...
They make everything interesting.
I'm so happy that they accept everything
I'm very happy.
Thank you very much.
Master Neh.
I think this is the first job of my life.
When I started high school.
I joined Ebichu when I was in high school.
I got a really big job called Kannai Devil.
I was given a very big part-time job called Kannai Devil.
It was very precious.
Precious... I don't know how to say it.
It's like...
I think it's a very valuable job.
The first time I worked at Kannai DeVille
When I got my first part-time job...
The sound...
Sound alone is...
I could hear it.
There's a game where you listen to what they're doing.
There's a game...
But it's not sound.
But there's an image on the screen.
And then...
What's that? I'm looking at the image, and I'm wondering if it's okay.
It's the first time I thought...
I think I made a mistake.
That's what I remember most.
It was very interesting.
Kannai DeVille is a place for me
Kannai DeVille is a place for me to learn how to speak.
I'm not good at talking to people
I'm learning how to speak with people.
I am now able to speak "properly".
The first time I went out by myself
during the recording of Kannai Devil.
You know...
I was asked a quiz...
During the quiz
last week's episode guessed it for me.
That there was chocolate under the montplant
That there were chocolates under the montplant.
I was so happy.
I thought it was a place where I could grow
I thought it was a place where I could grow.
The masters and the camneres...
They would ask me to do all kinds of things.
and I would respond to them
And as I tried to respond to them
I've never been good at variety.
I wasn't very good at it.
I was anxious about it.
But as I was doing that at Kannai Devil
I'm not afraid of variety.
I lost my resistance to it.
I'm still not good at it, but...
There are still things I can't do
I think it's a place where I can grow
I think it's a place where I can grow in variety.
The master told me at the previous Kannai Devil's
Master told me I was funny.
I was...
I've never been told I'm funny.
I hadn't heard that very often.
So I was like...
"I'm funny!" I'm really funny.
I was really
I was really worried.
I was a little relieved to see that I was doing it right.
I'm a little bit relieved.
From now on
I'm going to do my best to respond
I thought I would do my best.
After the show
Well, I was
I was so busy with various things.
But you're still the best!
I dare to be scared...
I'm afraid to go down the flower aisle...
Yes...
Say something funny.
Wow! Scary! Say something funny?
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
But I...
But I'm glad I got my first part-time job at Kannai DeVille.
I'm glad I got my first job at Kannai Devil.
Oh~!
PUTUTUT so cute~!
Yay~!
Yessssss!
Even I, with my BFF
I didn't think I'd be laughing at Cocoon.
That was awesome!
Because you were the only one who came out of the backstage...
Because she was the only one who came out of the dressing room.
That's right.
So, everyone!
Please continue to support Kannai Devil!
Thank you very much for today!
Well then...
Hoshina, tighten up again.
And now, let's go!
To all of you in front of the video!
And everyone here!
Let's have a hand!
How many patterns? One?
Ipponjime!
Yo~!
Thank you very much!