Ebichu's video!
What is your favorite tower?
Of course, it's Tokyo Tower.
Yeah!
What is your favorite tree?
Sky tree.
Yeah!
What is your favorite banana?
Tokyo Cutlet!
I've been told that the director and the
thumbnail are in sync since the first
recording I took.
I'm really nervous, but I think KANNAI
DEVIL is the only TV show that can
challenge me without being nervous.
I'm really looking forward to the KANNAI
DEVIL's role every time.
So it's a fun place.
The director said, why don't we sing
together?
I was very impressed that the director
asked me to sing as a love song.
That's where the BFF started.
I'm very happy to be able to sing on TV
because I rarely have the opportunity to
cover the song.
Please sing Yasumoto Maiko.
The flowers of light that bloom
The blood flowing in this body
The blood is running down my shoulders
I'm from Kanagawa prefecture.
I feel like I'm back in my hometown.
I'm a little nervous every time I go to
the set.
But it's really warm when I go to the
set.
I'm relieved and have a good time
shooting every day.
I was very happy to be able to sing
KANNAI DEVIL's song in the corner.
I was very happy to be able to show what
I enjoy as a hobby.
I hope I can do various things at the
KANNAI DEVIL level.
I want to continue to challenge myself.
Thank you.
I think I'm going to be a little more
like a comedian.
Hoshida was an original Yanyan, so she's
like a new title.
I'm a comedian.
That's right.
I'm like a second home to me, and I'm
willing to do whatever I want.
I got a part-time job at Dider for the
first time at the Kannai level.
I didn't know anything at the time, but
I wanted to try something.
I'm impressed that you're accepting all
of that.
I'm glad I got a part-time job at Dider
because of that.
Wow!
It feels good!
It's amazing!
It's good.
It's a good feeling.
That's it for the video.
Thank you.
The two of you will be left here, and
the dojo will come down.
I feel like it's an at-home place.
It's a place where laughter is really
important.
I can go home with the feeling that
everything was fun after the shoot.
I had a time attack at the Kannai level,
so I had a plan to be the first place.
I can't read the air, but I'm going to
break the record.
I was really sorry that I was the first
place.
I'm grateful for that.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Oh, I got it.
Meow!
Gyaru!
Gyaru?
No, Gyaru!
It's like a live performance.
There are many people who come to the
concert.
I think everyone says that I can listen
to their stories every time.
I feel comfortable in a warm place with
the staff and the master.
When I first met the master, I thought
he was a difficult man.
He was a friendly and funny man.
I enjoy listening to the master's
stories.
Please.
Huh?
Did you get it?
No.
Yes.
I'll do it again.
I can't do it normally.
Please do it normally.
Last.
Please do it in a cute way.
I'm fine.
I can do it freely without any tension.
I do a corner called the imagination of
living things.
I imagine myself by listening to the
name and draw an illustration.
I'm happy that everyone laughs at me
when I draw something that I think is
different.
I'm happy that people in the variety
show say that it's not interesting.
I'm happy that people in the KANNAYE
DEVIL say that it's interesting.
Thank you, Master.
I'm glad that I drew it because I was
able to draw it recently.
I'm glad that I drew it recently.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Go ahead.
You always say that you should greet me
with energy, but you're the most
energetic.
Thank you.
I think it's the first time in my life.
When I entered high school, I was in the
beauty industry and I was in the KANNAYE
DEVIL.
I got a very big job and I thought it
was a very valuable job.
When I got a job at the Kanae level for
the first time,
I had to listen to what I was doing with
just the sound.
I was not only listening to the sound,
but also the video.
I was very impressed that I made a
mistake for the first time.
It was very interesting.
I was the most nervous at the live show
so far.
Why? I thought you were more nervous.
It was a complete throw.
It was like a free dance.
I thought it was a mistake.
It was a perfect move.
Kanae level is a place where I learn to
speak.
I'm not good at talking to people, so
I'm starting to speak a little bit.
When I was recording the first time I
went out alone,
I was happy to see the chocolate on the
Mont Blanc that the last week's person
gave me.
What's up!
White and Nightville!
We are EBiTU!
Let's go, EBiTU!
I'm the 13th member of EBiTU's Hesodashi
Mameiro.
I'm Sakurai Kokono, Sakurai Hamaemichi.
Thank you.
Next, Yuna.
I like My Pace.
I'm 14th member of EBiTU, Kokono.
I'm Kokun.
Thank you.
I want to be a white cloud blown by the
wind.
I'm 15th member of EBiTU, Subie and
Kazami Nanoka.
Thank you.
I want to grow up with variety.
I'm worried that Kamen Rider will do
various things and I will respond to
them.
I'm not good at variety.
I was worried.
I was not able to resist while I was
doing it at the level of the ship.
I can do it.
I think I can grow up with the help of
the members.
When I was doing my debut as a singer,
the master told me that I was funny.
I've never heard that I was funny.
I was worried that I was funny.
I was relieved that I was able to do it.
I will do my best to answer to the
questions.
Please enjoy the special live part until
the end.
I will do my best to answer to the
questions.
Thank you for watching.
I'm scared.
I'm glad I got my first job.
I think I'll win the national
championship in the EFF.
That was amazing.
You were the only one who came out of
the dressing room.
I'm scared.
I'm going to think about it from now on.
Thank you very much.
Close your eyes again.
Close your eyes.
Everyone in front of the video, please
give me a hand.
What kind of pattern do you want?
One or two.
Thank you very much.