Yakan and Idol
Please give us a title call
My three main elements
Amazing
It's like the three main nutrients
As expected
Let's hear it
Please tell us the three elements
The first is cheer dance
The second is bonjiri
And the third is moji
This is a good answer
The reason I got into Stardust
Was because I was learning cheer dance
From the 3rd grade to the 5th grade
I learned cheer dance from my local
school
I've always wanted to be an entertainer
But I don't get into auditions easily
So I got scouted and got an interview
And I learned cheer dance
If I hadn't done cheer dance, I wouldn't
be here today
I'm glad I got an interview after I got
the chance
If I hadn't done cheer dance, it would
have been difficult
I was told that
It's about the time when you were
popular
Yes, that's right
So I told the agency that I had a cheer
group
I'm an experienced cheer dancer
You're not a
That's right
At that time, the manager wanted to do
cheer dance
And he put a girl in the group
To dance cheer dance
If I hadn't done cheer dance, I wouldn't
have been here today
That's a bad way to say it
I thought so
The agency told me that
So I decided to do it
That's great
I didn't expect to do cheer dance
I did it
Can I do that?
I can do the Y-shaped balance
I can lift my legs
If you wear a cheer dress, you'll look
cool
I haven't worn a uniform for a long time
That's not true
I'm happy
Really?
I'll think about it
Cheer dance is your origin
That's right
I'm happy
I don't know if you took care of me, but
it's really delicious
Do you emphasize cheer dance earliest,
The gelen root of cheer dance