Thank you for watching.
I'm going to eat a sandwich.
This is a squintail.
I haven't had this for a long time.
I'm going to eat a sandwich.
Good morning!
It's inside.
It's Christmas Eve!
Satori is waiting for us.
I can see you.
That's why I'm hungry. It's already
noon.
We had breakfast.
I was hungry.
We're going to eat.
Today, we're going to eat chicken
nanban.
It looks delicious.
I'll do my best!
I warmed it up.
Merry Christmas, everyone.
I'm wearing this this time.
I got a Christmas candy from a makeup
artist.
Good morning!
We're going to the rehearsal.
We'll do our best.
We're going to do the Potato Cross.
Merry Merry Christmas!
Merry!
Ho Ho Ho!
Merry Merry Christmas!
It's cloudy.
Merry Christmas!
Ho Ho Ho!
Merry Merry Christmas!
It's sunny!
Thank you for coming today.
You are so cute.
Oh, you are so beautiful.
Thank you.
You are so cute.
Oh, my god. Everyone is applauding.
I'm so happy.
Let's do our best.
I'm here at the opening.
I'm sorry.
You are so beautiful.
You are so cute.
I can't see anything.
It's a little bit dark.
It's a little bit inside.
You are so cute.
Snow is melting.
There are some areas where it's white
Christmas.
I see.
You are so cute.
Snow.
I can see the whole of Bali from above.
There are many houses.
We have the same tool.
What?
We haven't taken a sample of the goods.
We have a lot of things to do.
Thank you.
The costumes are cute.
We always wear glitters on our eyes.
The glitters on my eyes are all over
here.
I don't have it today, but I always wear
glitters like this.
I have a forehead today.
I'm thinking about how to look cute.
I'm like this now.
How is it?
I'll do my best.
It seems that it wasn't here.
It's been a while since I've had a twin
tail.
How is it?
Yay!
Isn't it cute?
It's cute.
The notes are scattered.
I think there are only two people.
Lastailleurs
Did I do it?
It was fast
Fork is
cute
Really fast
Very quick
Quick change inst the good impression
Thank you for watching.
Cute Although he is cute
I can't see the video.
I'm sad.
It's the first snow.
The BGM is stopped.
It's edited.
It's great.
The BGM is stopped.
I'm going to put it in my mouth.
Is it heavy?
Yes, it is.
I'm going to sprinkle it.
The camera doesn't move at all during
the rehearsal.
It's always moving up and down.
I'm heavy.
You are heavy.
I'm going to fall down.
I'm holding you.
I don't want to.
It's muscle training.
Arm muscle training.
Muscle training.
Press it.
I'm going to take off my camera as soon
as I hold it.
I like you, but...
I'm so scared!
I can't do anything about it!
I'm embarrassed.
You are a clever girl.
Thank you for watching.
I remember the old days.
Like a magic school.
I remember the twin tail.
It's similar.
I had a twin tail.
Twin tail?
The first one.
When you cried at the end of your life.
I did it like this.
Hey!
It's getting full of bandages.
I see.
Kanami.
Julia.
Hitoka.
Haruka.
Aiki.
Hiyori.
Then, TOKIMEIKI-SENSEI, rock on!
I'll hit you when I'm not in full power.
Please subscribe to my channel.
It's a bit different.
In the opening video, Pabllin appears.
I always look forward to seeing what he
does.
This time, he is playing the role of
Shion.
What is he doing?
He is playing the guitar.
He is cute.
He is using the guitar.
I'm not sure if I can do this.
Thank you for the rehearsal.
Thank you for your cooperation.
I'm not a fan of you anymore.
I got a present from DOKI-SEN.
I'm so happy that I got a lot of
presents in the first day.
I got a lot of presents in the second
day.
I'm so happy.
I'll give presents to DOKI-SEN BAND.
You are wearing a school uniform.
You look so cool.
Excuse me.
Is it okay to come in?
Nice to meet you.
Thank you.
I'll do my best.
I'll give you a present.
Thank you.
Please enjoy it.
I can't wear school uniform anymore.
Thank you.
Let's have fun for two days.
Let's have fun. Thank you.
Thank you.
Let's do our best.
I'll give you a present.
What should I do?
I can't wear school uniform anymore.
I brought some snacks for staffs.
But, there were almost none.
Did you eat a lunch box?
I did.
It's not strange that you ate a lunch
box.
I brought some snacks.
Please take it.
I have some.
Thank you.
She is cute.
Yahoo!
Let's go to Asukani.
Thank you for watching.
I'm sure you'll be able to do it!
It's gonna be a star!
I don't know the scenery in front of me
But I'll go wherever it takes me
Goodbye, goodbye
Thank you for yesterday
The city after the rain is colored
On the canvas of my damaged heart
I'll draw the fragments of the future
And guide me
Now I can say
The reason for my tears
When I'm lost, I'll be right there
I remember
Even if it rains
So that I can laugh
Look, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye
Yesterday's me
The city after the rain
The waves are sparkling
My heart is like a sunny pattern
The rainbow plays the mario
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye, goodbye
Yesterday's me
The city after the rain
The waves are sparkling
My heart is like a sunny pattern
The tears are flowing
I wear a rainbow dress
Please subscribe to our channel!