Yakan and Idol
Can you give me a cute title call?
My three-year-old son
That's good
I think I got the cutest title call in a
while
Thank you
Thank you for watching
This is a corner where you introduce the
three elements that make up you.
Please announce the three elements.
The first is a smile.
The second is clothes.
The third is a friend.
I think that smile is very important to
you, right?
Yes, it is.
I think that smile is the most important
thing in makeup.
I got your order.
Thank you.
Wow!
I used to have a complex about people
who are far from me.
But I heard that people who are far from
me have a cute smile.
I think I am becoming a person who is
impolite.
I think I have laughed a lot.
I have been told that my smile is cute.
I started to think that it is my weapon.
I have been taking care of my smile.
Who is it?
Is it someone around you?
My mother.
I have been told that I don't want to be
far from you.
I can't be far from you.
I'm far from you.
My mother told me that my smile is cute.
That's true.
I have a smile.
I have a smile on my face.
I feel happy.
I think that's what my mother said.
My mother said that my smile is a
healing.
Did she really say that?
Did she say that my smile is a healing?
She said that my smile is a healing.
I think that it is good to talk to you.
I think that you are a person who heals.
You have a lot of models.
What is your specialty?
What else is your specialty?
You are a model.
What is my specialty other than my
smile?
You have a lot of features.
I have a lot of features.
I like it.
What does that mean?
Please tell me your specialty.
You're in trouble.
You're really in trouble.
This troubled eyebrow is amazing.
You don't use a model's makeup, do you?
No.
No?
But there are various things.
This is...
I'm going to be in trouble.
Can I turn to the camera again?
This is...
I'm in trouble.
This is for my mom or my seniors.
I use this when I buy something.
This is a trick.
I think you can use this.
This is good.
This is a good research.
Do you use this?
I use this a lot.
Does your mom use this?
Yes.
Please subscribe to our channel.
I'm the one who's the most likely to get
a heart attack.
No, I'm not.
That's amazing.
Really?
I can't study, but I think that's a
little bit of a difference.
This program was brought to you by
Tartar Chili Pepper, Shiotani, Yuya,
Ietenezo, and Mont.
Thank you for watching.