The day will start
Here comes the customer
What will be the work today?
Today, is
the day to take fan-makeup suffer photos
This time,
heigaерьm습니까 will make a video of fan-
makeup suffer
And?
I'm happy
I'm filled with happiness
That person has finally joined us
Thank you for watching!
Fabien remains silent for a month until
the end of the season
On this day, her official cam was taken
It's gone little by little
Normally I wear natural make up
This is dangerous
You look quite naughty
Do I lookaho?
Show me
What?
Until now, the new members who had
mostly natural makeup
were all in the picture with the fan-
flat.
I completed it because the long sleeves
were heavy.
Thank you.
She showed her idol-like image with the
costume.
And the completed one is...
Ta-da!
Cute!
The bangs are like this.
Thank you.
Cute
Like a girl in a tennis club who is
having a picnic
The shooting starts from the senior
members who are ready
Thank you
Cute
All of us are tired
Yes, we are
The new members who were watching
Hoshina's shooting
Cute
It's perfect
Each one of them has a strong expression
and pose
I'm going to study hard
And
Nice to meet you
It's the turn of the three members
I think the three of them are the best
among the new members
At first, Yuno was a little stiff
Cute cute
Cute
Very cute
Cute cute
It's like spinning
Each of their charms is pulled out by
the shooting staff
Thank you for watching!
Cute!
It's cute when it moves.
It's cute when the shirt moves.
Cute!
It's cute!
It's like a musical.
It's like watching a scene.
It was fun.
I had to buy a fan and make it fluffy.
I had to wear a pink girl's clothes.
I was excited.
It was fun.
It was cute.
While waiting for the shooting in the
waiting room...
Ta-da!
Hello!
Ayaka Yasumoto was on leave for about 8
months.
The members?
Yes, green and refreshing green.
I'm a bit nervous.
I feel the same as the new members
today.
On May 5, the day when the announcement
of the entry of the three new members
was made.
From today, Ebi-Chu will be a group of
nine with these three members.
Yasumoto was not on the stage, but...
But...
They were happy to start a new year with
new members
And...
They are starting to start their new
activities from this month
The beginning is...
So cute!
Thank you for watching!
Ayaka-chan!
Finally, all nine of them are here!
What?
I don't want to!
What's your favorite part?
Your voice is so loud.
I'm so old.
We're different.
Ayaka is a person who makes the place
bright.
She is a person who makes the place
I'm so happy to be shooting.
I'm so happy to be the 9th member.
Cute.
Thank you.
Come here.
This is the time everyone has been
waiting for.
Thank you for watching!
I'm so happy.
I've met Aya many times since we started
working together.
We also had lessons together.
We were able to shoot with nine people.
Everyone's expressions are soft.
Aya herself is very cheerful today.
I didn't feel like I was on a break for
a long time.
I was in contact with the staff, so I
was able to do it.
And Kashiwami is...
Thank you.
It's a pin.
I'm happy.
Today,
as a nine-member group,
I took a picture.
I was
impressed.
I don't know.
From here,
It's not like I'm starting a new life.
Finally,
as a nine-member group,
I was
at the starting point.
I was impressed.
I was very excited.
I took a picture.
I think
I can work
like this.
I think
I'm the most impressed.
I can feel
the aura of it.
I was very happy.
If Yasu was happy,
I would be happy, too.
I felt it again.
I'm sorry.
She's moving.
How do you feel about the staff?
Did you get along with them?
I think we got along pretty well.
Yuno and I have learned how to treat
each other.
During the lesson,
we used to say that we would untie our
shoelaces forever.
We used to tie our shoelaces forever.
But when we untied our shoelaces,
they would say,
I'm going to do this again.
We're getting old,
but we're still doing it.
We're getting along well.
What do you think about the staff?
They're cute.
It's fun to film.
It's fun.
I feel refreshed.
I feel like I'm a new person.
I feel like I've made a new start.
I've never been able to take a photo in
the kitchen.
I was lonely because I was watching from
a distance.
I'm glad I can take a photo with
everyone today.
I feel good.
How was it?
I've made a new start.
The new start has been made in the true
sense.
Shiritsu Ebisu Middle School
It's a little fun.
They keep running towards the end.
Thank you.