This week's Ebichu Tastas is a live
festival for the whole summer for 3
weeks in a row.
The first stage is the Haltua Final
stage, which is full of excitement.
And finally, the collaboration between
Ebichu and HIA is realized.
The whole venue is excited to see each
other.
The first tour final, start!
I'm so into you
What should I do with my heart?
Moratorium, moratorium, moratorium,
junior high school student
Add many things to your private Ebisu
junior high school
Ebichu Justice
This program is brought to you by these
sponsors.
The day after the phase 2 at the f nadie
They are about to escutche the ulитout
final this morning send
How is it going?
I think it's going well.
We're going to do our best because it's
the last week.
There are two Sakuraibis today.
I'm Sakuraibis.
I'm sorry.
I'm Hashiyagi.
I'm Sakuraibis.
The reason why Sakuraibis came here
today is...
We're going to do the song and the song
connection of the space station.
Sakuraibis will be on stage as a
surprise performance as a tour final.
And there's one more surprise for the
fans.
A spring tour that went around 15 places
from April to the whole country.
Among them, the most exciting song is...
Spring vacation, Volatoliev October.
Spring vacation, Volatoliev, a junior
high school student, also a theme song
of the program.
The song is written and composed by the
member of TAS TAS, Kaichi Ogata.
The song is about the feeling of love
for the shrimp.
This man wrote the song.
Good morning.
Thank you.
They came to the tour final stage to
collaborate with the debutant.
This is also a surprise project.
Without announcing to the fans, it has
been promoted in great secrecy.
Therefore, the rehearsal of Ebichu and
Hiyaato is only on the same day.
Members also check the movements of the
five members for the first time on this
day.
I can't do it. I'm so tired.
Almost the main performance.
Will it work?
I'll do my best.
I can do it!
The lesson ends with anxiety.
The rehearsal on the stage begins soon.
Good morning!
Let's do it!
I feel relieved.
Because we are friends.
It's been a while since they had a
reunion.
Tsukanova is back on stage in serious
mode.
The rehearsal has begun.
Then...
I'll sing for 5000 people.
Yes.
Thank you.
She'll sing for 5000 people.
And she's full of surprises.
She's different from usual.
I'm nervous.
I'm full of thoughts.
I'll do my best.
I'm scared.
I'm full of thoughts.
I'm wondering what's difficult.
I have to show my best.
I'm looking forward to it.
The members who have experienced various
stages so far are also anxious.
And finally
Thank you for your time.
Rehearsal with a band
This is the first time for H.E.R. to
perform on this stage.
To create the best moment, they
carefully make the sound.
And, they make the sound for the first
time with Ebichu.
Thank you very much.
If you have any questions, please ask.
Even though it's their first time,
they've been together for a long time.
Their smile is overflowing like a lie.
Thank you very much.
After the rehearsal, the members...
At first, it was different from usual.
I was worried.
But the last two songs were so fun.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to the audience's
reaction.
I'm looking forward to it.
I met Kaiki-san at this time.
I didn't think I would meet her.
I was a little embarrassed.
I was embarrassed.
What kind of surprise stage will the
audience expect?
Just before the show.
The audience is waiting for the show.
Let's go!
Where am I?
The audience is waiting for the show.
We are...
GAKU!
KAIRO!
Yahoo! Gokusai Forum!
The audience is waiting for the show.
Are you ready for the tour finale?
We are also anarchy
I'll be waiting for you
Thanks for watching!
Thank you for watching!
Ah, please, from now on
I'm going crazy, crazy, crazy
I want to fill up my vacation from here
And become rich
Try! Try! Try! Try! Try!
Chin chin, gui gui, boy boy
Creation power, boy boy boy
Let's do it, let's do it
Please go somewhere, bye bye bye
Bye bye bye
The answer of adults is...
I won't ask anymore
There are things that only children can
do
Meanwhile, Sakuraibis are on standby at
the stage.
It's fun, but I'm a little scared.
I don't know the reaction.
Do you have an engine?
I don't know.
Mizuha!
Sato!
Ayame!
Sara!
Sakai!
Fight!
And, at the view of E defendant, Hagak
bus bir financially gets for eggplant
and Nagano or
everything
All right!
Let's go to school!
Everybody, say hello to everyone!
Everybody, Diamond!
Everybody, everybody
Sorry for the early bird
Everybody, Diamond!
I'll smile for you
Please forgive me, Sensei
Let's apologize with the best smile
Laugh and deceive
So don't get angry
Laugh and forgive me
Happy now, everyday
Let's laugh together
What's wrong with either of us
If our smiles look happy?!
Look at me like that
Shirtless
yr away
entirety
All right, let's do this!
Everybody, let's say hello to everyone!
Ready?
Everybody, let's say hello!
And then...
Let's go
I'm going
Finally, that time came
Leaving with the fragrances of
ringtones!
Everyone, you get it now, right?
You get it now, right?
G.A.B.S.JUMA with the real
Middle school students who get along
with the others
Let's shout out! Let's shout out!
I can't say anything
I'm just a little bit confused
What should I do with my Juvia Rinno
heart?
I can't do it anymore!
I'm tired, but I'm tired
If I keep on going, I'll be kicked out
I'm so frustrated, I'm going crazy
If it's not love, then I'm going crazy
Look, a flying junior high school
student
Ready, set, go!
Thank you for watching!
High tension high mission
One shot one shot
Joy joy, a little bit nervous
I'm excited, I'm excited
I'm a real survivor
I'm super super super cool
I still can't do anything
High tension high mission
One shot one shot
Until my heart goes away
Thank you for watching!
The surprise was a huge success.
The best way to end the spring tour.
Lastly, please give us your impressions
of today's concert.
Do you want to do it again?
No, not that much.
I was surprised.
What was your impression?
My impression of this concert?
I think everyone has grown a lot during
this tour.
I think we were able to take a step up.
Thank you very much.
Next time, we will have 3 consecutive
live events in the middle of summer.
The second one is the birthday solo live
by Ayaka Yasumoto.
Why does she look so similar?
The set list of Yasumoto's speciality.
This program was provided by the
sponsor.
Show! Ken is the last.
ist】
Good Job!
Bye bye!