It's good.
I'm glad I saw this.
I bought a souvenir.
This is a monmotako.
I'm going to have a cool face.
Thank you for watching.
Hello everyone. Good evening. I'm Mizuki
Yamashita.
I have a shooting for the morning drama,
MAIAGARE, from tomorrow.
I haven't been able to go on a walk or
sightseeing, so I came here alone.
I'm going to eat various things. See
you.
I feel like a YouTuber. I'm a little
nervous.
I'm embarrassed to walk around with a
self-timer.
There's a store I wanted to go to.
I'll go to the store I was looking
forward to on the Internet.
Where is it?
Are you tired?
There are many delicious-looking stores.
I'm in trouble.
I'm worried about my happiness.
What should I do if I get a face-
punishment tomorrow?
Kurumi's face is a face-punishment.
I found it.
10 yen bread.
It says 500 yen.
I'm going to buy 10 yen bread.
Excuse me. I'm a YouTuber.
Can I take a picture of you?
Are you okay? Thank you.
I'm lost.
Cheese, custard, chocolate, matcha
custard, and azuki beans.
This is cheese.
Wow.
I bought something.
It looks delicious.
It's like a grilled cod.
I bought 10 yen bread.
Thank you for your viewing.
Let's eat.
It's warm. Look.
It's 10 yen bread.
It's really 10 yen.
Let's eat.
It's still warm.
Crispy.
It's crispy.
Thank you for your viewing. Thank you
for your viewing.
It's fluffy.
It's like a grilled oban.
It's crispy and fluffy inside.
It's delicious.
It's hot.
It's good.
It's like mozzarella cheese.
I think it's mozzarella.
It's cheese that will stretch forever.
It's the best.
Thank you for watching.
Crab? I think I should eat crab. I want
to eat crab.
I came to crab paradise.
The original taste of crab paradise.
What would be good?
Grilled crab charcoal.
And crab miso cola with soup stock.
Sounds delicious.
Excuse me.
I'd like a special crab miso cola with
soup stock.
Sounds delicious.
Crab miso cola with soup stock.
Look at this.
Thank you for it.
I can't see it.
But it's soft.
Thank you for it.
It's delicious.
I'll try the crab.
Look at this.
Crab.
It's amazing.
It's delicious.
I'm sad that I can't buy it anymore.
I'll eat it right away.
This is cheap.
I think that I should be aware of the
Osaka dialect when I come to Kansai.
I think there are many things that are
wrong about Indonesian.
I try my best to speak as much as
possible so that I don't speak standard
language during the play.
It's delicious.
Look at this.
I'm full.
I ate well.
It was delicious.
I came to NHK.
This is a place called BK Plaza.
There are panels of my performance and
my life-long panel.
There are also various programs of NHK.
I have produced a series of TV series
and Asadora.
This is amazing.
I always broadcast this work.
I will also appear in the program.
There is also a big poster of the
program.
Osaka.
Is this the same place?
This is a rice bowl.
I want to buy souvenirs.
There was a shop that sold souvenirs.
I will go there.
I can buy souvenirs only in Shin-Osaka.
I can't buy them because of the time.
I want to buy souvenirs that I have
never seen.
There are many people in the street.
I want to buy souvenirs for members.
I want to buy souvenirs for my childhood
friends.
I want to buy souvenirs for HARUKA and
AKASHI.
I want to buy souvenirs for MAI and
TAKASHI.
This is a picture of a toilet.
This is a keyboard.
This is a color pen.
This is a pen for thinking.
This is a bamboo shoot for a bamboo
shoot.
This is a pair of socks.
I collect a lot of strange socks.
I also collect socks.
This is cheap.
This is a flint.
This is 880 yen.
This is amazing.
This is cute.
I am lost in the world of the unknown.
I found a shop.
I want to buy a wooden box in Osaka.
I decided what to buy.
I want to buy a skewered pork cutlet.
This is written on the back of the box.
I want to buy souvenirs for MAI and
TAKASHI.
I bought souvenirs.
I will shoot this tomorrow.
I am glad.
I feel better when I am in Osaka.
There is a shooting range in front of
me.
Can I go there?
Look at this.
It says no shooting.
I'm nervous.
I don't think I can go there alone.
I will shoot.
I put this in.
What should I do?
This is not good.
This is bad.
This is good.
This is a good shot.
Can I shoot with this?
This is fun.
I want to shoot something amazing.
This is difficult.
I got it.
This is better than I thought.
Thank you.
This is amazing.
This is a good shot.
This is fun.
This was fun.
I bought a friend's animal ramune and a
cigarette.
This is a good idea.
This is fun.
I can't believe I can shoot on a
weekday.
This is Osaka.
I will shoot the next one.
Can I shoot this?
Tourism.
I'm hungry.
Mr. Haro is beating the drum.
I think I saw this.
I saw this.
This is difficult.
This is fun.
Look, there's a dog.
Look, there's a Wutan.
I've been working on this since I was
little.
I can work on a song.
There was a version of Domo's Osaka
grandma.
I'm glad I can come to Ame-chan.
I found a souvenir shop 2.
I'll go into 2.
I want this.
Look.
Look at this.
This is a
I bought it.
I'm grateful for the many things.
I'm glad you're here.
I've prepared a gift for you.
What?
I'm Tako.
Takoyama.
Oh, my God.
Takoyama is amazing.
I'm embarrassed because I'm so famous.
There was a steak shop.
Steak sushi, Kobe beef steak.
There are many kinds of steak.
I'd like a medium size steak sushi.
Look at this.
It's a cow.
Hello, I'm TAKO.
I'm Yamato.
I'll enjoy this.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's very eye-catching.
I thought I bought it as a disguise.
I'll be able to hear a lot of voices if
I wear this.
Here it is.
medium fatty meat sushi.
It looks delicious.
Look at this.
There's only one of these, so it's a
waste to eat it.
I'll have two bites.
I'd like to have one bite for each
person.
I'll have two bites.
Thank you for watching.
It's good!
I said I'd eat it in one bite, but I ate
it in one bite.
I'm sad.
Takoyaki, takoyaki, takoyaki shop.
Where?
Where is my takoyaki?
My octopus is here.
It's a dancing octopus.
A whole octopus.
Takoyaki with one octopus.
There is a dancing octopus.
Sauce and soy sauce.
I like the sauce.
Gaen.
It looks delicious.
Gaen is also the best.
I'm lost.
What should I do with the sauce?
Sauce and soy sauce are herbs.
Can I put all the toppings on it?
Yes, please.
Thank you for waiting.
Please be careful.
Thank you very much.
I will enjoy this food.
Can you see this?
This is amazing.
I will enjoy this food.
Hmm!
Delicious!
The octopus is very plump.
The dough is too soft and I can't hold
it.
The next day
It was hot.
I got carried away and ate it in one
bite.
Look!
It's a regular octopus.
It's hot.
Octopus is delicious.
I want to go on a one-way trip.
I don't study.
Please subscribe to my channel.
It's soft and chewy.
I was worried about the sauce and soy
sauce.
This is the best.
I have to eat this.
Fashion check.
Necklace.
Finger.
Nail.
Yellow.
Earrings.
Necklace.
Finger.
Nail.
Yellow.
Wow.
I have a lot of things.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I arrived at the music room of NHK.
I don't usually introduce music rooms.
This is the music room.
The music room is divided by number.
Today was the first time I saw the night
view.
I'm very happy.
I put my script here.
My chair is like this.
There is a gate on the same side.
I came to the music room.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm very good at it.
Is it a coat?
It's a tambourine.
I'm going to dance.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I'm going to the takoyaki shop I wanted
to go to.
Excuse me.
6 Ario Aureo sauce and 6 Torio Fugio.
Thank you.
I'm looking forward to it.
The first Ario Aureo.
Wow, here it is.
Ario Aureo.
It's cute.
Torio Fugio smells good.
I ate this a lot when I was on tour.
And this is a flag.
But when I was on tour, I didn't have
this flag.
It's like a takoyaki shop.
I'll eat it.
Look.
It's a cafe with a nice atmosphere.
I'm grateful.
The drink looks delicious.
Excuse me.
I'm going to eat the takoyaki of Creole.
I'll eat it.
It smells good.
The smell of Torio is amazing.
Mmm.
It's delicious!
The salt is delicious!
Is it because it's delicious salt?
Is it because it's true salt?
I said something normal.
Next, what was it?
Olive de Olive
Ario Oreo
I don't know what Ario Oreo is.
I'm a fashionable and thick person.
I eat this.
This is different.
This is very delicious.
This is not like takoyaki.
This is refreshing.
This is a loose type of onion.
I ate a lot of takoyaki.
My face is a little red.
I'm going to the Shinsuibashi.
Where did I go?
Shinsuibashi?
So, I came to Dotonbori and I ate a lot
of food.
I became a octopus.
I bought octopus, I bought souvenirs, I
ate a lot of delicious food, and the
people at the restaurant were all kind.
It was a great time.
It's going to be cold, so please be
careful.
Please subscribe to the channel, like
the video, and press the good button.
Please come to Osaka.
I'm waiting for you.
Please watch the video of the dance.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
Oh, I can see it.
I love seeing Osaka Castle from the
school building.
I love seeing Osaka Castle from Osaka-
Nen'ichi-K.
I'm excited.
Today, I'm going to have a rehearsal.
I'm going to have a rehearsal for the
whole week.
I have to memorize the scene for a week
by Monday.
I have to go soon.
I will do my best.
What time is it?
How many scenes are there?
I memorized a lot of scenes because the
amount of scenes was large.
Please watch it.