you
Konbanwa!
We are the morning chimes, Shiru TV junior high school.
Before we start, we will decide the MC for today.
Please vote for your favorite number from 1 to 3.
The person with the number on their number tag will be the MC for today.
So, let's vote.
Oh, sorry. Everyone is in a team.
Good evening.
So, let's start the voting.
Which number should I choose?
Emma-chan might be the MC for today.
She's been a MC for 3 months.
2 months?
She might be the MC for today.
What do you think?
Everyone's got a big tail.
Ema-chan's got a big tail.
Wow!
It's like this.
Yuno chose it.
Yuno chose it?
Yes, Yuno said,
Ema-chan, this is it.
It's cute.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1
Hi
How is the result?
What do you think?
Number 3
Let's show it together
Ready, go
Oh
Yuna again
Why is it always me?
Yuna
Yuna is the MC today
Please
Did you see this?
I didn't see it
Please
I'm Kokubo Yuna
I'll do my best
Please do your best
Yes
Did you see this?
Well
Let's start
I'll call the title
Ebichu no Yukai de Fufufuna Showroom
Yeah
Today is the 52nd
Thank you for watching Ebichu no Yukai de Fufufuna Showroom
Ebichu no Yukai de Fufufuna Showroom is a show about our little sister, Uka
Let's see the ranking
How is it?
5th place is Ganryu Shimaotai.
4th place is Mayuge.
3rd place is Kasabutta.
2nd place is Kittos.
1st place is Monta.
You can get the original Avatar of Showroom by registering for Showroom.
There are a lot of Avatars.
Onion!
Onion?
No, no.
You wrote it.
There are a lot. Thank you.
If you click the Twitter mark below the screen, you can spread the promotion of
this program on Twitter.
Please.
We will announce the promotion on Twitter, so please retweet.
Thank you.
Please retweet.
Please.
Let's move on to the next topic.
Yes.
The topic is
fun and funny questionnaire talk.
Before the talk, we will take a questionnaire
and decide what to talk about.
That's what questionnaire talk is.
Yes.
I will announce the topic.
Ta-da.
There are many.
There are 7.
I will choose from the comments.
I wrote all the letters,
so I don't know who it is.
I don't know who it is.
Please leave a comment
about the topic you want to hear.
Please vote.
I will start voting.
I wrote all the letters
so that I couldn't judge.
I don't know who it is.
What do you think?
But there are only food.
That's right.
All of them are food.
What do you think?
First, number 2.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Time's up!
What's the first theme?
Number 2!
Number 2 is 34%.
The second theme is...
Hina Kashiwagi's graduation ceremony and university reunion.
Yay!
Let's start with Hina's graduation ceremony.
It was held at the Makuhari Messe event hall on the 16th.
It was a graduation ceremony for Hina called Smile4U.
The first day was a live performance with a lot of Hina's favorite songs.
There were four people in each unit corner, and Hina sat on a very flashy and
cool chair as the boss.
She was wearing a black mask.
There was no chair at first, but suddenly a chair came out.
Hina is wearing a black mask.
The costume was a black mask with a boss's set-up.
I sang a high-pitched song called YUNOMA HAITO TEKI.
I've been watching you since before.
You must be more nervous than your family watching.
I was really nervous because I felt like I was watching you.
I was surprised to hear that you weren't there when I sang Nagareboshi.
I'm glad I sang with all my heart.
I remember you shooting a gun at the school's tobacco roll.
I shot a gun at the school's tobacco roll.
It's very light, but it contains dry ice.
I was able to shoot a gun at the school's tobacco roll.
I was watching you at the scene.
I was surprised to see your shout.
YUNO and I did it.
We were both very excited.
I'm glad I did it.
YUNO, please shoot a gun at the school's tobacco roll.
I'll shoot a gun at the school's tobacco roll.
I'll leave it to YUNO from now on.
I'll shoot a gun at the school's tobacco roll on the 17th.
Did you have a song you wanted to do on the 16th?
I wanted to do the school's tobacco roll after school.
I liked YUNO's part.
I like the part after school.
YUNO doesn't usually say that, so I liked it.
YUNO said the same thing.
YUNO said she wanted to do the school's tobacco roll.
It's fun to dance.
I was watching the archive.
The pen lights were all on the X part of the school's tobacco roll.
It was very beautiful and interesting.
That's great.
How was the 16th?
It was a lot of fun.
The strings sound was amazing.
There were a lot of people coming to see the 4 songs.
It was very beautiful.
I've done it in a band before, but it was different with strings.
It was the best.
I'm glad.
I was moved by the last hug.
It was so cool.
I don't know what they said.
I don't know.
I won't tell you.
The heat of the hot amp was amazing.
The 17th was the same.
The fire was burning.
It was very hot.
It was hot.
It was not so hot in the last university concert.
It was between the front and the back.
The last part was very hot.
It was very hot.
Was the fire hot?
The audience was hot, too.
The family was hot, too.
I was happy that the truck came to the side.
It was the first time for us to ride a truck.
It was the first time for me to ride a truck.
It's getting more and more.
I'm glad that the background was the same as the background.
Hello! was a camp.
It was a theme called a journey of a girl.
It was a school trip.
The costume was casual school trip.
We talked while we were camping.
It was morning.
We woke up when we rehearsed.
We baked marshmallows.
It was fun.
The background was beautiful.
The heat was transmitted three times.
Did you feel the heat?
I didn't feel the heat.
It's hot when you're close to people.
Let's talk about the 17th.
It was the first time for Mayana to perform on the 17th.
How was it?
The scenery was beautiful.
I was impressed by the penlight.
It was the first time for us to perform on such a large stage.
There were many people on the stage.
I was happy.
What do you remember most?
The song?
I think it's the Superhero.
I sang the first song in a circle.
Then I joined the chorus.
YUNA IMAI, KOKOENO NO KA, KAHORI, JUNEN.
The chorus of Superhero is quite high.
I was impressed by YUNA IMAI's performance.
We were surprised.
I don't know if I can say this.
The director asked us to sing together.
We said we would do our best.
We were singing together before we came out.
Mayana's power was overwhelming.
We did our best.
On the 16th, we performed as a band.
But on the 17th, we performed as a group.
We performed as a group.
We performed 8 songs in a row.
And we performed the last song.
How was it?
Did you feel like you were not MCs?
We were talking, but we were not MCs.
Hot-up is cool.
I liked the dance.
Thank you. I was nervous.
Mayana's power was overwhelming.
I was exhausted.
I was exhausted, too.
YUNA, you did your best.
The fire was amazing.
I was surprised.
I was sweating a lot.
Mayana, please introduce yourself.
It's your first time to be a MC.
There may not be many people who know you.
Let's start.
Please.
When I say, please smile.
1, 2, 3, smile!
Thank you.
I was laughed at.
I'm Sakurai Eva, the 16th member of the group.
That's good.
Kino-san came up with this.
How did you decide?
We started talking about what kind of character we wanted to make.
And many people asked me what kind of character I wanted to sell.
But Fujii-san said,
I think it's a good thing to keep smiling.
So I thought it would be good to make a character like that.
That's how I came up with the idea of smiling.
That's good.
Ema-chan's smile is cute.
Everyone's smile.
Yuna-chan's self-introduction is in Fukuoka dialect.
We're still talking about it.
When we can do it again,
we'll all be smiling.
I'm looking forward to it.
I want to do it.
The song that's playing now is called Voyager.
There were 9 people, but there were 10 people on the 16th.
We did it for two days.
The song changed and the chorus became Ema Yuna-chan.
It was amazing.
There were many songs for the unconfirmed students and the special university
game.
Only the unconfirmed students are on YouTube now.
Please watch the other videos on the stream.
There are still tickets.
There is an archive until the 24th, so please watch it.
Shall we move on to the next topic?
Please vote.
You're good at selling.
I'll do my best.
Everyone, please watch it.
What do you think?
What will come?
How will it be?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10
Time's up!
Which one is it?
Which one?
I'm going to eat curry now, so I want curry.
Number 7!
It's Rika's birthday.
That's right.
Rika's birthday is December 16th.
Happy birthday!
We all gave her a cake on the 15th.
Hinata-chan wrote a cake plate.
She wrote it with a chocolate pen.
She couldn't write it.
She wrote, Maya-chan, happy birthday.
She couldn't write a happy birthday.
But still, happy birthday to you, 26 years old!
I went to Rika-chan's birthday party on the 16th.
I always send her a message on her birthday.
But I thought I didn't send her a message.
I remembered that it was on the 17th.
I was in a hurry, so I sent her a message.
Happy birthday!
I met her and went to her birthday party.
I thought I should send her a message.
I drank all the chocolate pen.
I was like, you have some left over.
I was like, is that okay?
I drank all the chocolate pen.
Happy birthday.
26 years old Maya-chan, you are so good.
I'm 26 years old.
Then, 26 years old.
Who is it?
I'm 26 years old.
It's not much.
I can't tell you how much I know.
I'll tell you how much I know.
Let's go in 3 seconds.
I'll go first.
Start!
She teaches me a lot.
She's kind.
She's the same height as me, so she's cute when she stretches her back.
We have a lot in common.
I like her cool low voice.
I respect her jumping ability.
She gives me easy-to-understand advice on LINE.
She's always there when I'm in trouble.
She gave me a birthday cake with chocolate on it.
There was a lot of chocolate on it.
She praised my makeup.
I have 10 of these.
She taught me a lot of things I didn't know in the lesson.
She's kind when she stretches my back.
Am I okay?
Her eyelashes are big.
Her face is small.
She's wearing cute shoes.
She's wearing the shoes Yuno wanted.
I'm not good at soccer, so I think I'm amazing.
How many did you get?
I like her school uniform.
I got a lot of clothes from her.
They're cute, so I wear them at home.
Thank you for talking to me.
How many did you get?
19.
7 more.
Her nails are beautiful.
She always praises me when I change my nails.
You're talking about Emma.
I just thought of it.
Really?
She always praises my nails.
She said my thumb is cute.
She also praised my pinky.
She praised my nails.
I can't do it.
What else?
She taught me a lot of things when I was training.
She's good at cooking.
I'm thin.
Last one.
What's the best thing about me?
I think I look good in everything from pop to mature.
I said 26 years old.
I have more than that.
Congratulations.
I hope you have a wonderful 26 years old.
Please do.
Let's move on to the next topic.
Please vote.
Left all the time?
The horns are on the right.
Heavy.
I'm moving when I nod.
I was surprised.
Emma was like this.
It was cute.
It was bigger than I thought.
It was funny.
How about this?
Are you ready?
5,4,3,2,1, start!
What is it?
5.
Curry and curry.
Who is this?
This is me.
I have something to say.
I'm doing a little bit of a forced interview right now.
I can do it.
When it's over, I want to go to a curry shop.
Cheese naan looks really good.
I want to eat a lot of curry toppings.
I remembered curry.
Did you eat spicy curry?
It's strange.
I didn't eat it at all.
I ate it while saying it was a little spicy.
I was surprised when I ate it with everyone.
I'm not good at spicy food.
I want you to tell me the recommended toppings.
I'm really looking forward to it.
Do you eat curry at the store?
I think there are more take-out shops.
I have a lot of curry at home.
I'm at a curry shop near my house.
The cheese and shrimp in the curry shop are delicious.
The shrimp is also big and delicious.
I like to eat it with naan.
I like the potato in the Obelgine curry.
I understand.
The butter is delicious.
There are a lot of toppings.
I think there are a lot of variations of toppings.
How many are there?
I want to eat natto.
What about you?
What do you like?
I like natto.
I like curry with a lot of toppings.
I like simple things.
I've never eaten curry with naan.
I also like eggplant.
It looks delicious.
There are so many.
Really?
Where is it?
Oh, it's true!
Wow!
Last time, when we went to Osaka for the 2man zip tour,
we went to a curry shop with Hinata, Ucchi and I.
The curry there was really delicious.
I forgot the name, but it was spicy soup curry, but it was delicious.
Soup curry is also delicious.
What was the name of the curry shop?
There are so many.
I want to know because Hinata tweeted.
I want to add cheese, but I want to add cheese and natto.
I'm thinking of adding cheese and natto at first.
I think so.
Thank you.
That's all.
What I want to talk about is...
I remembered! It's Watanabe curry!
I went to Watanabe curry and it was delicious.
Osaka?
Yes, Osaka.
I want to eat it when I go there.
What should we do next?
Shall we go to the next place?
Let's go to the next place.
I will go to the next place.
You can choose the same one.
Let's talk as many times as you want.
OK. I'm fine with anything.
You can talk about curry as many times as you want.
Please vote.
I'm glad. My ears turn red right away.
It's good to be able to hide.
It's good. This is very warm.
Emma-chan has been fixing her horns.
It's heavy, isn't it?
5, 4, 3, 2, 1
What's the result?
Number 3!
What is it?
Favorite snack!
Who is it?
Emma-chan!
Please go ahead.
My favorite snack is...
I've been into this lately.
Do you like beans?
Beans?
The green beans?
The ones that are a bit dark.
I like that.
I made that into a snack.
Really?
There's a snack called Mino.
I've been into that lately.
I saw it in a commercial.
I thought it looked really good.
But I always forget to buy it when it's on sale.
I don't really recommend it to my friends.
I don't really like beans.
I like beans.
It has a bit of a smell.
I've heard that it goes well with beer.
Everyone says it's a secret.
My grandma likes it.
You're buying it with your grandma?
It looks good.
I want to buy it.
Do you carry it around?
I've been carrying it around a lot lately.
I'll make you eat it.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm happy.
Do you like ginnan?
Ginnan?
The yellow potatoes?
Yeah, the beans.
I can't understand you.
I've never eaten ginnan.
I don't like ginnan.
I thought there were more people who could give it to me.
What does it taste like?
It's like a chawanmushi.
It's beans.
It's like yellow potatoes.
Oh, our favorite sweets?
Yuna's basically got a gummy.
Do you have any recommendations?
What's your favorite gummy?
What was it? The cloud gummy?
They sell cherry flavored ones at Family Mart.
That's the best.
Oh, I got that a while ago. It was delicious.
And that's Ruri-chan's favorite gummy.
She said the dark cherry flavor was really good.
I got it, but it was so good that I thought I'd buy it, but I didn't.
It's not sold much.
Oh, it's not sold?
It's not sold much, so I don't know if it's sold out.
But Ruri-chan said she's already buying it.
She said, when you want it, you can go anytime.
I was surprised.
I usually eat chocolate.
I don't know.
It's ice cream, but there's a convenience store called Koeda.
They sell ice cream at Koeda.
It looked really good.
I didn't have the money to eat it right away, so I thought it would melt.
But I couldn't find it.
It looked really good, so if you find it, please let me know.
I really want to eat it.
I like chocolate.
I found a chocolate ball ice cream today.
I've had it before.
It's really good.
Please come and buy it.
What's your favorite snack?
It's not a sweet snack after the live, but it's not a salty snack, but you want
to eat it.
What's your favorite?
There's a Koeda ice cream at Lawson.
I'll go to Lawson.
You're a good girl.
Wasabi beef.
Wasabi beef?
I've seen it, but I've never eaten it.
What kind of spicy?
I'm going to put the crunchy dried plum on it. It's in the manager's bag.
He's preparing it.
I put it in the bag so I can eat it anytime during the lesson.
It's a salt supplement.
I bought a dried plum with no colorant.
It's a natural one.
I ate a lot of dried natto.
It's really good and healthy.
I thought it would be good for when I wanted to eat sweets.
It was natto.
It was natto. It was delicious.
That's all.
There was natto on the 17th catering.
There was.
It was delicious.
So, let's move on to the last topic.
What is it?
Please vote.
Start!
I'm sure you're all aware of this.
Yeah, I am.
She said she ate a few slices of chocolate at night.
I heard a celebrity eat chocolate before going to bed, and she ate two slices of
it.
I told you that's not true!
I'm sure it's not!
I think it's 70% chocolate.
I was surprised.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1, time's up!
What was your last talk?
What was it?
Number 4!
This is Yuno's.
Yes, Yuno's.
I was curious about this one.
I ordered a dashi rolled egg.
It was a take-out.
I ordered it and it was sweet.
The egg rolls in Tokyo are usually sweet.
Like bento.
Aichi's is a soupy one, not sweet at all.
I wanted to know if you like sweet or salty.
I like salty food.
I know, right?
I said it.
I've eaten salty food.
I've only eaten sweet food.
My mom and grandma make sweet food for me.
My mom is a salty food lover.
What do you guys like?
I sometimes want to eat sweet food, but I like salty food.
I think it's better to have a lot of soup.
Let's vote.
Number 1 is sweet, number 2 is salty.
Please vote.
I like the egg roll.
I like the normal egg roll.
I like the soup.
I like both.
I was surprised that it was sweet when I received it.
I wanted to eat this.
Sweet food is good, though.
I don't know how to make eggs sweet.
Some people like it.
I'm disappointed when I eat it in a bento.
Which one is more popular?
The egg roll at a sushi restaurant is sweet.
Time's up.
Kyushu is famous for sweet soy sauce.
I want to eat soy sauce.
I like salty food.
I think it's a big difference.
44% and 55%.
I think it depends on the region.
Is Kanto sweet?
Nagasaki is overwhelmingly sweet.
Kyushu is different.
Which one is Yuna?
I think it's Fukuoka.
I think it depends on the region.
Kansai is salty.
I saw an omelette earlier. Is there a sweet one?
Omelette? I think it's sweet.
Omelette is just an egg and sugar.
It's not tasty without sugar.
Wait, wait, wait.
It's about omelette.
It's about egg.
I see.
But omelette and rice are not salty, right?
Is it sweet?
Wait, isn't it sweet?
I think it's salty because of ketchup.
You don't put ketchup, do you?
Is it salty because I don't put it?
It's not salty.
I don't feel the sweetness.
I think it's important not to put sugar in omelette.
I just remembered.
I heard there are both in Fukuoka.
It says you can put mentaiko in Fukuoka.
Mentaiko looks good.
I like the omelette in the bento.
It looks delicious.
I like the one that you can make at home.
I like the one that you cut the ham into small pieces and put it in the middle
of the omelette.
I like the one with cheese.
I've eaten the omelette.
I wonder what it tastes like.
There are many different kinds of soup stock in each region.
I want to compare the taste of each region.
It looks fun.
Sweet omelette goes well with mentaiko.
I see.
Does it mean sweet and salty?
I don't know what it means.
Time's up.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
I'm a salty person.
That was a fun and fun questionnaire talk.
This is the end of the 52nd episode of the showroom.
Let's read the questions.
Yuno, please.
Emma, please.
Please read the questions.
The F.C. Family Gathering 2023 will be held at Pacifico Yokohama National Hall
on February 12, 2023.
The tickets will be on sale on the 17th.
You can find out a lot of new things about MNL48.
Last year, Yuno and the others wore pajamas.
We were supposed to change into our pajamas and go to work.
What will it be like this year?
Please look forward to what will happen this year.
And there's one more.
Please look forward to it.
Yeah.
Mayamania Level 7, KTZ Yokohama.
Mayamania's birthday solo live.
We just celebrated it, so please come and enjoy it.
There is also a Stapler Festival in January, so please come.
We will now look at the top 5.
What's the ranking?
5th place, Jimmy-san. Thank you.
4th place, Kasabutta-san. Thank you.
3rd place, Kids-san. Thank you.
2nd place, Ryota-san. Thank you.
1st place, Monta-san. Thank you.
So, it seems like this was the last showroom in 2022.
Is that so? I hope it was okay.
It was okay.
Oh, I have a question.
What was the year like for the three of you?
What was the year like?
What should I do?
I'll go first.
You go first, Emma.
Okay, I'll go first.
Well, we had a spring tour and a family tour.
A lot of things we couldn't do last year came back.
We can't say it yet, but we've had more opportunities to meet with our families.
I've been on stage, and I think it's a year of growth.
I think there will be a lot of acting work and live performances next year.
I hope you'll come.
Great.
What was the year like for Yuno?
January was...
What was January like this year?
It's okay.
January was...
January was a lot of things. February was...
There was Fushiibe. March was...
There was a lot of things. April was...
Albums.
We released an album.
We had a spring tour, and then we started releasing 10 contents.
We recorded a lot of songs.
We had a fan meeting, a fan meeting, and a concert.
We also had a Taiwan tour.
We had a Taiwan tour.
There were a lot of live performances this year.
That's right.
There were a lot of things.
Next year...
Oh, I forgot. We had a singing contest last year.
That's right.
There were a lot of live performances.
I hope we can do a lot of live performances in 2023.
That's right.
Thank you.
How about you, Emma?
I'm used to being a new member of Ebichu this year.
It was a big year.
It was a year of great changes.
It was the first live performance at the university concert.
I was very nervous.
I think it was the best memory of this year.
Yes.
It's only been four days since the show.
That's right.
Oh, really?
It's strange.
I feel like it's been a few days.
I feel like it's been a month.
There are a lot of live performances next year, so please come and see us.
Thank you.
That's all for the 52nd episode of the showroom.
We'll tell you the next episode as soon as it's decided.
Please check out the feedback session that will be held after this.
The show will end, but we'll be back soon, so please stay tuned.
If you have any comments you want to tell us, please leave them in the comments.
That's all for today.
We are Shirite Ebichu.
Bye bye.
My mom made me a dango with the name of the three dango brothers.
I really liked it.
I don't know.
Because I have a speciality of my family.
Do you have any?
What did you like?
Octopus sausage.
I really liked it.
I couldn't make octopus sausage.
I cut the octopus sausage.
There were a lot of flowers inside.
Thank you for the meal.
We talked about food a lot.
I'm hungry.
Kokubo was the MC today.
How was it?
I thought Yuno would come to the show.
I expected it.
Yunopi's MC is getting better.
I'm glad.
Yunopi looks a little mature.
It was the best.
I'm glad.
How was it?
The first time was with Yuna.
I was glad to be able to be a senior.
You are a senior.
Yuna is the same age as you.
We are all 15 years old.
Yes.
Only the coconut is different.
I see.
Well, you know, you two look like older sisters.
What?
Cute.
This week, or rather, the showroom is during Christmas, so everyone is wearing
hats and doing live streaming.
This is the first time I've seen everyone wearing reindeer hats.
I see.
Doremu prepared a lot of hats for us.
Everyone is wearing reindeer hats.
Usually, Santa Claus is in the middle, but this time, the middle looks like a
strong reindeer.
It's like a reindeer herd.
That's what I'm talking about.
That's good.
It's all reindeer.
There's no main character, is there?
Well, it's up to you.
That's about it.
Well, the year is over, so please look forward to next year.
I think there will be a lot of live streaming next year.
I've said that there are 26 hats, but I think there are 27 hats in total.
Oh!
I don't think there's enough.
We have to do it next year.
I want to do it for everyone's birthday next year.
Because it's Yuno's birthday next year.
Oh, that's right.
Yuno's birthday is March 16th, so I want to do 16 hats.
You're saying, it's coming out soon.
It's coming out soon.
Let's say one at a time at the end.
Let's go like this.
The color of my eyes is beautiful.
My bangs are always beautiful.
My manager often says that I look like a child when I eat sweets.
Your manager says that, not you.
I like new gummies and Mayaba, so if you bring me Haichu, I'll give you some
sweets.
That's good.
Thank you very much.
See you again.
Happy New Year.
you