I'm a nightclub and an idol!
We have a special project for this show.
We're going to have you say the title to
the camera.
Is that okay?
It says, I'm cute.
I'm sorry.
I'll do my best!
I'm going to say it! My three main
elements!
Thank you!
Now, it's time to introduce the three
elements that make up you.
We'd like to learn more about our guest,
Ile-san.
So, can you show us your three main
elements?
Here are my three main elements.
First, Shonen Manga.
Second, ice cream.
Third, sports.
I see!
I chose this one.
I'm curious about everything, so I'd
like to dig one by one.
First, Shonen Manga.
Yes.
I love Shonen Manga.
I have three brothers.
Oh, I see.
I grew up surrounded by manga.
So I drew Shonen Manga.
Oh, Shonen Manga.
I love Shonen Manga.
I graduated from college,
but I also wrote my graduation thesis in
Jump.
What?
I'm sorry. What do you mean?
I wrote my graduation thesis in Jump.
How did you think of Jump?
I read the definition of a popular manga
from Shonen Jump.
Oh, I see.
I wanted to know the definition of a
popular manga.
I have a lot of favorite manga in Jump.
But the definition of a popular manga
changes with time.
Yes, it changes.
Yes, it's a market theory.
No matter how interesting a manga is,
if the result of the survey is not good,
the legend will change.
So I thought, if I knew the definition
of a popular manga,
I could never finish it.
I see.
I thought so.
You did a research.
Yes, I did.
I actually asked the publisher for help.
No way!
I went to ask them.
You did?
The editor of One Piece and Kimetsu no
Tanto
told me about the definition of a
popular manga.
I said, of course, I wrote it in Jump.
He said, it's interesting.
I asked him,
and he told me about the definition of a
popular manga.
He said, in the 90s, the main character
is a bad guy.
Or, it's better to make a manga about a
guy who is more popular than the main
character.
Or, it's better to make a manga about
four people.
Or, it's better to make a manga about a
martial arts.
long technique.
There were many opinions.
I see.
I was curious about the most popular
manga.
The most popular manga was Yu Yu
Hakusho.
I see, that surprised me.
I was wondering which manga you'd come
up with.
There are many elements.
The elements that make it popular.
Yu Yu Hakusho has all of them.
That's the result of my study.
There's a lot of media mixing now,
but the number of window openings is
increasing.
I think the number of layers of the
viewer is increasing.
I see.
So you're also working on that?
Yes.
You're laughing.
Do you have any other recommended works?
Right now?
Yes, Shonen Manga.
What should I do?
I'll start with Jump.
Jump's Akane Banashi.
Akane Banashi?
Yes.
I've been reading it for about three
volumes.
You've read it for three volumes?
Yes.
It's a story about Rakugo.
It's a new kind of Kirito.
That's amazing.
The girl's father was a Rakugo artist,
but he got fired.
The girl thinks,
why did my father get fired?
She's like a reverse teacher.
And she says,
I'll take the top spot in Rakugo.
That's really interesting.
I want to read it.
I know, right?
I want to read it now.
One Piece's Oda-sensei is also praising
it.
He's praising it?
Yes.
That Oda-sensei is also good.
He's a 10-year-old.
He's good at recommending.
He's reading Hiroshi.
It's interesting.
Ice cream is sold out really fast.
Every week.
Every week, a new convenience store ice
cream is released.
This program is brought to you by...
Tosakamin-san
Sadaaki-san
Hidepio-san
Kurobake-san
Kagichi-san
I'm sending you these manga!
Today's recommended manga is...
Danga-dan