The members are divided into three teams
and each challenge a completely
different project.
In the last week's broadcast, what is
the routine?
Teens who wear boot socks.
The new interpretation of the routine
was born in the self-talk of Kobayashi
Yasumoto.
And this week,
Men!
With a shrimp-chewing cut,
Don't go over there.
The members are
Let loose.
Apparently a
A new interpretation of the routine was
born in the self-talk of the local
Kobayashi
And this week
No, no
With shrimp chou
Don't go there
What will happen to the members?
In addition, the second half of the
Mayama Ayai walk
Looks delicious
What?
Full of shopping street foods
This week, the shrimp chou tastas start
The second half is four
High school, high school, high school,
high school
Never ending school
Add various things to private shrimp
chou school
Shrimp chou tastas
This program is provided by the sponsor
you see
This is also delicious
Let's eat the shrimp chou
Shrimp chou mini-corner festival
First of all
Mayama Rikato
Hirata Aika's Mayama Ayai walk
This program fully conveys the charm of
Yanaka Ginza shopping street
Wow
What is this?
Looks delicious
Eat all the shopping street foods from
one side
And the takiue who should be together
I'll sell this
While walking, he sells the omen he
bought on his own
However
1000 yen
What?
The price of the omen he bought for
20,000 yen is only 1000 yen
Yanaka Ginza is delicious
What will happen after this?
The second half starts
Two people who are eager to eat shopping
street foods from the end
What came into their eyes?
What?
Hey
Are you doing it?
What?
What is this?
What do you have in your hand?
What?
The omen he should have sold is in his
hand
Right?
Why do you have this?
I want you to know
The omen he bought for 20,000 yen
The price of the omen was 1100 yen
It's a little bit half
That's right
Actually, when he was selling
1000 yen
Takiue was not convinced by the price of
So
Takiue has used this many times
Please give me more than 1000 yen
He added the value of the top star
Takiue
I will give you 10%
I will buy it for 1100 yen
He made 100 yen with the value of the
top star
But
I can't let go of this cute girl
I can't let go of her
Takiue is in the omen
What are they going to do next?
It looks delicious
Is this a donut?
He is interested in food
I can't eat the tail
It's not bad
Yanaka Ginza shopping street is famous
for cats
Yanaka Ginza sells donuts with a cat
tail motif
I want to eat
You ate a lot
I ate a lot, but if I see this
Please like the four colors
Which one is recommended?
Pumpkin rice
Pumpkin
Pumpkin is delicious
Mayama is interested in pumpkin
What is Mayama?
Really?
Do you want to make it a marigold?
The hero recommends pumpkin
Don't ignore it
I will make it a pumpkin
Mayama, you have a place to go
Let's eat
It's warm
I will eat
What is inside?
It's delicious
The usual eating insert
Eating insert is strange
It's kind
The dough is kind
The outside is crispy and the inside is
fluffy
If this is the insert, I will be excited
What is the insert?
I want to eat delicious food
If it's Hinata, I will definitely know
it's chocolate
If it's Mirei, it's this
Mirei is definitely a maiden
Ayu is a camel
There are many members
Members are coming out of the food
Is it a feast during the day?
They still have no appetite
Hello, father
Is it delicious?
It's delicious
Thank you
It's good to eat like this
I want to come here in private
Cute
It's Shin-chan
They are interested in other than food
Cat
There are only cats
Amazing
I tried to eat
This is strange
It's a strange thing
It's not a cat
They found a store that is full of cat
goods
What is going on inside the store?
There are many black cats
Excuse me
They have to move fast
Hello
Amazing
Is this Shin-chan?
Shin-chan
The store is full of black cats
How old are you?
6 years old
I'm also Shin-chan
Really?
It's a cat
Shin-chan, hello
I'm scared
You are scared
I'm sorry
I have something to decorate this mask
It's a problem to be told like that
I will wear this
Cat ears that look good on the mask
Can you wear it?
I think it's a problem
You can wear it
I will wear it
Shin-chan is saying
You wear it
I didn't say
OK
Cat ears that look good on the mask
Cat ears
It's a shrimp ball
It doesn't matter
Shin-chan, look
Let's leave the cat Shin-chan alone
Thank you
Shin-chan, bye
You got a good one
I'm glad
Mayama-san found something again
What is this?
Mayama-san found a shop
This is Zakro
It's a restaurant where you can taste
the local food of Iran, Turkey and
Uzbekistan
I think it's good
Hello
Cute
You two go to the shop next to that man
Why are you going there?
That person is used to the TV
Did you say something?
I didn't say anything
Let's go inside the shop
Come
There are colorful torco lamps on the
ceiling
Beautiful
Wait, there is a camel
Camel
There is a big camel doll in the shop
What is this?
Come in
We have to leave this to the flow
You are getting angry all of a sudden
Are you OK?
Mayama
This shop is doing free rental of
traditional costumes to enjoy local food
more
Wait
It's delicious
I don't feel uncomfortable
It's good
Mayama-san is in a hurry
Let's eat the recommended food before we
forget that this is a restaurant
It's called Gyozlama
Gyozlama?
It's made by three grandmothers in the
market
The taste of the Turkish home food
What is this?
It's delicious
It's like pizza
I've never seen this before
How was the walk?
It was fun to walk slowly
It was a first experience
It's different from the start
I think everyone is young
It was a shocking experience
Next is Ebichu
It's a project that tests the sense of
humor of the members
Before that
Ebichu Game Quest
Ebichu game project is currently in
progress
Ebichu songs are arranged in the game
and used as BGM
So today we will reveal some of them
Amazing
Let's play
The game is amazing
The members have come up with various
ideas about the game
This time they will think of the songs
they want to use in the game
First is Mayama
Esax
Esax game
Run more
It's good to run more
It's like playing more
Next is Hoshina
I'm a middle school student
I'm doing this and that
Next is Kobayashi
Sting
It's like a magic
It's terrible
The last one is Makayama
I'm your manager
Please open it
It's not over yet
I'm out of the mood
I'm wearing school uniform
So I don't look like a school girl
The reason is reasonable
How is this request?
I hope you will have a good game
Thank you
Ebichu game project is still in progress
I took a new sea fish
After this, the legend of Matsu starts
Mini corner festival
Ebichu game
Ebichu game started
It's the end of the game
Please introduce yourself
I was told to wash my hands
I washed my hands
My hands became dry
I'm Hoshinami Rei
Thank you
Recently, I was watching a magazine with
my mom
My mom was too mobile
I was surprised
I'm worried about my mom's fun
Please
It's not a mobile screen
I have a pet
I'm not used to it
I'm Kashiage Nata
Please
I'll do my best today
I'm Riko Nakayama
Please
Who will carry the futon?
I will carry the futon and happiness
Thank you
First question
Bring the present
Please give it to everyone
Please write the answer
Write the answer
Hoshina
Let's try
I like Ebichu
The first answer is the best
Bring the futon
Kashiwaiki
In a very wonderful and shining group
Su
Please bring one
No
Please write the answer
Matsuno
I like Takoyaki
No
Ebichu
Matsuno
Rina
I see
One
Yay
Nakayama
Not Taa
To
It's very hot
I can't think
It's a scary story
Why did you change the Taa?
It's hot
You did it with Tosu?
I wanted to start with Tosu
Don't say that
Next question
Here it is
Hoshina
Write the answer
I will write with a young person
Both are pretty
It's pretty but it's not as I expected
Peach Peach
Nakayama
Write with Chuuen
I will write with a strong person
Both are cute
Let's give Nakayama one
Yay
Kashiwaiki
I will write with Hirota Aika
I will write with people who are getting
married
Both are lovely
It's pretty
Open one
My friends said that
That's a thief
There was a mystery class in elementary
school
Mystery class?
Sorry, I'm still thinking of mystery
class
You can do that
I wrote with a fan
I will write with a fan
I will send a signal
Both have to be blue
The fan is gone
You were expressing it with your face
I wrote with a fan
After that
Nakayama
I wrote with a wrong face
It's in the pot
After that
They got a lot of buttons
The third one is Haranga
Here is the topic
Pay attention to the members' words
Hiratsuka
Bring me something
From now on
Everyone in the shrimp is a guard
I will say go down
I will ask what happened
Please answer
Go down
Pay up
What happened?
I'm practicing live
Good job
Amazing
It's like a show
Nakayama
Don't go
One
It's cute
It's not related to the topic
Please watch it
Take two
Pay up
I'm surprised
Take one
Don't go
Hiratsuka
Wait
I'm hungry
Nakayama
One
Here it is
Matsuno
I took a new picture
Keep
Nakayama
Wait
Kakashi
One
Here it is
Matsuno
You are cute
Would you like to eat this fish with me
tonight?
One
I did it
You were trying to show the fish
Here it is
The first hero
One
The technique is good
Here it is
The hamburger with the new fish
One
Here it is
I did it
What are you doing?
Stop
One
Here it is
Please
The new fish is shining
Take one
It's over
The new fish is funny
We look forward to seeing the new fish
The mini-conert festival is over
What did the members think?
We did it
How was it?
Maybe the next hero will be born
Maybe
The hero who can beat you
Really?
Okatsu
I made a new legend
We started from the reflection
It's serious
Okatsu is serious
How was it?
We have a new hero
I want to draw
What?
What is it?
I saw it
Pass
Watch the VTR
The mini-conert festival with two new
characters
I look forward to the future
Next episode
New song special
New song information
What will happen to the big monster?
And the person who missed Ebichu Tastas
On the star dust channel of the school
video distribution site
Ebichu Tastas is being released
I'm not going
If you want to enjoy more like Nakayama
Ebichu Tastas is free of charge for 400
yen per month
There are also a lot of exclusive videos
that are not released
Search for the details on the star dust
channel
This program was provided by the sponsor
you see
This is good
I'm doing it
A big number
Thank you for your viewing