Ebichu no Douga Toka
【Ebichu no Douga Toka】
I'm Hoshino Mirei, a trainee at Lucky7
Tell me, Hoshino-sensei!
Yes, yes, yes
When are you going to study the roots?
Right now
So, today
I'll be teaching you
Let's write it down
In my easy-to-understand way
Like this?
I'd like to introduce you to peaches.
This is a peach.
Don't say you can't see it.
Yes, peaches are either roses or
peaches.
Oh, it's like a girl.
Wonderful.
There are three types of varieties,
white, white, and golden.
From abroad, China and Europe.
We import from Turkey and the US.
In Japan, the first place is Yamanashi
Prefecture.
The second place is Fukushima
The third place is Nagano Prefecture.
About 70% of the total population is
imported.
These three prefectures are the king of
peaches.
Let's write it down. It's like a class.
The first place is Yamanashi Prefecture.
The second place is Fukushima
Prefecture.
The third place is Nagano Prefecture.
The peaches are so cute.
The peach is so cute.
Please remember that.
The point is that it is cute.
And the season is now.
From early summer to summer.
So, please eat peaches now.
Choose delicious peaches.
Choose red peaches.
Why are my peaches symmetrical?
Did you follow the peach lesson?
Please remember.
Varacan Peach Tribe China. Yamanashi
Fukushima Nagano.
Please eat delicious food like this.
Bye bye.
Today, I would like to introduce my
favorite fruit.
Please guess what it is.
It's easy.
What is it? Is it shiny? It's shining.
Yes, what is it? The correct answer is
Shine Muscat!
Ah, it's Shine Muscat no matter how you
look at it.
Yes, so I really like Shine Muscat.
The reason I like it is because it's
eaten all over the river and it has a
taste even on the river.
It's so delicious that it's quite
expensive, but I'll put up with it and
buy it.
It is cote land
Shine Muscat is made by mixing Akitsu 21
and Hakunan.
Akitsu-san
I couldn't read this at first.
To explain it roughly, Akitsu-san is a
mixture of American and European grapes.
Hakunan is a mixture of European grapes.
Shine Muscat is the one that took it
well.
It's a hybrid grape.
It's easy to eat the whole skin.
And there are few seeds.
1st place is Nagano Prefecture.
2nd place is Yamanashi Prefecture.
These two prefectures are the second
strongest.
These two are the fruit empire.
You can eat it at room temperature, but
if you put it in the refrigerator 2-3
hours before and eat it cold, it will
pop in your mouth.
It's really delicious. I love it.
Did you get a little more information
about Shine Muscat?
I'll put it in the test, so remember it.
Bye bye.
It took 3 minutes for everyone to be
quiet.
What do you mean?
Are you serious about the class?
Let's switch.
I'm scared.
Today's fruit is...
See you next time.
Ta-da! This is it!
What is it?
No matter how you look at it, it's a
mango!
I could only write this.
Mango is
Mukurojime
Urushika
What are you saying?
Mu-ku-ro-ji
Mukurojimoku?
Urushika!
What is Mukurojimoku?
I thought it was a glaring eye, but it's
not.
It's a Urushika mango that came to me
and glared at me.
It's easy to remember!
The first mango I ate was the Pelican
mango, which is popular in Southeast
Asia.
I was surprised.
From there, I was also addicted to the
dry fruit mango.
The highest production in Japan is
Okinawa, and the second is Miyazaki.
I thought Miyazaki was the best, but
it's famous for its sunny eggs.
But Okinawa is the best.
Did you remember?
The season is May to August.
The best part of mango for me and my mom
is
the part where you eat the seed.
The seed is so delicious.
When I'm cutting it, I'm eating the seed
by myself.
It's so delicious.
So, like this, everyone.
Today, we talked about mango.
Did you learn about the Mukujiro
Urushika Mango tribe?
I'd like to end the lesson here.
Bye bye.
It's summer break.
The difference is how much you study in
summer break.
Let's do our best.
I'll write the fruit of the day.
I know this. I know this. I know this.
Strawberry!
Strawberry is a type of rose or other
plant and it belongs to the Dutch
strawberry family.
I have a big news for you!
The part where I eat the strawberry is
not a fruit!
It's surprising, isn't it?
It looks like a fruit but it's not.
It's shocking.
It's a flower.
There are many types of strawberries.
It's called Amao.
Beni-hoppe, Tochi-otome, Sachi-no-ka,
Saga-ho-no-ka.
These five varieties make up 80% of the
total in Japan.
Amao, Beni-hoppe, Tochi-otome, Sachi-no-
ka, Saga-ho-no-ka.
These five types have a total of 80% of
the votes.
Now, let's say it together!
Amao, Beni-hoppe, Tochi-otome, Sachi-no-
ka, Saga-ho-no-ka!
Yes!
Hmm? Did I say it right?
Well, never mind. I'm not trying to
mishear you.
I'm going to say it here. Please
remember it.
Where?
I'm going to say it here.
1st place is Tochigi.
2nd place is Fukuoka.
3rd place is Kumamoto.
I thought it was January to May.
I talked about strawberries today.
Did you listen to me?
I'm going to end the strawberry class.
Bye bye.
The basics are important for studying.
Let's solidify the basics and move on to
the next one.
Today's Tsuru-tsu is this.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Oh! I'm pretty good at this!
It's melon!
This is so easy to understand!
I feel like it's the easiest to
understand.
In terms of plant science, it's the same
as watermelons.
It's a cucumber plant.
It's a vegetable, right?
But what's normally distributed is...
It's distributed as a fruit.
It's usually a fruit.
Cucumber plant.
Everyone, did you remember?
It's a cucumber plant.
It's surprisingly vegetable-like, this
name.
It's a cucumber plant.
The variety is net type and netless.
And both of them have Prince Melon.
It seems that there is also a melon of
good place.
The season is from May to July.
It's a little late now.
But still.
I think it's probably in the
supermarket.
Please try it.
The production amount is.
Ibaraki is the first place.
The second place is Hokkaido.
I have a lot of melon images.
And third place is Kumamoto.
How to choose a delicious melon.
If you want it to be sweeter
you can choose the one shaped like a net
and you will save money
but there is an App for this time-
you want to buy it and try for yourself
than being in a yes hand with that kind
of mind to check the GTA
It's packed with meat and it's really
good.
How to eat delicious melon.
I wanted to eat it, so I put it in the
refrigerator about 3 to 5 hours before.
It's really cool and delicious when you
cut it and eat it.
And for adults, it's like a brandy with
raw ham.
It's a little mature.
Raw ham melon is really delicious.
Children can eat it with vanilla ice
cream.
I think the whole family can enjoy this
big melon.
Please try it with everyone.
That's it for the class.
Bye bye.
This is the last class today.
Thank you for watching.
I hope you all do your best and enjoy
the class.
I will draw the fruit I will introduce
today.
It's full of horns.
What is it?
The correct answer is lychee.
Where is the lychee?
I don't know.
Lychee is also that.
Mukurojika.
I got it. Mukurojika.
What kind of mukurojika was it?
It's mango. It's the same as mango.
Mukurojika.
And lychee has kanji.
Kusakaite.
Toto...
Kishi.
I imagined a shinomiya with a pair of
jeans.
It's a pair of jeans.
I remembered!
Everyone can write Raichi with this!
In Japan, the letter C is Kagoshima.
You can write it in a warm place.
Miyazaki.
Raichi is in the middle of May to early
August.
It's a last chance.
There is a type called Green Lychee.
It is said that it was sold under the
name of Hishishou because it was so
delicious that it made Chinese people
smile.
Hishishou.
I came here and I felt it a lot.
Did you remember?
Lychee is full of vitamin C.
Lychee is small.
4 Lychee is equivalent to 1 lemon.
Vitamin C has the effect of preventing
colds and skin diseases.
So especially on a sunny day, Lychee and
sugar,
If you eat 4 of them, you might be able
to recover the next day.
You don't see Lychee that often, do you?
If you see it, buy it, and freeze it, it
will last for a year.
Wonderful!
Thank you for listening to the class
until the end.
I introduced 6 of them this time.
Did you get to know more about fruit?
See you somewhere!
Bye bye!
To be continued.
It's time to go out.
I think you've learned a lot about
fruits in a week.
I think the questions I'm going to ask
you are very easy.
Let's get started.
These were the fruits that are popular
all over the country.
Question 1
What is Hoshina Mirei's favorite fruit?
This is easy. I told you.
What is your favorite season now?
I like all kinds of fruits.
I like seasonal fruits the most.
I like Shine Muscat the most.
The second question.
What kind of fruit is Milly not good at?
Do you know?
You don't know this.
I'm going to announce the correct
answer.
Do you have the answer?
Let's see the correct answer.
I have no idea.
Did I get it right?
I was talking with Ucchi.
Where did I eat it?
I ate durian.
I was told that it was very smelly.
I think I got it right.
I will challenge strange fruits.
Did I get it right?
You are all great.
You are my students.
Let's start the third question.
What is your favorite fruit?
This is...
What is it?
I haven't been able to answer this
question in the past week.
But I'm glad to have answered this
question.
So, everyone, is the answer correct?
I would like to announce the correct
answer.
The correct answer is...
Sakuranbo!
My grandmother's house is in Yamagata
and since I was little
I've been going to Sakuranbo hunting.
And at that time, it was a very
memorable time for me.
And this year,
I was able to get a present from
Yamagata Prefecture.
I'm so happy! Thank you! Thank you,
Grandma!
It's different!
The difference between buying it at a
supermarket and the one my grandma sends
me is the thickness of the meat.
The sweetness is also great.
When I was little, I often said I wanted
to fly seeds.
So I took the seeds and competed to see
how far I could fly.
The point is to put on the clothes and
do it.
Everyone, please remember.
Then I will continue.
Question 4
What fruit does Mirie want to grow?
This is a hint.
The hint is...
If it's this, I think I can grow it too.
That's the size.
Then I will announce the correct answer.
The correct answer is...
Blueberry!
I searched and found it.
It's easy.
It's sweet, but it's sour.
I don't think I'll notice if I fail.
I'll put it on ice cream and eat it.
I'll ask you the last question.
How many correct answers are there in
these four questions?
Last question.
I will give you 10 points for each
correct answer.
Please try your best.
You will never know the answer.
The fifth question.
What is the unknown fruit of the bush
nabire?
I have never eaten this fruit before.
I have eaten it, but I have never eaten
this fruit.
I have never eaten this fruit, but I
think I will never know the answer.
I think no one will know the answer.
I will give you a great hint.
This is the kind of fruit that has
appeared in the previous video.
Please think about it.
I have given you a great hint, so I will
announce the correct answer.
The correct answer is...
It's a strawberry called Tochihime.
I'm sure I haven't got it right.
I think the person who got it right is a
super smart.
It's a strawberry made of Tochigi, but
it's too soft.
It's also very sweet and delicious.
It's too soft to be shipped to the
market.
It's so soft and delicious that you
can't go to the strawberry market.
I'm sure I haven't got it right.
I couldn't go to the strawberry market
this year, so I'd like to go to Tochigi
next year.
How many questions have I answered so
far?
My favorite fruit is Chai Muscat.
And I don't like fruits that I'm not
good at.
I'm not good at fruits.
There were a lot of fruits, so I think I
can try it someday.
And the fruit of memories is cherry
blossoms. Thank you for always
remembering.
The fruit I want to see while growing up
is blueberry.
It looks easy.
And the fruit of unknown is princess
land.
Someday I will be a princess land.
It's a little strange.
I love fruit that I can't eat.
I want to be a fruit master.
I hope I can eat various things.
Thank you everyone.
It doesn't matter at all.
Please study fruit properly.
Bye bye.