Emi-cha!
You don't know the feeling of the season
when you are here
Yes, but it's spring
You are a junior high school student,
right?
Yes, I am
I want to eat crepes
In Jukuhara?
Yes, I want to go to Jukuhara
I want to go
But it's fine, right?
Professional junior high school students
are free
Really?
What are you doing?
I woke up at 10 o'clock
That's unfair
It's 10 o'clock
Just called DD, Aqua Park
I will be waiting for your job
Good
Staff came
Help
Choose the exclamation system that is
part of the lie that SOLAR created
Please leave a lie
We will cooperate and do our best.
We will leave two.
Cooperative.
Team play.
Ready, go.
It's impossible.
How was it?
Can you tell?
I don't know.
It's a group play.
It's not a group play.
I like this.
No one can do push-ups for you.
What does it mean?
I don't know.
My goal this year is inner muscle.
I feel my destiny.
I chose the real word.
Wow!
Amazing!
The next one is Jim Rohn, a successful
philosopher
Muscles are not a lie
I see
I was a genius
Emi-chan
Aya-chan
Yes
It's difficult
You don't use the word genius
So I can only write to someone who has
the power
That's right
The quote I chose is the real quote
Correct
Geete is the poet
There is no priority among shrimp,
right?
Is it about food?
I chose the head of the fish
The head of the fish
I'm stupid
I don't think it will change if I say it
I think this is possible
Horse?
The idea is amazing
I'm curious about this too
This is the most difficult
But it seems possible
Really?
People learn best by teaching
The quote I chose is the real quote
Nice
Ms. Seneka?
Seneka-san?
Seneka-san
What do you teach in Ebichu?
She teaches me a lot about Seto Ryo
During the live, she teaches me a lot
about Seto Ryo
She teaches me a lot about Shunji
She has a good initiative
Initiative?
Yes, initiative
I'm curious
Before I go to bed, I'm like, wow
But I don't have to think about it
The quote I chose is the truth
The truth!
Is Colin Powell a politician?
You know this right?
I know it very well
I'm often told I'm a political figure
You don't have to worry so much
It's true when you go to the hospital
What did you do in the hospital?
I was a politician
Konnichiwa
OK, the second round
What should I do?
I think everything is real after the
first round
I have to say where it's truly normal
Do ordinary people do that too?
Yasumoto and Izumo
Places for其 ounces
Maybe a small town
Because others are using it
The quote I chose is the real quote.
Correct!
Wow, it's Ichiro-san, the major leaguer
Oh, I didn't know that
Wow
That's the sound effect
Wow, it's Ichiro-san
I'm glad
I didn't know that
Everything is awesome, it might be real
The third one is Ai-chan
I'll go with this one
Wait, isn't there a more safe one?
Safe one?
I'll go with this one
I'm not designing clothes, I'm designing
dreams
It's cool to read like this
I want to say something like this
This quote is the real one
Wow
Thank you!
I'm Ralph Lauren, a fashion designer
I'm a brand
What kind of dream do you have?
What kind of design?
I want to go to the island of red and
white
You are serious
I'm thinking if I can make it or not
It's hard to make a dream come true
You are going to be a celebrity
I didn't understand what you said
If you think if you can make it or not
It's hard to make a dream come true
Shibuya Yasumoto
No laughter, no one understands, no
response
That was the worst
Hello
Are we good at this?
We are stupid, so we are not good at
this
Really
I'm curious about this
This is hard
I think there is a time
Time is
The quote I chose is the real quote
So cute!
I knew it!
Alexandra Vinesa, a private scholar
No, no, no
What is a private scholar?
A private scholar
I see
Do you do anything to improve yourself?
To shorten the time
To work hard
To work hard for what?
I don't know, what am I working hard
for?
Maybe I'm not working hard
I don't know
This is the last one
You can't be so relaxed
I'm scared, this is the last one
This is the last one
Did you get it?
It says speed
It's fast
If you ride it, you can go forward
without looking at anything
You don't look around
Yes
You don't look around, you can go
forward
You don't think about unnecessary things
The answer is the real one
I'm sorry!
By the way, this quote is from Charles
Schilt, the creator of the cartoon
Snoopy.
There were many quotes, but did you
learn them?
Yes, we did.
Let's keep looking up.
That's right.
I'm so happy.
That's the secret of life.
That was a good switch.