Please subscribe to my channel!
On January 30th, the Korean version of
SKI will be released.
What does that mean?
On January 30th, the Korean version of
SKI will be released.
That's what it means.
Look, my phone is blue.
Why?
Is it your favorite color?
No, it's not.
It's my parents' cell phone.
My cell phone is broken.
It's just broken.
I'm sorry.
I can't reach it.
It's always got an Apple mark.
I can't react to anything.
My mom's cell phone is 14+.
I made it blue.
I chose it.
That's good.
You're conscious.
I made my cell phone blue, too.
I made it blue this time.
If you keep using it,
you'll be able to use it.
Please make your cell phone blue.
It's cute.
Look at this.
I made a video.
Thank you for watching.
It's a shower ring.
It's a gacha-gacha.
I hold it like this.
It's a shower ring.
It's cute.
I can use it because I'm pure.
Really?
I left it to you.
I'll do it.
Just follow the direction.
I can't see it.
I'm a photographer.
I'm getting a little thicker.
I'm working on it.
It's good.
Is it good?
I'm nervous.
I'm a camera girl.
No, you're disqualified.
I can only see your head.
No way.
It's heavy.
How much do you weigh?
8kg.
I don't know.
I'm a camera girl.
Cute!
I'll put it inside.
Look at this!
Please subscribe to my channel!
It's cute!
I want to decorate my room with this.
Let's go to the real show.
It's all together!
This time, we'll do the Sezyo badly.
Orinato
It's been a while since I danced in a
costume.
I'm nervous.
I love this costume so much.
I'm so nervous.
I'm nervous.
Thank you for watching.
The winter wind is so cold
All I could remember was your warmth
At last, there's nothing left for us.
To rememberかな…
It reminded me of Fukui.
It was like a costumeджacat version of
the live show.
See you next time!
I'm going to take a picture with you.
I want to ride a swing with you.
I don't want to.
Can you ride a swing?
You can hold my head and say,
It's fun!
We can also ride a slide together.
I can do it alone.
You can do it alone.
You can say,
It's fun!
You're so cute.
I'll take a picture from a distance.
Apply now to open the door
Hello everyone.
Hello.
Today, we are going to show you the
behind-the-scenes of our Japanese radio
program.
Isn't it the first time?
It's the second time.
We will show you how we usually record
our radio program on the 4th day.
Please watch it.
Thank you.
It's the 4th day of recording.
We're recording.
It's a little simple.
I'm going to do it.
I'm Haruka Koizumi, a super pink Haruka.
I'm Hiyorin, a super green Hiyorin. I'm
Hiyori Yoshikawa.
I'm Kanamin, a super blue Kanamin. I'm
Kanami Chishono.
I checked the microphone.
This is the 304th broadcast.
Yes, please.
The new song is coming out soon!
FM924, AM1122, Radio Nippon
Halei Tokidoki Super Exciting Promotion
Club!
Good evening, everyone.
Saturday at 1am,
what do you think?
What do you think?
Halei Tokidoki Super Exciting Promotion
Club!
Today's Halei Toki MC is Kojimi Haruka
from Super Exciting Pink.
Who are the members we'll be sending off
today?
Yes, I'm Kanamin from Super Exciting
Blue, also known as Tuji.
I'm Pink from Super Exciting Pink.
Pink?
The song is pink, though.
The song is pink, so it's a song.
Wow.
We've been doing this for 8 years.
You wanted to be pink, didn't you?
Yeah, I don't know if it's because I'm
saying this after a long time.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
Let's get back on track.
I'm Hiori Yoshikawa from Super Exciting
Green.
So, we'll be sending off these three
this week.
So, everyone, the camera is rolling,
isn't it?
That's right.
I think it's been a while.
I think it was taken because it said
pink on the script.
Maybe that's it.
It was a little short, wasn't it?
It was a little short.
I'm Hiori Yoshikawa from Super Exciting
Green.
So, the reason why I'm turning the
camera around in this recording is
because I'm turning the camera around
for YouTube.
It's a little spoiler.
Tokibaro.
I think YouTube will be uploaded later,
so please take a look.
I'm in the fourth day of the shoot.
That's amazing.
Is it the first time when it's sunny or
when it's cloudy?
I don't know which one.
Which one is it?
What day is it today?
Today is the second day.
That's right.
Which one is it?
So, if it's this week, it's the first
time when it's sunny.
Then it's a spoiler.
From YouTube.
Let's make it a spoiler.
I'm sure it's all cut out in the good
parts.
Edit.
YouTube.
So, please check out YouTube.
It was very cold this week.
It was so cold.
It was extremely cold.
And the wind was so strong that I
thought my house would be blown away.
Really.
It was so cold.
I thought my house would be blown away
like three little pigs.
I checked if the window was open.
It was closed.
Is there anyone who can't sleep because
of the wind?
I'm fine.
Then, Haru, are you okay?
Everyone is sleeping.
I think so, but I can sleep.
I see.
It's cold, everyone.
I was surprised to see the bathroom
today.
I washed it before I went to bed because
I wanted to go to bed.
Then, the edge of the bath sponge was
frozen.
What?
I think the water was too cold and it
was frozen.
I thought it was a little crispy.
It was frozen.
It was so cold.
I thought it was cold.
I took a walk there.
If it was raining, it might have snowed.
That's right.
There are places where it's snowing.
That's amazing.
I didn't know that.
Did you see it?
I saw it in the morning.
It was raining.
It was snowing.
It was snowing in Kyoto.
Everyone, be careful not to catch a
cold.
Please be careful.
It says that the three of us will have a
lot of talk.
Adults.
Adults are the image of growing up.
Everyone is over 20 years old.
That's right.
You're an adult.
Five months later.
I'm 24 years old.
You're an adult.
What will you do when you turn 24?
What should I do?
What will you do?
Open car?
That's cool.
I want to drive.
I want to drive in a proper facility.
Not a normal road.
I want to experience it.
That's amazing.
24 is amazing.
I will be that age.
Everyone will come at any time.
And February 3rd is the year of the
rooster.
The year of the rooster is a little
south of the south pole.
It's a little hard to understand.
Do you have a reservation for the year
of the rooster?
I'm going to spread it at home.
Do you have a reservation?
I have a reservation.
I see.
I've never done it.
I'm going to sell it on the day.
It's pretty good.
It's a good deal.
I see.
Ehodol is also famous recently.
It's a sushi cake.
I want to eat seafood Eho roll.
I agree.
I want to eat a little good thing.
I think there was a year of the south
pole.
I've heard of it.
I'm sure I've eaten Eho roll in the
south pole.
I'm confident.
You can eat it.
I remember eating Eho roll around my
house.
I thought I would go around the south
pole every year.
Does the location change depending on
the year?
How do you decide?
Who decides?
Is it a person in the Eho roll industry?
I think it's decided by the year.
What season is it?
It may be the year of the year.
It's like the Olympics.
The south pole is west.
What?
East, in, out...
What's an east pole and a long pole?
Where's the pole?
East...
That's the northeast poles.
Let's stop.
It's northeast, eastern and eastern.
East che tookiemhi.
The year is this.
It might be a picture book of the North
Atlantic War.
It might be.
And I'm writing down a memo.
Julia, the stage is now.
Now.
So, Osaka is now.
Go for it, Julia!
Go for it, Aki!
Go for it, Yukino!
Go for it, Yukino Honjo!
It's a cold season, but what kind of
sweets do you want to eat at this time
of year?
Sweets...
In winter, I want to eat strawberries.
Strawberries and mandarin oranges.
Oh, mandarins.
I haven't eaten mandarins.
I haven't eaten them.
I had a box at home.
Wow!
And then I had a big mandarin.
Like this?
Like a swimming pool?
I ate a lot.
I ate a lot of mandarins.
It's good.
Maybe it's because it's yellow.
It's yellow.
It's a food of the royal family.
Like daifuku.
Like oshiruko.
I want to eat sweet sake.
I want to eat.
Please warm up and eat warm food.
I had a taco party the other day.
Is that okay?
I had a taco party with my family.
That's nice.
I want to have a taco party with a
bonjour.
I want to have a barbecue party.
That's nice.
I gave Julia a taco party set as a
birthday present.
You gave it to me, didn't you?
I used it with my friends once.
I did it in the room in the winter.
I bought clothes in the room.
Clothes?
I bought a hanger rack.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm out of my pace.
I can smell it.
The opening talk is endless.
I'm going to see the first song of the
night.
Please listen to it.
It's love.
I like this. It has a timer.
I don't know what I'm talking about.
The opening talk was 12 minutes.
How long have you been cut?
Manga!
But the opening...
I was told I could talk for 20 minutes.
Yes, yes, yes. If you don't talk for a
long time...
It was short!
It was short, wasn't it?
I got a lot of letters.
In small letters.
I've already announced it.
I'll try.
Let me make it.
I have a question.
I'll do it.
Which one is better?
I'll do it first.
Yes.
I'll do it.
FM924 AM112 Radio Nippon Hale Toki Toki
Super Exciting Promotion Club
Oharu, Kanamin, Yurin
From here, we will introduce the e-mails
we received from these members.
It's a good time.
It's true. It's written here.
This time
Yes, so I would like to read it
immediately.
Yes
Then, from Koizumi-san, the name of the
sunny time
Oh, Koizumi-san
Nice to meet you
I received an e-mail from Koizumi-san,
who lives in Tokyo.
Oharu-san, Kanamin-san, Hiyori-san, good
evening!
Good evening!
I always listen to it with fun.
I live in Saitama.
I am 22 years old.
Oh!
I often remember Tokisen's Oharu.
The same name
Yes
I'm into muscle training recently.
Oh!
So, I have something to ask Kanamin and
Hiyori.
Oh! What is it?
February has Valentine's Day, but are
you two planning to have a party?
Please tell me!
Well,
Then, please tell me about your body.
There is something.
Well, I'm careful about various things
at the end.
Yes, we are also worried.
Oh, you are worried.
I want to make a Valentine's Day.
Yes, but we are talking about making it
now.
Yes, yes, yes.
The date is decided.
Yes, I'm deciding the date now.
Kanamin and I contacted me saying that
the date is open.
We couldn't meet.
Hahaha
The days when we are open are not the
same.
Yes, that's right.
But I definitely want to do it.
Do you have a revenge?
Basque cheesecake.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Hahaha
It's not delicious.
It's sometimes on TikTok.
It's bad.
Hahaha
That's a failure.
The more I say it's a failure, the worse
it is.
Kanamin's YouTube is posted on Anson.
Yes, yes, yes.
When I make sweets with Piyo, I always
fail.
But it's delicious.
It's delicious to eat.
It's delicious because it's a habit if
you eat it.
I really can't eat it.
Is that so?
What?
Stop it.
I don't want you to bring it as a prank.
It's good.
I tried to eat it.
I wonder what kind of reaction the
members will have.
It's delicious.
I wonder if they'll react.
Be careful. It's delicious.
It was fun.
I should have brought it.
Don't do that to Aki-chan.
I hope you don't do that.
Aki-chan will definitely be careful.
It's really delicious.
Hahaha
I don't have that kind of feeling.
It's a new feeling.
I don't know what to say.
I can't say that.
I'm sorry.
So, at this Valentine's party, we have a
goal of making successful sweets.
I'll do it.
I'll do it in the second half of
February or the first half of February.
That's good.
Is there any recipe you want to make?
I want to make cookies.
Cookies are easy.
Icing?
It's okay.
You mean cookie cutter?
Yes.
You can change the color.
You can shape it in a milk carton.
You can make a square or a triangle.
You can make a round shape.
You can make a heart shape.
I want to make a cute display.
You mean a cookie can?
Yes.
You can make a set of various shapes.
It's cute.
You can make a cake.
That's good.
I don't think I can make cookies.
If I fail, I'll be in trouble.
You'd better not to make cookies.
I'm not good at making cookies.
Cookies are easy.
I want to make more.
You can make cute cookies.
You can make a display.
You can make a chocolate cake.
I want to make a chocolate cake.
I want to try something difficult.
I want to do it.
I want to make something difficult.
I found a way to make a fluffy and
delicious chiffon cake.
But if you fail to make a chiffon cake,
it will be difficult to make it.
I want to try something difficult.
We can do it.
Yes.
It's good to succeed, but it's also fun
to fail.
I want to make a good chiffon cake next
time.
Please look forward to the Valentine's
Day of Kanapio.
The live photo is also on sale now, so
please check it out.
Please send me an email.
I will send you an email.
I, Haruka Koizumi, will appear on the
show called Nagano's movie is a movie
with Nagano, a comedian.
The show is on air from 20.30 on
Wednesdays.
Please listen to the talk with Nagano.
See you next week.
I'm Haruka Koizumi.
I'm Kanami Tsujino.
I'm Hiyori Yoshikawa.
We are Kimi no Heart.
We are CHO!
We are TOKIMEKI CHANNEL.
Bye bye.
Please watch our YouTube channel.
Good night.
Thank you very much.
The first performance is over.
It's over.
We always record like this.
Yes.
How was it?
I was relaxed.
It was fun.
Thank you very much.
We will do our best in the second one.
I'm looking forward to it.
Well, everyone, goodbye.
See you later.
Hello, everyone.
Good evening.
Are you watching?
We just recorded a program for Radio
Nippon.
And we are covering this program now.
So, between those two.
Like this.
We're doing it like this.
So, every Saturday from 25 o'clock, we
are broadcasting the commercial program
of Super Tokimeki Advertising Club,
Hale! Tokidoki! Super Tokimeki
Advertising Club.
Thank you for your emails and comments.
If you haven't sent it yet, please send
it to us.
Please send it to us.
Please listen to the radio.
I wonder why, when I smile, it's as if
the world is shining
I can turn my umbrella around and be at
ease
If I don't, I can't walk
I'm sure someone is crying somewhere
I wonder if I'll get wet and cold
somewhere again
I'm sure someone is crying somewhere
I want to share just a little bit of my
feelings with you
There's still a view I've never seen
before
So let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye
Thank you for yesterday
The city after the rain is colored
On the canvas of my damaged heart
I draw fragments of the future
I encounter with you
Now is the night, and the reason for my
tears
When I'm lost, I remember right away
Even if it rains, I'll smile
Look, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights up after the rain
My heart is like a sunny day, the sound
of the rain drops
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights up after the rain
My heart is like a sunny day, the sound
of the rain drops
I wear a rainbow dress
Please subscribe to my channel!