This week's Ebichu Tastasu is a 100th
episode special!
A bowling match with super high quality
items!
And then...
Oh, it's beautiful!
It's beautiful!
The battle is more intense than expected
And for some reason, a mysterious dance
battle has started?
What is it?
Emichu Tastasu 100th Battle Start!
I'm so into you.
What should I do with my heart?
Moratorium, moratorium, moratorium,
middle school students.
Add various things to private Ebisu
middle school.
Middle school students.
Ebisu middle school.
That is Cuckoo band
Yes,right now,i got it
Please subscribe our channel
I'll be watching.
Whoooo this is...
HOT
She's proning to it
O zabag
Open the lid
The members are gathered in a certain
room
What is it?
Today, Nichi-choco is really...
She has a serious mic
Who is Nichi-choco?
It's a karaoke shop
Do you do karaoke?
There are so many people
What do you do?
This Maga Magic
There's no Takie-san
What's this music?
Suddenly
Make the movement
Thank you very much!
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Sorry, I'm not doing this.
It's quite lively today.
What's going on?
It's lively, isn't it?
Can you guess what this is?
Why do you think it is?
Are we turning 38?
We're turning 38.
No, no, no.
This one, please.
What does it mean?
Look at this!
Look!
What does it say?
We are 100% live!
Yeah!
Mic! Mic!
Go!
Since the start of the 2015 broadcast,
thanks to everyone's support, we are
finally able to have 100 broadcasts!
So we have a special project!
The 100 battle special for the luxury
goods!
We will play 3 games that are related to
the 100.
The winners of each game will be able to
challenge a game that has a luxury
product.
That's a bit of a nuisance.
The game is this!
Ta-da!
Darts!
You've seen this before, right?
The board that appeared is a board with
a luxury product that you've seen
somewhere.
It looks like there are a lot of darts.
From popular ramen, to luxury brand
beef, to fruits and sweets,
to gourmet products,
to the products that some members of the
Tetsudo Museum would want.
And also, the gag that will decide if
you win or lose,
and the most surprising product that the
program has prepared.
Please look closely.
It's really 100,000 yen!
Wait a minute!
I'm not looking!
I'm not going to keep paying for this
program!
Could it be that he'll get 1 million
yen?
The members are getting excited, and the
first battle is...
The bowling battle to see who gets 100
points!
So, it's bowling, do you all play
bowling?
We all play
You all play?
Yes, with the staff
Nakayama, do you know what bowling is?
I know, I just do this
To celebrate 100 times, the first member
to score 100 points in bowling
Will get the chance to try darts
Who is the member with the advantage in
this game?
Who is the best?
Hinata
I was a bit low
How many points?
How many?
I don't remember the score, but I think
it's 100
I think it's 100
I think it's possible to score 100
Really?
If you don't score 100, the member in
the top will win
So, do your best to score 100
Yes
Let's start with Mayama
Mayama, how many points did you score
last time?
I don't remember the last time, but I
had bowling in high school
In class?
Yes, in class
That's really good
The highest score was 36
That's a good score
Are you ready?
Yes
Please give us a high score
You won!
You are a woman in her 30s!
Aku-chan is different.
And now, onto the next situation
You're good!
You're making it exciting!
Next is Yasumoto!
By the way, how many times do you fall
before?
I don't know, but...
Everyone remembers, right?
But when I'm in a good mood, I fall 3
times a day.
Then you can get some expectations.
It's a good mood day.
Please show us!
Good mood!
You're good!
You're a good-tempered person.
I was wondering which one of us would
fall next.
Yasumoto's second attempt!
YES
Looking at the way you threw it, it
reminded me of a grandma who grows
vegetables.
Hirota, you did well.
This excitement with just 7 balls is
good.
Next is Hirota's throw.
This is my third time today.
It's your third time in your life.
So, I'll do it with my spirit.
Let's go with your spirit.
Hirota.
I was surprised.
It's not a rival pin.
I'm sorry.
I always hit the back of the head.
Do you always do this?
This is a promise.
My arm hurts.
She is back to the game.
Go.
Great.
She broke Ayaka's record.
Next is Hoshina
Please
Wow!
Amazing!
The difficult situation, what will
happen?
But it's a Nahaon
Hoshina got a spare with a super shot
Matsuno is also looking forward to it
It's a good flow
I'll do my best
If you go around more and more
Is it here?
Matsuno
Matsuno distributing the materials
Imagine a fox
Aim for the middle of the line
Aim for the middle
But if you knock it down, it's cool
I don't want to do it
I'm not laughing
You're not laughing?
You're not saying something that funny
I'm not laughing
Get on
Good luck
Go go go
Game over!
This program is interesting
What?
I'm getting excited
The second throw is
Too bad
And the real Kashiwagi's turn
I'll strike
I can get it
From there
It's a great distance
Amazing
It's like a women's soccer
It's a clear shot
You are good!
Next is Kobayashi
Scary! Scary!
It's not scary!
Kobayashi's second throw is a little
regretful.
Kobayashi's third throw is a little
And the first one to cry
What's wrong?
It's like a golf
I see
I'm sorry
That was close
Please subscribe to our channel!
Good luck!
Oh, it's beautiful!
It's beautiful!
Thank you!
Herrmann Audio Inc.
Our pleasure!
Bye bye!
You're the one who's close.
Rina-chan, come back.
In the middle of the game,
Kashiwagi's new strike
has made Hoshinao run to the top.
Was it the strike that stimulated her?
Here, the other members are also getting
excited.
The second pitch from Gutter.
Go!
Hey!
Woo woo!
Rio you are fast!
Wow, Amazing!
You should have done it together
Next is Maya
You can do it
And then...
Oh, wow!
That's good!
Wow!
That's great!
That was good!
So far, Hoshina is the top.
She's the highest so far.
But Matsuno and Kashiwagi are chasing
her.
We don't know yet.
Matsuno is the first spare?
Yes, yes, yes.
Really?
You like bowling, right?
I can only say that.
Yay!
Meanwhile, Yasumoto is still in the
middle of the game.
Huh?
He's slow.
Wow.
Come on, come on, come on!
Ah, ah, ah.
He's a man who's perfect at baseball.
Come on, come on, come on!
Next is Hirota.
Has Yasumoto's voice reached him?
This is a high pitch.
Oh, he's going, he's going!
He's going!
Oh!
Yay!
Thank you for watching!
It's out!
Now we don't know what's going to happen
The end of the game, the bowling battle
From here, one mistake can decide the
winner
The most nervous moment
What's wrong with everyone?
However, there's a big problem
Let's go. Can he get a spare here?
Huh?
Did he get it?
He got it!
Thank you for watching!
What a spectacular spear!
And now, Matsuno is in 3rd place,
chasing Kashiwagi.
Oh, that's nice!
That's nice!
Go, go!
He's going for it!
That's nice!
Matsuno attacked Kashiwagi with a gun.
He missed a pin.
Wait, wait, wait!
Rina got a strike and it's my turn now
The machine was too kind and it got the
wrong idea
She should have left one pin, but the
machine's malfunction caused a strike
Is this allowed?
To be continued
It's a 100th anniversary, so strike!
Congratulations!
This is a game of losing and winning
It's going to fall
It went in!
It's a miracle!
Congratulations!
I'm getting excited!
Finally, in the 9th frame, Kashiwagi
beats Hoshina Shui.
And Matsuno, who struck a strike, has a
high possibility of turning the tables.
Finally, the final frame of fate!
If you get a strike, you might get 100
points.
This is a scene where you definitely
want to get a strike.
About to do it.
The battles begin with the Fall
Yasumoto, Hiroha, and Nakayama are
finishing without getting a perfect
score.
You're fast!
You're fast, Nagisa!
I love you!
Mayama is the last one.
Isn't that good?
What?
Good luck!
A strike that pays off!
Kobayashi, who was in a row, is finally
getting better.
But it's too late.
To be continued.
Why did you say hi-touch with only 9
pieces of Kobayashi?
The battle for the victory is between
these two.
Who will win?
Hoshina, you have 100 points.
I have.
I'm scared.
She broke the 100 points with turkey.
If she breaks the 7 pieces, she will be
the winner.
What will happen?
She finished with 85 points.
She danced alone.
I'm counting on you.
If you beat 2 pins, you'll get the top
of the game.
If you beat 9 pins, you'll get a big
chance to get 100 points.
Let's see.
Let's go.
3, 4, 5...
Wait, I went too far.
Come here!
I don't know anymore
The one who can't beat 3 pins is the
winner
Where is the winner?
If she can beat 4 pins, she wins
The result is?
How is it?
She did it!
Thank you for watching!
And so, the final result is Kashiwagi
who won the battle
But he didn't get 100 points
We said this at the start
It's a 100 points celebration
Who gets 100 points first
Do an impersonation of 12 points
Then you get 100 points
Then it's better if there's not that
many points
Then, please do an impersonation of 12
points
3 seconds ago, 2, 1, go!
Sunshine, Kashiwagi
Thank you very much
It's a little...
It's a little over 48 points
Since he got 100 points, he'll challenge
the darts that Kashiwagi put on
What are we aiming for?
High-class, brand (?) beef
Our number 1 star
Brother!
I bought it!
Thank you for watching!
Next, we'll enter the second round of
the 100th battle!
Who will obtain the luxurious prize?
100 sec count-free battle
Not only a승count a everyone
but there is the game how many count can
you obtain in 100 sec
You really can use you arms
with arms and legs
Incidentally Ms Kobayashi
You just舉na the quiz
This is the revenge
Good luck
Let's start the 100-second freestyle
battle.
Ready, start!
Please smile.
That's good.
It's like a national festival.
It's a bit chaotic, but the atmosphere
is great.
Everyone, 30 seconds have passed.
There are still 70 seconds left.
Yasumoto-san is being cursed.
Yasumoto-san regrets what he did to his
feet.
He's like a customer who came to see a
rock band.
He's like a man who's desperately trying
to dance because he's bitten by a snake.
He's trying to dance, but he's sleeping.
But his hands are still moving.
3, 2, 1, time's up!
Stop!
You can't move from there
100 seconds is too long
Is it?
Kashiwagi-san, please contact the
headquarter
Please contact the headquarter
Kashiwagi-san, your hair volume has
increased
Don't do that
Let's check the result
And Mazo-san, 137
Nakayama-san, 185
And Hoshina-san, 240
It looked easy but it was actually hard
And the result of the previous two is
the same
How about the volume up?
Hoshina is the best so far
Will she get a revenge?
Hoshina is the best
Asumoto, 233
So close
7 more
You can't do it anymore
Hoshina is the winner of the second
round
The girls challenge on the
special{\fad{\i12200kmhr wraps&d контрol
slttrtrtrtrtrtrtrtrtrtrtrtrtrtrtrtrtrtrt
rtrtrtrtrtrtrtrtrtrtrtrtrtrtrtrtrtrtrtrt
r
Where are you aiming?
Let's have a party with fruits!
Everyone will be happy!
Now, Hoshina, what is her fate?
It was close!
She was slightly off from 1 million yen
The result is a draw
Why are you guys looking at me?
Let's move on to the next game!
Next time, it's the 100th episode
special, the second half!
Super high tension karaoke battle!
The final episode of the 100th episode!
This program was brought to you by these
sponsors.