Ebichu's video
Good morning
I'm going to bring my jacket
The second day of the first day has been
postponed
Today is the first day in a realistic
way
I'm glad that the first day was
celebrated with 9 people
I want to do what I should do and do my
best to challenge the live show
I said something like a school
I want to do my best because it's a live
show with a lot of volume
I want to do my best
200 yen
Good morning
I will start the live show
It's cold in Niigata.
I was right to wear a knit sweater.
I'm glad.
I think it was a gift from God to
welcome me with nine people.
It's my first spring tour with nine
people.
I want to make this member feel good
until the end.
It's an important first day.
I will enjoy the time I couldn't do the
other day.
Niigata.
Do you like my bangs?
I'm going to put it in front of you for
the first time.
Thank you for your hard work.
This is Nonoka's impression. She is
popular among the senior members.
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute. This person is doing it.
She is cute.
Nonoka is cute.
This is the first time to tour the
Tenshi Anime City Tour 2020.
TuTamaIn 대박アニメラ wherever you are, do you
want to de?
強 counselors tension
Natakata
misnames
fire
ana
This is the end of our rehearsal.
I'm eating Hegi soba.
I love eating the same food as my
parents.
I'm grateful.
It's really delicious.
I'm looking forward to the tour.
I'm nervous.
It's been a long time since I've been on
a tour.
I'm glad you're here.
I want you to enjoy it.
I'm too nervous because I want to do my
best.
I want to tell you my memories.
I want you to feel good.
I want you to share that feeling with
me.
I'm eating Hegi soba.
It's delicious.
Thank you.
I named her.
This is my little finger.
This is Eguchi.
This is the nail art of Light Green.
I'm Eguchi.
I'm a little embarrassed.
This is my Eguchi.
I'll do my best.
Where are we?
NINJA GAR!
B or H?
Finally!
NINJA GAR!
Thank you.
We have finished supporting HAYUGATA!
How was your first time in Niigata?
How was it?
I think there were many people who came
from Tokyo,
but there were also people who came from
Niigata,
and there were also people who saw the
first 9 members.
How was it?
We also had some new songs from our new
album.
How was the arrangement?
I'm curious.
There are many songs that we want
everyone to dance together.
We will also do various songs through
the upcoming tour.
We might do various things.
We might do it.
Please look forward to the performance.
We can't go.
There are many people, so please come to
the tour.
I was nervous.
We did it once before the tour, so we
did it twice.
It was like a two-time concert.
It's different from having people.
It was fun.
There was a lot of adrenaline.
It's good that we were able to do it in
9 members.
It's good.
It's a food tour, isn't it?
The food was Niigata soba, strawberries,
and popo-yaki.
Did you eat popo-yaki?
I ate it too.
It was very delicious.
We want to go to the food tour.
The completion rate of each park is
increasing.
At the end, we will do our best to
finish it.
Next is the 5th day of Osaka.
It's our 10th anniversary.
Our 10th anniversary of our major debut.
We will do our best.
The next day, the 5th day of Osaka.
It's our 10th anniversary of our major
debut.
We will make fun memories every day from
now on.
The members are getting ready for the
concert.
We will do our best.
Wow!
This is the second part of the food
tour!
So, what I'm going to eat today is...
I already opened it.
It's a gyoza.
There was also a pork bun.
They said the pork bun was good, so I'm
going to eat the gyoza.
Itadakimasu.
It's delicious. The skin is chewy.
I think it's good to eat before the live
show.
The garlic and garlic are like, yeah!
Is it okay?
It's really delicious, but it's a little
small, so I can eat it quickly.
Yay! I ate it.
Shake, shake, shake, shake.
I'm not good at shaking my neck.
Shake, shake, shake, shake, shake.
Oh, it was really hard.
This is ice cream.
This is...
This is probably not the right time.
It wasn't the time to drink.
I'm not in the mood.
Alright!
We did our best!
Let's go!
Rei Kaoru with combined power
It's a macaroni.
It's a member color macaroni.
It's amazing.
Congratulations on your first
anniversary.
Congratulations.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
We will announce the 10 items released
this year to celebrate our 10th
anniversary!
It's cute, so look at it.
It's really cute.
Look at it.
Komatsu, look at the T-shirt.
We have celebrated our first
anniversary!
Thank you.
We had a great time.
How was Osaka today?
There were a lot of people who
celebrated our 10th anniversary.
It was very exciting.
There were a lot of people who
celebrated our 10th anniversary.
I was happy.
I'm really happy that we were able to
celebrate our 10th anniversary.
Riko-chan wasn't here today, but she's
here.
She's not going to be a member of the
group.
We will support them.
We have to work harder.
We still have a lot of time.
We will work harder.