Ebichu's videos
I'm Kashiwagi Nata, number 10.
I'm going to answer your questions.
Ready, go!
I like keyaki gyudon and hayashi rice.
My qualifications?
My qualifications...
I don't know.
I want to do a kanji test.
I see.
I used to play Rubik's cube a lot when I
was in elementary school.
I liked it.
I played it for 2 to 3 hours a week.
I can be an idol with this.
I don't care what it is.
The important thing is to enjoy it.
Don't forget to smile.
I wanted to get a driver's license, so I
thought I'd go, but I haven't gone yet.
I'm going.
What?
Yes?
Basically, I'm called A-chan.
I have the most A-chan.
What about women's clothes?
There's no basic.
I want to give it to you, but there's no
basic.
I love accessories like this.
That's all.
Yes.
Well...
Good... Good love...
But I want to use my voice to narrate.
I want to do the shadow narration
myself.
Yes, I want to do it.
I haven't done any impersonations
recently.
I'm not good at it.
I'll practice if I have a song I want to
do.
Please give me a song.
I'm waiting for you.
Club activities?
Club activities...
I wanted to join a dance club.
It was tough, but I want to join a dance
club.
Why?
I have an image.
I'm sure I'm the one who's in the middle
of everyone.
I'm sure I won't dye it.
I have a fixed concept.
I wanted to break that.
I wanted to change myself during the
self-restraint.
That's how it turned out.
Iwase Yuki has something in common.
I think we have about 20 to 30 things in
common.
I'm glad I continued my studies.
I think I'm a grown-up because I have a
good environment.
Thank you for your support.
What I collect?
What I collect is...
Oh, I just realized...
This...
This T-shirt is...
It's a punishment game for the
instrument player.
I have a grandma T-shirt, too.
I've collected Matsumoto-san and Hamada-
san's T-shirts.
I'd like to collect Tanaka-san, Endo-
san, and Tsukide Hozen-san's T-shirts,
too.
I think it's the cutest.
Smiles are important.
This is embarrassing.
Cosmogaze...
Ali?
What is it?
The End
I don't know. I don't know the words of
JK.
I don't know. There are a lot of bad
things. I'm sorry.
What is your dream as a shrimp? My dream
as a shrimp is to be a second grade
student forever.
I want to be in a history textbook. I
want to be in a history textbook and be
in a group called Shisei Bishuu.
My personal dream?
I want to have a ceremony.
I'll do my best.
Basically, it's rice.
But I've been into naan bread recently.
Naan bread is delicious.
I want to be in a history textbook.
I love radish. I eat it every day.
Big failure?
I'm often thought to be able to do it,
but I'm making a lot of mistakes.
Big mistake?
Recently, I shaved my eyebrows because I
thought I'd get a pimple on my forehead.
This is a mistake.
I made a lot of mistakes, but it was
okay.
What if I fall asleep?
I'll try not to sleep.
For the time being, I'll move my face.
The muscles in the face are important.
I can't give up this.
I can't do this.
What is it?
I'm a little strong, but I'm going to be
a performer.
I guess it's my feeling.
It's decided.
Can I do it? Repertory?
I haven't increased it.
I can't increase my repertoire.
I can't increase it.
What should I do?
It hasn't changed since I was a kid.
I wonder if I'm always laughing like
this.
I'm laughing.
I'm laughing recently.
I think I'm getting more and more adult-
like when I'm over 20.
I feel that.
I don't know.
I remember the song, Utae Odore Ebidada.
It was in 2012.
I don't know why I couldn't remember the
choreography of Ebidada.
I cried a lot on the way home.
I remember it very well.
I want to work at a BBQ restaurant.
What I want to sing the most now is...
How should I say this?
If I were to sing Ebichu...
I want to sing Hot Up and have fun!
My parents always tell me that...
I'm a parent myself, and I think that
I'm a parent myself when I'm on stage.
I want to continue doing this.
I'll do my best.
Thank you, always.
What do you think of me?
What do you think?
Please answer.
I'm Ayaka Yasumoto, the fifth place in
the attendance.
I'll answer Yasumoto's questions.
What's your name?
I'm Hinata.
Ah, listening is a song selection, and
making is also a song selection.
So cute
It's been a while
What is love after all
I thought it was water but it was tea
No way
I can see it
What is it?
I don't know
I'll save it
What I want to tell you is
Come to the adult world
I'll watch it
I like it a lot
A hairdresser
A mobile phone
My teeth are beautiful
France
Soy sauce
Yes.
A kid.
What is your favorite anime?
My favorite anime is...
Jasmine
What is your favorite anime?
Mayama
Thank you for watching!
8 hours to 4 hours.
Please listen to the playlist.
Thank you for your viewing.
Parisienne
It depends on the person, but if I think
of it, I'll do it in about 30 minutes.
Sugamo
SPECTRUM
I had a lot of meat and potatoes for
dinner last night.
Transparent human.
Hello, everyone. I'm Mirei Hoshino, the
lucky seven.
I've received a lot of questions, so I'd
like to answer them.
How many hours?
How many hours a day?
Game?
When I have a lot of time, I spend 5 to
6 hours.
That's a lot.
What's a quick tip?
Mocha gave me food and I was so hungry
that I woke up today.
Thanks to Mocha.
Thank you.
Ice cream.
I eat one at night.
I eat it almost every day.
I love it.
B type. The moment I think I'm a B type.
I'm very particular about things I don't
understand.
Everything else is just about to be
done.
Charging? I'm always fighting.
I always charge my phone thinking it's
20% bigger.
I'm happy if I'm in the comments.
What's the number?
Fried shrimp?
If Riko-chan was my younger sister, we
would go shopping and wear clothes
together.
What's the most delicious word?
You look like a nice person.
What subject did I do well?
I was good at politics and economics.
What I wasn't good at was art.
I can't draw.
Charm? I didn't realize it myself.
What is it?
Charm? Actually...
Actually, I'm worried about the details.
What kind of ramen do you like?
Miso!
How do you relieve stress?
I sleep or sing in the bath.
The furthest I've gone is driving from
Nagoya to Kanagawa, half a distance away
from my family's house.
I changed places with my dad.
I'm motivated to keep working hard?
I like talking to everyone. I like live
performances, too.
Where do you want to go?
I want to go to Hawaii again and do a
marathon.
What is the cutest pose?
Cute lines?
What is it?
I like yakiniku today.
Do what you like all day.
If I'm asked what I like all day,
I want to go on a trip.
Where can I go?
Occupation?
When I see someone's live, I think,
this kind of performance is wonderful.
I see a lot of that.
This is the pose I want.
The ratio of men and women?
Probably
6 men and 4 women
Recently, there are many girls in my
family.
I'm glad if you come without any worries
because everyone is good friends.
I think you can be friends soon.
10 years later
What are you doing?
Do you still like cosmetics and clothes?
Do your best to polish yourself!
What kind of person is Rika Mayuma?
What kind of person is it?
Actually, she is like a younger sister.
She is like a younger sister because she
is a younger sister.
But she is a friend.
She is a member, but she is a friend.
What song do you want me to listen to?
What is it?
Jump!
What is a good way to study?
I couldn't concentrate for a long time,
so I'll make a plan for the first day of
the break and the time when I don't.
Charm point?
I often get this kind of mouth in my
drawings.
This kind of mouth.
If I were reborn, what would I be?
But I want to be reborn as a girl again.
See you again. It's fun.
I think?
What's a happy event that happened
recently?
A happy event?
What is it? A happy event.
Oh!
I got a lot of compliments from everyone
for the island creation.
I did my best.
Q. Do you have a favorite food?
Recently, I've been eating a lot of
sushi.
I couldn't eat it before, but I can eat
anything now.
Is there any episode that you thought
was a little bit messy?
I was told to put rice in the bowl, but
I was washing it with a bowl, not a
colander.
I thought the water wouldn't fall at
all, but it was a bowl, not a colander.
I'm Nakayama Riko, 12th, the number 12
of the Shibitsuebi Shishigi.
Let's start!
I'm good at putting on my clothes
quickly.
A cuckoo?
It's like it's going to wrap me up.
I wonder if it's my head.
Project?
If I leave it to me, I'll be in a daze
again.
I'm going to do a project to be in a
daze.
Is that okay?
Tension is...
I can leave the tension to you.
If it doesn't go up, it won't go up.
But the basics are up.
Tomorrow...
Kaho-chan?
Kaho-chan.
I'm still enjoying my teens.
Congratulations.
What? A family question?
No.
30 minutes ago?
That's too early.
After the omelet?
After the omelet,
I'll eat an omelet.
I don't have any impression of getting
angry.
Have I ever been angry? Yes.
But I don't get angry at all.
What I want the most now is
Salasano's hair.
My hair is messy because of Salasano's
hair.
I'm told I don't look like I'm thinking
about anything.
Yes.
I get nervous at live performances.
I get nervous no matter how many times I
do it.
Except for the part where I fall in
love?
Heart.
When I turn 20?
What do I want to try?
Cooking.
I want to try cooking a full course
meal.
Tsubuan? Koshian?
I don't know what this is, but maybe
it's koshian.
Tsubuan means a grain of rice.
Eat something delicious.
Do something right after you wake up.
I've been drinking water lately.
What is your ideal watermelon?
My past life? What is this? A photo?
My past life?
Hmm...
Alinko.
No reason.
Huh?
What song?
Huh? What is it?
It's a spring song.
Rika's...
Ah!
I want to sing, but I can't.
I guess.
Right now?
I want you to be a college student.
What kind of job do you want to do?
Dance, dance, dance.
Student's performance.
School drama.
Makeup tips? Please tell me too.
I started to like cucumbers a little
before I started to like M2.
I don't know. I've liked it since I was
born.
If I could ask for one thing, what would
it be?
I hope I can have a live.
What song do you think is the most
difficult?
Your dance is noisy.
But I think it's a jump.
Freedom, the way.
Not the best.
How do you get rid of stress?
I wonder what it is.
How to get rid of stress?
I sleep.
I want to drink alcohol with you.
What is it?
I said yes to you the other day.
I can't do this.
I don't like it.
A bird!
I'm sorry.
A pigeon.
A bird.
I'm sorry, bird.
I'm Kobayashi Kaho, the number 11.
I'll answer the questions.
Let's start!
What kind of questions will come?
Two people?
Cooking!
Riko made fluffy omelet rice.
Kaho wrote,
I want to be a mother who wants to raise
a gentle girl who likes to sing.
And I became Kaho.
What did I buy? I don't remember at all.
What did I buy?
Ah! Sofa!
I bought a sofa in the back of the room.
I bought it at the home improvement
store.
I was involved with the electrolysis....
the mop was not operational
It's hard to process speed
It was you!
Truly,... It was so difficult
...............
I want to drink whiskey that Maya gave
me.
What is it? Soda?
I want to drink whiskey as a highball.
I have.
When I drink alcohol, I feel like a
friend.
We are friends.
I'm a cocoa bread.
I was excited when I was a cocoa bread.
I sleep at 1 o'clock in the morning and
wake up at 9 o'clock in the morning.
My room?
I watch the YouTube of Masahiro Ehara's
family on YouTube.
I haven't decided what to give for the
10 yen.
What should I give?
I broke my iPad case.
I'll give you a new iPad case.
What's in my bag?
Wallet
Wallet and
I'll give you a new iPad case.
My wallet.
When I go to a festival, I eat yakisoba.
I'm 20 years old, but nothing has
changed.
Nothing has changed, but I can't drink
alcohol.
A word that I can't say?
What?
I don't know.
I fell in love.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you for your hard work at school
and at work.
Good luck!
To myself 10 years ago?
10 years ago?
I was 10 years old.
I was running around too much in the
summer vacation and I had a nosebleed.
When you have a nosebleed, make sure to
cool it down.
Band club?
I think it's cool.
Drum.
Adult woman.
Adult woman is
a person who is doing high heel.
If I won a million yen,
I want to go on a trip somewhere.
High heel?
When watching a Japanese movie,
No matter how
chic the girl is.
Hey..
No..
She is soooible..
....
Wait, my diction is all wrong.
What?
So difcult.
Rice,
submit,
Thank you for watching!
This is difficult.
I eat what I like first,
eat it in the middle,
and eat it at the end.
I eat little by little.
Well, Mr.Yasumoto,
I want you to get up because you are 20
years old.
But sleep is important.
What is the most memorable thing in my
teenage years?
I can't choose the most.
Everything is the most memorable.
The first CD I bought was a Lion Mask by
Rika Mayama.
It comes with a poster.
I don't have any regrets. I have never
thought of it.
Oh, I got a comment from Riko.
Riko, I'm sorry. I'm in my 20s, so I'm
waiting.
I'm waiting for 4 months.
I'm sorry. I'm 20 years old.
I didn't get drunk for two days.
I haven't drunk at all until I got drunk
for two days.
I'm fine.
The drink I want to drink is...
Calpis.
Kobayashi Produce's official goods,
right?
What official goods do you want to make?
But I want something important.
Something like this backpack.
What?
You're 20 years old.
You're paying attention to this?
I'm paying attention to my inner color.
Rika Mayama
I'm Rika Mayama, the third place.
Let's get started.
Well, I'm wearing beige today.
I'm into beige these days.
The member I want to be my sister?
Hirata is very solid, so I want to be my
sister.
I want to try my hair.
Blonde short hair.
Eternal longing.
Health management.
Really.
Eat well.
I have a lot of luggage, but I don't
know the condition of shampoo when I'm
on a trip, so I always bring a shampoo
set.
Kinoha
I want to know that.
Don't touch your phone too much the day
before.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Recently, I've been drinking Melrose, a
night-drinking green juice.
I've liked it for a long time.
See you later.
What do I want to do?
Well, I want to try something.
I want to try something.
I can't think of a book.
Parachute.
I'm touching it.
I touched it today, too.
I want to write a letter and drink it.
Congratulations.
Let's go drinking together.
It's about 10 to 20 minutes.
If it's early, it's done in 5 minutes.
About 10 hours?
Almost.
Eat 3 meals properly and drink water
well.
Everyone is growing.
I think everyone is growing.
In various aspects,
I think it's Hirata.
Oh, no.
Oh, I have. I've been to a party for
Momokuro.
Dog? I want to be a dog of a big family
living in Daikanyama.
Well, Chinese.
Choto-tsu申
Thank you for watching.
Marshmallow?
Maybe it's an anime.
Or maybe it's a beauty salon.
Yes.
If it's a miso soup made by my mom,
I like cabbage and egg the most.
I'm not sure how I'm doing.
I hope I can continue to grow up
healthily in 10 years.
I'm a silent type.
If you do it like this, you can train
your muscles.
Music is a color.
I will upload videos from Monday to
Friday.
Please look forward to it.