It's time to make sweets.
Today I will make my favorite sweet
potato.
I love sweet potatoes.
My family has always told me to make
sweet potatoes.
I will make sweet potatoes.
If you have a chance to make sweet
potatoes, please call me.
I will make my favorite sweet potato
this time.
I haven't eaten sweet potatoes this
fall.
I'm looking forward to eating what I
made this year.
I don't make sweet potatoes because I
want to eat it.
I make sweet potatoes to make you happy.
I will do my best.
good morning
Let's cut sweet potatoes!
First, peel the sweet potato skin and
cut it into 2cm pieces.
The water pressure is a little high.
The color is very beautiful.
First, clean the sweet potato.
Cut it into big pieces.
The sweet potato is big.
Wash it.
Let's wash it.
Wait a minute.
This is not a cat's hand.
This is a cat's hand.
I wash it.
Wait a minute.
I'm scared.
I'm going to be caught in the first 10
seconds.
I'm wondering if I can make sweet
potatoes.
I think it's okay.
Do you cook?
I don't.
I used to do it a lot last year.
I'm 20 years old now.
I'm not ready for this.
I'm not ready at all.
Is this curler broken?
Is it broken?
This is strange.
My goal when I was 19 was to be able to
cook.
I wasn't a member of the S.A. at the
time.
I was doing it.
I'm not ready.
But I had my mom stay with me in the
kitchen.
She was watching over me.
It was my first time doing it alone.
I can't turn it on.
I think I'm going to run out of battery.
Why can't I turn it on?
Where are you going?
Here we go!
Ah, but it's looking good.
I can see the end of the line.
This is the last part.
If I go too deep, my favorite potato
will get smaller and smaller.
Oh!
I'll do the last part around here.
Is this okay?
I think I'm being told that I'm peeling
too much.
Is it too much?
I wonder.
Should I peel this part too?
This one?
Please help me.
Okay!
Okay, so I've peeled the skin off.
I'll cut it into 2cm pieces.
I'm making a very distorted shape.
I'll start now.
This is a good potato.
I'm always told that I use a saw when I
use a kitchen knife.
I cut this from above.
I was scared.
I cut this to about 2 cm.
стро23 years old
It's hard.
It's a lively potato.
Hello.
When I was cooking with my mother,
I was using this kitchen knife.
I was saying, cat's hand, cat's hand.
But she said, cat's hand doesn't mean
anything.
I wonder if I can do it today.
I wonder if my mother can do it today.
I've only cut potatoes and washed them,
but I'm making the staff nervous.
Oh no.
This is a sweet potato.
What did I just say?
It's a potato.
Does this look like a potato?
I think I should cut a little more.
I will put the potatoes in the bowl.
It's done.
I will put the potatoes in the water and
let it sit for 5 minutes.
I put it in the water until the bottom.
I watched a lot of videos last night.
I just watched them.
I will put the potatoes in the water and
let it sit for 5 minutes.
I will wait for a while.
I made the spicy chicken, meat and
potatoes and the omelette by myself.
I think it was about 6 months ago.
I didn't have a kitchen.
That's right.
Do you have any ideas to make this?
I want to make this sweet potato today
and if it's good, I want to let my
family eat it.
I want to let my family eat it.
If I have a member, I might look a
little bad.
Hello.
Next is this.
I'm going to microwave the potatoes.
I have to make sure I don't throw away
the sweet potatoes.
It's surprisingly good.
I've dropped all the ingredients before.
How much is this?
I think everyone will not think that it
is completed.
I will heat it.
I will use 800W.
5 seconds.
1 minute.
1,2,3,4,5.
Go!
There is a cute girl who shares
delicious potato information.
She is a member of the Batten Shouzu
team.
Her name is AYUKI KIYAMA.
She posted a photo of potatoes on her
Instagram.
I thought she liked potatoes.
When I saw her lunch box the other day,
I was excited.
I'm researching.
SUWAAKI likes potatoes.
I want to go to a potato hunt.
I often post food on Instagram.
I want to post a story.
I want to eat potatoes in this season.
I like potatoes.
I'm a little shy to post food.
I added a photo of potatoes to the
highlight of the story.
Please follow me on Instagram.
What did you say to your mother when you
were a child?
I loved eating since I was a child.
I said, what do you want to eat?
I said, potatoes.
I was very excited about the potato
hunt.
I couldn't go to the potato hunt on the
day of the hunt.
I was very excited at home.
The next day, I saw a newspaper on my
desk.
I saw a newspaper on my desk.
I was very excited.
Hello potatoes.
I smell good.
Wow!
Let's go.
Ta-da!
Wow! Nice color!
It's a little hot.
Oh, wow!
Ta-da!
It smells good.
It's hot, so I'll do it gently.
It's warm. It's quite hot.
I will crush the potatoes.
I don't know the name of this potato.
I'm impressed.
This is amazing.
This is getting smaller.
Do you make sweet potatoes?
I don't have it.
I heard that you have a project to bring
your own potatoes.
Yes, I'm going to do a project I like
this time.
At first, the word potato came out.
I decided to make it by saving potatoes
or making it.
I wanted to put the first anniversary in
the video.
So, this is my first sweet potato.
Hello!
So, I finished crushing it nicely.
Next, I'm going to add sugar, butter,
vanilla essence, milk, and egg yolk.
I'm going to add it.
This is 20g of butter.
And then, I'm going to add sugar.
Add sugar.
And then, egg yolk.
Beautiful egg yolk.
And then, vanilla extract.
Oops, I put too much.
Add 1 tablespoon of milk.
And then, mix it.
Is it enough?
It feels good.
OK.
Now that I've put all the ingredients
in, I'm going to mix them all.
I'm going to mix them all.
It's important to mix them all.
I've never made it before, so I don't
know.
It's a great texture.
I don't know what it tastes like. It's
too sweet.
I don't like it when it's not sweet at
all.
Please make it sweet.
Hello.
Next, I will shape it.
It smells like sweet potatoes.
It's really good.
I will use a plastic wrap to shape it.
I'm particular about the shape of the
last.
I want to make it look like it's there.
This should be good.
I'm going to make it look like a ball.
I feel like I'm making a rice ball.
I'll put this in.
I'm going to make it look like a ball.
It's like a potato.
I'm going to make some of these.
It's starting to look like a sweet
potato.
I can see the end, mom.
Can you see it?
It's starting to look like a sweet
potato.
How much is left?
It's getting too big to fit in this
bowl.
I look like an artisan, don't I?
I'll do it next time.
I want to make sweet potatoes next to
the storage space.
What should I do?
The last one is going to be huge.
She's making a big one.
Is this really going to be on air?
I wonder if it's really going to be on
air.
The last one!
Ta-da!
It's done!
Hello, potatoes!
Now that the shape is done, I'm going to
add the yolk.
Adding this makes the color look really
nice.
It's my first time making it, but it
looks like this when you look at the
recipe.
Like this.
The appearance is important.
The color is getting better.
Everyone uses egg yolk in every recipe.
I think this is important.
The taste is important, but the color is
important.
The sweet potato has a dark color in the
center.
I think that's because of the yolk.
This is the first time I've heard of it.
Hello.
I finished painting.
This is almost the end.
Next, I will bake it until it is browned
with a toaster.
I will bake it.
I will put it in the toaster.
It will be a nice color and come back.
I'm looking forward to it.
Good.
What should I do? If it burns at the
end, I will be shocked.
We can't be together.
Is it OK?
Hello!
Did you burn it?
Oh, you're right!
OK, cut!
I've finished adjusting the camera.
I'll take a look at the first floor.
It smells really good.
This is it, everyone.
This is it.
Ta-da!
Oh, no. The last one is a little...
It's a little connected.
This is a little...
We're getting along.
Oh, well.
So...
I baked it!
Wow!
I'm so moved right now.
I'm so happy.
I did it.
But today,
It's not over yet.
From here on,
I'm going to make it my first time.
I'd like to decorate it.
Hello.
OK, let's start the last step,
decoration.
OK.
Please guess what I'm going to draw.
I'll start.
I'll draw this girl.
Wow, it's been a while since I drew a
chocolate pen.
But I'm sure I'll draw a potato and a
chocolate.
It fits.
Oh, I got something on my face.
I got something on my face.
It's different from what I thought.
OK.
And then...
I'll draw this.
I'll use orange.
Can you see it?
It's done!
I decorated it!
Hello!
So, finally,
Sweet Potato is done!
Thank you for watching!
It was a long way to get here.
But I made it!
Do you know what this decoration is?
Do you?
I think it's a little bit of a plus from
the quiz I gave earlier.
First of all, this!
The correct answer is...
I also thought it was cute when I saw it
in the recipe.
It was a chick!
I drew the eyes and legs with a
chocolate pen.
I think you all know the four below.
These are the members of BOLT.
Aya, Nano, and I'm the Rumpan.
I drew everyone.
Thank you for watching!
I'm going to eat it now.
I feel sorry for the members, so I'll
eat the chick.
It's so soft.
It's soft, but I wonder if it's the
right word.
I wonder.
I'll enjoy it.
Mmm!
Mmm, mmm, mmm!
It tastes like a new type of sweet
potato.
It's like...
It's seasoned with a moderate amount of
sweetness,
and it's also sweetened with sweet
potatoes.
But, um...
It's like a little bit of a mashed
potato,
which is left over.
But, it's delicious!
How many points did you get?
Well, I got 72 points!
72 points!
It was my first time, so I got 50
points.
I wanted to have a more moist texture.
But, I got 72 points for decoration.
I got 72 or 73 points.
This is not my style of decoration.
But, please try to make it.
Bye bye.
This is Imomusume.
Imo-kyun.
Imo-kyun is a Japanese word meaning a
sweet potato.
The member, Tanaka Saho, has a
mysterious side.
I want to deliver the message I want to
deliver as clearly as possible.
I'm the type of person who says, thank
you.
I'm the type of person who thinks, can I
sing well?
dance well?
I made a mistake because I was nervous.
But I want to deliver the message I want
to deliver the most.
I want to deliver the message I want to
deliver as clearly as possible.
I want to deliver the message that I
want to deliver the most.