Ebichu's videos!
We have prepared a snack.
Staff bought it for us.
It smells so good.
This is the salt-grilled one.
It's made of blue cheese and kusaya.
Kusaya?
Have I ever eaten kusaya?
Didn't we eat it at the location?
This is a snack.
It's a snack.
It's famous for its smell.
I thought it was a snack.
Even now, I can't imagine it.
The salty and spicy taste of blue cheese
is fighting.
It's a great atmosphere.
It's a savory taste.
Have you ever eaten it?
From now on!!
I like it. I've been eating it since I
was a kid.
I've never had blue cheese.
It's my first time eating only this
cheese.
First, salt.
I'll eat it.
How do you eat it?
I eat it with rice.
I've been eating it since I was a kid.
I'll eat it with rice.
It's delicious.
I like it.
I haven't eaten it for a long time. It's
salty and spicy.
She said it's salty and spicy.
I like it. It brings back memories.
I can drink alcohol with this.
This is the taste of the past.
It's salty.
I can drink alcohol with this.
It's delicious.
I think it's different if you mix it
with alcohol.
Is this the alcohol?
This is sake.
My father told me that sake is good for
a little bit of sourness.
What about blue cheese?
Blue cheese is not good.
I can't eat cheese until Mayma.
I can eat a little bit when I grow up.
But you can eat cheese souffle.
I can't eat cheese souffle until Mayma.
I like cheese cake recently.
It's black.
I'll enjoy it.
I'm going to do it.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Is it good?
It's good.
This is good.
You're an adult, Riko-chan.
You're an adult only with your tongue.
I can do it.
Riko-chan will buy this.
It's good.
You're addicted to it.
I don't eat this much.
What kind of alcohol do you drink with
cheese?
Wine?
Wine.
It's a wine.
You're an adult.
It's blue cheese and wine.
I don't know what's red and what's
white.
What's this?
It's white, so it's white.
Is that so?
I don't know at all.
It's white, so it's white.
It's white, so it's red.
This is the most childish reaction in a
row.
It's white, so it's red.
It's white, so it's white.
It was good.
It was good until now.
It's like a common alcohol.
It's like an adult's taste.
It stinks.
Do you all eat this?
Do you all eat this as a snack?
Do you eat this?
I don't eat scraft.
Everyone does.
If you eat this, you'll be an adult.
There's a reason why we haven't opened
this much.
Is this your first time eating this?
I'm afraid of opening it.
It's a type of grass that you can eat as
it is.
It's dangerous to bake it, so they
prepared this.
Open it.
Open the scraft.
I'll try it.
I don't know what it is.
It's a drop.
It's food, so it's not a drop.
I didn't eat it, but it's in my throat.
No! No! No!
Don't look at me like that!
Eyy!
Wait, wait!
I want to write something like this!
I'll add some salt.
Wait, this is bad.
It's still in the bag.
Wait, this is a bag in a bag.
It's going to be gross.
There's a bag in the bag.
Is this a pair of scissors?
No, I can't open this!
Damn it!
This is my seat! It's always in front of
me!
I don't know what's going on.
It stinks!
Why?
It's hard to see.
Why is this in front of me when you're
eating it?
Wait, wait, wait.
This is bad.
My hands are starting to smell.
It smells good.
This is pretty bad.
I'll clean my nose.
I haven't cleaned it yet.
It's a problem.
Open! Open! Open!
Are you going to open it?
Damn it!
I can't!
Please subscribe to our channel!
This is bad.
It's not because you're facing this way
that the smell is gone.
I opened it.
Go ahead!
Egu-chan, go ahead!
What should I do?
These guys are the bad guys.
OK, invincible. If you pinch my nose,
I'm invincible.
There's a film on it.
I'm invincible!
Film.
Good job, Riko.
It's so good!
Yes!
Which one?
You're eating it?
And the powder around it.
It's bad if it mixes with the powder.
That's pretty bad too.
The cream cheese is bad too!
This is the worst!
Wait, we're supposed to eat this right?
Can we eat it with our nose stuck in it?
Are we really eating this?
What are we eating?
It's the same taste as the inside of our
mouth right?
We're going to eat it
It's hard
We don't have to open it?
What do you mean?
Wait, what do you mean?
And the smell is the same as the inside
of our mouth
So we're definitely measuring the same
amount
We're measuring it wrong
We're really eating this right?
Wow
Maybe some people like this
That's what you mean right?
There's a demand for it
It's smelly
Of course
We're going to eat it
It might taste good
It might be good
It's good
I don't want to be an adult
I can't eat it all at once.
I'll eat it.
You eat it later?
It's good.
I'm scared.
To be continued.
So, we had Riko-chan try three different
flavors. How was it?
I feel like I'm 5 years older.
You're already an adult.
I'm glad. I'm the same age as you.
I'm so tired.
The smell was really strong.
It was really strong.
It's just that it's there that it
smells.
Until then, I didn't have a chance to
think about what would go well with
alcohol.
What does it go well with?
I want someone to tell me.
If you eat this and make it a snack,
please leave a comment.
I saw a lot of courage today.
I saw Riko-chan's courage.
It was the best.
Thank you.
The most interesting thing was that I
didn't want to be an adult if I ate
this.
You don't have to be an adult if you eat
I won't eat this even if I become an
adult.
I don't eat it.
I'm not getting older because I'm a
grown-up.
I don't think I'll eat it.
I don't think so.
But there are people who eat it.
That's right.
I think that's what it's about.
Riko-chan's smell was more than adult.
She took everything.
Riko-chan challenged herself.
Is there any alcohol you want to drink
after you turn 20?
I can drink carbonated drinks.
I don't drink it at all, so I want
something that's not carbonated.
I recently looked up birthday alcohol.
What is it?
It's like a birthday.
There are birthstones.
There is such a thing.
I looked it up and it came out.
What is it?
Maribu Pine?
Maribu and Pine.
There is one person for each person.
I looked it up and it came out.
It's called Maribu Pine.
I like oolong tea, so I'll have oolong.
Jasmine tea.
Then, on the 29th, you'll have a toast
on the 29th.
Then, let's have a toast with oolong
tea.
Riko-chan's favorite oolong tea.
I'll have a toast in about two months.
About two months later.
Do you feel like you don't want to grow
up?
I'm a little bit now.
That's completely because of the grass.
My hands smell like this.
Your hands?
My hands smell.
I'm carrying the grass today.
What are you going to do? You may not be
able to do it until tomorrow.
I'm sorry for the members.
We don't smell that bad.
I don't think I'll ever eat it again
when I grow up.
Let's say goodbye today.
Goodbye.
I may eat it someday.
October 28th.
I'm turning 20 in about two months.
Don't forget.
Remember.
If we can celebrate something like Kaho-
chan,
I hope we can celebrate Riko-chan
together.
Please celebrate together.
At that time, we'll have a Malibu pie.
Malibu pie.
I don't know if I can drink such a
fashionable drink.
I don't think I can drink it at home.
The first theme was something I could do
when I turned 20.
Did you have it?
Nothing has changed.
Why did we come here today?
Why did you come here?
To be honest, nothing has changed.
In conclusion, I found out that nothing
has changed.
Thank you.
That was Riko-chan's challenge.
The topic has changed.
That's right.
Challenge to smell bad.
Challenge to taste good.
That was Riko Nakayama's tasting guide.
Thank you.