Ebichu's videos!
I was a fan of First Take, so I was very
happy to see Ebichu.
At the same time, I had a question.
I was really curious about First Take.
When I recorded it, it was really the
first take.
I was so nervous.
I thought I'd never been so nervous.
I was sweating like crazy.
I was really nervous.
I didn't expect to be able to
participate in a wonderful project
called First Take with six people.
I'm glad that I was able to finish it in
the form that will remain in the form of
the last six people.
How was it to be able to participate in
the first take?
The period of time I was able to
participate with six people was probably
short.
I couldn't show it in a proper way.
In that sense, I think it was a very
long period of time because I was
particular about the number six because
the period of time I was able to
participate with six people was short.
And I was happy to show it to you at the
end.
I was able to participate with six
people.
It was similar to how I felt when I was
shooting my graduation album.
How did you feel when you were able to
participate in the first take?
Ayaka was able to take a breath when she
was able to participate in the first
take.
I was very happy at that moment.
I was happier than when I was singing.
How did you feel when you were able to
participate in the first take?
I was very impressed that many people
kept the shrimp-chewed in their hearts.
I was very happy.
I was able to participate in the first
take because of everyone's support.
I was so happy to hear that they were
all saying that the path we are
supporting is such a wonderful idol.
I felt everyone's power.
How do you feel about the new team?
The new team is actually starting, but
the 3 of us will be recording our first
performance at the fan meeting.
I want to be like this.
It's a story of the 6th generation, but
there's no clear goal in Ebichu.
I want to make it.
We had a meeting and then we talked
about not aiming for Meiji Jingu.
I think it's a very clear path for an
idol to understand.
Is there a song program you want to
appear on?
Or is there a venue you want to perform
at?
I think it's a very clear goal that I
wanted to give them.
I want to perform at Jingu Stadium.
And for that, I want to work more hard
next year.
I think this year will be the year of
the seeding.
First of all, I want to make the fan
meeting successful and make everyone say
that the 9 members of Ebichu are also
fun.
And if we can share fun and happiness
with everyone at the live performance,
we will be able to become a better
group.
I hope that we can go to Meiji Jingu
Stadium with everyone in Ebichu Family.
I thought about Akarin's warehouse at
the music festival, but it's really hot
in the evening.
First of all, I want to take good care
of my health and perform carefully so
that I don't get sick.
I would be happy if I could share fun
with everyone.
What is your plan for the live
performance?
At first, I didn't plan to return to the
stage.
I was planning to return to the stage at
the live performance.
Thank you for your viewing.
I talked to the star Sonny and Fujii
and decided to try it or enter the
competition.
I didn't think that would be the return
line.
At first, I felt the pressure.
But I've always wanted to appear on this
channel.
I was looking forward to it.
How was it to enter the competition?
I wasn't nervous that day.
I was happy that I could go to a place
where the fans could finally listen to
my song.
I was very happy when I imagined the
faces of the listeners.
I was excited all day.
It's been a long time since I've been
nervous.
I wanted to experience that moment.
I was happy to experience that moment.
I was excited and nervous.
What was the most memorable moment?
The first word we said when we were six.
It was the word PRIDE.
PRIDE is a word that fits very well.
We were very proud of ourselves.
We were very confident about ourselves.
We were able to show our strength.
We were very popular.
What is the most memorable moment?
I saw the trend on SNS.
I saw the name of the channel and the
words on my finger.
I was very impressed.
I still feel strange.
But for me anyway...
I was the happiest when I received the
message from the fans who believed in me
and waited for me.
I was hoping for that.
I think that's how I was able to spread
the message to the fans.
The fans worked hard to spread the
message we sang.
They were happy to be able to appear in
the same video as me.
I felt that we had a long bond with the
fans.
I was happy to be friends with the fans.
What was the most important thing to
you?
I was able to meet the three of them and
have a lesson with them.
I was also able to receive a lot of
encouragement and energy.
I think it's a good time for me to level
up.
I'm looking forward to seeing how the
three of them will change.
What do you want to do in the future?
I want to appear in the video as soon as
possible.
I think the explosive power of the live
performance will be amazing.
I realized that I really like singing
while I was on the flight.
I'm looking forward to singing in front
of the fans.
I haven't tasted the air for more than
half a year.
I want to feel it soon.
What are you doing to take care of your
throat?
I've been taking care of my throat since
the day before yesterday.
I'm trying to take care of my throat.
I've been using all the items I need to
take care of my throat.
I was nervous in the morning.
I was excited.
I'm trying to take care of my throat.
I tried to add more to the first take
I think I was doing one by one
What was the most nervous thing about
the first take?
That was the most nervous thing
I was really surprised when I was told
that the first take would come out
I hope that everyone will always be one
of the top songs
I hope that the song will be the Ebitune
song
But it's the most wishful thinking, and
if I don't get into it
I'm going to be on the first take
I think that's what made me a little
nervous
What was the most impressive thing about
the first take?
I was so moved
I read each comment one by one
I'm really happy that I'm getting more
and more comments every time I open it
It's all warm words
I don't know the face of the person who
hit me
There are so many warm messages that you
can hear
It's not just about cheering, it's
really a member of the group in the
Ebitune
I feel that you are supporting us again
What was the most impressive thing about
the first take?
I was a member of Ayaka before the first
take
Ayaka has gotten better and I was
concerned
I was meeting Ayaka, but I was able to
perform with six people, including
Ayaka, in front of various people
It's been a long time since I've done it
Ayaka fought against this disease
I'm so happy that I can recover so
quickly
The first take is the song we believe in
These six will send the most hearts with
content
I'm so grateful that I can deliver that
Ayaka has revived.
I've been doing this with this member
for a long time, so I'm sure we'll
follow each other when we have
something.
I think these six are the best friends
in my life. I think I'm living with
people who think those words are really
appropriate.
I really love this member. I've overcome
various trials.
I've been with six people, and I've been
happy and happy.
I've been hoping for this moment for a
long time.
I was able to accept that we had made a
mistake.
That's what I'm most happy about.
What is the most important thing about
Ayaka?
We're going to make a new member do what
we should do.
I think that's how we'll be born.
We're a group that can show each of our
nine colors. We're going to make sure
that we don't ruin the image of the new
members.
I hope we can see the new members live
and say,
That's the best thing about Ayaka. I
hope we can continue to be that kind of
group.
I'm going to make a live show that makes
you think,
I've been out for a year, but I'm sure
this is it.
We have two days, so I want to make sure
everyone is in good health.
I want to make a live show that makes
everyone say,
I had a lot of fun with a smile until
the end.
Thank you for watching.