Ebichu no Douga Toka
Ahoriko 6th Year!
Yay!
Ahoriko 6th Year
We joined on January 4th, 2014.
Before joining, we were in a group
called Team Dayoika, which is a limited-
time unit.
We joined a group that was disbanded for
a year.
I met Riko for the first time.
We met at the entrance of the lesson
hall for the first lesson of the fourth
period.
I remember it well.
By the way, you looked like a baby.
I was 10 years old.
We are the same age, but we are
babybeasts.
So I remember you as a baby.
You were a mood maker.
I did a lot of fun things by myself.
That's weird.
No one followed you.
By myself.
By yourself.
I did something by myself.
I was driving a car.
I did that too.
I was doing cartwheels.
I miss that.
There was an hour of free time between
acting and dancing lessons.
I did that too.
I was outside.
I met a lot of members.
I was doing cartwheels.
I was crazy.
You were always on the base.
I was the most focused.
I was on the base.
And then Riko and I went to Ebichu.
I don't know.
I don't know. Suddenly...
Even if I'm in the crowd, I'm not in the
picture.
I was embarrassed.
I did a diving.
After I decided to go home, I'm a pretty
high-spirited person, so I feel sick.
After the show, I came here and held my
breath.
Then, I thought, she was out of breath.
I'm glad you took a picture of me.
I feel sick.
It was dangerous.
It was the last time we sang as a whole.
The 7-color Star Dust.
When we sang Star Dust, Riko and I were
wearing shrimp-shaped T-shirts.
We were like, isn't that too much
shrimp?
It was a situation where we were like,
isn't that too much?
And it was a surprise.
I didn't want anyone to find out.
I didn't want to tell anyone.
I was really nervous.
And at that time, on the way home, there
was a pamphlet.
Fujii was doing this.
What was it?
With Kaho.
Unconfirmed.
It was a flyer.
It was distributed.
I was worried that it would fall on the
floor.
I was sad.
I was thinking about it.
Osaka Back to the Future.
It was the first stage.
We did more than 20 songs in two months.
I thought that the memory power at that
time was amazing.
I can't remember putting in one song in
a day.
At that time, I put in two songs in a
day.
I put in two songs the next day.
On Saturdays.
I sent a video of the choreography to
the staff in advance.
I was so worried that I was alone.
I was alone.
I was so worried.
It's a good video, so you have to do it
properly.
There are people who are waiting for
you.
To be continued.
2015 is going to be crazy.
2015 is going to be...
Kimbachi Dance Music.
2015?
Kimbachi is...
I'm scared.
Because I joined in the first year.
You were on the stage.
3rd year in middle school.
I went to school on Monday.
My classmates said,
Pon pon pon pon.
They said that.
You said that.
Yes.
The next day of M-STEP,
I went to a fan club event.
Yes.
I was like a celebrity.
I joined in the night.
After M-STEP, I joined in the venue.
I was like a celebrity.
I realized that I was doing that.
15 years.
It was my first album.
Kimbachi.
I was not surprised.
I was surprised that I recorded so many
songs in such a period.
I listened to the songs that I performed
in the live.
Everything is fun.
I haven't been able to do it with
everyone for 15 years.
It's natural that I do it now.
I haven't been able to do it for 14
years.
I don't think I've had that many.
I suddenly get involved with a lot of
people.
I didn't know what kind of person he
was.
It took me 15 years to get rid of him.
I just remembered.
I'm grateful for it now, but I haven't
been able to speak.
I don't know if it was 2015 or 2016.
I sang with him on a tour without
passing the microphone.
I don't remember.
I couldn't hear my voice at all.
I sang with him.
I didn't think about anything at that
time.
I had to do it.
I'm surprised now.
I was educated.
The teachers said that.
We are still students.
We don't have any basics.
We have to be strict until we understand
the basics.
That's what they said.
I'm grateful for that.
I'm glad.
To be continued.
2016!
2016 was...
What was it?
The year I released my best album.
Since 2016, your dance has become very
dynamic.
I don't know. I just like to dance.
I might have thought it was dance.
In 2017, I was already called wild.
But in 2016, I started to move.
I thought Riko-chan had changed.
I was impatient.
When did you learn how to sing?
16 years ago.
It's the same!
I'm glad!
I know, right?
I know.
I was embarrassed, but in 2014 and 2015,
I was very much in love with people with
thick voices.
I love this story.
In the morning, Hina-chan had a deep
voice.
I was in love with her, but it didn't
match my voice.
It sounded like a mispronunciation.
When I heard Super Arena's live CD in
2015, I was surprised.
I was surprised, too.
Then I told my vocal trainer that I had
a voice like this.
I told him that I liked this way of
singing.
He taught me how to sing in pop-corn
tone.
I was 16 years old.
16 years old!
I'm glad!
We were together in 2016.
I think I've changed.
I'm glad!
I think it's the most memorable.
The first song I sang was Bird's Life.
We sang it at the opening.
When I think of the first song, I think
of that song.
I remember Riko-chan covering Perfume's
Macaroni.
I've been listening to Macaroni since
then.
I can't sing alone.
Everyone was dancing behind me.
It's a live performance that focuses on
singing, but I'm dancing.
Until now, I've been taking care of my
personality on the 2017 tour.
Since the 2017 tour, I've been trying to
improve my performance.
The teachers were serious about teaching
me, but I was more focused on improving
my performance.
I wasn't good at sports, so the tour was
hard for me.
I was late to absorb what I was told, so
I couldn't do it right away.
I had to be careful not to get angry.
I think it was hard at that time.
I was so excited.
I was scared of batons before I joined
M2.
I was so excited because I was a
Spartan.
Everyone else is the type to get angry
when they're angry.
I'm the type to not get angry.
I was the type to get angry when I was
angry.
I was so excited at that time.
The tour in 2017.
To be continued.
We became 6 people.
It's so fast.
Budokan was tough.
Everyone said it was a good concert.
I think the result was good.
We were so focused on it.
We didn't know why.
I don't know why since I joined.
I can't remember.
Dekadonden.
And then high school...
3rd year.
I did Dekadonden,
I did Hamien,
I did Uchuu,
Where did I do my college entrance exam?
3 days.
I did it!
We did a unit performance.
We did 3 songs.
We all did it, but the pair changed
depending on the day.
We performed a song and it changed.
I don't know why.
I was so focused on it that I don't
remember it now.
I know that.
Even if I was told to do it now, I was
like,
I don't remember.
My grandfather remembered Pink Lady when
he saw it.
I'm glad.
Kaho and Riko.
Riko and Riko.
When I saw the unit performance of Riko
and Kaho,
I remembered Pink Lady.
There was no Pink Lady element at all.
I wondered where I had thought of it.
I guess you were inspired.
I'm glad I did a unit performance with
Riko.
I was relieved.
I was a third-year high school student.
I didn't rush.
I had to take the entrance exam.
I had to decide whether to go to college
or not.
I thought I would be a professional.
I was a professional.
I studied hard.
I didn't have the ability to study and
go to college.
I'm a freshman now.
I thought I could go to college no
matter how old I was.
I thought I'd finish my studies early.
I didn't want to go to college.
But my friends were worried about me.
My teacher was worried about me.
I was in a hurry.
I was wondering what to do.
I didn't go to college.
I was forced to go to college.
After I had decided, I was forced to go
to college.
I was forced to go to college.
You were a playful student.
I was worried about that.
I was worried about the students.
I was relieved.
I was grateful to my teacher.
It was last year.
I started to enjoy live performance from
last year.
I enjoyed it until now, but I was
worried about being scolded.
I realized that it was not the case.
I realized it.
It was late, but I started to think that
I should enjoy it.
It was late in 2019.
I realized it.
I should have done it earlier.
It was the 10th anniversary of M-TUBE.
I was very grateful.
The people who were involved in the
festival were very nice.
I felt like I was at the festival.
I felt like I was at a festival.
It was a great day.
And at the end, the festival was held.
I felt like I was in a group for 10
years.
I think it's amazing that you've joined
a group that's been around for 10 years.
It's like a little bit of a little bit.
But it's a time when you've become very
mature.
I only remember the time I cut my hair.
I graduated from high school and cut my
hair.
I only remember the time I cut my hair.
I felt like you've become very mature.
I felt like I was.
But you haven't changed.
We haven't changed.
I haven't changed.
I think I've gotten better at speaking.
I'm getting better.
I've been a little bit of a cat.
I didn't get a chance to watch my old
live videos.
I've seen it.
I'm not myself.
I'm glad I'm getting better.
I've been a little slower than the
others.
I've been learning the basics of how to
absorb and grow.
I've finally learned it last year.
I've been learning it for a long time,
but I'm learning it so fast.
It's the fastest.
I've been learning it for about four
years, and I've finally learned it.
I was very happy to hear that.
I'm glad I've grown up.
However, the hyales are apparently not
the only song in the tour.
I know, right? There were so many things
in 6 years.
Yeah.
When did you start thinking?
I don't know.
6 years is a long time.
16, 17, 18 years.
Like a wild.
Wild?
I'm doing my best.
I think it's time to change my mind.
I can't move because I don't have many
live performances.
I'm thinking about it.
I'm meditating now.
Are you meditating?
I'm meditating.
I see.
I'm in the middle of it.
We're the same age, so we're taught.
We're really growing together.
We have the same mental changes.
When I was on a live show, I was like a
mom.
I thought you were coming now.
I was like, too.
I'm doing my best.
Mom.
We're the same age.
I think we're all growing up.
I was in a world where I didn't know
anything.
I've been doing it without knowing
I was having fun, but I didn't think I
was growing up as a human being.
I've been worried more.
I thought I could worry.
I thought I was growing up as a human
being.
I was like, Riko, what's going on now?
I think you're a little ahead of your
time.
When I was on my birthday, I was wearing
a big, cute, and loose-fitting outfit.
I was wearing loose clothes all the
time.
When I saw that, I was like, Riko.
Let's grow up together.
Please subscribe to our channel.
We have been producing idol activities.
I am a producer.
I am in charge of idol activities.
We are idol members.
I was a little upset.
Members' opinions didn't match.
When I looked over there, I was looking
over here.
I was nervous.
I decided to look in the same direction.
We had a meeting.
Finally, we were able to meet.
Everyone is looking forward.
We will have a detailed formation.
I want to make a major debut.
I was worried about the two before.
What is the major debut?
We have already taken the forced debut.
It's a half debut.
It's still a lesson.
I'm a member.
It's complicated.
I'm sorry.
I can't hold it in this lesson.
I can't go to the ground.
I'm sorry.
I was motivated to sleep.
I don't know when I can make a major
debut.
I think it's within the year.
I want to eat food that sticks to my
teeth.
I can't eat it now.
I may be able to eat it.
What is a stick?
I can't eat it.
I can't eat what I like.
I ate a lot of gum.
I like the lemon candy.
I want to make a major debut soon.
I think it's still within the year.
I'm still ahead.
Let's do our best.
It was a serious idol situation.