Who is today's guest in the room of the
showroom?
I'm Riko Nakayama, the 12th person to be
the host.
Finally, you came.
I finally came.
I was surprised.
But the response is amazing.
Riko Nakayama is finally coming.
I was also asked by the manager to
appear in the room of the showroom.
I was wondering what to do.
When I first came, I thought I finally
came.
It's like a red hair.
If you're not good at it, is it okay to
refuse?
I was wondering what to do at first.
At first, I ignored the reading.
Pretending not to see.
I pretended not to see, but I was asked
directly what to do.
I'll try it.
I have no choice but to do it.
Why am I talking to you today?
I have a foreshadowing.
I've been interviewed a few times.
I remember it was hard.
Do you remember?
I don't remember.
I had my first best-ever interview.
Best version?
That's right.
I had my first full interview in 2016.
I have a very hard memory since then.
I don't remember at all.
I talked about the album.
It's not about the album.
It's about life.
I'll have you talk to me from the
beginning.
I don't have enough words.
I'll explain it in detail.
I remember that kind of interview.
You don't remember much.
I don't remember.
I heard that you were doing well.
I think I did it well.
I don't have enough words.
I think I can talk more.
I can see that you're an adult.
That's right.
I have a new member.
You have more members to care about.
You were 15 years old at that time.
That's right.
I was a junior high school student.
I had a hard time.
I remember the BLT.
That was the last interview.
That was three years ago.
I had the opportunity to choose 10
questions that I wanted to ask.
I wrote it on the premise that I would
talk about it.
I remember the questions repeatedly.
You don't remember, do you?
I don't remember.
I remember your current worries.
You were asked what your current worries
were.
I was asked a question.
You didn't raise your head.
I'm scared.
I'm scared of that time.
I was surprised.
Is that true?
I will reproduce it.
I don't have any recent worries.
I don't have any.
I want to hear a deep story, but I don't
have any.
Then don't write the questions you want
me to ask.
I'll tell you what I'm going through
today.
It was hard.
Thank you.
I thought it was interesting.
I enjoyed it as an interesting thing to
do my best to get there.
When I announced that I was going to
appear this time, I was asked in the
comments,
Mr. Go, weren't you not good at Riko?
I'm not saying I'm not good at it.
I'm wondering if it's okay.
I'm saying it anyway.
I'm a tough guy, but I'm not learning
anything bad.
I just didn't have enough words.
I often thought, eh?
That's all.
I went to an event called the Craftsman
Conference that I was doing at Loft Plus
One.
I went to play and it was said that it
would appear in the flow.
I was asked how it was at the best band
time.
Anyway, Riko Nakayama is a strong
opponent.
That's the worst.
I talked to her, but that's a little
bit.
It's like Riko Nakayama is dangerous.
Today, there's a versus.
It's out.
It's not a versus.
I'm not expecting it.
That's right.
At that time, I said, why do you talk so
much?
I said I'm not good at talking alone.
I was bad at it.
It was like, why again?
Why again?
This is also impressive.
What is it?
What are you confident about?
It's like talking to everyone when they
support you.
It's not about being confident.
It's like a draw.
I was 15 or 16 years old.
I'm scared.
I'm too scared.
At that time, you were not good at
talking.
I was bad at it.
I was also bad at talking about myself.
But it's a job where you have to talk
about yourself.
You're asked a lot.
Almost every day.
What did you think?
Nothing comes out.
What should I do?
When I was interviewing with the whole
group, I was talking to other members.
I was obviously worried.
I didn't hear it.
I don't talk at all in interviews with
all the members.
I suddenly pass the last mission.
I can't talk about anything.
I can't get it together.
Did you feel depressed at that time?
I don't think I was depressed.
I didn't think I was depressed.
I was depressed because I was always
like this.
I don't think so.
The people around me were kind and
supported me.
I didn't feel much pressure.
I'm scared now.
You were doing well in that scary state.
I didn't notice anything.
How did you notice it?
What made you notice it?
I thought I had to do better.
I noticed it last year.
It was very recent.
Last year, three people joined the
group.
I noticed it.
It doesn't matter if you're 20 years
old.
I thought I would be the youngest.
I thought I had to do something.
I finally realized I was 21 or 20 years
old.
Did you feel like a crisis at that time?
I was told that my juniors were coming.
I was surprised.
I wonder if there was a change in the
atmosphere.
But I've been doing this for about seven
years, so I don't think there was a
change in the atmosphere.
I think that's what happened. When the
two of you entered the stage, there was
a talk about whether to include the
members. I don't think there was a
thought of what to do.
But the timing was the timing. We've
been working as six since 2018, but
we've all been through a lot, and we've
never been able to do a live with six
people.
So I was worried that I'd have to
include three of them.
There was a thought that you should
wait.
Yes, there was.
But everyone said that it was good to
include the members when you were a
member of the KAHORICO team.
I think it's right to include them.
I think so.
How was it when you entered the stage?
I think it's finally coming together
over the course of a year.
At first, the three of us had a lot of
firsts, and we were all hit by the older
sisters.
I think they did their best.
It's completely different from the
number of members when you entered the
stage.
The direction of the songs you're doing
has changed, and it's probably harder to
remember.
You're nodding with a really sad face.
It was hard to remember a lot of songs
at that point.
It's twice as hard as the first time.
It's a difficult song to remember.
I thought, well, I wonder if I could do
it.
I don't think you could.
I think they were doing more strict
voice training and dancing, so I think
they couldn't stand it.
How do you feel about them as a senior?
I wonder how they would feel. I think
they are the most senior-like, so it's
easy to get along with them.
I was just an educator.
You were? You were in the past, right?
You weren't an educator.
I'm already talking about it.
I've been talking about it since I was
pretty early.
What kind of education did you have?
At first, I said I wanted to be an
educator.
I was really doing it.
Why did you suddenly have the
motivation?
Ayaka-chan was the one who supported me
when I joined the team.
I wanted to do the same thing, so I
applied for the team.
It was hard.
What kind of hard time did you have?
I couldn't tell them well.
It's hard for someone who doesn't have
enough words to raise their hand.
You're not very suitable for education.
I didn't realize that.
If you're motivated, you can do it.
I was very motivated.
But when I tried it, it was hard.
I got sick and I thought I wasn't
suitable.
You were a little mentally affected.
I was.
So I decided to do it with everyone.
I don't think I'm suitable for a tight
education.
I don't think you're suitable for a
senior.
I'm not suitable.
Be friends.
That's the best way to be friends.
So I stopped drinking right away.
How long have you been an educator?
I don't think I've been an educator for
a year.
Tell me what to teach.
And do what you like.
My sisters, Rika and Mirei, told me.
But it changes when you have a different
position.
When you have more followers.
I feel like I'm getting better.
What kind of thing?
I'm getting weird confidence.
For example?
I think I'm doing well.
You were a teacher and you struggled,
but you were confident.
I was confident.
I thought I could do it.
But I had to protect those three.
You're a solid person.
I'm a solid person.
That's a good thing.
When I was announced as a guest on Go, I
was worried about Twitter.
I was tweeting that I was fine with Riko
Nakayama.
I don't have to worry about it.
I think you're recognized as a person
who did it properly.
I'm glad.
I'll do my best.
I'm just saying.
I think I've been feeling safe since
last year.
It's because the three of you came in.
The door is still locked, but it's not
going to work in the past.
I'm glad you're okay.
I used to say that I didn't have to ask
you a lot of questions here.
You're here.
You've grown up.
But you've been here for seven years.
You've had a hard time for seven years.
You're not even talking.
I don't think I noticed that.
I didn't see it.
I'm having fun with the live show.
That's right.
I always talk about how much fun the
live show is.
I can feel the moment I'm doing it.
It's still the same.
I'm glad you're having fun.
You say you forget things in a day.
I don't drag it out.
That's a good thing.
What are you worried about lately?
I'll ask you the same thing again.
I had a dream that I couldn't read
kanji.
I've been saying that for about six
years.
It was so real that I didn't know it was
a dream.
I've been hearing stories that I'm not
good at Japanese.
I couldn't read the script, so I was
really angry.
I should have read the script and the
script.
I've been telling a lot of people that I
should master the minimum.
I read books.
I remember at the time.
I don't think there's anything I can't
read because I have a nickname.
I think I got it.
I don't know what happened.
Did you get a English name?
No, I didn't.
I don't know what it was. I might have
said it back then.
I was wondering if that kind of person
was really good at English work.
That's amazing.
You were doing something, weren't you?
I was doing it!
English work.
I was doing it, but I only remember the
kanji for enema.
That's all?
Yes.
I've been doing it for months.
And what did you get?
I got the kanji for enema.
That's all I remember.
That's a lot.
It is.
Because you've had a lot of work and a
lot of scripts in your career.
It's not easy, is it?
There's a lot of things you can't read.
How did you get there?
How do I say it? I've been looking it
up.
You're looking at your phone every time.
What is it?
That's right.
I asked the staff.
And you had a dream of getting scolded.
I was so angry.
I thought I'd really get scolded
someday.
You get anxious dreams.
Oh, yeah.
I've been wondering about that.
I'm glad you're here.
I'm glad you're not anxious about the
recent anxiety.
At that time, for example,
Why don't you study a little bit and get
rid of your anxiety?
I want to study.
I want to.
When I couldn't leave the house due to
the coronavirus,
I bought a work.
Work?
I bought all the math work.
I don't even do a page.
I leave it at home.
You're motivated, aren't you?
I feel like I want to study something.
Don't waste this time.
And I read a book to remember words.
I heard that you're not good at reading
or writing.
Are you able to read books?
I've gotten better at it, but...
Not much.
I don't improve my words and kanji.
I often hear that you don't read the
interviews I did.
I think I'm reading.
Are you okay?
I don't remember now.
You don't remember, but you read it,
right?
I read it.
I've got the motivation.
Kanji drill.
I'm doing it.
I'm not doing it, but I'm buying it.
Do you want to do something?
I do.
Do you want to grow up?
That's amazing.
I'm scared.
I'm afraid I can't read.
I often read a text book for the first
time.
Sometimes I can't read clearly.
I don't know how to read it naturally.
I try not to make the meaning of the
text weird.
I don't pretend to be confused.
I'm obviously doing something like,
I took off the one-blocker.
That's amazing.
I'll try to learn that skill.
I have a skill that makes me confused
and I don't know what it means.
It's a little likely to be found out, so
I'm skipping it.
I can't read it for the first time.
But I have a skill.
I'm working, but I'm suddenly asked to
read this.
I can read it before I go on the radio.
Have you gotten used to talking to
yourself?
I'm getting used to it.
Can you do it at all?
I don't know.
It depends on the content.
What kind of content?
I can finally talk about myself
recently.
Why didn't you talk about yourself
before?
I'm not interested.
Everyone was asking me about something.
I guess you weren't confident.
I guess I wasn't.
I really liked listening.
I don't think I talked about myself to
the members.
I think I talked about myself before I
became a member of the group.
Let's talk about it.
But it's more fun to listen to yourself.
It's more fun to listen to myself.
It's still the same.
I'm the same.
I think it's better to listen to other
interesting stories than to talk about
myself.
I can't help it if I'm too excited.
That's what I think.
If you're asked about yourself, you
should prepare an interesting story for
yourself.
It's not fun to talk about yourself, so
it's okay to talk about it.
So I'll take a good picture and make it
fun to talk about the interesting people
I interviewed.
That's a little exciting.
I'll make a few escape routes.
But I think there's a feeling that
people aren't interested in my story.
There was.
I definitely want to hear from the fans.
That's right.
I want to hear it.
I remember when I was in BLT.
I was told that I didn't want to say my
belongings.
Why?
I didn't want to be imitated.
I thought I was a strange person.
I guess you were interested in my
belongings.
I started to think that I could talk
about it little by little.
I talked to the members about it.
Please talk more.
Today is the day.
I will talk about what you are thinking
about.
My mother wants to appear on the show.
Do you want to appear on the show?
Let's invite your mother.
I don't talk at all.
My mother is more knowledgeable about
Riko.
I want to appear on the show.
I think you can talk about many things.
You are close to your mother.
I don't talk to my mother about me.
I don't talk about my work.
I go shopping with my mother.
I thought you were close to your mother.
I go shopping, but I don't talk to my
mother.
Are you a rebel?
I haven't talked to my mother since I
was born.
You don't talk to your mother.
I don't know.
I think your mother is not interested in
me.
I don't think so.
I don't talk to my mother.
I feel like my mother is listening to
everything I say.
I think she's worried about me.
I don't want to be told many things.
I don't talk to my mother.
You may be an adult.
I can't speak loudly.
You are an adult, so you don't have to
worry about it.
You are more accepted than you say.
What kind of talk do you usually talk
about?
I usually talk about it.
I talked about it in advance.
I talked about what I've been into
lately.
I talked about my love for Thai food.
I talked about it at that time.
I said something strange at that time.
I said, I don't think Thai food has
calories.
I don't know.
I said, there is.
I don't think so.
I think it's not calorie.
I have a new member called Yuno Kokubo.
I think she is very Yuno.
I see.
I will call her when she is old enough
to appear.
I'm like the old me.
You're not struggling, are you?
Yuno is smart, but she talks a lot.
But she is a little...
You're off the track.
I think it's interesting.
I've heard this kind of conversation
before.
There was a very impressive statement in
the previous interview.
I just want to be an idol.
I heard a story that I would quit if I
couldn't be an idol.
Do you remember that?
You don't remember, do you?
No.
I wanted to be an actress, but I'm doing
this now.
I'm talking about thinking only about
this.
Has that changed?
It hasn't changed.
The most important thing is to be an
idol.
I've been doing a lot of work in that
regard.
Your career is going well, so I wonder
if it's changed.
I'm the most idol in the idol world.
You recently said in an interview that
you were going to give up being an idol.
What happened?
The environment has changed.
I think it was the spring tour this
year.
I was sick.
I had a bad cold because of the
coronavirus.
I had a bad cold.
I couldn't stand on stage.
I was in the middle of a tour, but I
couldn't relax.
The first time I was on stage.
I couldn't feel the feeling of life
there.
But when I left the tour, I couldn't
sing at all.
I thought I'd quit if I didn't sing.
I thought I'd keep trying.
But there were times when you were a
little shaken at home.
That's right.
My condition has changed over time.
There were times when I couldn't keep up
with it.
You've been through a lot lately, right?
That's right.
At that time, I felt a little shaken.
Yes.
I felt that.
You can't perform outside because of the
number of people who like it.
Yes. That was the hardest part.
You can't perform outside because of the
number of people who like it.
And you have to be sorry for the people
who don't have you.
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
And because of the corona, the tour was
postponed.
But I couldn't go out if I didn't feel
good.
Yeah, like that.
I forgot what I was trying to say.
I forgot in an instant.
I was able to get out because I was a
human being.
Oh, yeah, I got out.
I got out.
I got out of Niigata.
As expected, even in such a serious
story,
I get a little shy.
I'm sorry.
I think it's a good part.
So even if you don't worry so much,
You'll be able to do it without
worrying.
I think so.
I've been thinking about it over the
past few years.
I've been thinking about my life over
the past few years.
If I say that in an interview,
The fans and family will be worried.
It's scary.
If you suddenly say something like this.
I was worried about your words of giving
up.
I'm sorry for that.
But, well,
I'm sure you're happier to hear the
truth.
When you do what you think you're doing,
You should tell them.
You can say that because you've decided
not to give up.
So don't worry at all.
I'm not saying I'm going to give up now.
No, I'm not.
Don't worry.
It's okay.
So, what was the reason you were
prepared?
As I said earlier,
When I finished the tour,
I was not good at all.
But this tour...
The tour is a long time during the
flexible performance.
I had to grow up.
I couldn't do anything.
I was frustrated with myself.
I realized that I should do it.
But it's good.
Don't be depressed about it.
I couldn't do it.
You're not feeling well.
That's right.
It's the second time.
Last year,
The three of us joined the first stage
of the nine members.
At Jam.
That's a high-level prize.
I couldn't participate.
The thing that inspired me in the past
interview was...
I'm sure Ibi will let the members rest
well.
I was very dissatisfied with the fact
that there were too many days off.
I'm sure Ibi will let the members rest
well.
I'm looking forward to every day.
That's right.
When I was a student, I really wanted to
do more work than school.
I can say it now, but I didn't go to
school at all.
You did?
No, he was really prioritizing his
studies, but I really wanted to do more
work than that.
I was so focused on my work that I
couldn't wake up in the morning.
I had fun going to school with my
friends, but I wasn't good at studying
abroad.
So I focused on my work.
When I graduated from school, I was told
that I couldn't do anything without
work, so I wanted to work.
I think I was 15 or 16.
Did your thoughts change a little bit?
Do you still want to go to school?
I want to go to school.
I want to know.
If I can, I want to try out different
jobs.
Do you want to keep working non-stop, or
are you looking forward to your own
life?
Ah, I wonder which one it is.
I'm looking forward to my own life.
I guess you didn't think about your life
that much at the time.
I didn't think about it at all.
You just watched YouTube when you had
time.
That's the same now.
That's the same.
I see.
But you started to think about it a
little bit.
Yes, yes.
I guess you were serious about going to
school after work.
Oh, I've said that before.
I'm serious.
Well, it's really good that you found
something to put into it.
That's right.
But really,
For people who can't think of anything
other than idols,
Do you think about how far you can go?
Idols?
Yes, I'm thinking about it.
You've started to think seriously.
Yes, I have.
When you graduate, you think about
yourself, right?
I think about it.
Hinata is about to graduate soon.
I think about what I want to do in the
future.
Can you say something about your future?
I don't think about the future at all.
I don't have any plans for the future.
You want to be an idol until this point.
Do you think you can do it?
I think I can do it.
I don't like it.
I said something and I said something at
this time, but I can't say anything.
I'm worried about the people who are
watching.
I'm worried.
I remember you were worried about it
when we were together.
I'm afraid of the way I say it.
You said, I'm afraid of promises, so I
won't do it.
I'm the same.
It's best to have fun.
Of course, there's no one who keeps
saying that.
I want to do it in a state of fun.
I'm really an idol now.
I think you're starting to understand
the fun of acting.
I want to challenge myself more.
How did you change?
I started to work on stage.
You met a stage that suits your taste.
Is that right?
Like Shuuko Nemoto?
Yes, that's right.
It was really fun.
You don't write a blog much, but you
write a very passionate blog.
That's right.
It was really fun.
I want to do it again.
It's not like you.
It's not like me.
I want to do it again next year.
Do you not have anything to show off?
I don't have anything to show off.
Have you ever said something like this?
Can I ask you again?
I don't know.
What's wrong?
I enjoy performing on stage.
I'm glad to hear that.
It's fun.
People who only exist in live
performances.
Is it because the stage is live?
That's right.
I think so.
I didn't realize it.
It's not just a song.
It's a live performance.
I see.
I think it's fun to perform in front of
a big audience.
That's right.
That's what I mean.
I'll keep you updated.
Thank you.
Don't worry about it.
Let's shake hands while drinking.
Let's do a live performance.
It's been 41 minutes.
That's right.
It's been a long time.
That's good.
It's been about a quarter of an hour.
Don't get impatient and answer quickly.
Don't say it's not good.
I'm not scared of the other members.
Please tell them.
Yes, because I'm with Rika and Gao.
Who's next?
Yes.
The Kobayashi-san meeting was pretty
peaceful.
You were chatting all the time.
I was chatting all the time.
And it was remote.
It was remote.
Wow.
The theme was how far we could bring out
the peaceful atmosphere of Kobayashi-
san.
It was not my evil or mischievous nature
at all.
A peaceful meeting.
A peaceful two hours.
I delivered it.
Mayuma-san even asked me to be her maid.
Really?
When I was not working.
She did it for me.
That's amazing.
You can do it because you are Rika-chan.
I also asked Nakayama-san to be my maid.
I can't do it.
But that's why,
Mayuma-san also had a friend called Ko
Shoji-san.
Yes.
She was my best friend, but she had
never been involved in work.
We had a chat almost without any work.
You can do it too, Nakayama-san.
If there is someone.
You have two best friends in the world
of idols.
Yes.
You can do it with someone like that.
That sounds fun.
Here.
I want to do it.
You can do it.
Then you can talk.
I can talk.
I want to do it.
I will think about it.
Please.
I will tell you how to do it when I
can't move.
Yes.
Yay.
Do you have any work-related things?
No.
Who are you talking about?
I'm talking about the people on the
slope.
Oh, not at all.
Not at all.
I haven't had any recent partners.
I see.
I've been in touch with them a lot to
get together for a year or two.
But they are busy,
and the timing is not right,
so they are not gathered at all.
So you are saying that the people on the
slope are your friends.
That's right.
The people on the slope...
But the people on the slope...
They don't really have much work to do.
That's right.
That's why,
friends in the idol world
don't really have much work to do.
They might take pictures together at big
festivals.
That's right.
It became a buzzword that you are
talking about it with such a bare hand.
Oh.
It's not like you are a big sister.
Oh,
we are friends.
That's right.
I want to see how you will be when you
talk to your friends with bare hands.
Are you so passionate at that time?
What?
I wonder.
I think I am talking about myself a lot.
I am definitely talking about myself.
Do you think I am talking enough?
I don't think so.
I think my friends are pointing at me
and following me.
I think I am the one who is trying to
get friends together.
The name of Buster and Mugi...
No problem. I won't get angry.
I am the type of person who can say that
I want to get along with Misuna Aruka,
Kodama Ririka, and Yodayuki.
I am the type of person who can say that
I want to get along with Misuna Aruka,
Kodama Ririka, and Yodayuki.
You are a person who is very social.
Did you talk to me when you were in the
gym?
Gym? Gym?
No?
I saw a comment saying that you were in
the gym.
Gym? Gym?
I saw a comment saying that you talked
to me when you were in the gym.
I don't know you.
Who are you talking about?
I picked you up because I didn't know
you.
I am sorry.
I don't think I am talking about you.
It's okay.
But you have the ability to invite
people to you.
I have the ability to invite people to
me.
I don't care what people say if I don't
invite them.
I don't care.
You are strong.
I am strong.
Gou-san, you and Yodayuki are meeting at
the press conference.
Is that so?
I was there at the press conference when
this program started.
I heard that many people would come.
At first, King Kong, Nishino-san, and
Horiemon were on a different show.
I was a friend of them.
I was invited to the press conference.
I was the only one there.
What?
They were holding a board.
I was the only one who was cut off from
the board.
Let's look into it.
Let's look into it after the show.
I think that's the correct answer.
If a man I don't know was holding it
with me, I would have been cut off.
I see.
I'll look into it after the show.
Finally, President Maeda joined us.
We were doing a show called Kitagagen
together.
I was playing the role of President
Maeda.
I was there at the time.
I didn't talk to him at all.
I see.
That's interesting.
That's what happened.
You're so detailed.
I am.
This is like your conversation.
It seems difficult to talk to a
businessman.
It's impossible.
It's difficult.
You're seriously frightened.
I can't really talk.
But when you're doing this kind of work,
you don't have to go that far.
You don't have to talk to people from
other worlds.
You don't?
No.
I think I'm running away.
Do you get along with people you don't
know on stage?
Yes.
I don't.
Do you?
I don't know.
I think I can talk.
You were worried, but it's actually
okay.
I'm 22 years old, and I'm okay.
You can handle most things.
You don't look confident.
I'm not sure if I can do it.
Do you have any other work you want to
do?
I want to do photo books and acting.
Why do you want to do photo books?
The first one was in 2017.
2016?
I published it on my birthday about 5
years ago.
I had a goal to do this much from that
time.
That was 2022.
You were on a news program on the radio.
I don't do it.
News?
You haven't done it?
Shrimp...
I've been on it a few times.
I have.
News?
I did it a while ago.
What kind of news?
Huh?
7, 8, 9, 10...
About 4 years ago...
I think I was on it twice by myself.
You were able to handle it?
I wonder if I was able to handle it.
I don't remember.
You don't remember a lot to the point
where you're surprised.
It's amazing.
I wonder if it was able to respond.
Do you remember what you did?
You don't remember.
I don't remember.
It's okay.
There is no such problem.
There are many people who remember.
I don't know if I read the comments
wrong.
I don't remember.
That's right.
Is it economic news?
I'm doing it on the air.
I don't know anything at all.
You don't even have a clue.
That's right.
It's difficult.
It's amazing.
What was the first thing you said in an
interview with the owner of the coffee
shop?
About 2014, right after I joined Ebichu,
I was interviewed by a TV program called
TASTAS.
I was bullied by the interviewer and I
was in a big hurry.
Did you cry a lot in the past?
I didn't cry.
Did you cry when you were auditioning?
I was crying.
I couldn't sing well, so I went out and
cried to Kaoru.
That's about it.
Do you want to take a picture of the
swimsuit?
I don't think I'll wear a swimsuit, but
I want to.
It's a cool and beautiful feeling.
Please look forward to it.
The comments are coming in a great
momentum.
I can't read it at all.
I'm asking if you're not interested.
I am! I am!
I am, but I really don't remember.
The past is not forgotten.
What about you, UFO?
You forget a lot of things at a pretty
high speed, don't you?
What is the most memorable thing in that
kind of thing?
I can only remember things within a
year.
That's amazing.
I had a lot of fun.
It's just a short-term memory. Long-term
memories are gradually erased.
I wonder what I can do without this.
I've been having fun lately.
It's okay. It's okay.
On October 30th, I was doing a show
called Kashiwagi Project with Hinata-
chan.
The first show was with Rika-chan,
Ayaka-chan, Mirei-chan, Hinata-chan.
10 years of experience.
The next two shows were with Riko Kahori
and Hinata-chan.
We were six people at the encore. We
were able to do a live show with six
people who couldn't make it happen.
It was fun.
It's been a while.
It can't be helped. It's fun.
It was fun.
It was fun and I wanted it.
I wanted it.
It was fun.
That's great.
You're the type of person who forgets
about the problems in a day.
You forget everything from good things
to bad things.
I think there are parts that make it
easier to go.
That's true.
That's impressive.
I don't think I'm the type of person
who's good at interviews.
Really?
What?
Oh, I see.
I see.
It's hard to talk about the past.
I don't remember.
It doesn't swell.
If you ask me what happened that time.
It's my 10th anniversary of my debut.
I have interviews that look back on the
past.
Of course.
I can't remember.
You read other people's interviews and
think, oh, that's right.
That's right.
I remember saying that it was fun to say
things like this in the past.
I can't remember a single person.
You can't remember.
I think it's amazing.
It's a job that has a lot of
opportunities to look back on your work.
I think your memory will be restored
naturally.
I think it's going to get stronger.
I don't think there's anyone who's been
so fluffy.
But that's it.
Recently, I had my own birthday event.
I had a mysterious event where I called
my classmates from my specialty school
and my colleagues from the company I
first joined.
I don't know about the needs.
When I do that, I keep talking about
things I don't remember at all.
It sounds like fun.
I don't remember where the lid of my
memory opens.
I don't remember.
I don't remember anything like that.
I'm the one who should remember
relatively.
I can't help it.
I don't remember today's interview at
all.
I don't remember saying that I really
said it.
Let's read it all.
I don't remember at all.
The first thing is that.
Even if there are members, they kill me,
but I'm not good at summarizing words by
myself.
I'm not good at it.
Yes, I'm really not good at it.
I've been there, but I can't put it
together well.
I only talk like that.
If you think about it, you've grown a
lot.
I don't remember anything.
Even if my memory is fluffy, it's okay.
If the result is interesting, I'll be
able to do something.
I've already collected 100 comments.
It's almost an hour.
It's too fast.
It's okay. I'll pick up the questions in
the second half.
I didn't think the time would come when
I would organize a two-hour program with
Nakayama.
To be honest.
I was worried.
But it's been an hour.
It's going well.
I forgot, but I managed to do it.
I managed to do it.
Have you ever had trouble with things
you've forgotten in the past?
I've forgotten a lot of things.
I have.
I can't remember anything when the
members are talking.
Do you feel lonely when you do that?
I don't feel lonely, but...
I try to remember it, but I really can't
remember.
When you were born in an interview,
I can't remember.
What are you talking about?
So, when you were talking in the group
interview,
you were clearly heartbroken.
I'm thinking about it.
You can't remember.
You were probably fighting with
something.
I was fighting.
I was wondering what you were talking
about.
I'm starting to understand.
I forget things that were hard.
Good thing.
It's a good thing.
Well, I'm sure there were a lot of hard
things,
but I think it's probably easier to
forget.
It's probably easier to forget.
I think the results are okay. There is
nothing to worry about.
Today I'm doing it to make a decision.
I'm not trying to push you. I'm doing it
to say that's okay.
It's okay.
I'll pick up the questions a little
early.
I'll go to the question corner. I'll
pick up more and more.
You've overcome one difficult enemy.
How many more do you have?
I don't know.
You're in the top three.
You're still the same?
I'm looking for Twitter.
It's in the top three of Yoshida Go's
search.
I'm looking for Twitter.
Do you get sleepy when you remember
something?
Yes, I get that a lot.
I get sleepy.
You don't get sleepy.
No, I don't get sleepy at all.
It's just that my eyes look like that.
My eyes are drooping.
You're the type who always overwrites
what's fun.
I think so.
I'm late for my class.
I might have forgotten to cry.
15 hours?
Oh, this is when I first went to Nagoya
for my first tour.
It was my first room alone.
I was late for that.
And then, the one in front of me, Kaho,
was also late.
Kaho was crying so much.
I was watching that, so I was calm.
It was in the making and it's still
there.
Kaho was crying and saying,
I'm going to be fired.
But I was looking outside alone.
I think I was crying.
Did I cry after that?
I don't remember that.
Do you remember the lyrics and
choreography for the song?
I've been doing it over and over again.
It's okay.
You're a person who likes to dance.
I like to dance.
Did you remember that well?
I used to remember it well.
Now I'm getting worse.
I used to put in two songs a day when I
joined the army.
It was amazing then.
I like the story of the cream puff.
Cream puff.
When I joined the army,
I was eating cream puff while walking
home after the lesson.
I'm going to use my brain for a while.
It's important.
About being scared by Yuna Emma.
That's right.
Yuna Emma joined as two new members.
I'm scared.
What happened?
At the audition,
Hinata-chan said I was the boss.
I was afraid of her eyes because I was
next to her.
I was afraid of her serious expression.
It's my first time being told that.
I'm always scared of her.
I've been told Rika-chan and Hinata-
chan.
I don't feel bad about being told for
the first time.
When the two of us started fighting in
the show's prank,
Kaoha-chan was crying, but Rittan was
laughing.
It was a
two-person fight.
Did you have that kind of story?
Kaoha-chan always cries at times like
this.
I'm flustered.
What's that fluster?
When one person is crying, it's hard to
think of it.
I think so.
I'm calm.
How's your relationship with the
principal?
I haven't talked to him at all.
Relationship with the principal?
I haven't talked to him at all either.
I want to talk to him.
What kind of talk are you talking about?
The principal's guest was amazing.
The principal's sleep and water.
Oh, my God.
My sister.
She called me out of the water and the
members.
Oh, my God.
I'm glad I didn't see the principal.
It's a legend.
Thank you for watching.
I'm sorry.
It says, Paruru Akkina, my opponent.
I see.
Paruru was a strong opponent.
It was interesting.
Paruru is not wrong.
He is not wrong.
I was not so nervous about Paruru's
pressure.
I was in a good mood.
I forgot what I was talking about.
I was asked,
How is it?
I hate it the most.
Please ask me more specifically.
Is it recent?
No, when I was in AKB.
I thought it was amazing.
That's right.
I was in trouble.
That's the correct answer.
But no one can do that in their teens.
I thought it was cool.
I thought it was amazing.
I can't say it.
It's a question of each other.
Please let me talk about it.
I'll try to say it someday.
How is it?
I'm nervous.
I can't stand it.
I want to hear your memories of talking
to Angerme.
I'm in my 10th year of my major debut.
I was doing a two-man live.
Angerme was the only idol I was able to
meet.
Memories.
Hinata and Angerme's writer Rikako were
friends.
Memories.
It's the hardest question to ask.
Memories?
Angerme and Harupuro dance in high
heels.
When I first met them in their casual
clothes, they were small and surprised.
I was surprised to see them in high
heels on stage.
That's all.
It was a great memory.
Memories.
What is the most important thing when
you're washing?
What do you mean?
When you're choosing between this and
that.
For example, washing?
What's wrong with that?
I don't think it's coming out.
What is the oldest memory you remember
now?
What?
I think it's a question that's asked a
lot.
The oldest memory...
I wonder if there's nothing.
Oh, I remember.
How old was I?
I don't know how old I was. Three years
old?
Four years old? Five years old?
I was having dinner with my family,
and soy sauce...
It probably flew somewhere.
I was crying.
My brother called me and said,
If you cry so much, I'll call the
police.
I remember that very well.
Soy sauce flew somewhere.
I think my face was tingling.
I was crying.
It was too noisy.
I remember being threatened to call the
police.
You're too scared to remember.
I remember that very well.
You were seriously scared.
I was scared.
I think that's how much I remember.
What is the oldest memory you have with
Kashiage-san other than recent live
performances?
Hinata-chan...
Hinata-chan is much better than Daibu.
Yeah.
Hinata-chan...
I'm sleepy.
I started going out for dinner more
often than work.
I feel sad when I realize that
graduation is approaching.
It's like a conversation between adults.
We talk about our future, what we want
to do, and what we want to do.
Do you answer what you want to do at
that time?
What do I want to do?
Like I said earlier?
Yes, I say the same thing.
Which is better, Kikikirin or you?
It's different from the greatness of a
veteran.
It's the difficulty of a teenager.
Who is the only star you're close to?
I'm going to the bathroom.
He is saying something.
Yes.
Who is it?
Sakun?
Ah!
There was!
Ah, there was!
Tako Niji's Kiyoi Sakiti.
We did the same role together on stage
this year.
We became really close from there.
I really don't get it when things like
this happen.
I'm sorry, Sakiti.
Paru is amazing.
Kocho is still in self-restraint.
What is your role after you quit?
My role?
What is it?
Hinata-chan is now quite a dance, and
she often summarizes things other than
dance, and I don't think I'll do it
myself, but I think I'll do it well with
everyone, but I wonder what will happen.
Really, Kashiwagi-san has become a
proper viewer, hasn't she? At some
point, I really want to do it with these
six people.
Do you talk about your future with Kao-
chan?
That's right, I'll talk.
What kind of shrimp do you want to make?
What will happen? I don't know that
either.
Don't you want to do this for yourself?
But, with the five sister members, it
will be a 5-5.
I hope I can show the freshness of the
young people and the sisters well.
Did you get along with Angerme?
It's difficult, isn't it?
But I got a new contact information.
What did you think when you were in
charge of the part of Jump?
Jump is still in the works.
How did you feel?
How did I feel?
I felt a lot of pressure.
When Ayaka wasn't around.
I couldn't say it out loud.
So I didn't think about it much.
How did you feel when you were off?
How tall was I?
What was my mood?
I felt a little scared.
I have to wait.
I was waiting for this.
I got a comment saying, don't ask me
about the past.
What?
It's weird to ask me about the past.
I don't remember.
I'm sorry.
Oh, I see.
You were able to appear in the show
because you were not allowed to appear
during the show.
Was that right?
What?
Yeah.
Oh, I see.
There was something like that.
What?
Yeah, yeah.
What is your ideal idol for Riko?
What?
Ideal Idol?
Yes.
What?
Ideal Idol?
Yes.
I don't like idols, but I like idols.
I like idols.
Why is that?
Is there something you like?
I like idols.
I like idols who shine on stage.
I don't care about their private life.
I like idols who are professional at
work.
I like that kind of person.
I think it's cool.
Who is that?
Who is there?
For example, if it's STADIR, it's A-LIN.
Yes, yes, yes.
I feel like I'm doing my best.
That's right.
It's A-LIN.
You're being swept away.
I wanted to see AB6IX again, but I'm
sorry I can't.
Do you have any memories?
AB6IX?
AB6IX.
It was fun.
Who is the entertainer who felt the aura
of the first time?
Everyone has an aura.
Who is the entertainer who felt the aura
of the first time?
Manager-san will tell you everything.
He will tell you everything.
Don't you want to do something with the
two of you?
Oh, but this year, at my birthday live,
Kao-chan played ukulele and we sang
together.
We did two songs together, and this
time, we want to do a live with just the
two of us.
I want you to release a sound source.
I don't think I'll die until then.
Who will be the dance leader? I don't
know yet.
I don't know who the leader is.
Is there a possibility that you will do
something like a staff member next year?
There's no possibility. Hinata-chan will
continue to live her own way.
Hinata's managerial work is also doing
it.
I asked her what's going on, and she
said she was going to tell me what's
going on.
She said the unit was good.
Do you feel like doing a choreography
like Kashiage?
No.
I like to dance, but I don't know how to
dance at all.
It's hard to explain in words.
I can't do anything.
What do you think of the idol and
current artist path you like?
What do you ink of the idol and current
artist path you like?
I think I should do Bribri Bribri solo
live.
I think it will be fun to do it live.
Both.
Please tell us a little bit about the
idol image that you have.
Everyone wants to know.
It's difficult. What is an idol image?
But it's the same story as I said
earlier.
It's really cool to be able to do it.
Is live important?
No matter how busy you are, it's
still...
Is it possible?
It's amazing. I'm a professional.
Momokuro-chan? Everyone is like that.
It's really cool.
Is your instant block still unlocked?
I got it.
What was it? Where did I talk about it?
This is the brother who tried to report
to the police.
That's right.
I think the comments on Instagram were a
little too much.
Your brother left a lot of comments.
I don't reply to his DMs, but I
sometimes read them.
My brother was the one who wrote the
comments.
It was too much.
I asked him how I could block the
comments.
I said, okay, I'll block them.
About two years ago.
Recently, I talked about Instagram.
But I was told that I couldn't see the
post because I was blocking it.
I forgot that I was blocking it.
I don't know anything about my
activities for two years.
I felt sorry for that.
I canceled it.
Were you so scared to comment?
What was it?
It was amazing.
You think it's good, don't you?
No, I think it's probably a little...
You don't like it?
It's not good.
I don't like it.
Why do you hate your sister's Instagram?
I think it's really good.
I didn't like it a little bit.
Don't you do blonde hair?
No, I don't.
My hair...
If I bleach it, it's over.
Is it over?
My hair... They say this hair is over.
You're weak, aren't you?
I guess so.
I want you to pull out the shrimp paste.
I'll do my best.
It's a small voice.
I'll pull it out with everyone.
Can you drink alcohol?
I'll drink it.
With members.
How does it feel to drink?
I don't think it's going to change.
With this tension?
I don't think it's weak.
Can you drink it properly?
No.
I think everyone can drink shrimp paste.
Sister, member.
You're probably not making any
impression at work right now, are you?
I know.
Do you?
In the video of shrimp paste...
I drink alcohol with a sweet rice drink.
I have a story about Mr. Fujii, so I try
to avoid drinking alcohol as much as
possible.
At that time, Mr. Fujii came to my
house.
Even then, Mr. Fujii and I drank with
only the three of us.
Have you ever seen the true identity of
Mr. Mayama?
What do you mean?
Actually, it's a part like that.
Please give us an interesting recent
episode of the sloppy but ridiculous
act.
No!
Oh, I'm sorry.
I've already said it on Instagram, but
Ayaka and I are traveling to Mie
Prefecture.
We went to Ise Jingu.
There's a place called Gai...
Gai?
Gai...
It's like the place where you can find
the outside and the inside.
Is there a place like that?
Outside and inside?
No, not the outside.
Geku...
Geku and Naiku.
At first, we went to Geku.
Naiku...
We couldn't find the place.
We thought there was no place like that.
But Naiku said,
there's a place like that.
We thought it was stupid.
There's a place like that.
But it's closed.
We thought there was no place like that.
It was fun.
That's the story.
I understand that you don't like to hear
about the past.
That's right. Please don't ask.
It's been about a year or two.
What did you think of Lenny's marriage?
I was surprised.
I saw it on Instagram after the special
event.
The top of the Instagram is a picture of
Lenny and a man.
I was surprised.
I thought I made a mistake.
I wanted to tell you.
Then I will tell you.
I was happy.
I was excited with everyone.
Will you continue to be an idol even if
you get married?
It's cool.
I don't know.
I think I will continue to be an idol
even if I get married.
I don't know what the future holds.
Please do what you want to do.
Oh, I remember.
When the principal came here,
When we talked about the story of the
Kajuzonite and couldn't talk well,
I said, Mr. Yaguchi, it's okay to make
it funny.
That's why I decided to appear.
That's right.
What about the ideal?
What do you think?
I should have used it.
It's not over yet.
There's really nothing coming out.
That's right.
It's not coming out.
What would you do if you got married?
What would I do?
Would you bless me?
That's not what I'm saying.
That's...
If you want to continue,
I'll support you.
I don't know which one is the best,
but I have to support the one I choose.
I'll support you.
You said you have the ideal idol image.
What? What are you talking about?
You don't talk about that much?
No, I don't.
But you felt it somehow, didn't you?
I'm glad.
Riku Nakayama will be the ace of the new
team.
You really don't act.
I'm not sure if I'm the best.
I'm glad that the people who support me
are kind.
Is there an idol you want to talk to?
What?
An idol I want to talk to?
You haven't played Master 2 Man?
No.
Who is it?
Idol?
There's definitely someone, but I can't
think of anyone.
Do you have any songs you want to see?
I wonder what it is.
It sounds interesting.
Vish was really good timing.
Vish's orchestra was really good.
It was really good timing.
I couldn't remember.
You couldn't remember.
But there are some.
If you suddenly forget, it can't be
helped.
I'll remember it.
Thank you for watching.
Who invited you to go to Ise?
I had a lot of free time, and I was busy
with my live show at the end of
December.
I wanted to do something at this time,
so I invited her to go somewhere.
There were many things, but Ayaka felt
the charm of the sea.
So I decided to go to the sea with her.
The interview that Rittan is most
excited about is the story of the
upcoming stage.
It's difficult.
It's difficult to talk about the future.
I feel that the voice of the moment when
I was asked this question is getting
smaller.
It's difficult.
What is the topic that switches in the
interview?
What is it?
I used to like Ebichu, so I liked
talking about the past.
You went to the live with your dad.
I was very passionate about it.
It was like, at a fan event, you saw the
otaku people going wild.
That's right.
There were fans who were going all out
without the adults knowing.
I thought it was crazy.
It was a crazy scene.
But I thought it was funny.
I saw a family that was about to fall
into a pond.
Please tell us about your dad's story.
My dad's story...
I've talked about it a lot.
He started to have a dog in May.
He was very opposed to it.
He said he didn't like it because he
knew how hard it was to raise animals
when he was little.
He's the most affectionate dog now.
He's got a camera on his gauge.
When I checked it out, he was already...
It's not a baby's word, but...
He's saying that to the dog.
That's what's interesting.
Oh, I see.
When I saw the video, my dad was talking
to him.
He's talking to him.
I thought, this is how it changes.
It's interesting.
People who oppose it.
I think there are many people who like
it too much and oppose it.
Don't doubt the truth.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It's a good story. It's a good episode.
I was really surprised.
It's difficult to be in a group with
Erika.
I'll support you even if you get
married.
Even if you become a mother, you're
still a junior high school student.
It's amazing.
Well, after a while, the three of us did
everything.
That is true.
As the favorite by the watcher Satomi
The Ebi family will keep your memories.
Thank you!
Thank you for your time.
That's true.
You can leave the things you can't
remember to others.
I do this often.
I forget the story when I drink.
When I drink and hear a good story,
I call my friend and ask him to remember
it as an external memory.
I heard a great story, so I want to
remember it.
I call my favorite person and ask him to
When you wake up, you remember it again.
I forget it.
I feel like I heard a great story.
A story about this area.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Please talk about your plans.
Please talk about your plans for the
university.
For the university?
For the end of the year live?
Yes.
Thank you for watching.
The lesson...
The two new members are doing free
lessons, but they haven't met yet.
They're going to get closer in the
future.
I wonder if they're going to do
something different for the next two
days.
That's right. Hinata's graduation live
and new student.
I think it's going to be different.
I'm worried that I'll be okay if I get a
head start.
Is there anything you're interested in
in your room?
Something I'm interested in?
I was surprised the moment I came in.
You were surprised, weren't you?
But you're just surprised, so you're
interested.
That's right.
There's a lot.
That's amazing.
Do you watch other members' shows?
I don't know.
It depends on the situation.
If you are interested in it?
Yes, I will watch it.
Do you watch your own?
What kind of person is it?
For example, if you check your own
radio.
I listen to radio.
What is it? Do you get depressed?
Is it good?
I will do it.
But soon.
In half a day.
I don't think about the past or the
future.
Riko Nakayama who lives in the present.
It's cool to write it like this.
I understand why Yoshida is a strong
opponent.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I have an image that you like cute
costumes, but do you have any future
costumes?
I do. I like frilly and frilly costumes.
But no one will wear a costume of the
member of the group.
So I always wear costumes at my
birthday.
I've never seen anyone in full costume.
There was. Where was it? Kashiwa no Ha?
I often said Toyosu and Kashiwa no Ha.
There was. I was surprised.
It's a thing the principal often says.
There used to be a lot of crazy otakus.
I wonder if there were many.
It was lonely.
But it was fun. It was really fun.
What kind of person is the mayor?
I saw a lot of photos of the past on
Instagram.
I don't like the photos of the past.
So I sent him the latest photo on my
birthday.
I asked my manager to post this.
He gave me a picture of the past that I
didn't know.
only have one.
He gave me a picture of the past that I
It's not like the recent Nakayama.
Do you hate old pictures?
I hate it.
Because the face is young.
It's not bad.
I'm embarrassed.
I see.
I won't give it to you.
At that time, I was told by Yoshida that
I shouldn't approach Ebichu.
Really?
I was told.
What?
There was a time like that.
Why?
I really don't know.
When I was working with Momokuro,
Don't come to Ebichu.
This is a holy place, so don't come
near.
There was a time like that.
At that time, I was on Twitter.
I think Ebichu is a great group.
I think they have a lot of high-tech
music.
I can make a song called High-Tech.
Wow!
I haven't spoken, but I think that's the
flow.
What was your first job with Ebichu?
It was a best band.
I knew it because I was told.
I said I'd keep my distance.
I've been keeping my distance.
That's the flow.
It was a best band.
Yes.
I got an offer, so I said,
I'd like to talk to you.
From there, I had more opportunities to
work for a short time.
That's the flow.
That's great.
I didn't know anything.
It's okay.
Are you glad your mother didn't come
today?
My mother was talking more.
I think she's watching.
I think so.
You can comment on my brother's video.
I'm scared.
I'm like, I'm Nakayama.
Have you repaired the air conditioner in
your house?
Air conditioner in the house?
How many years ago was that?
I'm fixing it.
The momentum of the comments is really
fast.
Please tell me about the dog.
The story of the dog?
I don't know.
No, no.
The story of the dog?
It doesn't come out.
Dog?
I went to the dog run for the first time
the other day.
Even if it's a house, it's a lot of
noise.
But when I went to the dog run and was
with the other dogs, I was very
surprised.
Are they similar?
It was cute.
It was similar.
At home, it's amazing.
I'm kidding, but when I go outside, I
become quiet.
I like dogs.
I like to communicate with dogs.
Communication?
There are dogs that want to play.
I watch the dog and think, will this
person play with me?
I like the moment I react to the dog
playing.
I like to pat the dog that the person is
holding.
I'm trying to do that.
What kind of action do you do?
When I don't have a mask, I pat the dog
with my mouth.
I think, will this person play with me?
If it's not a dog that's crazy about
walking, it will eat.
Let's do it at the dog run.
I'll wave my hand and say, let's play.
Let's do it.
Please tell me the secret of the family
of the dog.
I think it's the opposite of the type.
Is that it?
Is it true that there is no conversation
in the family?
There is no conversation.
There is, but I don't know how the other
families are doing.
You don't know how much you're talking
about.
It was interesting that Po-chan was
pulled by a dog.
Hii?
Is it a story of MV?
What is your favorite song as a top
idol?
I listen to Nogizaka-san.
You really like that kind of middle
ground.
I like Sakura-zaka-san.
The music is strong.
I think it's useless to listen to this,
but I'll ask you.
Please tell me your first impression of
Mr. Yoshisago.
I was scared.
I thought a scary person came.
I thought a scary blonde came.
I can't speak.
Sorry.
I was not very interested in the house.
Have you been talking to him since then?
I was talking to him.
It was a peaceful interview.
It's hard to see, but don't you raise
the contrast?
Oh, that's right.
Isn't it right? Contact.
I don't think so.
But if you raise it, it gets worse and
worse.
It's worse if you wear something that
doesn't fit.
Is that so?
But today, I'm wearing something
different from my usual contact lens, so
it's harder to see today.
Recently, Kaho-chan has been doing this
pose a lot.
Really? You do it?
Apparently there is no repertory at all.
This and this.
It's really convenient to have this.
I'm doing this all the time.
I want to talk about it with this
momentum.
I always do this and do a pose like
this.
It's amazing.
It was a 15-year-old wood-fired iron,
but do you want to do something like a
surprise?
It's the best.
Oh, you did it. Right after you joined
the club.
As a surprise?
Do you want to go to the club again?
I wonder if so.
I'm looking for memories.
What about dinner today?
I don't remember.
I want to hear stories from the time of
the joint departure ceremony, but I
don't remember.
I don't remember.
I think it was when the Tendoon and the
lotus were united.
I don't remember.
Which is more similar to the Tendoon and
the lotus?
Which do you think?
My mother.
Are they similar in personality?
In life...
They are not similar.
My mother is a very talkative person.
I think that's probably my father.
My father is the one who talks in baby
language.
Are you scared?
I'm scared.
The story of the first time I met Reina
Ukaima.
Morning Musume? Reina?
Originally, Reina was pushing me, and
when I was in the 6th grade, it was the
same day as the first time, and she
called me.
It was the first time for someone to say
that at the same age, so I was very
happy.
We are still good friends.
I went to Yomiurinando the other day.
We are good friends.
You are a person who can communicate
properly.
I can do it.
Do you remember what you said when you
were taller than Mayuma?
I don't think the person who wrote this
comment remembers.
Do you remember?
I think you remember and you're asking.
I don't know. I don't remember at all.
I think I was killed right after I
talked about it a few years ago.
I don't remember.
Did you cry during the Ebichu Pride
lesson?
I remember that.
I often talk about it with the members.
At that time, I was really cornered.
I had a part in my part in Rock Lee that
I didn't believe in myself.
I had a part where I didn't have the
value to work hard.
When I was singing that part,
I was sad that someone who wasn't so
confident was singing this part.
You were stabbed.
I was surprised to see the members while
singing.
I don't know what it means.
I was stabbed.
It's okay.
I'll get over that part.
Niko-chan, don't you care about other
dogs?
I don't think so.
But after I started to have a dog,
Other dogs who were walking looked cute.
I've always thought they were cute.
I'm not a cat lover, but I like cats and
dogs.
I don't know what the difference is
between them.
I'm like, both are good.
What are you talking about?
What's the difference?
I'm like, what?
Huh?
Which one?
Huh? I like both.
I see.
I like both.
I don't get to interact with cats that
much.
Cats still have their own nora.
So they have fun communicating with
them.
Dogs don't have nora, so they have paku-
paku.
They communicate with each other.
Dogs have no choice but to communicate
with people.
They play with dogs that are waiting in
front of the supermarket.
I played with other dogs.
Oh, really?
I gave them a dog that my friend had.
I gave them better food than my friend.
You know that?
I know.
They get excited just by looking at me
while I'm walking.
I don't have a dog that I accidentally
gave to them.
They get excited when they realize I
don't have a dog.
They're smart.
They are.
They get disappointed.
What is your impression of the recent
members of the new member's style?
It was a tendon and lotus root.
Thank you for your viewing.
I want you to do something more fun.
I didn't look like that.
I want you to make a cute debut.
I think so.
The yakiniku that the person in the
voice was baking was eaten by a dog.
To explain this correctly, when I
interviewed a scary karate guy,
he asked me if I wanted to eat
something. He baked a hormone in the
garden.
I'm not a meat-eater, so I can't eat
hormones.
But he baked it for me.
He bought a cute pug.
He bit it and ate the one that didn't
taste good.
When I gave it to him, he was addicted
to it.
It was delicious.
He was a person who made me eat meat.
He was communicating like this.
Please make a memory of RINANAN.
I've been a model for a long time.
I was a model at that time, too.
I've always admired her.
She's beautiful.
She's beautiful and beautiful in
pictures and videos.
I've always admired her.
She's beautiful and beautiful in
pictures and videos.
I want to join the group.
I'm not really familiar with idol
groups.
I want to try dance and vocal.
I'm not an idol.
Do you want to try that?
I want to try dance and vocal.
I was really enjoying the song you were
singing.
Oh, the one in the middle?
It was last year, right?
In the solo corner.
Please say a few words about the
position you chose for the song.
I like it. I still like it, but I'm
really good at spicy food.
I couldn't eat spicy food before, but
now I can eat something like 3 times
spicier than the North Pole.
I'll give it up. I can't eat it at all.
I can't eat that.
About your current activities.
Oh, on the radio, in the middle of the
night.
I was doing it with you.
About my current activities?
What do you mean about my current
activities?
You don't seem to be coming out with
this.
What?
It's amazing.
Have you ever stayed at your house?
Yes, I have.
When I go to my house, my husband cooks
for me.
I can cook by myself.
Is it delicious?
Yes, it is delicious.
It's amazing.
Do you have any desire for love?
I have always wanted to have a love
relationship.
I am an idol.
You have a lot of ideal husband photos.
No.
You don't seem to think about it.
What is the live venue you want to do?
I want to do Saitama Super Arena and
Arena again.
Do you want to do a live show in Sanma-
koten?
No.
You can't think of a variety show by
yourself.
I like the expression when you're really
bad at it.
I can tell that you're serious.
I can't sleep just imagining myself on
the screen.
Do you often buy clothes?
I never buy clothes on the Internet.
Really?
I never buy clothes that fit my size.
I only buy clothes on the Internet.
How do you feel about the size?
I don't care.
Do you have a really small size?
I have a big size.
I see.
I don't want to give it to someone if it
doesn't fit.
I have to try it on.
When the price was a little higher, I
bought it from overseas.
Because it's cheap?
Because there are some things that are
not sold in Japan.
I love it.
It's really fun to watch you two on the
radio and see if you can rely on each
other.
I think I have to be strict with you.
You can do a demonstration, can't you?
Well...
I have to do it...
I'm going to be silent and let you do
it.
No, no, no, no, no. Please stop.
I can't pick up questions and make them
work.
Any member who comes close when you're
crying?
I think they all support me.
They don't cry so much.
Oh, they cry!
But I think they're all there.
Do you have a hard time with voice
training? Do you go through the same
thing in your own style?
No, it's hard.
Do you still do it?
I still do it.
Do you have a hard time with your voice?
Yes.
I think I can sing a little easier this
time.
It's emotional, but...
I want to sing a little easier.
I want to hear stories of fighting
within the family.
With members?
I wonder.
I don't think so.
In the first place?
Yes.
Not with Kobayashi?
No.
Riko, who woke up to motherhood with a
dog and new member.
That's right.
Do you have some kind of imbalance in
singing?
I do have, but..
current patch may
have caused some changes in the singing.
In the past Radon sounded
too threats to me smoking
after Requiem and
I foundichi before
every time.
Also, the voice seems
to be not smug at all,
so that will make me
Does it change that much?  Yes, it
does. It was big.
I think it's better to have a chicken
like this because it's gone.
Is there any part that's better? Like
health?
Yes, I used to get fever when I got a
fever.
But I never got a fever after I got
it.
Thank you for watching!
I was interested in Tsuya Nagamachi's
dog, too.
He took a dog with him to shoot a
movie.
His wife and family were so nice.
They were so nice.
Nagamachi's family, dog, etc.
They were trained to make a body
before shooting.
They made a studio.
They were running around with bench
press.
They were so nice.
I'm gonna do it in the tent.
I want to do it.
It's 55 minutes.
So fast.
How was it?
I did it for 2 hours.
I could do it better than I thought.
You can do it even if you are a shark.
It's hard to do it in a variety show.
You can do it in a place like this.
You are confident now.
Yes, I am.
You can do it.
Any announcement?
I have a graduation concert on
December 16th.
The next day is the first live show of
the new student.
It's at Makuhari Messe.
Is that all?
Yes.
You took 5 minutes.
I have a live show in Akita Bunko.
I do it every year.
I have a live show at the end of the
year.
You have a live show after this.
You had a time shift.
I have a solo concert at 22 o'clock.
You talk a lot.
Yes, I do.
I talk a lot.
Do you have a live show?
I want to do it. I mean, I don't have a
live show yet.
You want to see it or you want to
perform together.
Yes, I want to do it.
You are 10 minutes early.
I thought you were a fast learner.
It was fun.
It's okay.
I'm glad I didn't ignore you.
I'm glad I said I would be on the show.
I thought you were scary when you were
a child.
But you don't look scary.
When I came here today, I looked at your
photos and thought you were scary.
I thought you were scary.
Was it okay?  Yes, it was.
I'm going to pick up the questions
until the end.
What if you get an offer of 35,000
yen?
Please interview Go-san.
You like to listen to people, right?
I like to listen, but I don't ask
questions.
You just listen to people.
I don't ask questions.
Can you talk to the clerk when you try
on the clothes?  Yes, I can. But I
don't want to wear it. I run away.  I'm
just like that. I don't like the store.
I see.  I don't like the
communication when I buy clothes at the
store, so I buy clothes without trying
on.  Me too.   Do you want to try the
variety of the body?
I want to do the TV program.  If you
want to do it, you can try various
things.  No, I don't want to do it.
I really want you to find a variety show
of the local variety.
I will do my best.
I really can't believe this.
Thank you for watching.
How much is okay?
How much?
For example, it's safe to say that you
don't have to go.
I've been out.
It's safe to say that, but it's like
this.
The way the entertainer is doing it,
it's like that.
I'm scared.
But if I do it, I'll do my best.
Please tell us about your personality in
one word.
No.
Well, it's difficult. I don't know what
kind of person I am.
Please tell me something.
I've heard it before. I've heard it in
the first interview.
What did you say?
I said I was going to write a fluffy
answer.
I've heard it six years ago.
Then you're right. I don't know what
you're thinking.
First of all, what is your personality
like when you judge yourself?
It's like you're doing it because you
have a member.
You don't even know what you're saying
when you're alone.
I don't think that's your personality.
It's definitely not my personality.
What are you thinking about?
I don't know if I'm right or wrong, but
I think I'm that kind of person.
Correct answer.
Congratulations.
It was correct.
It was correct, so it's time.
It was a long time ago.
After this, it will be archived on
YouTube, but there is no problem.
It's okay.
I'll go up as it is.
Like that, next time, I wonder if the
guest will come out.
Next time, from November 24th to Tuesday
at 20 o'clock, the guest is Daisuke
Tsuda.
Do you know Daisuke Tsuda?
It's okay. I don't know.
It's Daisuke Tsuda.
Thank you for your time today.
Thank you very much.