That was the first time I got ready for
it.
I felt like I could fly.
I got lighter and I love sweet potatoes.
I went to a sweet potato cafe and ate
sweet potatoes with a sweet potato
bread.
You're pretty simple.
That's right.
I didn't want to lose to my brother.
Yakan and Idol
I'm Yakan, born and raised in the old
living room of Viva Home.
This is the second time I've been in
this room.
Let's call today's guest.
This is an idol.
Hello.
I don't know where to look.
You can look at the camera.
Let's look at the camera.
The fans will be happy.
I'm Kiyama Ai, born and raised in the
old living room of Viva Home.
Nice to meet you.
You're here.
I'm Kiyama Ai, born and raised in the
old living room of Viva Home.
I'm here.
You've grown up a lot.
I'm glad. Thank you.
I was watching you while writing the
nightclub.
Really?
This year?
I will be 23 years old.
23 years old?
That's right.
It's 2022, so you're in your 20s.
I was born in January 2000.
You shouldn't give information until
January.
January 10th.
January is a good time.
It's already the beginning of 2000.
That's right.
What day is it?
It's the 10th.
I will be 23 in 10 days.
You will be 23 in 10 days.
That's right.
I've been listening to this feeling for
a long time.
You're the manager.
You're a little shy.
That's right.
I'm very impatient.
When I'm waiting for the signal...
It's okay.
Please wait for the signal.
When I'm waiting for the red signal,
I think it's a good start when it turns
blue.
Then it becomes the first.
Will it end?
I want to get the first place.
Sometimes that happens.
I want to hear that.
I've been running since I was little.
I'm the best.
I have an older brother.
I don't want to lose to my older
brother.
I've been living like this.
I don't want to lose to my older
brother.
I don't want to lose.
I'm going to lose, but I don't want to
lose.
I've been living like this.
When the signal is good,
I think it's the best.
I'm walking.
Is your brother impatient?
My brother is also...
My head is spinning fast.
When you have a good relationship,
When you have a good relationship, you
have a quarrel.
My brother is stronger.
I'm told in cool words.
I don't understand.
I don't like to lose.
I don't analyze people's thoughts.
Today, I showed you various sides of Ai.
I'm eating dessert.
I like it.
Some people eat skin and others don't.
That's right.