We are Super Tokimeki Sennebu!
Thank you for watching!
Today we will be talking about the star
name present that the members named.
The title of our single is Star.
We chose the star name present as the
star's special feature.
The star name present.
We will be explaining what the star name
present is.
The star name present is called the Star
Naming Gift.
It is a service that you can name a star
and send it to someone important.
The Australian Springbrook Observatory
will find the star and send the name to
the person.
Each member of the Super Star
will name the star and send the name to
the person.
The star will be the only star in the
world that will be received by the
person.
The star will be named after the
Springbrook Observatory.
The star will be named after the 6th or
2nd star.
The 6th star is said to be visible even
with naked eyes.
If you are chosen, please look up at the
night sky and enjoy the wonderful time
we have.
The Australian Springbrook Observatory
is the research center of NASA.
It is a world-famous observatory that
has been providing Korean images to
NASA.
That's amazing.
We will be explaining the star names
that we have thought of in advance.
Let's introduce the names that we have
thought of.
It's the first time we're naming a star.
I was thinking about what to name it.
We will start with Kanamin.
The name of the star that I thought of
is Starmin.
It means the star of 2022.
We will put the name of the star on the
star and keep it in the record this
year.
I hope you will remember the year 2022.
That's what I thought of.
It's a good name.
The star that I thought of is Anjulia.
It's a star.
I was thinking about what to name it.
There are many stars with the letter SU
at the end.
I wanted to name it Anjulia because it
was called by Julia.
It's easy to understand.
I'm glad to hear that.
The star that I thought of is Love Star.
It looks delicious.
It's like a character.
I wanted to make the world where the
world is full of love.
I wanted to deliver love to everyone.
I named it Love Star.
Love is in it.
The name of the star I thought of is
Smiley Kira Star Haru Sharp 105.
I thought of stars as sparkly.
Kira Haru is cute.
I put my birthday in it.
The name I wrote is Starkey.
Starkey is similar to a star.
Starkey Starkey Starkey Starkey
I thought it was similar.
I wrote Starkey.
1 is written after the fire.
I thought it was very similar to love.
I want to use the number.
I named it Starkey.
Love Starkey
The name I thought of is
Star Dan.
Our agency is Starbust.
Star fragment
I named it Starbust.
1 and Hiyorin's N.
I named it Star Dan.
Hiyorin Star Dan 1
I want to be the best star.
I think it's a lie.
Star
No
I named it Starbust.
I named it Star Dan.
I wanted to put something in it.
I will write the name of the star in the
application form.
I will write the anniversary and the
star.
Let's write it.
It's the first time to write it.
It's fun.
This application will be registered at
the Spring Brook Observatory in
Australia and will be issued with a star
name certificate.
We will put the stars in the clear frame
here and put the star name certificate,
and the Australia Spring Brook
Observatory leaflet,
two entry tickets for the Spring Brook
Observatory,
and a naming star position map that
shows where the star is.
Wow!
It's fun!
Listen to the live music and apply for
the application!
For more information, please check the
official homepage or social media!
We'll be waiting for your applications!
So, lock on to your heart!
This was Takimeki-Sanrem!