The title of the night!
What is this?
It's a spicy ramen.
It's not a spicy ramen, but a spicy
ramen.
I like ramen with umami.
If it's just spicy, I get numb and lose
my sense of taste.
I don't feel like it's too spicy.
I like ramen that has umami and is
delicious and spicy.
Is there any ramen that you recommend?
I like the ramen of Nakamoto.
I also like the cup ramen of Nakamoto.
I like the frozen one. It's spicier.
There is a ramen of Nakamoto.
It's delicious.
I also like the ramen of Miyazaki.
I also like the ramen of Nishin.
I like the ramen of Nishin.
I like the ramen of Shirunushi.
I like the ramen of Shichigano.
I eat those three kinds of ramen at
home.
I see. You can eat those at home.
You can eat spicy food, right?
Yes, I can.
It's delicious and spicy.
Is there any other spicy food besides
ramen?
I like the ramen of Marbou Dofu.
I like the ramen of Shisenfu and
Sanshouwa.
I like the ramen of Suikake.
You eat it while sweating.
Yes, I eat it while sweating.
I like the ice cream I eat after that.
You eat ice cream after that.
Is there a member who is the most spicy?
I like Oharu and Hiyorin.
I often go to eat with Oharu.
I often go to eat with Oharu and
Nakamoto.
I often exchange information with
Hiyorin.
I enjoy it.
I'm a little spicy, but Hiyorin is more
delicious when it's spicy.
I like Korean spicy ramen.
I like spicy food that is a little spicy
but different from K-TOWN.
You like spicy food.
Do you get told by your vocal trainer
not to eat spicy food?
I'm modest before the live.
You're modest before the live.
I see.
I had a live on October 22nd, but I
stopped it for 12 days.
Really?
You didn't eat ramen for 22 days?
That's amazing.
I try not to get swollen.
I try to do it.
That's the best thing to do when you're
in front of the audience.
That's great.
I really wanted to eat it.
I was really worried about it.
I was watching the show with my favorite
ramen.
Really?
I decided to stop eating it, so I
stopped eating it.
To be continue.
It's amazing. It's changing
periodically.
Please subscribe to this channel.
I'm sending this video to you with the
support of
Super Excited Keisuke,
Nara's Yuya,
Nickname Nashi,
and Tanazoku Hiroro.
Thank you for your continued support.
Please subscribe to this channel.