I'm Nagisa Kojima, a second-year high
school student from Nagano prefecture,
and I'm 17 years old.
ta-dah
That was so kind
No one has stepped on snow yet
Can you all see what our stages are
covering by now?
That's a layer of snow
See?
Look at this!
Wait, I don't have a camera.
Wait, I can't see it.
This is the biggest snowfall of the
year.
I'm happy that it's almost Christmas.
When I was in elementary school, I used
to play a lot of snowball games.
I used to play dodgeball and other
sports.
But I stopped playing since I became a
high school student.
I'm heading to the construction site.
I heard that if you apply this to your
head, you'll get smarter.
I do this every year.
I used to apply it to my head when I was
taking the exam.
I applied it to my head more than usual.
I'm here.
I'm going to go pray now.
I'm going to pray.
I can't do none of these.
I'm at Hankichi.
What is this?
I don't know if it's good or bad.
Good morning.
I'm here to eat.
I don't know. I don't know what Hankichi
is.
I hope it's good.
I'm going to the second shop.
The shop I'm going to is...
When I went there last time, it was
delicious and nice.
I'm going to go there now.
What flavor should I eat?
I'm going to eat my favorite Mitarashi
dumplings and Oyaki.
I've loved Oyaki since I was a kid.
My grandmother used to make it for me.
I haven't been to my grandmother's
house, so I'm happy to eat Oyaki.
I'll enjoy it.
I'm really sleepy.
I ate Oyaki for the first time.
I bought it because it said it was
popular.
It's really good.
What is this?
I'm sleepy.
It was delicious.
I've been learning piano since I was in
kindergarten.
I learned it until this March.
Today, I would like to share my favorite
piano with you with this snowy scenery
in Nagano Prefecture.
That's right.
It is one of my favorite pastures
It's good to look at with a keen eye
I want you to see it
Now
Translated by Releska