Night time and idols!
So, we've done three of them.
Can I take a break before the ending?
Yes!
I have some time to have some tea.
Wow!
The night time is big.
Thank you very much.
If you say so, I can serve you a warm
cup of tea.
Then, I'll have a cup of tea.
Is it okay?
Yes, it's okay.
Thank you.
It's very warm.
It smells good.
I'll try it.
This is the real night time.
Thank you.
I was waiting for you.
I was worried that I would drink if I
saw the
sennori-so.
I'm relieved that it was delicious.
It's an office that I can't trust.
I'm relieved that you can trust me.
Night time and idols!
Do you have any announcements?
Yes, on November 12th,
we will have a live performance called
Rock the Bolt at Saitama Heavens Rock
Saitama Sintoshin VJ3.
And, on November 20th,
we will have a live performance called
BOLT Autumn Special at the Tokyo Dance
Hall.
And, on December 23rd,
we will have a LUNA Festival at Yokohama
Bay Hall.
LUNA Festival?
Yes, LUNA Festival is a one-man live
performance
that Naito Luna will produce on the day
of her birthday.
By the way, the one-man live performance
at the dance hall on November 20th
is my birthday.
I see.
At Rock the Bolt on November 12th,
it will be a big challenge.
I'm sure the manager will be worried if
you miss this time.
I don't think you should miss any live
performance.
But, I hope you will make sure
that you don't miss any live
performance.
I hope you will.
I can't believe it.
We are working hard for that.
I hope you will come.
We are waiting for you.
And, we will release the fourth single
of BOLT.
We are also holding a release event
tour.
Please check the official website of
BOLT.
Thank you.
How was it to talk with you today?
I was looking at the camera.
I was able to learn a lot from my three
main points.
I think many people got to know me.
I was able to talk about a story that I
haven't talked about much.
I see.
I would be happy if you liked me.
Please close the camera.
That was BOLT's Chihon Takai.
Bye bye.
BOLT's Chihon Takai
Let's invite our guest today.
This is our idol.
She is a goddess.
I'm a goddess.
Congratulations.
She is a guest.
I'm a liar.
You are a liar.
I was chosen as one of the top 10 idol.
You were a little bit confident.
I'm the first place.
I think I've won 30 times in one song.
That's a lot.
I've been doing a lot of songs lately.
I think I've improved my Korean.
You've improved your Korean.
I was praised.
I'm glad.
I'm a liar and an idol.