Having her apologize, Nozinomi center
OPT2
DEVIl OST
Shooting Harmony
I'm hungry.
I got it, I got it
I got it
You need to get it
It's a steamed bun
Only this?
There are two loopholes in 9 steamed
buns
What?
I will announce the contents of the
loopholes first
What is it?
Ta-da
No way
Bye
No, it's impossible.
It's a flounder.
This is a flounder.
It's a caterpillar.
I don't know what that caterpillar is.
I don't need a caterpillar.
It's a lizard.
I don't need it.
Why do you eat that?
It's better not to eat it.
Is a caterpillar that kind of insect?
Oh, it's like a lizard?
Wow, it's not funny.
It's not funny.
Then I'll go.
Don't hold it.
The food has arrived.
I don't know why it's lined up next to
me.
Because you're the first one.
It's okay.
It's amazing that I got this right.
I'm sure you'll get it right.
I'm sure it's okay.
Hello, Mirei.
Thank you for eating.
I did it.
I'm going to eat this.
It might be in here
What is it?
It's not in here
I found it!
Start!
I'm in! I'm in! I'm in!
I'm happy, I'm happy
I'm happy, I love steamed bun and
chocolate
We're on air
Well, Aya-chan
Yes
How about this steamed bun?
But, when you put it in your mouth, it's
a little
Ah, like a tamarind
This is a little
This is
Your face is
OK, I've decided
Steamed bun roulette
I want to eat it
What is that?
I'll eat it
Are you going to poison me?
Are you going to go for a vertical
attack?
I thought my jaw would hurt
To be continued
No?
You did it!
Phew!
I feel so good
Ahhhh!
How do you feel?
I feel like a bug is biting me
A bug is biting you?
I feel so good when my teeth and the bug
are overlapping
I did it!
We are the third
What should we do?
I don't know
I chose this
What kind of bug do you like?
I like white ones
You mean like a larva?
Yes, larva
I like those that are not mature
How do you feel?
Is it really okay?
I'm not an experienced person
It's okay
Mushipan roulette
Start!
I'm going to start
Oh dear
表情 Alright?
Perfectgram
Go~!
She has promise
Thank you for watching!
Family dance
Let the fourth Walker go
Since he likes bread
How do you do?
You don't look like someone who would be
such an unreliable person
I hope you get the delicious bread
Hello, Walker
I will go home, just go home
Did you sign it?
With such creative力
He grabbed and wrung out the inside
What?
U- cannons
He waved at us
Now go on aрут of the game
Oh!
Good luck!
Is it good?
I was scared just now
Target found
Can we eat bugs?
No?
Not really
I don't think we hate bugs
I don't hate them but I don't like them
Nishipandoretto Start!
I want you to go to the side of the
tree.
You are studying very carefully.
What are you studying?
He sounded like an UFO catching close-
up.
It looks difficult.
It's amazing.
I decided to do this.
How is it? Are you confident?
It's amazing.
Don't lie.
What? I didn't lie.
It's amazing.
Miki-Pandere, start!
I don't know if I can open it
It's not in there
Yay!
It's hard
I forgot how to do it
Hello
The last one is Aiai
I'll open it
I can open it
Aiai, start the Mishpan roulette
Mishpan is good
Mishpan
Oh!
I don't know, it's chocolate
Bye bye
Aiai!
And there's more with a funny trick.
Is it good?
So this one was a jab
What the heck is that?
It's good
But that's not a cow
How was it everyone?
At the end you were able to deal with
the snakespad
The hunger delivered by the snakespad
was no less enough
The game is Winner square
Thank you.
Let's eat eat eat
Let's try our meal as we are quite
interested
Cooking Antonio
3.2.1
Great!
It looks like a deep-fried potato
I'm sure there will be
It's sticky
It's like this is combined with
chocolate
It's good, right?
It's like French fries
It's okay
It's okay?
It's good, right?
Wait a minute
It's okay
I'll do the same thing again
Please subscribe to my channel!
Oh, it's good!
I didn't have any idea what this was
when I was in parenting.
As soon as I ate my popsicles, I
thought,
... or really if it's really broken....
Ah!
El Ministro
We're in the middle of a debut!
So, let's see the results.
Wow!
What is this?
It's a monster!
There's a monster!
It's popular among young girls.
Wow!
Oh my god!
Who's going first?
Do you want to go first?
No, you go first.
Okay, let's do it.
You're going to take a picture of me?
I think it's better to take a picture
before that.
You're the best!
Thank you.
There are two out of ten.
What?
I love you!
Okay, let's start.
Miss Band U Red!
Good luck!
It's not in the cup.
The second one is Rino's.
I'll put it in the studio.
I'll put it in this.
Let's eat.
Eat it.
It looks delicious.
It's very delicious.
Let's eat.
I don't know.
Is it okay?
I think it's okay.
How is it?
It's elastic.
It's elastic, so I'm wondering if it's
in the cup.
It's there.
I'm sorry.
I haven't eaten it, but my butt is
getting bigger
No way
I'm so sorry
I wonder how big it is
I don't know
What are the experts behind you?
It's like that
Oh, I did it
It's not that good
It's not good. I want to eat it
deliciously
Experts, come back and sit down
Let's go to the next one
I'm sorry
We are in the middle of a wedding
How is the second one?
This one
It looks good
I don't know
Let's start the first one
It's like the last one
My butt is getting bigger
What's going on?
Isn't it different?
It's not in
What's going on?
Please look forward to the next one!
Witnessing the design of SNS
Thank you!
Which one do you want to choose?
This one!
I think it's a little bit wet
What did you like about it?
It's beautiful square shape
It's beautiful!
Certainly, the way of cutting is
beautiful
If it was cut inside, it would be broken
It's beautiful because it's A-type
Certainly, it's beautiful
It seems that there is also such a snack
Mishipan roulette, start!
I'll eat it!
Hit it!
It's a little bit short
It seems to be all right
Wait a minute!
I can't reach it
The butt?
What?
You said it without saying anything
It hurts!
You said you wanted to turn it
I'll open it right away
I see
It hurts!
I'm glad I didn't fly with this.
I'm scared. Are you OK?
I'm OK. I'm flying normally.
I turned on the switch.
You didn't know?
I'm communicating with someone.
I feel like a ramune.
If I mix it with sweets, I think it's
delicious.
I don't know. It tastes like myunmyeon.
I'm going to myunmyeon.
Hello!
How is it?
I chose one.
Which one?
This one.
You said it was a beautiful shape, so I
wonder if you got the right one.
It's a dance, right?
I'll take this one.
You'll take this one?
Mukbang roulette, start!
Let's eat!
I'm going to hit you
Are you there?
I found you!
Why did you hit me?
Don't you hit me here?
I'll hit you a little bit
I found you, didn't I?
Oh, no!
I found you
Why did you hit me?
I'm not a friend of insects, so I don't
hit you
You'll meet insects soon
I don't like insects
Let's go from this way
I'll hit you from there
Let's open the door and check which way
it is
Let's check
It's better to open the door
I'll hit you
I can imagine
I feel like an angel and a devil are on
your head
That's right
Let's go
Do we break it?
Let's break it
Will it go in?
I'm scared!
Luna!
Bite it!
What?
It's a horror movie!
Please subscribe to our channel!