1st place
The remaining is
Yes, 1st place
1st place
And Hina-chan
And I'm Ai Kawayakata
You have a daughter, right?
I don't want to
I think it's fine to have her as a
regular member of the group
No, no, no
You can do it
The third place is this
Come on, come on, come on
I got it, this is just right
The gap between the left eye and the
right eye is a bit narrow,
but you can show a very high level of
concentration
And when you set a goal,
you try to achieve it without shaking
your left eye
But it's a straight line
I like to concentrate
I like to make something in a quiet
place
I like to relax
Great
Here is Hirota's 2016 detailed fortune
Say something good, Ikebukuro
Great, great
I'm the one who wants it the most
I think I can bring it to you with my
luck
That's true
It's important
Amazing
If you have a goal, you will act to
achieve it
But it's hard to see around you
And you tend to be around yourself
So if you listen to people's opinions,
you'll be lucky
It's also a year of growing up by
meeting a lot of people and seeking new
encounters
It's important to listen to people's
opinions
I think it's meaningless if you don't
enjoy the time when you're 17 years old
So I think you should think more
I'm curious
I want to be 17 soon
I want to polish myself like I'm really
old
Like a flower?
We're done!
The remaining members are Ayaka, Hinata
and me.
I'm nervous! I'm so nervous!
I'm confident!
To be continued!
The winner is...
Come on, come on, come on...
Oh!
I won!
I'm so happy!
The second place goes to Hinata.
She is curious, imaginative, and has a
good sense of judgment.
She is easy-going, but she is weak in
flattery.
That's it!
If I get a little shy, I can easily get
flattered.
Wow!
She is good on average.
She is very good at girls.
39 points.
I feel lucky.
I'll report this.
She is good at girls.
Really?
She is lucky in general, so if she takes
care of her intuition, she will have the
best year.
And she has a very good skin color.
She is very lucky, but...
Her compliment is 80% right.
Her skin is very shiny.
I can see her skin's color.
Thank you for watching!
Before we announce the winner, we have a
bonus announcement.
What is the bonus?
You can drink this.
I don't care about your fortune.
I will announce the personality of the
manager, Kofujii.
She has narrow eyes and narrow left and
right senses. She is a nervous person
and is very serious.
Is she busy with work and lack of sleep?
Or does she have no sense of justice?
A big negative factor.
I'll put a pillow on her.
Let her sleep.
Kizuna AI
Finally.
We are the two who are going to sleep.
Really.
This is hard.
That's why I'm the first.
I'm happy when I think I'm the last and
I'm the first.
I'm the last.
I'll go.
Please.
This is the result of 2016.
The result is...
The third time.
Congratulations.
It's hard.
I don't want to do it.
I'll announce the personality of Ayaka.
Cheer up.
I'll read it.
She has a delicate heart and a sensual
personality.
She has a high sense of smell and a
tight mouth.
She is a lucky face.
Her contrast between black and white
eyes is clear.
She has a bright eye.
She is full of energy.
Her skin is beautiful.
She is healthy.
She is very energetic.
She is like a person who takes a bath.
I'll wear the costume of the next new
song.
Please look forward to the next.
I did it!
Wow!
What is this?
Touch!
You can see your luck by the color of
your skin and the shine of your eyes.
People come to the shining things, so
good luck will gather.
This year, you are in good luck, so if
you go forward with confidence, the
result will follow.
I'm not happy to be shining.
I used to like the eyes of Mayuma-chan's
dead fish.
Are you comparing?
Really?
Yes.
Are you comparing?
I'm not happy to be shining.
The winner is...
This one.
Who is it?
I'm sorry.
I read it worse than that.
It's okay.
With a sharp mouth,
Even with a closed mouth,
Between the upper and lower lips,
Draw a curved line like a wave.
I have a loved lip.
This is THE IDOL GROUP.
That's great.
If you live a proper life and take care
of your health,
You'll have a big break in popularity.
You eat with a big bite.
That's it.
You are a cute and loved type.
You can be forgiven for doing anything.
You should be careful.
This is you.
I've been thinking a lot about eating
with a big bite.
You?
No.
I'm not.
I'll forgive you.
Really?
The winner is...
I'm so good at drawing.
It's only one point different from me.
You're a girl of 10 years old.
That's great.
It's hard to react because I saw the
picture.
That's right.
It's good.
But, you're the tallest.
That's right.
But, you're back to reality.
Finally, I'll give you a lucky draw for
2016.
You have a good face color.
So, your luck is going up.
In addition, I want another person with
a good-looking hair style.
I want you to have a good-looking hair
style.
I'm going to do it.
Don't worry.
I'll do my best.
The head of the school stopped me, but I
should have cut my bangs shorter.
I want to cut my bangs. Let me cut my
bangs.