I'm Negishikare.
Today, my wish came true.
I will visit the anime sites in Tokyo.
Thank you, everyone.
There are places I've always wanted to
visit.
Today, I will visit the top 3 places
I've always wanted to visit.
I'm now in Arakawa.
I will explain what kind of anime it is
later.
It's a pilgrimage.
It's hard to do it alone.
I want to take a picture.
I have invited another person.
She is Saho Tanaka.
She also likes anime.
She came here today.
Thank you.
It's a pilgrimage to the place where
anime is based.
It's very fun.
It's like the scenery I saw in anime.
I will go alone and with my mother.
With your mother?
Are you watching it with your mother?
No.
I will take a picture.
You are friends with your mother.
Yes.
Thank you.
Let's go.
What kind of anime do you like?
I like interesting anime.
I like comedy.
I like Zombie Land.
I miss that anime.
I like Megami Tensei.
I like the weird one.
I like the one with the worst story.
I am impressed by it.
I know.
I know it well.
What kind of anime do you watch?
I watch anime.
You are very popular.
I chose three points today.
They are all love comics.
I like Jiro Kome.
I see.
What do you do in the pilgrimage?
I go to the places where the anime was
based.
I can't go to the places in the other
world.
For example, in the school, there is a
place where the anime was based.
I go there and take pictures in the
school.
I feel like I can enter the school.
I can see the world.
You can see the places you wanted to go.
I can see the places I wanted to go.
I can't see the places I wanted to go.
I'm happy.
The 3rd place we wanted to go to is...
Koito Senkyo and Chocolate's Junrei
Seichi!
Yay!
It's called Aragawa Rock Gate.
It's a place that appears in Koichako
several times.
It also appears in the beginning.
It appears suddenly.
It also appears in the second half.
It's a place that's a key point.
I see.
I'm glad to hear that. It's a rock gate.
It's a real one.
Wow.
It's amazing.
I wanted to take a picture of this.
What kind of picture will you take here?
I'm not sure.
I want to take a picture of various
places.
That's good.
The 4th place we wanted to go to is...
Koito Senkyo and Chocolate's Junrei
Seichi!
How do I take a picture?
How?
Like this?
What should I use?
Your phone.
How?
I thought you were a bicycle.
I'm so happy.
Can I take a picture of you riding on
the bike?
I'll take a picture from here.
I'll take a picture.
Cheese!
I'm so happy.
Thank you so much!
How do you feel about being the 3rd?
I've never thought I could come here.
I'm so happy to be here.
I'm so happy that I feel like I'm in
this world.
Thank you so much.
Let's move on to the 2nd place.
Let's go to the 2nd place.
Let's jump and move.
Ready, set, go!
We came to the 2nd place.
I think we jumped well.
We did the opposite.
We changed our fashion.
Where is this place?
What is this place?
This is the site of the work, How to
raise a wild boar.
I'm already looking at it in front of
me.
It's called Saekano because of the way
to raise a wild boar.
This is the main place of Saekano.
I see.
This is also the place where Saekano's
great name was born.
This is the place where they met.
I'm already standing on it.
You are already climbing.
This is the holy ground of Saekano,
Saka.
What do you want to do here?
I want to take a lot of pictures.
The story of the heroine of the Saekana
is that Kato-chan is standing on the top
of the hill.
The story of the Saekana is that Kato-
chan wants to make a game.
I want to make it more gorgeous in the
anime.
But it's too plain.
The color is amazing.
Thank you.
This is a broken one.
Are you going to climb this now?
Yes, I am.
Let's climb to take a picture.
The story of the Saekana is that Kato-
chan wants to make a game.
I want to make it more gorgeous in the
anime.
Wow, amazing.
It's so nice.
She must be a fan of you.
I don't know.
It's a little hard.
I'm fine.
Good.
I'll leave it to you.
I'll run to the other side.
See you.
I'll take a picture.
Cheese.
See you.
Where is the best place?
There is a scene where the hat falls
down.
The animation may not be so long.
I think it's a good place to say that
the hat falls down around here.
I see.
It's a meeting place, so I'm glad I took
a picture.
I want to bring the same hat.
I want to take a picture with the hat.
It's a good place.
The top of the mountain is where Kato-
chan stands.
We have arrived at the top of the
mountain.
It's a little hard.
It's a steep slope.
It's 22% of the slope.
It's amazing.
I can't understand it only here.
It's good, isn't it?
I'm going to take a lot of pictures
because there are no people.
I took a good picture because it was
beautiful when I took a picture like
this.
I'll take a picture with an air drone.
Thank you very much.
I'm happy to be able to take a picture
from the top.
I took a picture.
It's the best!
Are you satisfied with the second place?
I'm very satisfied!
I'm so happy that I passed the second
place.
I'm glad I could come here.
I've always wanted to come here.
Thank you very much.
Let's go to the first place!
Please!