This time, it's a new project.
Ebi-chuu 365th day.
They focus on a certain day of Ebi-chuu.
Perfectly in sync.
In the rehearsal of the first tour,
there was a figure of a member unknown
and a drama.
How are you feeling, Yasu-san?
I'm not getting better.
Something strange happened to Yasumoto.
What are the memories of the tour that
you saw at that time?
It would be better to leave an Personal
ahan
Let's do it!
Monatorium! Monatorium! Monatorium!
Let's show off our skills!
This program is brought to you by these
sponsors.
New Project, Ebi-Chu 365th Day
A project to focus on a certain day and
get close to Ebi-Chu members
The day to get close is
April 16th, 365th Day
This day is the first day of rehearsal
for the spring national tour which is
coming in a week
Ebi-Chu, the first day of rehearsal
The one who came to the studio with the
most energy is Aika Hirota.
She is still a newbie.
Good morning.
I'm most nervous during rehearsal than
during the actual performance.
So I'm nervous today.
I'm so nervous.
Thank you.
Good morning
And the last one who came at the last
minute of meeting time is
Good morning
As I want to it be Pentapц
The schedule for this day is like this
We are planning to rehearse all night
long, focusing on the new songs that we
haven't sung and danced to yet
The members who entered the studio are
now in their lesson suits
I take off my shoes and do it.
Yes, I do it to make a sound.
It's still the first day, so start with
stretching in a relaxed atmosphere.
I'm scared
What should I do?
Let's do it together
Let's do it
For some reason, the stage production is
involved
I'm scared
I can take a good picture
After being satisfied with the staff, it
is a physical training
I'm surprised
Next, vocal practice
Nishiyama-sensei, who is in charge of
voice training during the heavy, will
also participate in the rehearsal from
this day.
And the last of the preparation exercise
is
Yes, last run
One two
One two, go
Yes, go
I'm sorry
One two
Yes, run
One two, go
One two
Thank you
Last run
One two
What are you doing?
I'm doing exercise
But you are always in the front
I always become the front
This is how the voice training is over
The ones who check the new song, the
dance of the acne is
Kashiwagi and Yasumoto
I'm going to do it
Is it your turn?
I did it
I'm not a
date
I'm not a date
From the title of acne
To the age of a date
I want to be a blowfish
One blowfish
The title is blowfish, right?
No
Who is a blowfish?
Rika is a blowfish soon
Dangerous
When everyone becomes an adult, who
looks like a child?
Because it's me
I can always be called a pimple
I'm sorry
It's like a person from heaven
Because it's not a social race, I can't
look like the youngest even if I stand
normally
Look at the face of the cashier
Everyone's face
After the preparation exercise,
including such a chat, it is finally
confirmed that the choreography
First, try to dance without holding a
microphone
This time, we will show you the new song
of the 8th title.
8 songs at once, the members who are
still not fully in their minds
Let's dance again
I wonder if I can see the lyrics.
Interesting.
I can't see the lyrics at all.
The lyrics don't get into my head.
Like a rush.
I wonder if I can say it.
Close close, your eyes are coming out.
I'm going to work hard today.
The training is over.
The training starts.
40 minutes start.
I'm going to eat ramen.
They take a 10-minute break before the
rehearsal.
What is it?
Then...
I want to eat ramen.
There is ramen, right?
I eat ramen from now on.
I love ramen.
Where do you live?
I love this ramen.
This is very delicious.
I'm old.
I'm already talking about it.
I'm talking about the usual.
I don't know.
The topic is about Hoshina's college
life.
I think she cares about what to eat.
I ate hash browns and sandwiches with
fruit.
They looked very delicious.
I ate both.
I was told off by everyone.
I think so.
I didn't think so.
I didn't think it was noisy.
I thought you were a woman who was very
shy.
But you were actually an old man.
I thought you were a woman who was 360
degrees.
I thought you were a woman who looked
from there.
You are talking a lot.
This is also a story of a new life.
When I went to the entrance ceremony,
I was told that there were too many
people who showed themselves.
I thought it was bad, so I had to tell
them.
But I didn't know what to do, so I just
went ahead.
I apologized.
Didn't you tell them you were a member
of the Kobayashi-san mission?
I didn't tell them at all.
I was wondering why.
I was wondering if it was good or bad.
The break is over, and the rehearsal for
the song and dance is finally starting.
Thank you.
Shut!
I'm ¿the convinced?
The truth is a queasy
hell
Thank you for watching!
I'm
Thank you very much. Please check the
sound.
Mayama is struggling to say that it is
not perfect yet.
Thank you very much.
It's a new song, so it's okay not to
play it.
Next is the rehearsal of the spring
break moratorium junior high school
students.
New song
Are you watching Kaeki-chan?
Kaeki-chan
I'm going to sing now.
Moratorium
But I can't do it at all because it's
not finished yet.
But I'll have another lesson, so it's
okay.
I'm watching a lot.
The one in charge of the choreography
was the real Mikiti of the female idol
Nicho Haro.
What kind of person is it?
I love you, Mikiti.
I was worried about my hair.
My hair is falling apart, so I can't
dance.
Everyone, do it.
I can't dance.
Cute
Stop it.
I can't.
I forgot the choreography.
Thank you for watching.
Please subscribe to our channel.
It's hot.
This.
What is this?
It's really cool without hair.
I wonder if I should cut it again.
It's dangerous.
I have to do my best.
It's just as I imagined.
I'm just a little bit of a
I have to do my best.
I thought it would be like this.
From the chest.
If you do your best with the third one.
I don't want to take a photo of the
body.
Three chocolate.
Basically.
The next new song is.
I'll do my best.
I can't do it.
Thank you very much.
Please do your best for the music.
There are still some small mistakes and
timing deviations.
It's not good. The dance and the song
are not the same.
I have to do my best.
I have to do this many times.
I'm most anxious about this.
Because they have already been punked
because they have been hitting the
choreography and lyrics of the 8 songs
at the same time.
now..
Don't say, don't say that
Just look at me a little more
When will it end?
The first time I saw her, I was
surprised.
I was surprised.
Yasumoto is in a bad condition.
I have had a cold for about a week.
You are in a bad condition.
Yes.
I often get sick during the performance.
I often get sick before the performance.
I caught a cold this time.
She has had a cold for a few days.
She can't speak as she wants.
How is your cold?
I can't get better.
I didn't sleep in one place during the
tour.
I can't get better.
Actually, Yasumoto was in a heatstroke
during last year's tour and was absent
from Osaka Park.
There are few people.
Even in Nagoya Park, he was on the way
out of heatstroke.
Even if I had to go back, I couldn't get
in the race in the first two laps.
If I could do that, I would have gone
back.
But if I couldn't, I would have taken a
break.
He couldn't finish the race.
He shed tears of regret.
That's why I want to finish the race as
soon as possible this year.
Yasumoto wanted to rehearse with such a
feeling.
Will Yasumoto's feelings reach?
Ebichu Spring National Tour Rehearsal
First Day
Yasumoto struggled alone by breaking his
health a week ago.
What will happen?
Please take your meal
It's hot
The rehearsal of the new song has ended
It's dinner time
Meal
I don't want to be healthy
Did you see the
While the members are busy eating
Rest
I don't need a nasu, but I'll take a
mapo tofu.
I'll take a mapo tofu.
I want to eat it.
Is it a candy?
Yes.
How hot is it?
It's okay.
I'll take a bath and eat it.
The first meal
After dinner, they go to the second half
of the rehearsal.
From here, they will go to the rehearsal
which is more close to the actual
performance.
Yes, that's the end.
The members' faces as they dance are
starting to show the color of their
fatigue.
I feel like I'm in a balance that I can
see.
But in the midst of that, Yasumoto...
The wind was a bit strong today, so we
had to wait for the wind to get up.
The voice gradually returned after all
the new song practice from Yasumoto.
Thank you for watching.
Rehearsal with the worst of the worst
The feeling of going on a tour of the
Alps has increased.
This is how the members' thoughts are
put on the rehearsal day.
However...
The pressure for tomorrow's broadcast is
still not there.
I think it will be a studio in the
future.
Last time, I had a fever in Osaka and
couldn't go out.
In Nagoya, I had a fever and was
discharged from the hospital.
Last year, I was in a very bad condition
during the tour.
So this year, I ate well and worked
hard.
I was thinking about doing my best, but
I was discharged from the hospital.
At first, I was very anxious, but I
thought I couldn't speak at all.
But in the second half, I thought it was
impossible to fake it.
I was very confident, so I practiced
hard every day.
I'm very happy.
And finally...
7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12
The Where are we going,A fuerte west
Thank you for watching!
And I want to find your
Always
The stage created by all the members
closed the curtain of the great success
Next time
Yasumoto, Kashiwagi, Taku
The strongest tag team in Ebi-chuu will
be held
The team studying the strength together
will determine the strongest
The team that will win the game will be
the winner!
The mysterious battle continues!
What will happen?
The game of Ebichu is about to be
released!
Only the members of the Ebichu fan club
are currently receiving a special pre-
summoning registration!
We will be giving out items that can be
used in the game!
For more information, please search
Stardust Channel!
This program was provided by the sponsor
you are watching.