The members of Ebichu challenge the original 5 kinds of competitions at Round One! Which team will win?
At Round One! 5 kinds of team competitions! Photography cooperation Round One Stadium Itabashi
First event: Ebichu Go-Karting Team representatives will drive 3 laps of the go-kart to win!
I'm sure I'll be a safe driver!
This time, we are team C!
It's Kobayashi, myself and Yuno.
Yuno will drive the go-karts!
I've entrusted it to Kokubo.
I used to hit the walls and turn around.
But after I got my license.
I'm able to make turns now.
That's what I'm talking about! I can now turn properly!
Before I got my license
More and more and more!
Mirei...
I had an image of her as a dangerous driver.
Safe driving to save everyone's life.
I'm glad you've grown up.
I've grown up.
I put on my brother's clothes today.
Oh, really?
He's so cute.
And this?
This is for him too. ....
The first event, Koukunchu Ichiryoku Itto, the competition begins!
First event!
Corker!
Let's go! Hoshina! Here we go!
Hang in there. Hang in there!
I'll do my best!
I'm counting on you!
Leave it to me! It's a winnable match!
You have a driver's license, right?
And it's the same color as your clothes and your belt.
My clothes and my belt are the same color.
Totally coordinated!
You look fast, Mirei.
The way she's dressed...
She looks like a professional racer.
You're a stag, aren't you?
You're a stag, aren't you? You're a licensed driver.
Beautiful! Beautiful! Beautiful! Beautiful!
Oh, my God!
I can do it! Oh, my God!
It's a solid step!
Beautiful!
So beautiful!
Isn't it beautiful?
Like a role model.
Yeah.
Hey, guys!
It's over!
I finished three laps before I knew it!
You're a very safe driver.
You're a very safe driver. Yes!
I'll protect everyone's life.
I'll protect everyone's life. Safe driving. I'm Hoshina.
It's good, isn't it? I don't know... 37.45 seconds.
Yay! The record is 37.45 seconds!
Good job! Record 37.45 seconds.
Thank you! Good job! Record 37.45 seconds.
37 seconds. Isn't that fast?
Yes.
You can afford it.
I'll be back in 15 seconds.
No!
Do you have a plan?
A plan?
Oh, no...
I'm going to come back in a clean circle.
Good plan!
I heard about the AND E team's time.
I heard about the E team's time.
I'll do my best to beat their time.
I'll do my best!
Nonoka and I are cheering for you!
I'm cheering for you!
Cheering for you!
I'm off then!
Next, Hinata.
I'm Hinata.
How's it going, Harayan?
Hinata's good too, right?
Right!
That's good!
That's great! It's picking up speed!
Keep going!
One more lap!
One more lap! Yes!
Yuno's in trouble.
Yes!
That was fast, wasn't it?
Good job.
I think it was a good run.
But wait! But wait! That's the same.
How many seconds did it take?
We didn't lose!
We didn't lose, did I?
What was your time?
Provisional first, 37.21.
We're losing. That's...
We're losing.
If you go any faster...
She can't go any faster.
She's... She's going too fast.
Is that the safe driving speed?
It's Yunopi's turn!
I'll do my best.
I'll carry you.
Running wild...
Running away... You're going to blow up, aren't you?
I'll do my best to get past the He-team and the B-team.
START!
Go for it!
You're super fast!
Yuno!
Fast!
Ooh! Ooh! Ooh!
Oh! Oh, hey.
Mmm-hmm.
Go, go, go, go!
One more lap!
Ah!
Face forward!
Drive safely!
Why are you turning around?
What was that? It's over!
Record 40.52 seconds.
That's funny...
Did you get 4 laps?
Did you get it in 3 laps? Is that right?
I was fast.
She's starting high school in the spring.
Yes, high school!
If you make friends in high school, come to round one.
I'll try my best to make friends.
First of all...
The second event, Ebichu Throwing Hoops. Each team has 12 throws!
The second event!
Throwing hoops!
Let's start with team B!
Yeah!
Let's go! Let's go!
Are you ready?
Whoo-hoo!
Go for it!
I'm in!
Yah!
I'm sorry!
Ayaka, you can do it.
Nonoka, she's so athletic.
How are you so good?
Last? Last?
Maybe everyone's in it except me.
Kashiwagi-san!
Specialty ball thrower?
I'm not so good with this ball.
Oh, no!
That's great.
Let's go for E team.
Oh! Oh! Oh!
Ooh-ohh!
You can throw anywhere you want, right?
Even if it's close, right?
Like this...
Like this... Like this...
That's cheating!
Let's go!
She's dressed like a basketball.
That's good, that's good, that's good!
Yeah!
Aah! It's not going in!
You've got to throw it more.
She's a little slow, Maya.
Maybe we should aim for the back.
Yes, sir!
Go for it!
Please, Mirei!
It was harder than I thought.
Mayama's ball flew straight at me.
Doooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo!
It shows my personality, doesn't it?
She used to be in the basketball team.
Quit the basketball team right away
It looks like she's done the basics
I'll leave it to her...
Basketball is all about subtlety, isn't it?
Boldness and delicacy.
Oh...
That can't be helped.
I'm only bold.
Can I brag?
I put them all in the goal.
Four.
I missed them all.
Beautifully.
I missed all of them.
Let's go for it!
You have a very distinctive posture.
Good luck with the basketball team!
This team is good!
Didn't we have a three-pointer?
Wait!
Get it off! Get it off!
It's over.
It's over!
It was a lot of fun.
Surprisingly.
I'm thinking of making my specialty basketball.
Let's not do that!
But we came in second! Maybe.
Second place!
I wonder how many balls he put in?
The second event, Kukonaka Population 1i DUZ, the results are in!
7 balls succeeded
3 successful balls
5 successful balls
1st place B team: Yasumoto, Sakuragi, Kazami 20pt 2nd place E team: Mayama, Hoshina, Sakuragi 12pt 2nd place C team: Kobayashi, Nakayama, Kokubo 12pt
Billiards among Ebichu!
The third event: Ebichu Billiards. If all members of the team drop the ball, the game is cleared!
Break shot by the principal
I want to go up in 3!
3...
Keep hitting it straight, like this.
But 3 moved too.
That's not good.
What was that?
That's great!
Not that way!
The handball has dropped, so play resumes from the position of your choice.
Ha-ha-ha!
No!
Look out!
Lucky girl!
Lucky girl.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
The handball fell out, so play resumes from your favorite position.
Go!
Hinata Kashiwagi, success!
After Kashiwagi, no one succeeds until the fourth round. The members propose a rule change.
What is it? New rules
Third event, Ebichu in the Middle Billiards. The rules have been changed! Drop any ball!
Let's do that!
Yes! Let's do that!
That's it!
Five items are in. (Only Kashiwagi has succeeded so far.)
If you do this, you'll get it. Boom! Boom! I'm in.
Don't do it!
Do it right here.
Just push the button, and you're good to go!
Okay!
Sometimes...
There are times... There are times...
Yuno, you can do it!
1st Team B Yasumoto, Sakuragi, Kazami 30pts 2nd Team C Kobayashi, Nakayama, Kokubo 19pts 3rd Team E Mayama, Hoshina, Sakuragi 17pts Points awarded according to their rank 1st 10pts 2nd 7pts 3rd 5xts