Like videos of shrimp!
To be continued...
Next time...
Round 1
Team Taiko, please show us your skills!
Round 2
I'll show you the front of the train.
I'll talk to you when I want to speed
up.
This time, it's a team-seed team.
Kobayashi, Yunho, and I will do the
walkout.
I made a bet on the national team.
I used to hit the wall and bend, but as
soon as I got my license, I could bend
properly.
I'm getting a license.
I had the image of a train driver.
I'm glad I got a safe driver to protect
everyone's lives.
I'm glad I became an adult.
Today, I'm going to wear my brother's
clothes.
I think I can eat all of them.
That's great.
I can't eat all of them.
The first episode of the show!
GONKAN RATO!
Let's go, Hoshina!
We're going to do our best!
I'm looking forward to it!
We can win!
We have a license!
And the colors are the same!
The angle, the belt, everything is the
same!
Isn't it amazing?
The total coordination is perfect!
Nina looks fast too!
The outfit is...
Strawberry flavor.
It's beautiful.
It has the weather.
It's so beautiful.
Thank you.
It's over.
I don't know.
It's like a safe driving.
I'll protect everyone's life.
I'm Hoshina, a safe driver.
I think it's good.
Yay!
Thank you for your hard work.
How long has it been since you started?
30 years?
I don't know.
It's been 15 seconds.
Do you have any plans?
Plan?
I'll come back with a clean look.
Good plan.
I've been busy with the team's schedule.
I'll do my best to be on top of that.
Please support me.
I'll support you.
I'll be back.
Next is Hinata.
Hinata, how is it?
Hinata is good at it too.
Yes.
Wow, amazing, amazing.
The speed is coming out.
30 seconds.
So fast.
nice cute
It was fast, wasn't it?
I'm the last one!
I think it was a good run.
It was fast.
How many seconds did it take?
I'm not losing.
You're not losing, are you?
What's the time?
Yeah!
She's losing.
It's a long way to go.
I'll do my best.
I'll win.
I'm in a delusion.
Thank you for watching.
I think she's gonna fall.
I'll try to keep my balance.
She's fast!
Eh, wait a minute!
No way!
Wait!
Turn around!
Why me?
It's over.
I forgot.
I bought 4 weeks worth of food.
I bought 3 weeks worth of food.
I'm sorry.
I'm a high school student.
If you make friends in high school, come
to the playground.
I'll go.
Thank you for watching.
It's bad.
The second round is
Sliding Forbes!
Let's start from Team B.
Ready, start!
Are you ready?
Go for it!
Wow!
No!
I'm sorry.
She is athletic.
Why are you so good at it?
Last one.
I think everyone else is doing it.
Hashiaki-san, you're good at throwing
the ball.
Chiyo-san, you're a little bad at
throwing the ball.
Wow.
Amazing.
Well then, Team 1, let's do our best!
Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh!
You can do it wherever you like.
I can do it close, right?
This is...
This is cheating.
That's cheating.
Here it comes.
Let's go!
She's wearing a basketball and a clothes
that looks like she's going to go.
She's going to go.
That's good.
Yay!
Amazing.
I can't throw it.
I think I should throw it more.
I'm not happy.
I think it's better to choose the open.
Yes.
Good luck.
Thank you for your viewing.
Thank you for watching!
It was surprisingly difficult.
It was difficult.
I was climbing up the mountain.
I was going to be a little bit of a
mountaineer.
I'm more of a basketball player.
I quit basketball right away.
I think I did a lot of basic things.
Basketball is delicate.
There is a big difference in the level
of flexibility and sensitivity.
That's right.
There is only a big difference.
Can I choose?
I put everything in.
I put all the 4 ball.
I removed all the ball.
I removed it cleanly.
I will do my best.
I feel like I'm in a position.
I'm in a position.
Kcount seals really good.
What?
Yeah, I think I got a 3.
I got a 3.
Don't do it.
What?
Yeah!
I'm scared!
Open the box!
I got it!
The most...
Don't do that!
Did you get all?
Yes, all.
They are good.
Yes, they are.
It was so much fun.
I was surprised.
It's like basketball.
Let's play basketball.
Let's stop playing basketball.
Let's stop.
Let's play basketball.
How many balls did you get?
2.
They are good.
So close!
Two people are in the box.
I didn't put the ball in.
Thank you for watching.
EVIT dealing~!
One drop
She wants to go up as much as she can
I'm sorry.
The first try
Ah!
It's not that way!
The second try
The third try
The fourth try
The fifth try
The sixth try
The seventh try
The eighth try
The tenth try
That was close!
Lucky!
Lucky roll!
I'm nervous.
You were good.
Wow!
I'm nervous.
It's down
That was powdered metals
Thank you for watching!
I want to do it twice.
What is the number of the picture?
The number of the picture is 7.
Let's do that.
I'm scared.
It's difficult.
Do it here.
You can push it like this.
It's difficult.
The 2nd day in leur village
It was fun.
I was too interested.
Assistant...
Clapping
Yeah!
We can't miss
The children'shappy room
Thank you for watching.