Hello, I'm Aiki Taniguchi, 17 years old,
from Yamaguchi prefecture, and I'm in my
second year of high school.
Today, I'm in Kintaikyo, which is in
Iwakuni-ji, Yamaguchi Prefecture.
It's like this.
There is a river here.
When I came here in summer, I put my
feet on the river and swam.
The stones were slippery, so I fell down
and got wet.
My mother brought me clothes.
I was saved by that.
This is a shop called Musashi, which has
the most soft cream varieties in Japan.
There are 200 kinds.
It's so good.
My favorite food is...
pickled plums.
I like jerky and salami.
I like ham, too.
I love sweet potato roll.
I like beef tongue and beef tendon.
I like everything.
When I was asked to participate, I
thought,
is this a dream?
I was like, wow, I'm in.
I thought a lot about whether I really
deserve to participate.
But after I was chosen,
I thought I had to do my best
and spend the rest of my life without
regret.
I'll do my best to be chosen
and to be seen by everyone.
I'll do my best to make people think,
I'm interested in this girl.
I'll do my best to shine in the
afternoon.
I'm at the Actors School
where I went to when I was in
kindergarten.
I'm going to report to the teacher I was
in charge of.
Hello. Long time no see.
I'm Chris, and I've been in charge of
the school since kindergarten.
I'm Chris from the Actors School
Hiroshima.
Hello.
I'm a third-year student in the
Sakurazaka 46 group.
I'm going to participate in the school.
I'm here to report.
Congratulations on the Sakurazaka 46.
Thank you.
I'm surprised.
Back then, you had to practice all
night.
Yes, we did.
I thought you were taking too strict
lessons.
What did you think about that?
Well, there were some tough parts,
but the members said,
like, your hand movements are great,
and your footwork is beautiful.
They complimented me.
I think it's because Chris taught me
that.
I see.
I'm glad you're using that as an excuse.
Thank you.
I hope you'll do that.
I'm looking forward to your support.
Thank you.