Like a video of shrimp.
What is the best way to train your body?
Can you do a body roll with coconut and
yuno?
This time, we will introduce the team of
E-Pump, Mr. Kagewara.
The tape is divided like this.
The most gentle one is the pink one.
The color changes depending on the
difficulty.
First, let's try to climb these two pink
ones.
Let's go!
I'm going.
Only pink?
Suddenly, it's going.
Here?
Wait, I'm scared.
It's fun.
It's going up with the rope.
I'm scared.
Wait.
It's going up faster than I thought.
You can go up to here.
There is another rope on the left foot.
There is another rope on the top.
Wait, my hand is shaking.
I found it.
Is this the right way?
It's OK.
Can you go down?
I can't go down.
I'm scared.
I'm scared of the rope I just took.
I'm going down.
I'm going to put my feet down.
I'm scared.
I'm going to climb up.
Go for it!
Can you grab this?
I can't grab it yet.
I'm good.
Is there no footwork?
It's difficult to do.
You have to make it smaller.
Why did you go down?
You do the hands first, then the legs.
What about the shoulder legs?
What about the hands?
I can't get down.
Can you do it?
No way.
I'm using green.
I'm sorry.
I forgot to tell you, but when you get
off, it's okay to use it.
What?
I was just talking.
I got off.
I forgot.
It's okay to use green.
From the top, this is about 24 times the
height.
The height of the horse.
I feel like I'm at the top of that.
Yuna, you can't do it here. It's about
3.
I'm aiming for 3.
I'm aiming for 6.
Next is 7.
Please do your best.
I'll start from the top.
Is this it?
Can you do it?
Here?
Here.
There's no place to grab.
Stand up.
Don't stand up.
I can't grab it.
I'm done.
The difficulty suddenly came.
I got it.
My legs won't move.
I'll try it.
The difficulty suddenly came from the
top.
I'm scared.
I'll try it here.
It's hard to grab it.
Can you do it?
I can't, but I'll try.
I can't.
Raise your left leg.
That way?
It's right below the green corner.
Is it here?
The first one.
A little more to the right.
There.
That's it.
I'm done.
Why can you do it so much?
You're amazing.
I'm done.
The second one.
I'll try it again.
I can't see it.
The difficulty suddenly came.
It's hard.
Please say it while shaking your head.
It hurts.
It's not over yet.
Stand up.
You have to stand up.
You can do it.
I can't.
Put your right foot on it.
OK.
Put your left foot on it.
You can do it.
It's hard.
What should I do?
Stand up.
Don't give up.
Stretch your left foot.
If you fall, it's OK.
It's OK even if you fall.
It's not OK.
Put your foot on the small one.
You can do it.
Go!
It's scary to fall.
7th ball clear.
It hurts to raise your finger.
My arm hurts.
It's slippery.
This is dangerous.
I didn't use this.
It's too slippery.
This part is slippery.
8th ball clear.
Finally, we will do the 6th ball.
6th ball clear.
How do you run away from there?
Don't run away from there.
I'm scared.
Wait a minute.
Great.
8th ball clear.
I will defeat the enemy today.
Good luck.
I grabbed the ball with both hands.
You can run away.
I grabbed the ball with my hand.
Here?
No.
I grabbed the ball from here.
From here?
Like this?
From here.
From here?
I grabbed the ball with my left hand.
This way?
I can't climb yet.
Kure-san.
I did it.
Is this the way?
Do I go this way?
Yes, go to the right foot.
I can't open my legs that much.
How about putting your left hand on one
side?
Like this?
Nice.
With your left hand.
Left hand.
I can't.
Change.
Isn't it too fast?
I can't.
I'll do my best.
I'll clear it if I can.
I can't.
What kind of face is that?
Put your left hand out.
Yes, yes, yes.
I can't.
Do you use this part?
Both hands.
Left hand.
I can't.
Why?
Put your right hand on your head.
Do your best.
I can't.
It's so hard.
I'll do my best.
I'm tired.
It was hard.
It was really hard.
It was hard and my arms hurt.
I'm sure I'll have muscle pain tomorrow.
I think it was harder than the muscle I
didn't use.
It was fun.
I want to do it every day.
Please come to the gym.
I had a chance to go out.
Please.
I want to do it every day.
Next is the 6th level.
I'm going to do my best.
I'm looking forward to it.
Please come again.
Thank you very much.
I wanna come home completed after trying
for the first time
Without
the only goods
I don't wanna lose
I will be home
With simple skills
I am back with eighth degree
I wanna go home with eighth degree
You can do!
I did it!
You're good!
You did it!
I'll try again.
You can do it!
I'll do it quickly.
It was a moment.
I did it!
I did my best.
It was fun.
It was really hard.
My arm hurts.
Some people jump over the TV.
That's amazing.
It's slippery.
It's small.
I can't stand on it.
I want to do it with my hands.
I want to do it again.