Ebichu's videos
So we should choose a girl who looks
like 117?
117 is Aki's birthday.
If you say that, everyone will look like
117.
This is a momentum.
Cheers!
To be continued.
Congratulations!
I'm glad to hear that.
Let's celebrate.
Congratulations!
I finally got it right.
I'm so happy.
Don't be a judge.
I finally got it right.
I'm so happy.
I don't know.
What was it?
I remember only the last one.
Is it right?
The principal is right.
There are many problems.
I don't know.
I'm sorry, principal.
I'm sorry I couldn't hit you even though
I was sticking out.
I'm sorry.
Oh, that's what it is.
What are you saying, Yuka?
I don't know. I don't know. I'm not
going to write my name.
It's like a tataguchi.
No, it's not.
I'm sorry.
I got it!
Wow!
I see.
I want to avoid minus points.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry again.
OK.
I think this is the right kanji.
I'm sorry again.
Yeah!
I did it!
I made a mistake.
It's a very fast.
It's a DNA.
It's Yokohama DNA.
It's a small letter.
Oh, yeah.
Please remember.
I see.
I did it!
Wow!
It's amazing.
I did it!
What?
How long?
The second longest song?
I think it's about 8 minutes?
7 minutes?
I think it's about 7 minutes.
I don't know.
I think it's about 8 minutes.
Maybe this.
I don't know at all.
Wait a minute.
Something close to 8 minutes.
Is it a long song?
No, it's not long.
This is not long.
It's not long.
I don't know.
I don't know the length of the feeling.
I don't know the feeling.
Wait a minute.
I don't know.
This is not an official practice.
It's not an official practice.
It's not.
I think it's not.
Wow!
Great!
Mom, I did it!
Mom!
Wow!
It's difficult to answer all of them.
All of them are difficult.
It's impossible if the ratio of the
shrimp is not high.
It's a difficult question.
The answer is...
Answer James's, answer yourself!