Thank you for watching!
Let's sing and cheer up!
The idol group that will be in the
middle school forever, Shirito Ebisu
Middle School.
They will teach us how to dance to a new
song from the story of feeling a
generation gap between the new members.
We will deliver a lot of contents.
Shirito Ebisu Middle School's
interesting topics. First of all, here.
The recording time of each member is
different.
Before me, Mayuma-san finished first.
After that, my song.
I was listening to it at the recording
studio.
At first, I was like,
It's so embarrassing. Stop it.
I was really worried.
But after the recording, I was like,
I'm glad I'm here.
I was really happy to hear that.
But I was surprised to see that.
I was surprised to hear that the
recording was still there.
That's the most surprising thing.
I don't see other members recording.
I'm letting my senior wind blow.
Thank you for watching.
You've been in the business since 2005,
right?
Yes, I'm in 2005.
There are many generations gap.
There's a member named Kokubo Yuno.
She's 14 years old now.
15?
14.
She's a junior high school senior.
She asked me if I was free on a weekday.
I thought she was going to hang out.
It's rare to hang out with her. She's a
member who gathered in her heart.
I've never been to her place.
But she said she wanted to hang out with
me.
I thought it was okay.
I thought I could go somewhere.
She said she wanted to communicate with
me.
That's what she wanted to do.
It's a new era.
I felt that it was a time when I could
play online.
I think we're going to gather and play
together.
It's so new that it's always
stimulating.
In the chorus, there's a line that goes,
Every time our hands touch,
we touch each other's lips,
and every time our eyes touch,
we look at each other's eyes and say,
Let's do this!
And then we can do it freely,
and we can do it anywhere.
So I hope you can do it with your hands,
and I hope you can do it with your
hands.
I want to try it.
Can I?
Thank you.
Every time our hands touch,
Every time our eyes meet,
We feel the same way.
Anytime, anywhere.
Thank you.
You can do it with your hands.
This is a request from the staff.
Wait, wait, something's different.
What is this?
Actually, we received a request from the
staff in secret.
I'm scared.
Yasumoto-san.
What?
Yasumoto-san has a sick change of
clothes.
In the moment the manager is not
watching,
there are often changes from costumes to
uniforms.
Also, eveningontage is alarming.
When I asked Yasumoto to take a photo of
me in my costume,
she said she was already wearing a suit
and couldn't take it.
When I was little, I learned swimming.
When I was changing into a swimsuit at a
swimming school,
I had to give my senior a locker, so I
had to hurry up and change.
That was my habit.
When I learned swimming, I learned this
technique.
There is a way to take off everything in
one go.
I didn't know that.
There is a way to take off from the top.
I think that by doing so, I can change
my clothes many times faster than
everyone else.
I can take a bath quickly.
If you say hurry up, you can take a bath
in 15 seconds.
There is a way to wash it all in one go.
All in one go!
全然一回つねるの。
私立江口中学さんのカラオケプレイリスト!
今回は春といったらこの曲をテーマにプレイリストを考えていただきました。
私たちのカラオケプレイリストはこちらです。
Yasumoto-san, what is your period?
When I think of a karaoke, I imagine
myself in a karaoke.
I want to sing sentimental songs.
Spring is full of encounters and
farewells.
The song, Period, is full of the sadness
of farewell and the pain of being in a
I want to sing sentimental songs.
I want to sing this song.
And then, Hoshina-san will sing Yama-
san's 春をつける.
That's right. When I go to karaoke, I
always sing this song once.
It's a classic song in my mind, but it's
a little sad and emotional.
There are many lyrics like that.
I like karaoke that's just fun, but I
like karaoke that's for my skill up.
So I chose this song.
I don't sing when everyone's around,
but...
Don't you want to sing when someone's
around?
That's true.
But I really like this song.
And then,
Kashiwagi-san asked, what if Masutaka-
ko's 《Ashita Haru》 comes out?
That's right.
This song is amazing.
My mother...
She taught me this song.
When I sing this song, I feel like
spring is coming.
It's easy to remember the situation.
I often sing karaoke alone.
I usually sing at the end of karaoke
alone.
You sing a song that you can remember
after singing a little.
And Sakuragi-san's 《Blue》.
I really like this song.
The lyrics are about changing from
winter to spring.
It's a really stylish song.
It's a ballad, but it also has rap in
it.
It's easy to sing in different genres.
It's a song that's easy to sing for
family or alone.
It's fun to sing alone or with friends.
You can check the full playlist at the
karaoke's website.
Please use this as a reference for your
song selection.
In the karaoke, Sakuragi-san, the new
member, has told us what she wants to
become.
Vogue artists are constantly appearing!
Please like and subscribe!
Are you enjoying the RAM Channel?