Hello to all the fans of Akita Opa and Tamariba !
Applause!
Thank you!
I'm Shunto Hasegawa, a comedian from Tamariba
I'm Ayaka Yasumoto of Shiritsu Ebisu Chuugaku
I'm Riko Nakayama of Shiritsu Ebisu Chuugaku
Thank you!
Hello everyone.
On this programme, we call it Tamari.
We usually produce this show with 10 aces of Akita.
We also produce as a radio show on Fridays 10.20 pm.
We do things like that.
However, as you know, there are twists and twists in Ebi Tech all the time when
you appear on our show.
The pressure is right.
Have you helped the local community?
Yes, there would be then monthly meeting for us.
Remember
I don't have a radio show that I go to, so I'm really looking forward to it.
Yes, it's really fun to talk about this.
And it's a public recording, but we're also doing a live broadcast this time.
I'd like you to watch it on the live broadcast.
I wonder if Hasegawa will appear from time to time.
Before we start, there are two people, a makeup artist,
and a makeup artist. I'm not here, of course, so I was wondering what to do.
The makeup artist asked me,
Hasegawa, do you want to put on lipstick?
But I don't know whose lipstick I'm going to put on.
I said I'd lick it.
Natural lipstick.
I'm natural.
Natural gloss.
Is it glossy now?
It's already rough.
On the contrary, it's dry.
I should have applied it.
I should have applied lip cream.
So there's a live broadcast, so I'd like you to enjoy it.
That's it.
Now, I'd like to explain the schedule.
It's about an hour and a half from here.
Today's talk live, which is broadcast from the special venue of Akita OPPA 5th
floor.
Goodbye, our music room.
This is the schedule for the happy end talk live.
Yasumoto-san and Nakayama-san will be talking about the themes of the show.
There are themes.
I wonder what they are.
I'm excited.
We only have this much free time.
I see.
So we'd like to talk about the themes.
And we've decided to challenge ourselves to a big one.
I'm nervous.
I'll talk about this later.
You'll talk about this later.
So, how about you, Nakayama-san?
Is it rare to have a big one on Ebichu?
Big one?
We had a big one on the show before, but not recently.
I haven't done it since I became an adult.
You're not an adult.
I'm sorry to interrupt, but the people who are watching this show and here are
very precious.
I'm not good at it, but I'm sure you'll be able to see them.
I'm looking forward to it.
And about the TOWER RECORD Akita OPPA exhibition,
you can see a lot of artworks here.
I'd like to ask Mr. Saito, the manager of TOWER RECORD Akita OPPA, about this
artwork.
Please tell us about it.
Mr. Saito is a funny guy.
I'm looking forward to it.
I hope we can have a talk about our memories.
I feel like this talk live is already very lively.
It's very lively, isn't it?
Thank you.
I'll check if it's lively every time.
I'd like to play a song.
We'd like to introduce the latest song suitable for today's talk live event.
Please start with Ebisu.
Please listen to it.
Shiritsu Ebisu Junior High School Boys' Town
Jump out the chap and be a champion!
Thirty two two-two straights and he's out with a 0-0 over theまで.
The halfbacks look crazy.
.
The host of this show was Ebisu Junior High School's Boydger.
Now, let's get started with the first segment.
The first segment is the Odaibox segment!
Applause!
Thank you very much!
So, as I said, this is the first corner.
The theme box corner.
The venue is here, the floor of the Akihabara Bookstore.
We would like to proceed with some items.
Some items are here.
This is a box. Can you hear the sound?
There are many capsule toys in this box.
In the capsule, there are questions that you want to answer.
Of course, you don't know the answers.
I don't know what to talk about.
I'm excited to see what kind of questions will come.
By the way, you can't answer the questions once.
Is that a question that I can't answer?
It's a hard question.
It's a question from Stardust.
It's different from Yoshimoto.
So you can't answer the questions once.
You can't answer the questions once.
It's a precious one-time question.
And the theme of the questions is that there are two for Yasumoto and two for
Nakayama.
There are four questions that are common for the two of you.
So if Yasumoto pulls a capsule for Nakayama, you have to answer it.
If you don't answer it, you can't answer the questions.
Please answer the questions.
Let's start with Yasumoto.
I'll bring the box.
Thank you.
I wonder what kind of questions will come.
I'm curious about the questions.
I'll pull it.
It's really in the capsule.
I wonder what it is.
It's in the capsule.
Please look at it.
I pulled a question for Yasumoto.
It's just right.
The theme is this.
What advice would you give to someone who wants to be good at singing?
I think it's a very good question.
Then this is NG.
You're lying.
I'll use it all of a sudden.
I'm sorry.
I wanted to hear it.
My reaction was not good.
I wanted to do it.
I had time in January.
Don't say it.
I've always wanted to do it.
That's good.
Yasumoto sings in acapella in various places.
Please follow us on SNS and TikTok.
I think you're already doing it.
I think there are many people who go to karaoke.
What kind of advice do you have?
How to sing well.
It's easy to challenge.
But when you sing, you get nervous.
It's hard to sing when you're tired.
Don't you sing better when you're drunk?
You can sing louder when you're tired.
You can sing high notes.
You can sing high notes when you're drunk.
It's important to relax.
If you sing with a relaxed mind, you'll be able to sing better.
It's important to stretch your shoulders.
Relaxation around the neck and shoulders is important.
I'm conscious of it.
You don't seem to have a stiff shoulder.
I have a stiff shoulder.
You're lying.
It's easy to get stiff shoulders because it's a tense scene.
That's why I gave you advice.
I think it's a good idea to sing with a proud mind.
I think it was a great advice.
Let's move on.
Next is YOSHI.
I'll bring it every time.
Thank you.
I'll start.
Purple.
Oh.
How is it?
Umm.
Yasumoto-san.
What?
Umm.
She continued.
I can't hear you.
What made you start TikTok?
This is also a question I'm curious about.
Can I talk?
Yes, please.
What made me start TikTok?
It's a continuation of the song.
I love singing.
I want to strengthen my singing this year.
TikTok is a dance content.
But I thought it would be nice to sing because it's a video app.
I started TikTok because I wanted to sing.
I think most of the people who sing with that thought are followers.
You sing with a relaxed and fun singing style.
Yes, I sing songs that I want to sing when I go to karaoke.
Fans also told me to sing.
I always sing songs that I want to sing.
It's a fun TikTok.
What about you, Rita?
I'm doing my best on Instagram.
I think it's a TikTok that I can sing cutely.
No, it's not.
I have an official TikTok account.
I think it's a TikTok that I can sing cutely.
You always do it.
You are doing your best on SNS.
Next, Nakayama, please.
I'm sorry.
I'm the only one left.
Thank you.
How was it?
Alright, let's see.
It's in the gacha.
Oh, a common topic!
What was the first CD you bought?
Oh, that's a good one!
I'm curious about this one.
How about you, Rittan?
I...
CD...
High School Musical.
Oh, I see.
It's an album
with the songs
from the movie.
I bought it
with my own money.
With your own money?
Yes, with my own money.
I remember that.
And also AKB48's album.
Yes.
I think it's called Girls.
I don't know.
I remember both.
I don't know which one is earlier.
It's quite impressive.
You were quite young.
I was in elementary school.
In elementary school...
You must have bought it from your parents.
No, no, no.
I bought it with my own money.
You must have bought it with your own money.
Even I get my CD from my parents.
Even now?
What?
I mean, your father.
No way!
I'm not talking about me.
How about you, Yasumoto-san?
I remember that I bought
Amuro Namie's...
What was the title?
Best...
You bought the best one.
I bought the best one.
I think I bought the best one.
I also bought the MV.
I got the MV for the special edition.
You got the DVD?
Yes, I did.
I bought it for the first time.
I started to get interested
in the music.
You got interested in it.
Yes.
I bought the CD for the first time.
I watched the DVD every day.
My parents are both working, so I spend most of my time on the weekends.
I'm the same.
Oh, you are?
I watched the same DVD dozens of times a day.
I bought it when I was in the 5th or 6th grade of elementary school.
I think buying a CD is a way to meet music.
It's like a starting point.
I used to buy CDs when I was a kid.
Fans gave me their CDs at the awards ceremony.
AKB48, Momokuro-chan's CDs, etc.
They all participated in the awards ceremony.
They gave me CDs and I got to know my favorite idols.
That's amazing.
I've had a lot of opportunities to meet people through CDs.
I'm sure there are many people who bought CDs through Tawareko.
We still have time, so let's ask Yasumoto-san next.
I'd like to ask a question for Riko-chan.
Hello, I'm Noh.
I see.
What will come out?
Oh, here it is!
It's for Nakayama-san!
When do you want to take a picture?
Oh, this one!
Speaking of Riko, it's a picture.
When do I want to take a picture?
Basically, when I'm shooting, I'm into film cameras.
Oh, film cameras!
I have two film cameras.
When do I want to take a picture?
I'm also doing a series of photoshoots, so I feel like I have to take a lot of
pictures and save them.
It's like a photographer's opinion.
That's right.
When do I want to take a picture?
When I'm holding a camera, everyone makes a good face and gives me a peace sign.
I don't want to do that, but I want to take a picture of the place where I'm
talking to nature.
When I look at your Instagram, you look like a bird.
You look like a bird.
I think the pictures you took when you were looking back are really nice.
I think Instagram photos are really great.
I saw pictures of you and Yasumoto on a date in Asakusa.
I think it was a yukata or a kimono.
I think that picture is really nice.
I saw it.
When we go out together, we take pictures of each other.
We're both working hard on Instagram, so we're taking pictures of each other's
videos.
Ayaka and I went to Ise.
When we went to Ise, we took a video and Ayaka edited it.
You're like a video creator.
She helped us connect the good points.
I see.
When you take a picture with someone you can get along with, you can take a
natural picture.
You can take a picture with a relaxed expression.
I think that's the best part.
The song is the same, but the picture is also relaxed.
Let's move on to the next question.
I'd like to hear a lot of questions.
Please show us the answer.
What will come out?
We have a common topic.
Oh, we have a common topic.
What do you like about Akita?
Oh, this is also a question that Akita people are asking.
I want to ask what Akita people like about Akita.
Well, I like Akita people.
Everyone is so warm.
I can feel the warmth of the city that I can't feel in Tokyo.
I come to the shopping mall to work.
When I come to the mall as a group, I feel uncomfortable in Tokyo.
So I often feel cold.
But everyone is so warm.
They look at me with a kind look.
I think everyone is so warm.
I think it's natural to live in Akita.
When I come to Akita, I think of people from other prefectures.
How do you feel about coming from Fukuoka?
Did you feel the kindness?
I'm sorry. I was just about to drink tea.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'd like to ask you while replenishing water.
How about you, Ritta?
I feel like I'm surrounded by a warm barrier.
I feel like I'm surrounded by a warm aura.
The air is different from the moment I get off the bullet train.
It's completely different.
Is that so?
I feel calm.
I feel calmer than at home.
You're very calm.
I'm really calm.
You're like a person who's at home.
I'm in a state of mind.
When I go to a restaurant, the staff talks to me very casually.
I feel like I'm always going to the restaurant.
You're a regular customer.
I like the fact that we can have a normal conversation.
That's great.
I'm a representative of Akita.
It's called a shy person.
Do you know what a shy person is?
A shy person?
A shy person is a person who is shy.
That's what Akita is.
There are some people like that.
But I think that the shyness is a warm gaze.
I think that the distance between people and their hearts is close.
I can't talk to you very much.
What?
Next, next.
I'm sorry for the sad story.
I heard a good story.
Thank you.
This was the Odaibox corner.
And now, the corner we've all been waiting for.
The Oogiri corner!
Here it is.
Finally!
I'll say this first, but I'm not good at Oogiri.
Everyone's not good at it.
But the comedians are.
The comedians are doing it.
That's right.
There are a lot of them.
So I like the way the audience looks at Oogiri.
The audience looks at Oogiri?
I feel a little relieved that I don't have to answer today.
Are you running away?
I'm scared.
I'm scared because I'm at home.
So, I, Oogiri, will now stand up.
I'm nervous.
I'll do the round-off.
**This is part of the question, are picnics good or bad.
**The picnics come on TV as side quests.
There is a button to press quickly in the hands of Yasumoto-san and Nakayama-
san.
Here it is.
Oh, it's working.
No problem.
I, Hasegawa, will give you a question.
If you think of an answer,
please press the button.
It's very quick.
If you think of an answer,
you can answer it right away.
By the way,
you can answer one question
as many times as you want.
If you get a slip,
you can get a revenge.
It's OK.
Many people are tired of it.
You have warm eyes.
You are safe.
I didn't expect
there would be a corner
where I would be tested.
I didn't expect it.
It's a corner where you can get a slap.
Every time you get a question,
please press the button.
I will read the question again.
After that,
you will hear a sound
like a lion's roar.
You will hear a sound like a lion's roar.
Please answer the question
after that.
I'm so nervous.
I'm so nervous that I'm in the front.
I'm in the front.
But you are cheering for me.
I'm sorry to say this,
but please get ready to laugh.
I practiced a lot.
There is no problem
to practice for this.
Here is the question.
I will turn it over here
and give you the question.
I will look at the picture.
Let's get started.
Question No.1
Oh, I'm scared.
Oh, it's cute!
How can you make me move with this?
Here it is.
A word with a photo.
You can see a photo of Nakayama.
Now, if you think about it, please press it.
I'm going to do it with all my might.
Oh, it's Yasumoto.
Let's get started.
A word with a photo.
What are you saying, Mr. Nakayama?
I want to eat fried chicken!
Hey, hey!
Hey!
Let's be a little strict.
You're going to get a scar.
You look so nervous.
How about a photo?
Oh, it's her.
Let's go.
Say something in the photo.
What are you saying, Nakayama-san?
I forgot to wear my pants because I was in a hurry in the morning.
Oh, my God. What should I do today?
Wonderful.
Thank you very much.
You're wearing pants.
I'm wearing pants.
Wonderful.
Nakayama, you get one point.
Thank you very much.
That's great.
Let's move on to the next question.
Next, I'd like to ask you a question about your photos.
This is the photo.
I miss those photos.
It's cute.
This is the photo.
Well, Yasumoto-san is riding something.
Oh, you're holding it up.
You're holding it up.
Are you confident?
Let's go.
What is Yasumoto-san saying?
Dad, you took too many pictures.
Oh, that's harsh.
I'm sorry.
Okay, let's go, Nakayama-san.
Say something in the picture.
What is Yasumoto-san saying?
Did you get the Buster?
You're messing with me.
This is...
It's a face-to-face battle.
What I like about this is that Yasumoto-san's comment after that was good.
Thank you.
You're messing with me.
I followed you.
Let's do it again.
This?
This is the last one?
Let's see Yasumoto-san's ping pong.
Are you ready?
I'll start.
Say something in the picture.
Yasumoto-san, what did you say?
Yeah!
Thank you!
Oh my god.
I can't stop.
Well, momentum is important.
Yes, momentum is important.
Momentum is important.
Sometimes momentum is important.
By the way, you're a girl, but why are you saying Nya?
I'm a girl.
I don't have a reason.
You're cute.
Well, that's good.
Say something in the photo.
I don't say Nya.
Can I say something about me?
Say something in the photo.
I have a good idea.
What are you saying, Mr. Yasumoto?
Who put super glue on the rainbow?!
I didn't think it would be this slippery!
I'm sorry, there was a bad adult here.
It was slippery.
With my nose!
I'm a bad adult.
You're the kind of person who laughs with your nose.
It was super funny.
Now, let's move on to the next topic.
You can answer by looking at the picture.
So you can think of the answer in a flash.
But the next topic is the last one.
Ready?
Dossun...
Wow!
Wait, this is...
Yes, this is a slightly different,
but a little bit fantastic photo.
Please think about it carefully.
Please think about it in your head.
I think it's like this.
How is it?
Please do your best.
She's thinking so hard.
Oh, Yazo, you're fast.
You're a fast starter.
You're a fast starter, Yasumoto-san.
Okay, let's go.
Please say a word in the photo.
Yasumoto riding on the back of the Silver Dragon.
I like this.
The feeling of being seen by the dragon.
I think it's good.
I can't think of anything.
How about this three-dimensional picture?
This is a picture of Yasumoto.
I took a picture of it from Instagram.
I'm thinking about it.
Let's go.
The feeling of the dragon.
I'll say a word in the photo.
There's a guy with a smile on his face.
He ate too much grilled meat yesterday and his weight is heavy.
I'm sorry, but are you okay?
Ah, it's a little long.
It's long.
It's a little long.
But I like it when it starts with, you know.
You know?
I like it when it starts with, you know.
It's like you're trying to maintain your weight.
I'm sure you're feeling it.
So, that's that.
Shall we move on?
Let's go.
So, that's that.
But there's more.
But, how should I put it?
It was smooth.
I'm not saying it was super smooth.
By the way, it's 2 points each.
Oh, that's good.
It's even.
Next, we have a question about this, not a photo.
Let's go.
pa
And so, the name of the new series, Ebisu Middle School, has been revealed!
Now, what kind of name did you come up with?
Wow, thank you...
Thank you!
I knew it!
I'm so excited!
Wait, wait, wait!
Hey!
Wow!
I thought about it before I fell asleep!
I thought about it too!
This is pretty...
Even among the members...
This is pretty common, right?
What is it?
I can't remember...
I can't remember at all!
How was it?
It was good.
And so, the name of the new series, Ebisu Middle School, has been revealed!
What kind of name did you come up with?
It's pretty simple, right?
It's simple, so it's hard to answer, right?
I don't know anything.
Oh, here it is!
Are you ready?
Here we go!
And so, the name of the new series, Ebisu Middle School, has been revealed!
What kind of name did you come up with?
Just shrimp.
That was good.
You're good.
I don't like just shrimp.
I see.
It's like you're looking at the future.
You're like, shrimp and shrimp.
I'm a shrimp.
You're like, today we're two shrimp.
I think there's still a lot of them.
Are there?
There's a lot.
Let's see.
They're spinning at a great angle.
They're spinning at an angle I've never seen before.
Is it the best?
I'll do the classic one.
What's the theme?
Here we go.
OK. Painting Classwork.
So, what's the name of this?
She's...
Alcohol-addicted.
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
What is it?
In many ways!
I'm not sure if I can say it.
People often say that.
They say, I'm She's Ebisu Middle School.
There are people who are 25 years old.
There are people who are older than me.
Most of the time, adults say,
I'm an alcoholic.
I'm often teased by comedians.
There are many bad adults.
I'm often teased by bad adults.
I teased myself.
I'm 100% in favor of you.
I'm sorry.
I thought about it.
Thank you.
Let's go to the last one.
This is the last one.
By the way, this is a three-point game.
I'm leading by one point.
Is there anything in this?
The winner...
There was nothing in this.
Oh, no, no, no.
Something.
From Mr. Hasegawa.
I sold my down jacket because I had no work and no money.
I've been wearing a down jacket so far.
It was the ultimate.
But there may be something.
This is the last one.
The last one.
Ta-da!
Fujii-Kocho is in a big success.
Please think of a new title from Kocho to Honyarara.
From Kocho?
I'm glad you didn't say it's a common one.
I'm so relieved.
From Kocho?
I feel like Fujii-Kocho is a set.
Fujii-Kocho...
I didn't expect it to come from Rittan.
Fujii-Kocho is in a big success. Please think of a new title from Kocho to
Honyarara.
Kinjo no Ojiisan.
Get out of the way.
I wonder if he's a newbie.
He looks like a newbie.
But he's a newbie.
Yes, he is.
But it was fun, so it's okay.
Thank you.
There's a similar pattern.
Don't get too caught up in the newbie thing.
I see.
Kinjo no Ojiisan.
Next, we have a new person.
Sayato Tomoto-san has pressed the button.
Fujii-Kocho is in a big success.
Please think of a new title from Kocho to Honyarara.
Fujii Sennin!
Wow, that's great!
I don't need mine.
Please, please! Please, please!
Just any one is fine.
One? Okay, let's go.
Here we go.
The Fujii-Kocho was a great success.
The new katagaki is...
Fujii-Shodan!
Thank you very much!
That's scary.
Oogiri is scary.
It's scary.
So, how was it? Did you have fun?
Yes, we had fun.
Good. Did you have fun, too?
Yes, we did.
Thank you very much.
So, that's it for the Oogiri Neta Corner. Thank you very much.
Everyone is so kind.
Kind and wonderful.
So, we had a lot of fun with the Oogiri corner.
We had a lot of fun.
Thank you very much.
Let's take a break and get some water.
I'm so thirsty.
Let's take a nap.
I was nervous.
We don't have to push ourselves so hard.
That's right.
Everyone, please take a break.
I hope you all enjoy the rest of the event.
Now, let's move on to the next segment.
The next event is the Akita Art Festival, or Tower Records Akita Oppa.
We have a special guest here.
Please welcome Saito Tencho!
Sixtus Thurston.
Hello, I'm Saito, the director of Akita Opera.
Nice to meet you, Saito.
So, Saito, you are the director of Akita Opera.
I'm always watching your performance.
Thank you.
I'm surprised to see so many people here.
I feel like you are nervous.
I'm an amateur, so I'm nervous.
You have performed in Tamariba.
I have performed in Tamariba many times.
I often play with Hasegawa in another corner.
I always play with him, but I'm going to play with him today.
I'm looking forward to it.
As you said, Saito has been in charge of the selection of Tamariba since 2021.
So far, you have selected 65 songs.
Thank you.
That's amazing.
I don't remember what I selected.
Of course.
You have selected 4 or 5 songs for the album.
Of course, you have selected songs for the album.
You have selected many songs.
The first song of the new year is the 2021 version of the song,
which is the title of the album.
I love this song, too.
You have selected this song.
I love this song.
Akita Opera is open from the first day of the new year.
So, when the new year comes,
the customers come to buy CDs from their grandparents.
Wow, that's so warm.
When I see that, I feel like I'm in a refrain.
Oh, you feel like you're in a flow.
I spent such a wonderful New Year.
It was a job, but you felt warm.
I feel really happy.
Grandparents buy CDs for their grandchildren.
That's so nice.
I'm happy.
This year, many regulations have been lifted.
It seems that many grandchildren were restricted.
It's a little easier to listen to.
I think there was a exchange.
I love this song, too.
Nakayama, this song is a good song, isn't it?
Well, this song is...
It's like a bath.
It's like a bath at home.
I often sing this song at a family party.
I only sing it once a year.
I feel like it's a waste.
I feel like I'm getting older and more absorbed.
I feel like I'm 13 or 14 years old.
It's a completely different feeling from when I was 22 years old.
I feel like I'm growing up.
How about you, Yasumoto?
When I sing live, I remember my grandparents.
Some members cry.
As Riko said, the importance of family when you grow up.
I feel grateful because I'm far away from my family.
I'm getting older and more absorbed.
The importance of this song is changing.
It's a very promising song.
I wonder if my grandparents are doing well.
I wonder if next year will be good.
I wonder if the year after next will be good.
I'm totally in the same boat.
I think it's a really great song.
I'm Saito, the manager of the school.
I'd like to talk about Akita culture.
Before that, I'd like to give you a little imitation.
I'd like to give you a little imitation.
I'd like to play a song that was performed at the Akita Culture Festival.
I'm going to play it from the 5th Akita Opera.
Goodbye, our music room. Private Ebisu Middle School Akita Culture Festival
Please listen to Happy End Talk Live. Private Ebisu Middle School, Aile Chukichi
version.
Aile Chukichi, a.k.a. Happy End Talk Live, Aile Chukichi
Thank you.
The song we just played was the Ail Chukichi version of Siritsu Ebisu Chugaku.
So, I'd like to ask you, Saito-tencho,
what is your favorite song from the album?
My favorite song?
Yes, please.
I can choose from any song.
Of course.
If I have to choose,
I'd choose the song that heals me when I'm tired.
I don't know how many times I've seen the music video for Summer Night, the
23rd.
I know that song.
It's a good song.
It's winter now.
Yes.
It's a good song.
I'm sure it will be gone.
It's a good song that makes you forget the season.
When I watch that video, I feel warm and energetic.
I'm glad to hear that.
Especially, I like the part where Rittan is walking quietly at the station,
and he smiles at the moment he finds the station.
Yasumoto-san, I think the video is about 1K 46,000 frames.
It's very detailed.
I feel like I'm in that scene.
The reality is really nice.
Is it called a bees cushion?
Yes.
It's called a buff.
Yes, yes.
That kind of thing.
One scene.
It's healing.
That's great.
I'd like to watch it again when I get home.
Yes, please.
Please watch it.
Summer Night.
It's where you make me eat a doll.
You're watching it in detail.
You're watching it properly.
Thank you for watching.
This is a Happy End Talk Live.
I'd like to talk about my memories of Akita.
But before that, I'd like to present a little something from Hasegawa.
The name is...
I don't like this kind of grammar that Hasegawa Shun thinks!
So, please follow the mic while we do this.
Here we go.
Thank you.
I don't like this boring stuff.
Applause!
The speed is black.
How is it black?
What?
If you speak too fast, you'll be cursed!
Um...
What is it?
This is a rule of the Sakiage Otoko-juku, right?
Oh, you're into pinpoints!
Sorry, I had a hard time with the togashi.
Yakuta culture that you must not laugh at!
What happens if you laugh?
If you laugh...
Here!
If you laugh, you'll be cut by a sword!
Oh...
I'm so excited.
I feel like your heart is being cut off right now.
There's still more to come.
Drinking coke in the theater and saying,
all the famous things in Akita are effective.
That's true. That might be a bit tiring.
Sorry, which one is more tiring?
This space.
Both.
There's still more to come.
You can breathe, everyone.
The finale will be Denjiro's
electric shock game!
That might be tiring.
Can I get a round of applause?
Next, I would like to introduce the President of the Faculty of Culture,
Heihachi Edajima.
Thank you very much.
Can I throw away the sketchbook?
So, that's it.
I made a little editing point.
So, I'd like to start the talk again.
First of all, I'd like you to see this.
Actually, there is a video.
I'd like you to see it.
That's why I lowered the hurdle.
I see.
I think Mr. Saito noticed it, but it's a little bit of a mess.
So, this is a digest of the Akita branch of Shizu Ebisu Junior High School.
Here you go.
.
Thank you for watching!
I think everyone wanted to hear this song,
which is a song that really makes you feel down.
How do you feel, Rita?
It's been a while since we did a collaboration.
How many years has it been?
Since the pandemic.
I feel like I'm back to my original Akita dialect.
I thought the first song was the song of the attendance number.
It was really fun.
It looked really fun.
I think Camisole Brothers are used to it.
I think so.
Something came out.
There was a scene where they were holding a shrimp hat.
Ayaka and I danced to Omekashi Fever.
We did a collaboration.
We danced to Omekashi Fever.
I'm dancing.
I saw you dancing in the audience seat.
Rita, who is dancing with you, is also wearing a traditional Japanese costume.
They danced with me when we were practicing.
I was happy.
Thank you for remembering our dance well.
That's right.
Everyone looked like they were having fun.
And the audience was like,
Yeah, yeah.
There were a lot of fans who said,
this is the first time they've come to Akita Bunko.
It was the first time I've experienced an at-home event like this.
It was so much fun.
There were a lot of people saying,
please come again next year.
That's great.
I was happy.
I think it's really great that
people who have never been here
can come to Akita Bunko and have fun.
Yasumoto-san, do you have any memorable moments?
I've always wanted to do the last mission survivor.
I'm sure everyone who comes to Akita Bunko
has been waiting for it.
I was really happy that we were able to
collaborate with everyone.
I'm really glad.
And the Braugon, the supporters of JDK.
They were the first to participate.
It was a lot of tension.
I was surprised.
Each member sent a message.
They were like, somehow, somehow, later.
They cheered for us.
I was impressed.
I was happy.
The movement was also sharp.
It was sharp.
After that movement, it was so sharp that I thought I was going to fall asleep.
When we saw it at the rehearsal, we thought we were going to lose.
I was a little impatient.
Oh, really?
So, from the rehearsal, the members of TDK were in that tension?
Yes, we were serious. We were so excited that our voices were going to die.
It was fun.
And the members of TDK were so excited.
You've been performing since the beginning of the show.
You've already got used to it, haven't you?
Yes, I was nervous at first because it was a very quiet atmosphere.
But when I saw them, I was smiling and laughing.
You were relaxed.
They were so kind.
I think there are not only the scary side of live performance, but also the cool
side of live performance.
Rita, weren't you afraid of live performance?
I'm used to it. I've been doing it for many years.
I want to be able to talk about it this year.
And the superhuman Neiger is also very popular as a hero of Akita.
Yes, every time, Kaho was with the hero.
The video was cool.
The hero and Neiger are also very similar.
I think that's great.
And the new members, Nohka Kazami, Koko-tan, Yuno Kokubu.
The first time you appeared was at the Binokuni Festival in Akita.
But you were in Akita. I think the new members had a different expression.
Yes, the three of us joined the festival because of the coronavirus.
We have little experience of performing with various people.
We were happy that everyone enjoyed it.
Specifically, as your junior member...
Last year's program of Akita Bunko
showed the reality of the Shonen aged production says,
It was very important for me to see their progress.
Wow, really?
Judging from the audience,
although they are practicing hard
do you think it's especially hard for them?
Even watching their performance
I watched it and thought it was great.
Akita culture has a long history.
What was your first impression of Akita culture?
My first impression of Akita culture was...
There was a big happening.
I was supposed to come to Akita by plane.
But I couldn't land because of the weather.
I had to go back to Tokyo and take a four-hour train.
I couldn't rehearse.
I was in a state of being in a collision.
I remember being very nervous and excited for the first time in Akita culture.
I realized that Akita is a very far place from Tokyo.
I felt it.
You can come to Akita by plane, but you took the bullet train.
It's still a hot topic, so it's still in my memory.
It's a story that young people can remember.
I watch Akita culture every year.
I first watched it in 2017.
In 2017?
The third best school play in 2017.
I thought it was delicious.
I really watched it.
It was the time when Ebi Kurashi was released.
The coolness of the song.
I was very impressed by the live performances of idols.
I feel that the impression is updated every year.
You always look really happy.
I'm really happy.
I sell CDs at work.
I haven't seen Akita culture live yet.
I see.
Every year, Hasegawa-san looks at me with a little smile.
I'm glad.
I'm going to tell you with my face.
I saw Hasegawa-san's line of goods this year.
I was so happy that I bought it again.
I bought it twice.
I'm glad.
I think there are many people who bought it.
I think it will be a good memory for everyone.
I was able to hear a lot of great episodes.
I think there are still many people who are addicted to the hospital.
Unfortunately, I will say goodbye to everyone who is watching the live
broadcast.
I think that the family who could not come to the special venue of the talk
event here in Akita Prefecture
I think you enjoyed it on the live broadcast.
Yasumoto-san, Nakayama-san, and everyone who is watching the live broadcast now.
Would you like to say a word?
I think the fans of Ebichu are a little busy today.
Thank you for watching YouTube.
I will continue to act as a beautiful girl in Akita.
I hope that Akita's charm will be conveyed a lot.
Please continue to support Tamarima.
Thank you very much.
Now, Nakayama-san, please.
Thank you for watching the live stream.
I think you could see my detailed expression because it was a live stream.
I was so nervous that I stood up and I was so angry.
I said, Nakayama-san, don't stand up.
I'm sorry.
I think there were a lot of expressions, but it was a lot of fun.
Akita is a very attractive place, so please come and visit.
If there is a Akita station this year, let's meet again.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much, everyone.
Thank you for watching the live stream.
The live stream will end here.
Thank you for watching.