Thank you for watching!
Please subscribe to my channel!
iterating
Hello, listeners!
Applause!
Thank you!
I'm Shunto Hasegawa, a comedian and
personality of Tamariba.
I'm Ayaka Sumota, a private A-bishu
student with a number 5.
I'm Riko Nakayama, a private A-bishu
student with a number 12.
Thank you!
You don't have many opportunities to
talk about your hometown, right?
We do have a lot of events when we have
a release, but we don't have a radio
where we can meet with the members every
month.
So we are looking forward to it.
It's really fun to talk about this.
And we are recording this, but we are
also doing a live broadcast.
I hope everyone will watch it.
Thank you.
I wonder if Hasegawa will be on the
screen sometimes.
Before we start, we have two makeup
artists here.
They will fix your makeup.
I'm not here, so I was wondering what to
do.
The staff asked me if I would like to
put on lipstick.
But I don't know whose lipstick I'm
going to put on.
I said I'd lick it.
Natural lipstick.
I'm natural.
Natural gloss.
Are you natural gloss?
It's already dry.
I should have put on lipstick.
We will also be broadcasting, so please
look forward to it.
I'd like to explain the schedule from
now on.
It's about an hour and a half from here.
It's the schedule for Happy End Talk
Live at Shiritsu Ebisu Junior High Akita
branch.
After this, Yasumoto-san and Nakayama-
san will talk about the themes.
There's a theme.
I wonder what it is.
I'm excited.
We'll talk about it for a while.
And we'll also talk about the big-
cutting.
I'm nervous.
Let's talk about it later.
How about it? Is it rare to have a big-
cutting at Ebisu?
Big-cutting.
We had it before, but not recently.
I haven't done it since I became an
adult.
You haven't done it since you became an
It's rare.
I'm looking forward to it.
We'll talk about the art festival held
every year at Tower Records Akita Opa.
Thank you for coming.
I'm looking forward to it because the
owner of the site is also an interesting
man.
I hope that we can spread our memories
and talk.
So, today's talk live is already pretty
much me.
I feel like I'm getting excited, but I'm
getting excited, right?
Thank you.
I'm sorry to check if you're getting
excited every time.
I'd like to play a song, but I'd like to
introduce the latest song suitable for
today's talk live event.
Please start with the two of you.
Please listen to it.
Boy-chan at Shiritsu Ebisu Junior High
School
It's been a while since I've been here.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, too.
Trailor
I will always love you.
Mai
Hi Everybody
Iam
※The 21st gundam was produced
※Pursuing the development of the first
Gundam
※Prosthetic body
※ corpo cubes
※The plate we are using is slightly
different than the previous one
※3D printed
※5d printed
Thank you.
The program was brought to you by the
private Ebisu Junior High School,
Voyager.
Now, let's get started with the corner.
The first corner is the Odaibox corner!
Applause!
Thank you very much.
So, as I said, the first corner is the
Odaibox corner.
Thank you very much.
We will be using items from the floor of
the Akitawa Bokkai.
And one of the items is this.
This box...
Can you hear the sound?
In this box, there are many capsule
toys, usually Gacha Gacha.
In the capsule, there are questions that
you want to answer.
Of course, we don't tell you the
answers.
I don't know what to talk about.
I'm excited to see what kind of
questions we'll get.
By the way, you can't answer the
questions once.
Is that a question that I can't answer?
It's a hard question.
It's a question for Stardust.
It's different from Yoshimoto.
So you can't answer the questions once.
It's a precious one-time question.
And the theme of the questions is...
There are two for Yasumoto and two for
Nakayama.
There are four questions that you and
Yasumoto have in common.
So if Yasumoto pulls a capsule for
Nakayama,
you have to answer it.
If you don't answer it, you can't answer
the questions.
Please answer the questions.
Let's start with Yasumoto.
I'll bring the box.
Thank you.
I wonder what kind of questions will
come.
It's like a question that you can't
answer.
I'll pull it.
It's really in the capsule.
I wonder what it is.
It's in the capsule.
Please look at it.
I pulled a question for Yasumoto.
It's just right.
If you give advice to someone who wants
to be good at singing,
I think it's a very good question.
Then this is NG.
You're lying.
I'll use it all of a sudden.
I wanted to hear it.
My reaction was not good.
I wanted to do it.
I had time in January.
Don't say it.
I wanted to do it.
That's good.
Yasumoto sings in acapella in various
places.
Please follow us on SNS and TikTok.
I think you're doing it.
I think there are many people who go to
karaoke.
What kind of advice do you have?
How to sing well.
It's easy to challenge.
When you sing, it's hard to sing because
you're nervous and tired.
Don't you sing better when you're drunk?
I see.
You can sing louder when you're tired.
You can sing high notes.
It's important to relax.
If you sing, you'll be able to sing
better.
It's important to stretch your
shoulders.
Relaxation around the neck and shoulders
is important.
I'm conscious of it.
You don't seem to have a stiff shoulder.
I have a stiff shoulder.
It's easy to get stiff shoulders because
it's a nervous scene.
That's why I gave you advice.
I think it's good to sing with a proud
heart.
It was very helpful.
I think it was great.
Let's move on.
I'll go next.
Could you bring it every time?
Thank you very much.
I'll do it.
Please subscribe to my channel.
How was it?
Yasumoto-san!
How did you start TikTok?
This is also a question I'm curious
about.
Can I talk first?
Yes, please.
How did I start TikTok?
It's a continuation of the song.
I like singing.
I want to strengthen my singing this
year.
TikTok is a content that dances.
I thought it would be nice to sing
because it's an app for videos.
I started TikTok because I wanted to
sing.
You sing in a cappella.
You sing in a relaxed way.
I sing songs I want to sing when I go to
karaoke.
Fans told me to sing.
I sing songs that I want to sing in
karaoke.
TikTok is really fun.
How about you, Rita?
I'm doing my best on Instagram.
I'm doing TikTok.
That's not true.
I'm doing official TikTok.
I'm doing it.
You're doing your best on social media.
Next, Nakayama, please.
It's been a while since I've done it.
I'm sorry.
It's just me and the two of us.
Thank you.
How is it?
Okay.
Here's the Gacha.
Oh, a common topic!
What was the first CD you bought?
Ah, Iino Hita!
I'm curious about this one.
How about you, Rittan?
For me, it was a CD...
High School Musical.
Oh.
It was an album with the songs from the
movie.
I bought it for my own money.
Oh, for your own money.
I have a memory of that.
And AKB's album,
Girls...
Was it there?
I don't know.
Yes.
I have a memory of both.
I don't know which one is earlier.
But it's quite impressive.
Yes.
You were quite young.
I was in elementary school.
You were in elementary school.
You must have bought it for your
parents.
No, no, no.
You bought it for your own money?
I bought it for my own money.
Even I sometimes get my CD from my
parents.
Even now?
Huh?
I'm your father.
What?
You're kidding.
I'm not talking about me.
How about you, Yasumoto?
I bought my first CD from Amuro Namie.
What was the title?
Best.
You bought the best one.
I bought the best one.
Yes.
I think I bought the best version.
I also bought the MV.
The MV that comes with the special
offer.
You bought the DVD?
Yes.
Wow, that's great.
I bought the first one.
At that time, I started to be interested
in singing and dancing.
That's how you started.
Yes.
That's how I bought the first CD.
I watched the DVD every day.
Yes.
My parents are both working, so I'm
usually free on Saturday and Sunday.
Oh, you're the same as me.
I've been watching the same DVD dozens
of times a day.
I bought it when I was in the 5th or 6th
grade of elementary school.
After all, buying a CD is a meeting with
music.
It's really the starting point.
When I was a kid, I used to buy a CD.
The fans gave me other idols' CDs at the
special events.
AKB48, Momokuro-chan's CD, etc.
Everyone participates in the special
events a lot.
The fans gave me a CD and I got to know
my favorite idols.
I've had a lot of encounters with CDs.
I think there are many people who bought
CDs at the special events.
We still have time, so let's ask
Yasumoto-san next.
I want to ask a question for Riko-chan.
What will come out?
Oh, here it is!
This is for Nakayama-san.
When do you want to take a picture?
Oh, this one!
When do I want to take a picture?
Basically, when I'm shooting, I'm into
film cameras.
Oh, film cameras!
I have two film cameras.
When do I want to take a picture?
I'm shooting a series of films now, so I
feel like I have to take a lot of
pictures and save them.
It's like a photographer's opinion.
That's right.
When do I want to take a picture?
When I'm shooting, everyone looks at me
with a good expression, but I want to
take a picture of me talking naturally.
When I look at your Instagram, it's very
natural.
I think the pictures you took when you
were looking back are really nice.
I think the pictures you took on
Instagram are really great.
I think the picture you took with
Yasumoto-san on the Asakusa date is also
nice.
When we go out together, we take
pictures of each other.
We are both working hard on Instagram,
so we take videos together.
Ayaka-chan, where were you two?
Ise?
Yes, Ise.
Ayaka-chan edited the video when we went
to Ise Prefecture.
You're like a video creator.
She helped us connect the good points.
I see.
When you take pictures with someone you
can get along with, you can take a
natural picture.
Your expression.
You can take a picture with a relaxed
expression.
I think it's best to take pictures with
a relaxed expression.
Let's take another picture.
I'd like to hear a lot of things.
Please turn around.
What will come out?
A common topic.
Oh, common topic.
What do you like about Akita?
Oh, this is also...
Of course, Akita people are here today.
I want to ask what Akita people like.
Well,
I like people in Akita.
Everyone is really warm.
I can't feel the warmth of the city in
Tokyo.
I came to the shopping mall to work.
When I come here as a group,
I feel a little uncomfortable in Tokyo.
I often feel cold eyes.
But everyone is really warm.
They look at me with a kind look.
I think everyone is really warm.
It's natural to live in Akita.
I think so when I meet people from other
prefectures.
How do you feel about coming from
Fukuoka?
Did you feel the kindness?
I'm sorry.
I was just drinking tea.
I want you to listen while replenishing
water.
How about you, Rita?
I feel like a warm barrier is being put
up.
I always think that Akita is surrounded
by a kind aura.
The air is different from the moment I
get off the bullet train.
It's completely different.
Is that so?
I feel calm.
I feel calmer than at home.
You feel really calm.
I feel really calm.
You feel like you're at home.
I'm in a state of mind.
When I go to a restaurant,
the staff talks to me very casually.
I feel like I'm always going to a
restaurant.
You feel like you're a regular.
I like the fact that we can have a
normal conversation.
That's good.
I'm a representative of Akita.
I'm a shy person.
Do you know what that means?
A shy person?
It means a person who is shy.
It's a word for Akita.
There's a place like that.
I think it's a warm gaze.
I think it's a close distance between
people.
I don't talk to you much.
What?
Next.
I'm sorry for the lonely story.
I heard a good story because I felt the
warmth.
Thank you.
That's all for the Odaibox corner.
Next up is the long-awaited segment!
The Oogiri Neta segment!
Yay!
Here it is!
Finally!
I'll say this first, but I'm not good at
Oogiri.
Everyone is!
But the comedians are.
The comedians are doing it.
Yes, there are a lot of them.
So I like the way the audience looks at
me.
The audience?
I feel safe that I don't have to answer
today.
Are you running away?
I'm scared!
I'm not relaxed because I'm at home.
So, I, Oogiri Neta Kodan, will stand up.
I'm so surprised!
I'll ring the bell.
Will it make a sound?
It's making a sound.
So, it's a matter of whether it's good
or bad.
In this segment,
Yasumoto and Nakayama will press the
button.
Yes!
Yes, it's working.
I, Hasegawa, will say a topic, so if you
think of an answer, please press the
button.
If you think of an answer, you can
answer it right away.
By the way, you can answer one topic as
many times as you want.
If you get a slip, you can get a
revenge.
Yes, if you get a slip, you can get a
It's okay.
There are many people who are tired of
it today, and it's warm.
Everyone, it's warm, right?
Look, look, this sense of security.
It's warm, so I didn't think there would
be a corner like this.
Really?
I didn't expect it.
Every time you answer, please press the
button.
I will read the topic again.
After that, there is a sound effect, the
sound of a lion's roar.
That sound will play, so please answer
after that.
I'm so nervous.
I'm nervous and I'm looking forward.
I'm looking forward.
Everyone, are you cheering for me?
I'm sorry to say this, but please be
prepared to laugh.
I practiced a lot earlier.
I practiced a lot.
This is a practice for the big cut.
This is a practice for this.
There is no problem with this practice.
So, here is the topic.
I will read the topic here.
Let's get started.
The first question.
Oh, cute!
You can make me move with this?
Here, a word with a photo.
You can see Nakayama's photo and say a
word with a photo.
If you think of something, please press
it.
I'll do it with my spirit.
Yasumoto-san.
A word with a photo.
What are you saying, Nakayama-san?
I want to eat fried chicken!
Ah, wait!
Wait a minute!
Let's be a little strict!
Let's go over that!
You look so nervous!
How is it? Say something in the photo.
Oh, it's her!
Let's go!
Say something in the photo!
What is Nakayama-san saying?
That person is in such a hurry in the
morning that he forgot to put on his
pants.
Oh no! What should I do today?
Wonderful.
Thank you very much.
Pants...
I wore pants.
Wonderful.
Nakayama-san, you got 1 point.
Thank you.
You're good.
Let's move on.
Let's move on to the next question.
Next, let's have a look at the photo.
This is the photo.
It's a nostalgic photo.
It's cute.
So, Yasumoto-san is wearing something.
Yes.
You're holding back.
Are you confident?
Let's see.
What is Yasumoto-san saying?
Dad, you took too many pictures.
Oh, that's harsh.
I'm sure you're...
Okay, let's go, Nakayama-san.
Say something in the picture.
What is Yasumoto-san saying?
Did you get the Buster?
You're messing with me.
This is...
It's a face-to-face.
What I like about this is that Yasumoto-
san's comment after that was good.
Thank you.
You're messing with me.
I followed you.
Let's do it again.
This?
Let's see Yasumoto-san's ping pong.
Are you ready?
Let's start.
Say something in the picture.
Yasumoto-san...
What did you say?
Nya!
Wow, that was so intense!
Intensity is important!
Intensity is important.
Sometimes, it's important.
By the way, you're a girl, but why are
you saying Nyaa?
I'm a girl, right?
I don't say that.
That's cute.
That's a good one.
Say something in the photo.
I don't say Nyaa.
Can I say something about me?
Can I say something in the photo?
I have a good one.
I'm sorry.
Say something in the photo.
What is Yasumoto-san saying?
Whose crinkel-like arms have glue all
over them?
I didn't think it would be this
slippery!
I'm sorry, there was a bad adult here.
It's slippery.
My nose...
I'm a bad adult.
You're the kind of person who laughs at
your nose.
Now, let's move on to the next topic.
You'll be looking at the picture and
answering, so you can think of it in a
flash.
But the next topic is the last one.
Ready?
Dosun...
Uwaa!
Wait, this...
Yes, so this is a slightly different,
but a fantastic photo.
Please think about it carefully.
Everyone, please think about it.
It's probably like this.
How is it?
It's really light.
Yasumoto, you're really quick.
You're really quick.
Let's go.
Please say something in the photo.
Yasumoto riding on the back of the
silver dragon.
I like this.
I think it's good to see the dragon's
face.
I can't see it at all.
How about a three-shot here?
This is a photo of Yasumoto.
I took a picture of it from Instagram.
She's thinking.
She's thinking a lot.
Yes.
Let's go.
I'll show you the feeling of a dragon.
The feeling of a dragon.
Please say something in the photo.
There's a person riding on the back of
the silver dragon with a smile like
this.
I ate too much grilled meat yesterday
and my weight is heavy.
Is that okay?
It's a little long.
But I like it when it starts with, you
know.
You know?
I like it when it starts with, you know.
It's like you're trying to maintain your
weight.
Yes.
You're so tight.
So that's that.
Should we move on?
Let's go.
So that's that.
But there's more.
Wow.
There's more.
So that's what it was like for the big
cut.
Yes, that's what it was like.
But what should I say?
Everyone, it was pretty smooth.
It's okay.
I'm not saying it's super smooth.
It's totally okay.
By the way, it's 2 to 2.
It's 2 points each.
Oh, that's good.
It's a tie.
It's not a photo, but it's a topic.
Done.
The name of the new school has been
revealed!
So, what's the name of the school?
Wow, thank you...
Thank you?
I knew it!
I'm getting goosebumps!
Hey, hey, hey!
Hey!
Wow!
I thought about it before I went to
sleep!
I thought about it too!
This is...
Even among the members...
We were quite close, right?
What is it?
I can't remember...
How was it?
Right?
Well...
If you reveal the name of the private
school,
what will it be?
It's quite simple, right?
It's simple, so it's hard to answer,
right?
I don't know anything.
Oh, here it is!
Well, are you ready?
Here we go!
Well, then...
What?
Private Ebisu Middle School has been
revealed!
What will the name be?
Just a shrimp.
Nice.
I don't like that. I don't like just a
shrimp.
That's good. It's like looking at the
future.
Like, time, time, land, and shrimp.
Shrimp.
Like, today we're two shrimp.
I think it's good.
I think there's a lot of people who
haven't seen it yet.
Let's see.
It's spinning at a great angle.
Yakimoto-san is spinning at an angle
I've never seen before.
Is it the best?
Then I'll say the classic one.
What's the classic one? Let's go.
The name is the K tying!
She's an alcoholic.
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
What is it?
It's in many ways!
I've seen it in a store.
People often say that.
She's a schizophrenic.
Like, um, I'm 25 years old.
When I say, I'm 25 years old,
most adults say,
Oh, then you're an alcoholic.
I'm often teased by comedians.
There are many bad adults.
I'm often teased by bad adults,
so I tried to tease myself.
I'm 100 points, but I'm sorry.
I thought about it.
Thank you.
Let's go to the final one.
It's the last one.
By the way, I'm leading with a 3-point
difference.
I'm leading with 1 point.
Is there anything?
How many points do the winners have?
There was nothing.
Oh, no, no, no.
Something, something.
From Mr. Hasegawa.
I sold my down jacket because I had no
work and no money.
I've been wearing a down jacket all the
way here.
It was the ultimate.
But there may be something.
So, it's the last one.
The last one.
Fujii Koucho is a big hit.
Please think of a new title from Koucho
to Honyarara.
From Koucho?
I'm glad you didn't say it's a common
one.
I'm so relieved.
From Koucho?
It's a set, so I think it's Koucho.
Fujii Koucho...
Oh, it's from Rittan.
Here we go.
Fujii Koucho is a big hit.
Please think of a new title from Koucho
to Honyarara.
A neighbor uncle.
Get out of the way.
Did he get promoted?
He did.
He does look like a neighbor uncle.
But he did get promoted.
Yes, he did.
But it was fun, so it's okay.
Thank you.
There are also these kinds of patterns.
Don't get too caught up in promotion.
I see.
A neighbor uncle.
Next, please raise your hand if you have
any ideas.
Here it is.
Sayato-san has pressed the button.
Fujii Koucho is promoted.
A new title from Koucho to Honyarara.
Think of a new title.
Fujii Sennin!
Oh!
Isn't that a great achievement?
That's great!
Fujii Sennin is...
I mean, there's no one better than
Sennin, right?
There isn't, right?
Yes.
It's not something you get used to.
Yes, Fujii Sennin.
It was brilliant.
Please give her a round of applause!
Thank you!
That was wonderful!
I don't need mine.
Of course, please! Please use as many as
you want!
Just one.
I'm going to read it.
The great rise of Fujii-kocho!
Katagaki from kocho to honyarara.
The new katagaki is...
Fujii-shodan.
Oh...
Thank you very much!
That's scary.
Oogiri is scary.
It's scary.
So, how was it? Did you have fun?
Yes, we had fun.
Good. Did you have fun, too?
Yes, we did.
Thank you very much.
So, that's it for the Oogiri Neta
Corner.
Thank you very much!
Everyone is so kind.
Yes, they are.
Kind and lovely.
So, we had a lot of fun with the Oogiri
corner.
We had a lot of fun.
Thank you very much.
Let's take a break from water, including
me.
Yes, let's.
We are really thirsty, so let's take a
nap.
I was nervous.
We may not be able to push you this
much.
I'm sorry.
Please take a break.
Now, let's move on to the next corner.
The Akita Art Festival, aka Tower
Records Akita Oppa Store,
has a full seat here.
There was a seat available, right? I've
been wondering for a long time.
Here he is.
I would like to invite the manager of
the site.
Manager Saito!
Oh, Mr. Saito!
Hello, I'm Saito, the director of Akita
Opera.
Nice to meet you, Saito.
You are the director of Akita Opera, and
we are grateful for your support every
year.
Thank you. I'm surprised to be in front
of so many people.
It's rare to see you nervous.
I'm an amateur, so I'm nervous.
You have been on the show of Tamariba.
I have been on the show of Tamariba many
times, so I often play with Hasegawa in
another corner.
I'm always being played, but I'm going
to play with you today.
Saito has been in charge of the
selection of Tamariba from 2021.
So far, he has selected 65 songs.
Thank you.
I don't remember what I chose from the
65 songs.
He has selected 45,000,000 songs.
He has also selected several songs from
the Ebichu.
The first song of the new year is the
2021 version of the Ebichu.
This is also my favorite song.
You have been selected.
Akita Opera is open from the beginning
of the year.
So, when the New Year comes, the
audience comes to buy CDs.
It's so warm.
When I see that, I feel like I'm in a
refrain.
Oh, it's flowing.
I spent such a New Year.
It was a job, but it was warm.
I feel really happy.
Grandparents buy CDs to make them happy.
It's so warm.
I'm happy.
This year, many regulations have been
lifted.
It seems that many grandchildren were
regulated.
It's a little easier to listen to.
I think there was a place to listen to
and exchange.
I love this song, too.
Nakayama, this song is a good song,
isn't it?
I feel like I'm in the bathroom.
It's like a family bathroom.
I often sing this song in the family.
I only sing it once a year, but I feel
like it's a waste.
I feel like I'm getting older and more
absorbed.
I feel like I'm singing at 13 or 14
years old.
It's a completely different feeling from
when I was 22 years old.
I feel like I'm growing up.
How about Yasumoto?
When I sing live, I remember my
grandparents.
There are members who cry.
As Riko said, the importance of family
when you grow up.
I feel grateful because I'm a little far
away.
I'm born more and more.
The weight of this song is changing.
It's a very promising song.
I wonder if my grandparents are doing
well.
I wonder if next year will be good.
I wonder if the next year will be good.
I'm completely in the same boat.
I think it's a really great song.
I'm going to talk about my memories of
Akita.
Before that, I'd like to give you a
little imitation.
I'd like to give you a little imitation.
I'd like to play a good song that I
performed at the Akita branch school.
I'm going to play it from the 5th Akita
Opera.
Goodbye, our music room.
Happy End Talk Live.
AERU Chukichi version at Ebisu Junior
High School.
Eating ice cream is Noburu, right?
New Episode Coming Wed. 1700 JST
The song we just played was the Aile
Chukichi version of Siritsu Ebisu
Chugaku.
So, Mr. Saito, I'd like to ask you about
your favorite song from the album.
My favorite song?
Yes, please.
I don't mind which song it is.
Of course.
If I have to choose, I'd say,
I don't know how many times I've seen
the music video for Summer Night, the
23rd, which is very relaxing when you're
tired.
I see.
That's nice.
It's winter now, but it's so nice that
you forget the season.
When I watch that video, I feel warm and
energetic.
I'm glad to hear that.
Especially, I like the song called
Kakudeito.
When Rittan arrived at the station, she
was walking quietly at first, but the
moment she found me, she ran to me with
a smile.
It was said that she realized that and
spread herわんあぁまでっぽいおもちゃ into the把柵.
Yasumoto-san, you know, I think it's a
1K 46,000-ish image.
It's very detailed.
It's like you're there.
The reality is really wonderful.
Do you call it a bees cushion?
Yes.
It's called a buff.
Yes, yes, yes.
That kind of thing.
One scene.
It's healing.
As expected.
I'd like to see it again when I get
home.
Yes, please do.
Please watch the 23rd episode.
Summer Night.
It's where you make me eat a doll.
You're looking at it in detail.
You're looking at it properly.
I'd like to say it again.
Yes, that's what I said.
Now, Shiritsu Ebisu Junior High School,
Yasumoto Ayaka and Nakayama Riko, and
Tower Records Akita Oppa Store Manager
Saito.
Goodbye, our music room.
Shiritsu Ebisu Junior High School Akita
branch.
It's a happy end talk live.
Now, I'd like to talk about Akita
branch.
Yes, please do.
Before that, I'd like to present a
little something from Hasegawa.
The title is,
I don't like this kind of grammar that
Hasegawa Shun, the personality of
Tamariba, thinks!
So, I'd like you to follow the mic.
Here we go.
Thank you.
I don't like this boring stuff.
Applause.
The speed is black.
How is it black?
If you speak too fast, you'll be cursed!
Um...
What is it?
This is a rule of the Sakiage Otoko-
juku.
You're stuck on the pin point!
Sorry, I had a hard time with the
togashi.
Yakutabunko that you must not laugh at!
What happens if you laugh?
If you laugh...
Here!
If you laugh, you'll be cut down!
That's...
Your heart is cut right now, but there's
still more.
I'm laughing.
Drinking coke in the theater and saying
all the famous Akita words are valid.
That might be a bit hard.
Sorry, which one is harder?
This space.
Both.
You can do it.
You can breathe.
The finale will be finished by Denjiro
sensei's electric shock game.
That might be hard.
Can I get a round of applause?
Next,
The President of the Ministry of
Culture, Edajima Heihachi!
That's all. Thank you very much.
Can I throw away that sketchbook?
And so, we've created a little editing
point.
Now, I think it's time to start talking
again.
First, I'd like you to look at this.
Actually, there's a video.
I'd like you to watch it.
That's why I lowered the hurdle.
I see.
With that set.
I think Saito-san is editing it, but
it's a bit of a mess.
Now, it's time for the digest of the
Akita branch of Shizu Ebisu Junior High
School.
Here we go.
Thank you for watching.
It was wonderful.
When the VTR started, I felt like I was
watching a live performance.
I felt the unity of the audience.
It's a song that really makes you want
to listen to it.
I'm sure you all had a set list of
songs.
Yes, by all means, how about Rita?
Yes, it's been a while since we've
collaborated.
It's been three years. How many years
has it been?
Yes, yes.
Oh, after the coronavirus.
I feel like the original Akita dialect
has returned.
And on this day, I thought it was the
first song, the song with the number of
attendance.
I think Setori was the god.
It was really fun.
It really looked fun.
Camisole Brothers, too.
I feel like I'm used to it.
That's right.
Something came out.
There was a scene where they were
holding a shrimp hat.
Ayaka and I danced to Omekashi Fever
together.
I got to collaborate with her this time.
Yes, Omekashi Fever.
I'm dancing.
I was watching you from the audience
seat.
Rita, who is doing this with you, is
also wearing a tonfuku like her family's
past.
They've been dancing so hard since we
practiced.
I was happy.
Thank you for remembering it.
I think so. Everyone seemed to be having
fun.
And the audience seemed to be having
There were many fans who said they came
to Akita Bunko for the first time.
It was the first time I experienced an
at-home event like this.
It was so much fun.
There were many voices saying,
I'm glad I came to Akita Bunko.
It's great that the first person who
came to the event was able to be moved
like that.
Yasuho, do you have any memorable
moments?
I've always wanted to do the last
mission survivor.
I'm sure everyone who came to Akita
Bunko has been waiting for it.
I'm glad we were able to collaborate
together.
I'm glad we were able to collaborate.
I'm sure there were many people who
supported you.
I was the first person to participate in
the event.
I was very excited.
I was surprised.
I was able to send a message to each
member.
I was moved.
You were happy, right?
The movement was also sharp.
After that movement, it was so sharp
that I thought I was going to fall
asleep.
When we saw it at the rehearsal, we
thought we were going to lose.
We were a little impatient.
So, from the rehearsal, the members of
TDK were in that tension.
I was serious and my voice was going to
die.
You were doing it with all your might.
I was happy.
And you guys are bare-faced.
You guys have been going to the audition
since the beginning of the Akita branch.
You've already got used to it.
At first, I was nervous because I
thought it would be a very quiet
atmosphere.
But when I saw you, you were smiling.
I got a little relaxed.
I thought you were a kind person.
I think there is a coolness of bare-
faced.
Rito, weren't you afraid of bare-faced?
I got used to it.
I want to do anything.
I want to be able to talk this year.
Certainly, Satokakura-san is bare-faced.
And Reiga Choujin.
Reiga Choujin is also very popular as a
hero of Akita branch.
Every time, Kaho-chan was with the hero.
The video was cool.
The hero and Reiga are related by many
things.
I think that's great.
And the new members, Nohko Kazami, Koko-
tan, Kokona-san, and Yuno Kokubu.
The first time you appeared was at the
Binokuni Festival.
It was the first time at the Akita
branch.
But when you went to the Akita branch,
the new members' expressions were
different.
Yes.
We have joined the group during the
pandemic.
We have few experiences of performing
with many people.
We were happy that they enjoyed it.
What about you, Rito?
You are the junior of the new members.
I think you can see it if you watched
the last year's episode.
I felt that I couldn't stay as I was in
the Akita branch.
I felt my growth.
I see.
I saw the audience and you were doing it
without hesitation.
Do you have any conflicts in your mind?
I thought that our expressions were
different.
Akita branch has a long history.
Do you have any feelings about the first
time you came to the Akita branch?
The first time I came to the Akita
branch, there was a big happening.
I was supposed to come to the Akita
branch by plane.
But I couldn't land due to the weather.
I had to go back to Tokyo and take a
four-hour train.
I couldn't rehearse.
We were almost in a collision.
I was so nervous and excited to be in
the Akita branch for the first time.
I realized that Akita is a far place
from Tokyo.
You can come to the Akita branch by
plane, but you took a new train.
It's still a hot topic.
It's still in my memory.
It's a story that young people can
relate to.
I come to the Akita branch every year.
I came to the branch in 2017.
The third time I came to the Akita
branch was the best.
I was so happy to see the third time.
Ebi Kurashi was released at the time.
The coolness of the song.
I was very impressed by the live
performance of the idol.
I feel that the impression is updated
every year.
You always look like you're having fun.
I'm glad.
I sell CDs at work.
I haven't seen the Akita branch live
yet.
I see.
You always look at me with a smile.
I'm glad.
I'm going to tell you with my face.
I saw Hasegawa-san's goods once and
bought them again.
I bought two.
I think there are many people who bought
it.
I think it will be a good memory for
everyone.
I was able to hear a lot of great
episodes.
I think there are many people who are
still immersed in the hospital.
I'm sorry to say goodbye to everyone who
is watching the live broadcast.
I think that the family who could not
come to the Akita branch live event will
be able to enjoy it.
Yasumoto-san, Nakayama-san, and everyone
who is watching the live broadcast,
please say a word.
I think the fans who are watching the
live broadcast are busy today.
Thank you for watching YouTube.
We will continue to act as Akita beauty
girls.
We hope that Akita's beauty will be
conveyed to the audience.
Tamarima, please continue to support us.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Ms. Nakayama, please.
Thank you for watching the live
broadcast.
I think you could see my detailed
expression because it was a live
broadcast.
I was so nervous that I suddenly stood
up and I think I was very angry.
I said, Mr. Nakayama, please don't stand
up.
I'm sorry.
I think there were a lot of expressions,
but it was a lot of fun.
Akita is a very attractive place, so
please come and visit.
If there is a Akita station this year,
let's meet again.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much, everyone.
Thank you for watching the live
broadcast.
The live broadcast will end here.
Thank you for watching.