Thanks for watching!
My legs are shaking.
Why?
Your legs are shaking like a whale.
I'm shaking.
I don't feel like shaking.
It's in my body.
That's what it is.
It was fun.
Can you climb again soon?
I don't do this sometimes.
I said it.
Once every 10 years.
10 years?
It's shorter than the age of a blue.
Over there.
Please subscribe to my channel.
We're done!
How long did it take us to get here?
It's fast! It took us 30 minutes.
It's great to be young!
We decided on a good word for the end of
the day.
Megami-chu.
It's okay.
Mon-chan is coming.
Mon-chan is coming!
An-yo-ga-Za-Zu!
You don't look like you're in the mood
for it.
An-yo-ga-Za-Zu!
How many times have we done this?
Welcome back!
Here's the tape.
I'm going to eat ice cream.
It was good, wasn't it?
It's a rock climbing.
I tried rock climbing without
permission.
Everyone, time is running out.
I can't open my legs.
It's hard.
Hang in there, everyone!
I'm scared.
It's okay.
I'm going!
The end!
It was fun!
It was frustrating, but it was fun.
It was frustrating!
Trampoline!
Oh, my God!
I was hit.
I'm sorry.
Wow!
Thank you for watching.
I was in high school.
I was riding a train in the morning.
I was so excited that I could hear the
voices of the students.
Two high school girls behind me said,
I want to teach you this.
I thought I was definitely myself.
I was so excited.
I said I was definitely myself.
But I was so embarrassed to find
something to fix it.
I pretended not to know and put on my
earphones.
I got on the train and got off.
But there were so many people behind me.
I thought I was going to go to school as
it was.
I went to school and looked in the
mirror.
I found a lot of people behind me.
I was so embarrassed.
I thought the day was over.
I thought I was going to teach them.
I was so embarrassed.
I thought I was going to cut off my
collar.
I was worried about my collar when I got
home from school.
Ouch!
Don't worry about my collar!
What's this?
To be continued.
I didn't notice that you were alone.
Is it recording?
I'm in trouble.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to cut it.
I'm going to change it.
You're going to change it.
I can't use it.
She's changing it.
I'm going to change it.
I don't think you change the topic when
you change the topic.
Of course.
I think this is the end.
It's really good.
It's a good ending.
How was it?
Thank you for watching.
I don't hate the Pistol Pusher.
I'm just curious.
Do you want to drink a lot of mahi-mahi?
I think I can still do it.
It was delicious.
I came here with the feeling that I
would eat today.
I think I can eat a lot if I come here
with the feeling that I would eat today.
I will increase the ranking.
What do you think?
I was glared at by only one person.
I ate a lot.
I will loosen the belt.
I'm full.
I will eat.
I ate a lot.
What do you want to do?
I used to get a lot of money from my
fans.
I didn't mean that.
No, no, no.
I didn't have money like Suzuka.
I remember that.
I'm going to spin it.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Hello, it's started!
I can't see the bottom!
Suddenly, the questionnaire involves.
It's spinning on its own.
I don't know if it's usable.
I'm glad.
How was Anko?
It's cold.
I'm still keeping Anko here.
No.
I haven't touched it yet.
You touched the eyeball.
I'm sorry to Anko.
I should have been more polite.
I didn't think it was Anko.
Anko of the fight.
You haven't touched it yet.
I said,
It's an octopus.
It's a hair-removal product.
I heard that I cut it.
Is that so?
It's cute.
I want to eat it.
It's fresh.
It's delicious.
I want to put it in my mouth while it's
alive.
I want to eat it.
I want to do it.
It looks painful.
I want to put a camera in my mouth.
I want to eat it.
I want to do it.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Thank you for watching.
It's cold.
It was fun.
Thank you.
I feel the ground.
I got it!
I'll grab it.
I broke it.
Can you do it, Rian?
I can't do it.
Let's go!
Wait a minute.
I can't put my feet out.
Can you take it off?
I can put my feet out, but it's
dangerous.
I can't put my feet out.
Let's start!
OK!
Let's go!
Ready!
Go!
It's so hard!
Sorry, sorry, sorry!
It's so cold!
look!
I was so focused on the eyes.
Did you find it?
No.
No way.
I didn't find it until I came here.
This is also...
I think I fell down once.
Where did you fall down?
I found it!
Oh, thank god.
Thank you for watching. Please subscribe
to my channel.
This is good.
Yeah.
Thank you for the food.
It was fun.
But, you know,
today's stage was so big, wasn't it?
Yeah, it was.
We were surprised.
We were facing back and came out.
So, we didn't know the scenery in front
of us.
And we did like this.
We had to do like this.
We were about to get on the stage.
I thought it was something.
Mr. Goto was not in the audience.
Really?
But my manager told me that I can't do
it.
I think I was enjoying the live
broadcast.
I was.
I thought I might be able to do it.
Why are we doing the firework?
What?
I don't know why we are doing the
firework.
I don't know why.
We are doing the firework to burn the
black history.
I don't know why.
How long did you do this?
I did it for 15 minutes.
Without stopping?
I did it for 3 to 5 minutes.
If you stop, it's over.
I didn't do it with such a momentum.
I did it with all my strength.
What is that?
It's terrible.
We have our own efforts.
We are working hard.
You are a black background and a white
background.
We are working so hard.
We are not a chicken farmer.
Rie is serious.
Rie is dangerous.
Let's cheer for Rie.
Rie is serious.
How about today's lunch?
Today's lunch?
What should I do?
We worked so hard.
Please continue.
It's not our fault.
We are hungry.
Thank you for watching.
I found a banana.
Do you want to eat?
Thank you for bringing it.
Osaru-san.
It's been a long time since I ate a
banana.
You are like a lion.
It's the best.
The best?
Yes.
There is a strawberry.
I don't like strawberry.
I like strawberry.
Do you want to eat strawberry?
Why?
I don't want to eat it.
You ate it last time.
So, you don't want to eat it for a
lifetime.
I don't want to eat it at all.
Cute.
I'm taking a growth record as a
babysitter.
I heard a funny story about this girl.
She went to a team lab.
There is a place where you can sleep
with a projection mapping of flowers.
Everyone was sleeping and smelled
flowers.
We were watching a fantasy.
She was sleeping seriously.
We were watching a couple in a dry room.
It was a very noisy place.
She was alone.
She was sleeping seriously.
It was embarrassing.
How long did she sleep?
I don't know.
I don't think she slept that much.
But it was a fantasy.
She was healed.
I burst out laughing when I heard that
story.
She wanted to be alone.
But she got lonely on the way.
She was alone.
She was alone and she was heartbroken.
She was pitiful.
Let's go there next time.
But it was fun.
She wanted to be alone.
She wanted to go around as much as she
wanted.
She wanted to go there.
It was fun.
Please look forward to the next time.
Hello!
What are you doing?
Do you want to try this?
Like a shooting?
No, I don't want to do it.
I don't want to do it, but I will do it.
I'm shooting a visual for the summer
tour.
The train is coming.
Ta-da!
Akasatana, Hama, Ya, Wa, Kishiki, Ni
That's it!
I'm a voice actor!
But, Ya and Wa are three letters each,
right?
So, Akasatana, Hama, La
There are five letters, so 8 is 40
And the rest are three letters each, so
6, so 46
So, it's 50 letters
Wait, then, Agyo
Akasatana, Hama, La
Is this a Japanese class?
I don't know at all
What should I do?
So, you can do it with 8 letters each,
so 10 for each
So, it's 5 in Agyo, so 10
Wow
You can do it with Ya and Wa later
Yes
Who is good at Agyo?
I'm not good at it
Everyone!
Can you hear me?
We are...
I'm Ikinari Tohaku!
I'm Ikki!
This time, I, Sakura Hinano, will be
doing the voice acting.
Last year, I did the voice acting for
the Shikiusuki!
Today, we will be throwing the ceremony
kit!
Everyone!
I'll do my best!
Thank you very much!
Thank you!
I'm nervous.
Wow!
It's so good!
Thank you!
Go, Rengo!
Oh, beautiful!
Thank you for watching.
Wow!
Beautiful!
My hand is bent, so I'm going to go this
way.
You can do it slowly.
I'm fast, so I'm going to go this way.
You were a little fast.
Don't rush.
Slowly.
Stop.
Thank you for watching.