Please subscribe to the channel.
You can start eating now.
As expected.
I don't get many chances to ask
questions about myself.
I hope that the fans of other groups
will like this.
Give me the rice.
Thank you.
Oh, that's good.
Gant Idol
Welcome!
My favorite food is salt and pepper.
Salt is delicious, but pepper is a
little spicy.
It's a little oily, so it's good to have
a little spicy.
I love salt and pepper.
And I like it as it is.
When I ate fried chicken with vinegar,
it was really tasteless.
I like it because it's delicious even
without vinegar.
I was sent a video of Sakura eating.
It was delicious.
But it was crispy, so there was a rumor
that it was half-baked.
Did anyone get hungry after that?
No, I'm fine.
I'm glad.
I'm probably fine.
Sakura's fans, please be assured.
I didn't think she would eat it.
I heard that she ate it.
I was happy and worried if I would be
okay.
I was worried that there would be no
live performance tomorrow.
Thank you for your viewing.
I'll say thank you directly next time.
What should I say?
There is a member named Nao Aoyama.
Nao is good at moving her body.
I also uploaded a video of her singing
in VOLT's TikTok.
VOLT has a lot of rock and band sounds.
So, I'm not used to singing in the same
tone.
I've never heard her singing in the same
tone before.
I'm curious how she uses the same tone
as VOLT's songs.
She's still a junior high school
student.
I'm curious how she uses the same tone
as VOLT's songs.
She's cute.
She's cooking sweet potatoes.
She's cooking sweet potatoes for the
first time.
She's cute.
If you can do it, can you bring it to
Ai?
I'll bring it to her.
Why do you like Ai?
She likes sweet potatoes.
I can't lose to her.
I like her sweet potatoes.
She likes sweet potatoes.
Are you going to dig sweet potatoes?
I'll dig it.
I want to dig it.
I don't like sweet potatoes.
She looks like a demon.
I want to dig it.
I'm going to eat it.
I'm getting confused.
I'm going to be called a cheater if I
say this.
But I've been admiring her since I
joined STADIUM.
I respect her so much that I think it's
rude to say that she's a cheater.
I want to be a hostess of Tamae again.
I talked about this when I made sweet
potatoes last time.
I want to go to a potato farm with Aichi
Kiyama, who loves potatoes.
It's rare to be together in Kanto and
Kyushu.
I want to go to a farm with Aichi
Kiyama, who loves potatoes.
I want to go to a potato farm with Aichi
Please subscribe to my channel!
I'm sure it's hard to say this to
someone who's been doing cheerleading
seriously, but can you show us a little
bit?
Cheerleading?
I'm going to show you how to do a
flexible cheerleader's body.
Is that okay?
It's okay.
Can you do it?
I'll do it.
I'll be in the back.
This is it!
It's soft, but...
It's not easy to do.
It's not easy?
It's not easy.
I can do this, but...
I don't think I can clap in the back.
I'm sorry, I was just trying to get the
right angle.
It was hard to get the right reaction.
It's hard, isn't it?
I'm afraid I'll get cut.
It's hard.
I heard that you have a habit of acting.
From your manager.
When you play gesture games at events,
It's pretty difficult.
What do you do?
I don't know if it's because of your bad
feelings towards the audience.
I don't know if it's simply a matter of
your expressiveness.
It's pretty difficult.
I've been playing gesture games at
special events lately.
I don't think I can get the right
answer.
But you're mean to the audience.
If I finish the game right away,
I don't have time to talk.
You're not good at it.
People say it's fun because I can't get
the right answer.
If I get the right answer in two
seconds,
I'm sorry, I should have cut it a little
more.
You're having a hard time getting a high
score.
I'll try to guess the answer.
I'll give you a question so you can't
see it.
You'll have to guess the answer by
gesture.
I'll guess the answer.
You'll guess the answer.
It's hard to guess the answer at a
special event.
I like to see people in trouble.
Like Chiba.
That's a good one.
Is it that hard?
Like New York.
Please.
I'm having a hard time.
Thank you for watching.
Mmm mmm.
That's all.
I got it.
Ah!
When you're hungry,
you're going to be These two days
Football
You're wearing the wrong hat.
That's close.
It's close?
It's close.
Uber Eats.
I see.
How about this?
I think you're pretty good at
communicating with the doctor.
Yeah, I'm pretty much getting it right
now.
You were surprisingly good.
It's Uber Eats.
But it's hard for fans to guess.
I guess that's because you're an idol.
I think I'll give you a hard time.
Are you playing with me?
I think the fans are happy to see your
face.
Please come again.
I'll do it again.
I'll do it.
Please.
You're quite impatient.
That's right.
I'm very impatient.
I thought,
you're quick-witted.
But I was right.
Good for you.
Yes.
Yakanto Idol