Ebitune's videos
We've been doing videos for a long time.
We've done it 33 times.
I'd like to take a look back.
It was hard to do the radio show.
We did it on Zoom.
I did it like, how many people can join
the show?
We do it on Zoom.
I just did it with my fans on Zoom.
I didn't even have to do the live.
It was like a personal radio show.
I don't know what it was.
A fan meeting?
It was a radio show fan meeting.
I don't know if it's a good thing, but I
posted it on Twitter in the morning.
That's amazing.
I've never done that before.
There's a lot of things.
I've done it before.
I've done it once.
I'm scared.
It's the eighth time.
I've done it once.
Everyone's got something.
I think we can do it in a week.
I'm a Japanese artist.
I can't do juggling.
I'm not good at it.
It's cute.
I can't do everything.
I was surprised when I saw the rubik's
cube.
The vice president of the rubik's cube
told me.
I was surprised.
I was able to do it in six minutes.
I was doing a live broadcast.
The vice president came to the comment
section.
I was surprised.
Thank you very much.
I'm a Trump.
It was amazing.
I'm a Santa.
I was surprised.
Riko is an omelette.
I'm a fluffy omelette.
I made a fluffy omelette.
I made a omelette.
The material was a picture of an
omelette.
I was confused by the omelette.
I was able to make an omelette.
Did you do anything after you got into
this art?
I did.
I can't do juggling when I practice.
I can't do it because I have a lot of
hair.
I brought it to the TV.
I thought it was my hobby.
I wanted it.
I thought I could do it.
I wanted to do it when I was in the
final round.
I was impressed that I practiced hard.
I was impressed.
Hina did the Rubik's Cube.
I did it.
I didn't know the meaning of the four-
sided cube.
I didn't know there were so many types.
I did the six-sided cube first.
I'm used to it.
I thought it would be easier if I did
two cubes first.
I can't do two cubes at all.
Is there a procedure?
If you turn it this way, you can do it.
Do you use your head a lot?
I have to remember it.
Can you do it if you remember it?
There is definitely a color that is
symmetrical.
The yellow is white.
The blue is green.
The red is orange.
Is there a way to be a pair?
Are you a member of the Kyu-Fu
Association?
No, I'm not.
I haven't been able to get that far.
I don't know.
I'll be there in about 40 years.
I might be a couple for about 40 years.
I see.
Riko-chan, you also have a class to
learn the first step.
From that,
Riko Nakayama's
women's power.
You were cooking, right?
How was it?
I haven't cooked yet.
You haven't done it yet.
I've never seen you do it.
Let's learn the first step.
I was practicing hard to make eggs.
I've been practicing hard.
I've been cooking eggs for over a week.
Since then,
I've been eating omelette and omelet.
I'm tired of it.
I've been eating eggs for a year.
I had fun playing table tennis.
I had fun.
I don't know the rules at all.
I've been playing.
Have you ever won a zero prize?
Zero.
Is this right?
I heard you were like this.
I'm not good at it.
I didn't have a lot of time.
Was there any play
you had a lot of fun with?
I played Sushi Mayama.
It was a great play.
I got a lot of help
from Sushi Maru Sankaku of Shibuya.
I went to the sushi restaurant
I was able to get a sushi restaurant.
That's amazing.
I didn't think I would ever get a chance
to eat sushi.
It's difficult to make shari.
I see.
It's a bit thick, but I can cut it.
But it's impossible to make shari with
less rice.
It's impossible to make shari with more
rice.
I have to do it.
It's a skill.
If I had more training, I could have
improved.
I want to do it again.
It was really fun.
That's great.
I see.
I like my own face study.
Thank you very much.
I'm a professional.
I had a lot of fun.
Did you have fun?
I feel like I'm back to my childhood.
I had a lot of fun.
I was thinking about what to make.
What is the story of Riko Nakayama?
I was talking to myself.
That's great.
I don't have an image.
What was it about?
What did you talk about?
Riko, I don't remember this YouTube.
This is recent.
I was asked to do a stage.
I took a lot of recording time.
Three hours is 12 minutes.
That's strange.
It's really.
I took two minutes.
I was surprised.
That's great.
I also took a week's course.
I took a week's course.
That's fashionable.
I packed my luggage.
I took a week's course.
I asked the cameraman to take a picture.
I took a picture in a beautiful place.
I took a week's course because I had a
girl who was referring to MIE.
I also took a week's course.
There are various genres.
I was not tied to one.
I thought about some items.
I was talking about baseball.
Miyamoto came to me.
I was surprised.
I thought it was a video.
I didn't think I would fall from the
chair.
I was surprised that only the chair was
reflected.
I didn't think Miyamoto would come to me
in the video.
I didn't think it would be in such a
place.
Did you feel the prospect of coming?
I didn't feel it at all.
I thought there were many adult people.
I thought I was busy because I was busy
with work.
I didn't think it would be.
It was the last time.
I was at a graduation ceremony during
the Ebitu University Conference.
One by one.
I did my best.
I was in the graduation ceremony in
2020.
There were many plans in 2020.
I want to do various things in 2021.
It's hard to stay at home.
Do you have any plans to do it?
I want to go out.
I want to go out and play.
I want to go back to my childhood.
I want to make it a color.
I want to fix it with a camera.
I want to do it.
I love it.
I was addicted to bowling last year.
I went to the gym with everyone.
I want to do foot volleyball.
I want to do a round ball.
I want to do it.
I want to do something active.
I want to do a sport.
It's fun.
I want to answer questions.
I want to do something.
I want to dance.
I want to learn this dance.
I don't know.
It looks fun.
I want to do it.
I don't know.
I want to dance.
I want to do it.
It looks fun.
I can't make a song.
I want to dance.
It's fun.
There are many types of dance.
We will make various videos.
Thank you.