Tonight's Ebitu Tastas continues last
week
Tastas the Indian
PR for the Indian Ebitu
What is the number one Ebitu that the
Indian decides?
In addition, the full-scale fortune
teller appears
A shocking future is given
Ebichu Tastas, start!
I'm Nina.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Last time, the members of the Ebi-Chu
came to the party where Indians gather.
Wait a minute, brother.
What is a Russian gorilla?
Yeah, yeah, I want to wait a minute.
I'm sure you're talking to an Indian.
It's a rare opportunity, so I'd like to
promote shrimp chuu to Indians.
To let Indians know shrimp chuu, we will
hold a self-promotion competition.
Members will be wearing Indian
traditional costumes and will be self-
promoting freely in the stand.
The member who has the most Indian heart
will win.
The judges are Indians living in the
west.
On the other hand, the members who have
not thought of anything are...
It's completely away.
What should I say to make them feel
better?
The members are worried about the PR.
So, first of all, the shooting star will
warm up the venue in the prelude.
We are Japanese comedians, 流星の滝上と
Chua and...
I have a cough.
Handsome is here.
前説失敗
In the worst atmosphere, the shrimp-
chewing self-PR battle starts.
The top batter is Hoshina Mirei.
PR for the Indians starts.
The first person, entry number one,
Mirei Hoshina.
The second person, Hoshina Mirei.
The third person, Hoshina Mirei.
Namaste!
Konnichiwa!
360 degrees, Indian curry!
My name is Hoshina Mirei, lucky 7.
Please call me Mirei!
Mirei!
Thank you!
Okay, thank you!
It was like a soccer match
It's so embarrassing
Let's continue
Entry No.2 Aika Hirota
Hello!
Yes, today we can bloom the flower of
love, Miracle Magical Mascot
The no.6 is Ai Ai, Koto Hirota Aikawa
Ai Ai Ai Ai
A lot of people are waiting for you
Thank you
Thank you very much
What is it? Suddenly the call started to
be popular
It's like a
It's good
Entry No.3 Mayama Rika
I am Rika Mayama. Please call me Mayama.
She stands up without a word.
And then...
Mayama! Mayama!
I feel like I was helped by the
audience.
It's nice.
Kind.
So far, she managed to come here while
being helped by kind Indian judges.
Nakayama is waiting for her turn.
What kind of scene is spreading?
Entry No.4 Riko Nakayama
She is trying to be funny and start
self-promotion
Why are you laughing? Are you okay?
Riko Nakayama's self-promotion
12th, 12th, 12th, Rikutan, Rikutan, it's
Rikutan
This person, this person
Thank you very much
I managed to remember the name, but I
couldn't get a return call
Can he break the atmosphere? Entry No.5
Yasumoto Ayaka
I'm Yasumoto Ayaka.
I love tomatoes.
Thank you.
Too fast!
You ran away.
She was fine until the factory, but she
felt the dangerous atmosphere and ran
away in an instant.
Kaho Kobayashi's baton touch.
I'm singing enough.
I'm singing nice.
I like A-fan.
The venue is frozen by an
incomprehensible performance.
What will they do?
She succeeded in making the crowd
excited with her incredible power
I managed to do it
And the one to decorate the bird is
entry number 7, Rina Matsuno
Rina's
Thank you for watching!
It's spring
The sluggish Indian girl received the
message
What is waiting for her?
What is everyone? Say!
What is everyone?
Thank you very much
The fun ends with a mysterious call
That's all for today
How was it, Chuu-san?
The appearance is beautiful, but the
content is a bit
The content is more appealing
Matsuno-san is the leader
The appearance is beautiful, but the
content is a bit
It's quite obvious
I thought it was just a simple word
But you used the Indian specialty well
I see
The members who finished the
confrontation like this
Finally, the results will be announced
by the Indian new member
And before that
Ebitune Game Quest
Ebitune Game Quest Project is now in
progress!
The members who have challenged two
games so far for the game project that
was suddenly announced
Today's quest is
What? You're not opening it?
I'll open it
It's simple
You wrote it in the dictionary
I wrote it in the dictionary
Experience the games in the world and
aim for the level up
Today's game is Yamanote line game
The questions are all OK
The member who loses will get a sour
juice
This time, Ebichu will challenge the
Yamanote line game
First, Kotani will think of the topic
What kind of animal is there?
There are many
I'm hungry
Fish
The name of the fish is difficult
Animal?
It's a love dream
Let's try animal
It's easy
Yamanoku Sengen
Yay!
Let's try animal
Ready, set, go!
Cat
Dog
Rabbit
Monkey
Turtle
Sparrow
Bye bye!
Bugs!
Koalas!
Crows!
Penguins!
Kangaroos!
Gorillas!
Crows!
Monkeys!
Oralas!
BAM BAM
Lizard
Elephant
BAM BAM
Hitchhiker
Deer
BAM BAM
Crab
Whale
BAM BAM
Milk
Crab
Oh!
I got it!
I got it! I got it!
So, Yasumoto-san, it's your last game.
Good luck!
I'll eat it.
Ah, I got it!
Is it sour?
It's sour.
I'm going to get a drool.
I got it!
The game project of Ebichu. The journey
of the dangerous adventure continues.
After this, the results of the PR
meeting are finally announced.
The results of the Ebitu self-PR meeting
are finally announced.
Here, I wrote the information, but it
seems that they are really arguing.
It seems that the opinions are divided.
It's a fairly strict C-san.
Such a serious person.
It's serious.
It's serious for everything.
It's wonderful.
The Ebitu and the Indian C-san are...
The mothers argued.
And finally, the results are announced.
The winner is the only one who can
decide.
We will announce the 3rd place.
Please announce the 3rd place.
3rd place.
Hoshino-san.
Congratulations to the 3rd place.
Why did you want to get a autograph?
She was really cute
She was confident
As you can see from this, she is more
than you can imagine
I was surprised
Congratulations on getting an autograph
Thank you
2nd place
Please announce the 2nd place
Kobayashi
Why is 2nd place Kobayashi?
It's funny
I'm sorry
First place
The winner is
Rina-san
Rina Matsuno
Thank you very much
What is the reason?
It's natural beauty
I see
Natural
Gracious beauty?
Yes
What does it mean?
It's natural beauty
I see, it's not showing cuteness, but
natural cuteness
The winner is Matsu!
Matsu wins!
Ebichu vs. ER vs. ONE
Haruna Tajima and Matsu wins!
Thank you for watching!
Please subscribe to our channel!
It was good!
I was surprised!
I didn't think I would be chosen
Wait a minute
I want to have the Indian astrology
Hello, who are you?
I am Jyoti
Jyoti?
Yes
What did you do?
I am a teacher of Indian astrology
A teacher of Indian astrology?
Yes
Jyoti Arkesh appeared suddenly
There is a lot of fortune telling in
India
She will have the real teacher of Indian
astrology
fortune tell her Ebitu
Ebitu plus teacher of Indian astrology
The top 3 people who were chosen in the
PR contest
Let's have them fortune tell
Yay!
First, the 3rd place
Let's go to the bottom
Koshina Mirei
What is the teacher of Indian astrology?
Please
I have a bad shoulder pain
I have a bad shoulder pain and a bad
back pain
What do you mean?
You are not a doctor
You are not a plaster surgeon
That's right
Koshina has a bad shoulder pain and back
pain
Can Jyoti solve this problem?
Before I ask the question
I will tell you my good points
Wow
Please tell me different things
First of all, I like your personality
Thank you
Many people around me help me
I'm fine
I think it's about everyone around me
In the past, I was in a busy time energy
I was tired in that situation
Now my back has changed
So I don't have a back pain
I want you to make a time to heal
yourself
I see
There is an ashram in North India
You can relax there
You can go there and heal yourself
She met her prince charming, in the past
life.
And there is a good point.
In the past life, called karma,
there was a princess.
She met her prince charming, in the past
life.
I see.
What is Hoshina plus Sensei Jutsu?
I was a princess.
In my previous life, I was a princess.
Let's continue. Kobayashi, please read
the fortune.
Kobayashi Kaho, born in the year of the
Ox.
What do you want to be fortune-telling,
Kobayashi?
What is it like to be 30 years old?
Well, I'm 30 years old.
Can you speak Japanese?
You can speak a little bit of Japanese.
Jyoti predicts Kobayashi in 16 years.
You are very successful.
Your wish will be fulfilled.
Will your desire come true?
One of the best times in your life will
come.
You will have the best chance at the age
of 30.
You will be very active.
Marriage is very important.
Will you get married?
Yes, I will be 30 years old.
Please look forward to it.
What kind of person will be your
husband?
A very rich person.
Popular person.
And loved by many people.
How about you, Kobayashi?
The future is bright.
Everyone is bright.
Kobayashi plus Sensei Jutsu is?
Wow, the future is bright.
The future was very bright.
Now, the winner, Matsuno, shall we go?
I'm nervous.
Matsuno Rina plus Sensei Jutsu is?
Matsuno, what do you want to guess?
What was it?
For now, I asked her to guess.
Now, you are a little emotional.
I'm in a little emotional period.
I'm emotional.
Did you actually grow up?
I was nervous and cried.
But at first it wasn't like that.
But before the live, I cried.
Recently?
It's been two or three years since I've
been crying.
I see.
But in the future, she has a bright
future.
I'm looking forward to a bright future.
I will live a long life.
And I will live a long life.
As there is strong protective film, do
not worry.
There is also some sort of protection
around her
And she has strong protective hair
Please don't worry
If someone tries to be annoying or mean,
the person who tries to be mean will be
damaged
It has such a strong protective paper
What kind of protective paper is it?
This is a dragon
Dragon
Dragon!
This is the best protector
This is the strongest protector
Thank you
So, Eritu plus Indians are
Dragon
Wait is protected by the dragon
How was it? What will you add next?
We add Then leaving 안에
The next shrimp Chutas is
Shrimp Chutas
Members are over the fishing rod in one
hand
Just hanging on the net
It's a pity
In addition, the incident broke out
Please stop the resistance of the chest
Please subscribe to the channel
This program was provided by the sponsor
you are watching.
I won't let you go!
Shoot!
Stop resisting!
You're not the one who's supposed to be
here!