This week's Ebichu Tastas is the final
of the Ebichu cooking competition.
I was imagining what fried rice is like.
First, what is fried rice?
A serious cooking competition that can't
be seen ahead.
To be continued.
It doesn't taste good.
Will the winner be decided?
Ebichu Tastasu, Start!
I'm so into you that I can't stop
What should I do with my heart?
Monotrium, monotrium, monotrium, middle
school students
Add various things to private Ebisu
middle school
Ebisu middle school
This program is brought to you by the
following sponsors.
This is a fried rice with frozen
vegetables.
I'm looking forward to eating this.
This is the first episode of the
showdown between EBICHU and RYORI.
Last time, HIROTA and KASHIWAGI won.
KOSHIWAGI won.
Tonight, these four will play a cooking
battle.
Let's start the second round of the
cooking battle.
The second round is fried rice.
Everyone loves it!
The two of you will win this round
Have you made fried rice before?
I made it when I was 3 years old, but it
became a tragic event
It became a tragic event?
How about you, Nakayama-san?
Do you know what it is?
I'm imagining what fried rice is like
What is fried rice?
You've never made it before, right?
Kashiwagi-san, you made fried rice
before
I've never made it
We've already figured out who is the
lucky punch
It's mainly these two
The second round is Parapara fried rice
battle
The rules are simple
Within the time limit, you can make the
best fried rice you can think of
As you can see, you can choose your
favorite ingredients from the
ingredients and make the original fried
rice
Of course, you can make any type of
fried rice
Not only the taste, but also the
appearance and the texture of the fried
rice will be judged
Ready, set, go!
The time limit is 15 minutes
15 minutes?
15 minutes!
This is a dish that can be made quickly.
Welcome.
You don't have to come to get your
homework.
I'm going to eat this.
There is also a char siu.
Don't confuse the main character.
I want you to put it in.
I did it.
What kind of action is this?
This is a char siu.
This is garlic.
The shape of the carrot is important.
It's not cut.
This is a little difficult.
Please do your best.
I do not know but a while ago I used to
have comments told me if I add
mayonnaise at rice it crumps it up
The大哥 坐
I'm going to eat it now.
And, I'm going to put the egg on top of
the kashiwagi.
I'm used to putting eggs on top of
kashiwagi.
That's good.
Do you often put eggs on top of
kashiwagi?
No, I don't.
You don't?
Is this your first time?
Yes, it is.
You're very good at it.
Thank you.
Wait a minute.
What's with the bean sprouts?
Why did you put ham on top of the char
siu?
Why?
I don't know.
You don't know?
You don't have an answer?
I'm going to put garlic and chopsticks
on top of the kashiwagi.
I don't know how to do it.
I'm going to mix garlic, butter and oil.
Which one is butter?
I don't know.
I'm going to mix it with a knife.
I dropped it.
Wait a minute.
What's the original shape like?
Please think about the original shape.
I don't think it's a member who won the
first round.
I don't care.
I'm a man.
Takei, it seems that the ingredients
have been decided.
It seems that Nakayama will start
cooking.
I'm scared when Nakayama uses fire.
Kobayashi-san is making egg rice.
I'm going to go.
Do you make this at home?
My mom used to do this at home.
What about your mom?
Do you make it like egg rice?
Yes.
It doesn't taste good.
It's different depending on the family.
Hiroto is fast.
8 minutes have passed.
It's shaking.
Hiroto is good.
I hit it all.
Look.
This is a great showdown.
It's a great showdown.
It's good.
This is what you say when you are
surprised.
I'm scared again.
What do you think?
I don't have such a skill.
Kobayashi-san is also making.
It's going well.
Everyone is finally starting to cook
rice.
I ate it once.
Is this the same as home fried rice?
It's completely different.
It's better.
This is carrot rice, isn't it?
This is Kobayashi's.
This is Nakayama's.
It looks delicious.
Kobayashi's looks delicious.
Kobayashi's is a little...
I dropped it.
Minus point.
I'm going to praise you.
Nakayama is dirty.
It doesn't taste good.
Why doesn't it taste good?
Please season it from here.
It doesn't taste good.
What do you do?
I did it.
It's beautiful.
It's done.
It's carrot rice.
It's a work of dedication.
10 seconds left.
What is Nakayama doing now?
It's done.
Thank you for watching.
Here are the original fried rice of 4
people.
Each of them has their own unique style.
This is the first time for you to make
fried rice.
It was the last time to make it in a
shape.
It was the first time for you too.
I was very good at it.
Who was good at it?
I was good at it.
It's called Parapara Carrot Rice.
Parapara Carrot Rice.
Only two people can advance to the
final.
The judgment to decide the fate begins.
As usual, we have a variety of cooking
programs.
We have a cook, Junko Takagi, and two
people who are picky about taste,
Tomitoku Chu.
First, let's try Nakayama's fried rice.
The colorful lettuce and red pickled
ginger stimulate appetite.
How would it taste?
Let's eat
It's well fried
It's great
It tastes like char siu
I should have added more flavor to the
rice
It's a little salty
You enjoy different flavors
It's good to enjoy different flavors
It's not crispy, it's crispy
It's good
Everyone, please eat
It looks good
How does it feel to be judged by the
loser?
It's a scene from a K-drama
Large screen
I feel like something is missing.
Something is missing?
It's like char siu.
Char siu has a strong presence.
Next is Kobayashi's original fried rice.
It's a new combination of Naruto and
cheddar cheese.
How will it taste?
It's good.
Please subscribe to this channel.
The taste is different for each one.
It's difficult to make it so different.
It's amazing.
It's the first time.
It's a miracle that I drank it by
chance.
It's a miracle that you drank it by
I want something.
What is it?
But, I feel it's getting closer.
Excuse me, did you say you are in 7th
place?
7th place?
You are in 7th place.
I drank it from the top.
Next, Hirota's fried rice.
She mixed mayonnaise with rice.
What is the result?
There are only shrimps.
There are almost no shrimps.
delicious
It's delicious!
It's very mild and delicious.
The way it's cooked is very good.
The way it's cooked is really good.
It's better to change it to the way it's
cooked, not the way it's cooked.
The last dish is fried rice with dried
bonito.
A lot of dried carrots.
Dried bonito-specific carrot rice.
HitoShina, which has exceeded the frame
of fried rice.
You're laughing, aren't you?
What kind of laugh is that?
How is it?
It's hard.
It's hard. What's hard?
Let's eat, everyone.
The rice is good.
The rice has a good flavor and smells
good.
It has a good flavor and smells good.
The tasting of the original fried rice
is over.
Only two people will advance to the
final round.
The result of the judging is...
The chosen members are...
I'll announce the first place.
I'll announce the top two.
Please announce the first place.
The first place is...
The winner is...
Hirota-san.
Congratulations!
This is...
I knew it!
She used the ingredients well and the
rice was a bit too soft
But it was easy to mix and mix so it was
done well
Thank you very much
Ika-do-bun!
There are two finalists, so one of the
lucky punch members will be in the
final!
Please announce the second place!
The second place is...
Kashiwagi-san.
You did it, Kashiwagi-san!
What's the reason for this?
I think the fried rice was better than
the carrot.
That's right!
Really?
Really.
If it wasn't for the carrot, I would
have won.
The carrot was the problem.
Hirota and Kashiwagi won the fried rice
battle.
Which team will win the title of the
best cook?
Let's see the final number.
But before that.
Ebichu Sakushikai no Hosomichi
This project is a project where Ebichu
tries to write a song and tries to use
it for a new song
Last time, the theme of the song was
decided by the history of the members
Friday hand picked up songs and answer
questions to various questions in the
program!
And tonight, a new episode will be
broadcast!
It's a short way to the writing club.
Last time, we decided to write down the
history of the members.
How do we do it?
This is it.
A writing notebook.
It says private ABS junior high school.
We will turn this in order.
In the form of a diary.
We will write down the history of the
members.
The members will write down the history
in the form of a diary.
First, we will decide the top batter.
It's like a private show.
Oh, Matsuno-san.
You're here.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Wait.
So, Matsuno-san.
Let's go.
Wait, why?
I'm going to sing a song of Top Batter.
That's it.
Anything is fine.
I'm not satisfied.
Because I don't have much writing
ability.
I might be worried.
I might be able to write only 2 or 3
lines.
Please forgive me.
So, the top batter is decided by
Matsuno.
Finally, the writing project starts.
The final round of the Ebichu cooking
king.
There is a miracle in Kashiwagi's
cooking.
The final round of the Ebichu cooking
king.
Hiroto vs. Kashiwagi.
A serious cooking battle.
The two will be cooking a dish using
eggs.
Let's start with Kashiwagi.
This is a simple Niratama.
Simple is best.
How about you?
I don't have one.
You don't?
Have you ever made a Niratama?
Only once.
You made it once?
Was it good?
I was worried if I could make it.
How about you, Yuta?
This is a toast sandwich with a hot-
baked egg.
It looks delicious.
What is this?
Let's see it again.
Toast Sandwich with sunny side up egg
vs.
Muratama
It's like a fighting game.
It's good.
I can make it in a novel way.
Really?
I can expect it.
The theme of the final round is
the creative dish using eggs.
Hirota and Kashiwagi
The reason for their journey so far is
the first and second round
and the high level cooking skills
of the three.
Kashiwagi won with a lucky punch
against Hirota.
But the final round is
more exciting than expected.
The final round.
Ready, start!
Please watch again.
I'm so excited!
Right away?
Yes
You used a lot of basil
Is this basil?
I used it later
And then
You put olive oil in there
Is this enough?
Yes
And then
You mix pepper
I can't do it
Wow!
I'm already excited for the opening act.
First, I'll cut the chives.
I can smell the good smell of chives.
I saw on the internet that this side is
more crispy.
This is the net.
Is it started?
Kobayashi-san made an original song.
Chives!
I think she forgot the recipe
I'll have a bit of soy sauce
It's a friendship between soy sauce and
soy sauce
Kashiyuki, do you remember the recipe?
I'm a little worried because I'm a
little bit of a liar
I'm a little worried about this one too
It smells
It's true!
If you draw this one, it's a little
Chinese style
This one is a little fashionable
Really? We are in the middle of a
country
This is true!
Wow!
It's fun!
China and Europe were so close?
It's a little different
It's better not to roll it up like this
This is a hassle
This is a method that everyone wants to
recommend to Mire-chan who is good at
cooking
Say it again
Don't roll it up like this, but put it
close to the half-cooked state
It's different from cheddar cheese
Cream cheese
It looks delicious
It's fashionable
I've never seen cream cheese
I've never seen it
It's strange
You can use it as a flipping chopsticks
I don't know
Chinese style
Chinese style came
Chinese style is a very cool pose
It's super cool
Chinese style is fashionable
You fry this separately
That's right
Did you teach this like this?
Yes
From your mother
Separate the egg and Chinese style
It's a seasoning
It's chewy
What was the competition at the women's
strength competition?
I think this is the real one
Wow
It smells really good
It's a Chinese style
It's done
Congratulations
It smells good
It's good
It looks delicious
It's fluffy
It's definitely soft
It's amazing
It looks delicious
Do you want to go there at once?
It's so warm.
I want to sleep there.
We have finished cooking.
Thank you for the meal.
The egg-based creative dish is complete!
The two dishes of different styles have
been completed!
How confident are you, the two of you?
Ms. Hiroto?
I'm very confident with my egg.
That's great!
I'm really good at making eggs.
I want you to evaluate that.
I see.
One egg!
One egg, right?
And Ms. Kashiwagi?
Yes.
What do you think of the nira tama?
I think it's perfect.
Really?
I could tell that you were confident
with your egg.
I was confident.
You were confident this time.
Yes, I was confident.
Will the two dishes shine in the cooking
of the two?
Will it be the thick-baked egg sandwich
of Ms. Hiroto?
Or will it be the nira tama of Ms.
Kashiwagi?
The evaluation begins!
First, we will try the unique egg
sandwich of Ms. Hiroto.
The thick-baked egg is seasoned with
Japanese-style soup stock.
And it is seasoned with basil and olive
oil.
It has a taste of Japanese-style soup
stock.
What is the evaluation?
Ms. Hiroto, you can eat it without being
nervous.
Thank you very much.
The egg is fluffy.
Thank you.
I'm confident in the egg.
It's very original.
And the bread is
with the sauce.
This is
the Japanese style
and it gives an accent.
It's good.
The moment I put it in my mouth, the
basil is fluffy.
It's delicious.
Where can we eat this?
We can make it.
I'll bring it.
It's the same as the one in the
restaurant.
I'll bring it.
Next, they try the
Niratama of Kashiwagi.
They put mayonnaise
with hidden flavor in the egg.
They made the secret flavor of Kashiwagi
to be the best.
How does it taste?
Please, you estand
Let's eat!
It's good.
It's natural.
Did you add something to the egg?
Mayonnaise.
It's a little strong.
This is a big success.
It's so good.
The egg is good.
Obayashi's eyes are twice as big.
It's amazing.
It's a completely different taste from
the first and second round.
That's right.
This is not a lucky punch.
I'm happy.
Both of them are highly rated.
Which one will be the winner of the
final match?
Now, the judge, Ms. Takagi, please
announce the winner.
The winner of the first round of the
Ebichu Ebi-cooking King's final match
is...
Ms. Hirota.
Congratulations!
The winner of the first round is...
It was Niro-tan!
Nira-tama was also a famous dish in a
restaurant.
But it was a bit different from the
original taste.
Matsuno-san was also struggling.
I'm still shaking.
You're still shaking?
Next time, Ebichu's first best album
will be revealed!
I want you to compare the current Ebichu
and the old Ebichu.
You're right.
No, it's totally different!
And now, a special guest has come to
announce the best album!
The guest is...
Who is this?
Is this Hoshina?
You're so bad at laughing.
It's been a long time.
I'm sorry.