I first started playing games when I was
4 years old.
I'm really into Apex now.
I love FPS games.
I try to avoid games that make me think
I'm a girl.
I try to make myself a male player.
Hello, everyone.
I'm SAKURA, the member of BATTEEN.
Nice to meet you.
I'm nervous.
I've never filmed a video of me showing
you my work.
I'll do my best.
I haven't heard what I'm going to do
today.
I'm wondering what I'm going to do.
I'm sitting here.
I'll look for a hint.
This is suspicious.
This is definitely suspicious.
Is this this?
SAKURA, you are in an invisible game.
Did I do that?
I didn't do that.
To improve your ability to speak and
your ability to talk, I will not reveal
what game you are playing.
Please play the game without showing the
game screen.
I'm going to play the game now.
I haven't played the game recently, so
I'm looking forward to playing it.
And the game I'm going to play this time
is a game I've never played.
I've played a lot of Nintendo games, but
I avoided playing this game because I
thought it might be dangerous if I got
addicted to it.
I'm going to play it this time.
I will start with the character.
What should I do?
I like girls and boys.
The color of the eyes is purple.
The hairstyle is cute.
I've seen the game's live broadcast.
I saw a cute hairstyle on VTUBER.
I will play this game.
I was asked to play a cute hairstyle
today.
I often play the game with straight
hair.
I will play this game.
I will also play this game with
eyebrows.
Finally, I will play this game.
I will play this game with short pants.
I was able to play this game.
Look at this!
Wow!
I got a weapon.
I have a weapon that I want to use.
I have a big roller.
I think it would be interesting to play
a long-range weapon.
Please book your hand!
No, I can't move this screen.
Good luck!
I'm embarrassed. I look like a clumsy
person.
Thank you for watching.
I have seen this park.
Octopuses are flying.
I wonder what the old man will do with
me.
I get a salmon roe.
Good luck!
I'm not used to this game yet.
I can't get a salmon roe unless I
control it.
I wonder if I can get it today.
But I don't think I'm defending myself.
I'm not sure if I can get it.
This is a local salmon roe.
This is cute.
This salmon roe is eating my face.
I throw this.
This salmon roe is running.
I got it.
This is difficult.
I got it!
I got the engine number.
I think I'm getting used to it.
I'm getting used to it.
I want to play a online match.
I'm sure I'll be able to cause trouble.
I'll do my best.
I'll do my best with a low-ranking team.
I'll do my best not to lose.
I changed the setting, so I'll play
online.
Can I really do it?
The game is starting.
This game is very fast.
This is a very strong opponent.
I'm sorry.
I'll put this on.
This is very difficult.
I have to turn my back.
I died.
This is difficult.
I'm losing.
I will advance.
I will take the back.
I have only one minute left.
I don't have to kill anyone.
I lost.
I'm scared.
I'm frustrated.
I lost overwhelmingly.
This is not good.
I'm sorry.
I change my weapon.
I change to a wakabashuta.
I lost.
I will do my best.
Is there a way to aim at the target?
I was right.
I will do my best.
I can't say that I'm playing a game with
this.
I will do my best.
I'm doing my best.
I feel that the number of people who die
is decreasing.
I will do my best.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I was talking about my tongue.
This is not good.
This is a big explosion.
I'm not good at this.
I want to kill one person.
This is not good.
This is the end.
I can't get 1kg.
I won because my friend was strong.
He was very kind.
I thought he was dangerous.
He came to help me.
It seems that there are many kind people
in this game.
I can do it.
I was close.
I was blocked by a umbrella.
I think I can move faster if I try this.
This is good.
I did it! I did it!
I defeated it! I defeated it!
I'm going to die.
This is bad.
This is too strong.
Look at the back.
This is bad.
No, the board is not good.
I was defeated.
This is strong.
This is a big problem.
This is the only coat that can fight.
I won because I was able to win one.
I'm going to play a game now.
Do you know what game I played?
I hope you understand.
Finally, I will give you a hint.
I will give you a gesture for those who
do not understand.
I will do the movement of the character
I just played.
I have this kind of hair.
I can't get this hair out of my head.
I will do this.
I will get the kill.
I played a game for the first time
today.
I was able to defeat one enemy.
I am very satisfied today.
This is my personal impression.
I am very satisfied.
I think I was able to win.
If you understand this game, please
leave a comment.
I will tell you the answer.
Please leave a lot of comments.
I will end this video here.
Bye bye.
Please subscribe to my channel.
It's time to make sweets.
I don't make sweets because I want to
eat it.
I will clean the sweet potatoes.
I'm scared.
I can't open it at all.
I think I'm going to run out of
electricity.
I'm always told that I use a saw when I
use a kitchen knife.
I've never used this before.
I will start.
I will add vanilla extract.
I added too much.
I don't know because I've never made it,
but it's important to mix it.
It's done.