It was pitch-dark, but no one noticed.
I wanted to change myself in this song.
Oh!
I thought I might not have to quit.
Welcome to Kabul!
Welcome!
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it too.
Thank you.
I have a lot to ask you.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you.
floor swells
that now
firefight me
off
The
Thank you for watching!
Come on, tell me what you want
Let's stop talking about the difficult
things
For now, let's go up and avoid it
I'm repeating what I always say to
everyone
Come on, tell me what you want
From perfect drama to perfect life
No one knows what's happening during the
break
Who'll be ahead and sit down on the set
If it's past midnight Who'll be there
right away
synth-ikel in Tokyo
If everyone is looking for their dreams
It was as famous as I've heard
Is it called Bunki-ten?
It's a song that brings back memories of
me.
I was always trying to be someone else.
I was looking at the ceiling,
looking at the computer screen,
and recording.
But I was working during the day.
The ease of doing that
and the memories of those days come
back.
That's...
I think it's very important.
I can always remember my first
impression.
But at the same time, this song became a
song that represents myself.
I feel like I have to make a song that
represents me other than this song.
It's a bit of a curse.
There are things like that.
But if it wasn't for this song, I would
have been more concerned.
It was a song that I spent my life on,
and I think it was a good song to keep
on being a hit and to be able to
overcome it as a task.
It's a song that has a lot of meaning.
I think I'll be able to sing it forever.
Before releasing this song, you didn't
cover someone's song and
release it on YouTube, right?
Yes, that's right.
I wanted to make a song that was
original and release it.
When I was uploading the cover,
I was suddenly called by a person in
charge of Sony, Fujiwara-san.
At first, I thought it was a scam.
But it was not that famous.
I thought that I would be caught or
fooled by someone who likes me so much.
So I went to see him.
He said he liked my singing voice and
wanted to sing with me.
From there, I set a goal.
I will continue to cover the song.
My first goal is to reach 100,000
subscribers on YouTube.
I will do my best.
I was trying to do it while I was trying
to get into it, but it was quite
difficult.
There are a lot of talented people who
are looking for internet.
So I talked to them about how to make
them know more people than now.
I asked them to write an original song
and release it.
That's how I started making Haru o
Tsugeru.
How did you meet Mr. Kujira?
Mr. Kujira contacted me first.
Oh, really?
Yes. He asked me to participate in the
song called Sleepy City.
He contacted me to participate in the
song as a featuring vocalist.
We had a connection from there.
So we asked him to write the original
song.
So you were already featured as a
vocalist for KUJIRA.
Yes, but we didn't actually meet.
We just met through text.
You didn't meet at all?
No.
We just looked at each other's abilities
and made a compact song.
We had a modern conversation.
I think that kind of relationship will
last for a long time.
We respect each other.
That's right.
I met Mr. Kujira after I graduated from
high school.
But I think we have the same feeling of
respect for each other.
Thank you for watching.
KUJIRA, you wrote the original song for
the first time.
Did you get any requests from Yamada?
That's also a special thing.
When I was asked to sing Nemuro-machi,
I thought he was trying to show his own
side as a vocalist.
I thought he understood me.
So when I asked for the original,
I thought I wanted to leave it to him.
So I didn't even say BPM.
You didn't say BPM?
The speed of the song?
No.
I didn't say anything about sadness.
I left it all to him.
Do you remember the first impression you
had of the song?
I do.
I was still working at the time,
so I didn't think I could eat with
music.
I didn't even think of being a musician.
I like music, but...
I was just looking at the ceiling.
I was wondering why I was still alive.
I was really worried about that.
When I listened to the demo,
I felt like I was too attached to my
environment.
The song itself is something that links
to it.
When I listened to it,
my heart was pounding.
This is...
I remember feeling that there was a
great song.
I feel like I've heard it before.
I was excited. I thought there was a
great song.
I was already a vocalist.
But I think that
I was more likely to sing
when I sing.
I was more likely to be pulled by other
people's voices.
That's right.
I was a vocalist, but I was also a human
being.
I didn't have any emotions in me.
But I could see the image of the song
when I sang it.
I thought it was a song that needed a
lot of technique to get there.
You've covered a lot of songs so far.
It's even more difficult to learn the
skills.
I agree.
I wasn't sure if I could sing this song.
I thought I couldn't do it if I wasn't
confident enough.
This song is a difficult song.
Do you usually listen to someone's song,
copy it, and record it?
Do you spend a lot of time to do this?
I spend a lot of time.
I like recording the most,
so I spend a lot of time.
It's fun.
It's fun. It's really fun.
When I was doing covers,
I was doing the mix myself.
I was kind of taboo in my mind
to do the pitch correction at that time.
I just didn't do it because I couldn't
do it well.
I just did it until I could do it.
It took a long time to keep singing.
I started recording at 11 a.m.
I was taking a break, but I was
recording at 11 a.m. or past the
deadline.
Wow, 12 hours later.
I was so focused on recording.
I hate the fact that I can't recreate
the expression I had when I sang live.
I thought that if I could do it with a
machine, it wouldn't be my own song.
I spent a lot of time practicing and
recording.
Especially for Haru Tsugeru, I was
repeating it over and over.
Including the part where I said I was
going to stop singing in the middle, I
think I know about 2,000 takes.
Isn't 2,000 takes amazing?
I was told that it was a little.
Are there no 2,000 takes now compared to
that time?
It's gone. It's gone.
It's just really...
I think it was difficult for me at the
time.
It was so difficult that I had to
practice 2,000 times.
There was also the first original song.
I wanted to change myself with this
song.
I thought that something might really
change.
It also filled me with expectations of
the final しかしの期待を込めていたので
that it recalled me of the expectations
I held towards him and hope itrap this
show.
月月二の空間やく きくらくも sofas imagination
So you're saying that you're self-
producing the vocals?
Yes, basically.
That's amazing.
That's how I am.
That's my style.
I don't get much reaction from people.
So you're not learning from others about
singing,
but you're learning it yourself?
Yes, I am. I'm learning vocal technique.
I think everything about vocal technique
is like that.
Basically, when it comes to technical
things,
I don't have anyone who taught me or
gave me a reference.
Rather,
I think I'm not that talented.
For me, I think that's a simple,過度性.
I've been singing for a long time.
So, I'm wondering how I can be
recognized as Yama.
I'm thinking that this is something that
can only be changed by this person.
I'm continuing to sing while pretending.
So, I'm thinking that...
When I'm trying to do something, I tend
to think too much.
I'm doing it in a very mental state.
But I feel like I'm living my singing.
I don't want to be like someone else.
I'm a very ordinary person.
I'm always worried about whether I can
catch up with everyone.
I'm very happy when Haratsuger was a
hit.
I'm still not good enough to be
recognized by so many people, but I'm
still worried about what to do.
I feel like I'm being evaluated more
than I actually am.
You can try recording over and over
again.
I was a little behind in that, but I was
still active.
If you think about it closely, it's
probably true, but I'm sure you don't
dig that deep.
The difference in skills is obvious when
you're born.
I think there's always a difference.
Some people say that if you work hard,
you'll be rewarded.
Some people say that there are no
geniuses.
I don't think so.
I think there are people who show great
talent with little effort.
To catch up with such people, there is a
difference in skill level.
If you don't work harder than that
person, you'll be rewarded.
I don't even line up, and I don't even
vote for the same person.
I think we have that indication.
I was raised in a family of four.
I have a word in my heart.
It's a word I was given to a close
friend.
There are many talented singers in the
world.
You are not special.
I have been told that there are many
people more attractive than you.
I thought so.
I was actually over-confident.
I thought I was special.
I was surprised.
I started to see reality.
But I couldn't stop singing.
I wanted to stand out.
That's why I'm still here.
I think it's because I'm here.
I don't think I'll get angry.
Why did you say that?
I think it's probably kindness.
I don't think I want to hurt anyone.
To be honest, it's not easy to make a
living with just music.
It's very tough and I feel very sad.
I think I said it with kindness.
If I were to put words into myself at
that time,
I would probably say the same thing.
I think that if I hadn't said that, I
wouldn't have been able to improve my
singing.
I don't think I would have been able to
stand here.
I think that was kind.
It's a very important word.
I can't forget it even now.
So...
That's right.
Somewhere...
I was told that I was a singer, but I
couldn't give up.
I was trying to figure out what I could
do to be like myself.
I was working as a singer.
It was pitch-dark, but no one could find
me.
I was singing a song.
I knew that it was going to be like
that.
And then, a cover song by a vocalist
named NIL KAJITSU,
called Ozward, was released.
I thought I should stop singing after
covering that song.
So I released a cover song.
About a week after the release,
I hit theçown..
I got a DM.
Oh, really?
I thought...
Maybe I shouldn't stop.
That's what I thought.
I remember it very well.
That's the timing.
That's right.
I remember it very well.
I'm glad you took on that challenge.
Yes, I was glad to be found.
I'm a very ordinary person,
but I was able to move my heart
thanks to the support of one person.
That was the first time I had a chance
to do that.
I'm glad I continued to do music.
While we were together for a while,
Haruo Tsujiro hit the charts.
And now I'm standing here.
I always thought it was not natural, but
I'm happy now.
Of course, there are many difficult
things,
but I'm glad I'm still doing music.
I'm so happy.
That's why I chose Haru-Tsugeru.
Alright.