I want to make music for everyone.
I couldn't write until I was
irresponsible.
It's easy to like yourself, but it's
very difficult.
I want to make a chorus.
Welcome to Fukabori!
Nice to meet you. I'm looking forward to
it.
You two are really wonderful. I'm
nervous.
It's our first time meeting, so please
let us hear a lot of stories.
Thank you.
Please have a seat.
Everyone is 20, even 20, even 20
I love you too
Always 20, even 20
The usual characters everywhere
I see them, in these days of miracles
Translated by Releska
Take a final cycle
I want to be someone else
You're regretting it again
No no no no no no
Make up doesn't work
Out of grip
The tears won't flow
Shining
Money
Hard
Everything
Like it spilled
Thank you for watching!
20 years, 20 years, 20 years
I've been loving you
There were many turning points for the
band
But the characters are looking forward
to the future
They're actively approaching what they
want to do
That's why it's a very important song
First, there was the story of making an
album
I want to make one song for everyone
There was a story that I wanted to make
one song for everyone in the future
When I started the band, I was quite
active in making it all together
From there, I stopped
I had a long period of time to write
songs for each person
After that, there is a song called Mera
It was a song that I made after a long
time
parallel together
I think it was fun to make it, and I
think it was a good grasp, so I made it
again to try it.
I talked about what kind of song I would
make that song.
I want to make it a little more mature,
like a dance-able song.
I want to make a song that is fun but
persuasive.
I decided from the beginning.
I think that's it!
My Peppe and Anami made the song.
We went into the studio together and had
a session together.
We made it.
The song came up, but we had to redo the
melody many times.
It took a long time.
That's right.
After listening to it, I thought about
the lyrics.
At first, I tried to write it on a
completely different theme.
I want to know that too.
I'm sorry.
That's good.
Like travel ices?
I thought it would be better to have a
theme that's easy to understand.
We discussed about what kind of theme we
should make.
I wrote a plot on top of that.
It didn't work out well.
If we're going to make an actor album,
we should make it a song that helps the
actor a little more.
It's a song that helps the actor
understand more.
I thought that if I made a song, people
would be satisfied.
So I rewrote the plot.
Nagaya, Kobayashi, Anami, and Peppe are
the lyrics.
Did you make this song naturally?
This is the song Mera, which we made
together last time.
The composition is the same as the
composition.
We happened to have two songs written by
Anami and Peppe.
There's a melody.
We thought we could write the lyrics for
this song.
But it's a good idea to have everyone's
names credited.
There's a special pattern in the melody,
so we decided to try it out.
We wanted to go beyond the previous
song, so we decided to try it out.
I used to write lyrics that I wanted to
share with others,
but this time, I wanted to go ahead and
do it.
I wanted to be able to keep up with the
flow.
I wanted to be able to communicate with
others.
I wanted to make a song someday.
I thought it was about time for me to
experience it.
That's why I challenged myself.
It's going to change.
It's the same with age.
This year is the 10th anniversary.
I can say this now.
Even if I say the same thing without
experience,
I can't convey it well.
I can't convey it wrongly.
I'm saying this, but I'm not very
confident in the book.
I'm not confident at all.
I can't believe it.
It looks like you're confident. You're
good at singing and writing good songs.
I'm not sure why I'm not confident.
I often compare myself to other people.
This character is also a song that has
that theme.
I think there are a lot of people who
want that kind of thing because they are
like that.
I think it's a song that doesn't have to
be compared.
I have my own worries, but I want to say
that in a position where I can help.
That's why I wrote it.
When you write it, do you show it with
the lyrics of the entire song?
At first, it's a short film.
At first, Nagaya wrote the one chorus.
Oh, that's where it started.
I can't spread it out by myself.
Help me.
《The Note of Loneliness》
I was the one who wrote the plot, and
Nagaya was the one who wrote the lyrics.
But Nagaya didn't seem to finish in
time, so I decided to try writing it.
We both wrote the full song once.
The phrase that Nagaya originally wrote
for the chorus was the same, of course,
but
I thought about whether to use that and
add other things.
It was a tough decision.
I had to sing right before the
performance.
How long did you have to sing right
before the performance?
I had to sing right before the
performance.
On the day?
Yes, on the day.
I was like, can I sing here?
I had to sing in this way.
You had to sing in this way?
The lyrics that Mr. Kobayashi wrote were
like this.
Is there a time when you want to make it
easier to sing?
I think it's more about the message.
The content is important.
I think about the ease of singing a lot
when I write lyrics.
I've never been told that much.
I think that if you use this message,
you might be taken wrong.
So I want to rewrite it.
It might be interesting to see how you
write it.
I'm doing it.
I've been listening to it for a long
time.
I want to sing it.
I want to use words that I don't usually
sing.
My son, Anamiya, does that.
He makes food.
That's a challenge.
But it's fun.
I think it's better to have a sense of
discomfort.
Yes.
Somewhere.
It's like, what?
Even if you're listening,
I think it's better to have a moment
like, what did you say?
It's not for men or women,
but I think there are many lyrics that
don't feel gender at all.
songs that we can come up with together,
I guess that's what uneven in using
these styles.
song that we've come up with
individually are
about station looks in JAPAN,
meaning the
girl on this team,
we're nothing new.
Then again,
Thank you for watching!
It's very meaningful that we released
this song as a band.
For example, the composition of this
song is very difficult.
The chorus is catchy and easy to
remember.
The first and second parts are like,
I've never heard this melody before.
The majority of the time we spend on
this are directly related to the music
we want to do.
We talk about doing musicals for live
performances.
For example, dancers.
Or maybe we can add lines.
We want to do a lot of fun things.
We don't have a fixed plan.
We wanted to make a song that would go
well with the song we were going to play
when we were on our trip.
There's a lot of music challenges.
You like musicals, don't you?
We don't have a band's world view.
We have a lot of freedom and freedom to
express ourselves.
That's what's so exciting about us.
We've been saying this since we started
the band.
We think that's what we're good at.
And we can sing.
We're all very active in the chorus.
We want to add more of that.
We dance a little bit during the live
performance.
We're all very light steps.
We play around a little bit.
My guitarist, Issei, and my bassist,
Anami,
have been dancing since they were
little.
Oh, really?
My parents are friends from middle
school.
My mother runs a jazz dance class.
Oh, really?
And my mother is a teacher at a ballet
class.
We go to each other's studios to play
together.
You're always dancing?
I can't dance better than playing
instruments.
Really? Can I dance now?
It's not something you can show right
away.
There's something like this, so I want
to show the charm of those two in the
future.
I want to make a song like that.
It was a completely different
arrangement for the first take. It was
wonderful.
Thank you.
Thank you for watching.
I'm always 20, always 20, always 20
I love you so much
I'm always 20, always 20
It's a miracle day
where all the fun and the fun is shown
This is the first time we've done this
I'm always 20, always 20
Me, Peppe, and Anami from Bass.
That's a small shop.
I'm doing it outside of him.
I think the first take is a challenge
for us.
Are you nervous?
I am.
I always say I'm nervous, so I'll try
not to say it.
I tried not to say it this time.
If you say it yourself, you'll be
caught.
It was fun.
The tension is good.
It was good.
It's like Anami's bass is failing.
It's cute to have a failed face.
But it doesn't look like a failure.
I thought it was cute.
I like that kind of real thing.
Did you come to the scene?
I think it's good.
The chorus is also in the original song.
I want to sing the chorus.
I was really worried before I released
it.
I wanted to make it a song that we can
all support,
as if we were pulling our hands towards
the same direction.
I said this a lot in my last album,
but I said I didn't want to use such
words irresponsibly.
I can understand that.
Thank you for watching.
I think that sometimes we are taken in
the wrong direction or taken in a very
beautiful way.
So I was really worried that it would
reach as a message that we thought, but
after releasing it, I thought that there
were so many people who were lost in the
same way.
I was able to save them and I thought I
would do my best.
I was really happy to write and make the
song.
It's great to feel the real sound.
You don't know until you release the
song.
It's like sharing with the staff and the
members.
How do you convey what you think is
good?
It takes a lot of time to make a song.
It took a long time to make a song.
I was worried, but I'm glad.
Speaking of responsibility,
even after the release, Nagoya and I
have a slightly different
interpretation.
I couldn't write it without being
irresponsible to some extent.
Of course, I have some responsibility,
but I thought that all the reactions
that would happen after releasing this
song would be irresponsible.
I'm sure some people will feel bad about
it.
I'm not saying that I was actually told
that opinion,
but there are some parts that I can't
write unless I'm irresponsible.
Because I'm not doing it myself.
I'm writing the words with such a big
feeling,
and I'm writing the part that I want to
be myself.
I think everyone is suffering from
things that they can't keep up with.
I think that is the opposite of what you
said, that you are irresponsible, but
you are sincere.
It is a pleasure to see how things
change when you reach out to each other.
What kind of song do you think you will
be able to become?
I hope that this song will give you
hope.
It's not just a fun song.
Of course, I want you to feel that it's
a cheerful song,
but I want you to feel that it's a song
that will reach you as a message.
You're someone who will be with you
forever.
It's easy to like yourself, but it's
also difficult to like yourself.
But, I hope that this difficult theme
will be a good hint to us
to live a long life.
I hope it will be a good hint to us.
I hope it will be a good support song.
I love it. I love it. I can only say
that.
I wanted to be in a band with a
childhood friend.
I think it's fate.
I think we will always want to be a
national enemy.