At that time...
I thought, I'm not bad either.
That's when you realized you weren't bad
either.
I remembered.
You're still streaming?
I think the audience is better.
The audience is better.
I want to reach the audience.
You want to reach the audience.
That's the motto for today.
I want to share.
You want to share Fujita Aire?
Yes.
Let's all share.
Yakan and Idol!
One day, Yakan, who was sleeping in the
living room of the company,
showed up.
His name is Yakan.
Yakan, who is interested in idols,
asked the people of Stardust to talk to
the idols
because he would put delicious tea in
it.
The people of Stardust who are kind and
like tea are okay at once.
So, Yakan, who was born in the living
room of the company,
was born with a program to talk to cute
idols.
I'm Yakan, the cute idol born and raised
in the
Star Dust.
This program is a talk variety that
will bring out the amazing sides of
idols
who belong to the Star Dust Planet to
the guests.
Yakan will do his best to bring out the
talk that will
rise up.
Let's invite today's guest.
From Crown Pop, Fujita Airi.
Thank you very much.
Hello everyone.
I'm the queen of the entertainment
world,
Ai-chan, from We Are Crown Pop,
Fujita Airi.
Nice to meet you.
The first passionate
from the writer of this program is
Fujita.
Thank you very much.
I'm nervous.
Are you nervous?
I'm nervous before the live performance.
My mouth is like a bubble.
You've never talked to Yakan before.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Yakan and idols.
How was the summer of Crown Pop this
year?
Crown Pop was the biggest
live performance in the world.
The members were all aiming for it.
We gathered together and did a live
performance.
The stage was amazing.
It was amazing.
We don't have a member color.
The color of the group is blue.
The fans always wear blue pen lights.
The pen light color is 15 colors.
We change the color according to the
song.
We have a lot of color illuminations.
It's fun.
That's right.
The blue color is beautiful.
It was the biggest live performance.
And the Tokyo Idol Festival.
Yes.
Did you get out?
I got out.
It's a lot of light.
What does it mean?
It's a love story.
No, it's not.
It's not a love story.
It's a love story.
You're good.
Please stop.
I'm sorry.
You brought all the food.
You prepared it yourself.
I always bring food.
This is the place where the king eats at
the festival.