Riko's Room Part 5 Riko's Room is back! This time our guest is Ayaka Yasumoto. They often hang out in private, so please look forward to their talk!
Have a good day, everyone!
This time, we will be back with a special guest, Ayaka Yasumoto, who is a frequent guest in her private life.
By popular demand
This is Ayaka Yasumoto, our guest!
Please introduce yourself!
Ayaka Yasumoto, Ebisu Junior High School
Finally, you're here!
Thank you very much!
I'm the last one among all the sister-members!
You are the last one!
That's right.
Thank you so much.
I wanted to be there too.
Really? !
I look forward to working with you today!
This time, "Riko's Room".
A little bit, a little bit...
The font looks like it could be haunted.
It's carrying a scary feeling, but...
I'm carrying it!
I'm carrying it on my back!
As usual, it's peaceful.
Let's have a free talk.
The first question is...
Can I ask you how you spend your off-days?
It's a pretty standard question, isn't it?
Oh, yes~!
I understand.
I think I'm going to start talking at this rate.
I'm fine with normal.
Normal!
I'll be normal.
I'll do it.
On my days off...
Lately...
I've been watching "ONE PIECE".
The anime version of "One Piece".
I've been watching it.
I'm addicted to it.
There are dozens of series.
I can't easily catch up with the latest episodes.
I couldn't catch up with the latest episodes easily.
I'm just trying to keep up.
I watch it every day.
He's been recommending it to me.
"I'm in!" I'll recommend it to Riko as soon as I feel like it.
I'll recommend anything.
She recommended "Tokyo Revengers" to me.
I watched "Tokyo Revengers".
I was hooked on it a while ago!
I was like, "This line is so good!" "I love this line!
I love this line!"?
Robin said...
I want to live !!!!" I want to live!
If you don't know what she's saying...
"What are you yelling about?" If you don't know what she's yelling, it's like...
I want to go somewhere! What are you yelling?" It's like...
I want to live !!!!" And then there's a scene where she says, "I want to live.
Robin, who was being stubborn...
But the scene where Robin, who was being stubborn
I really liked the scene where Robin, who had been so strong
It was really good!
Do you understand? Everyone watching!
"I want to live! !!!!" That's right.
I want to be alive.
You often play with me.
Is there anything you want to do with me?
Like, "I want to go!" Something like that.
Wait a minute... there are so many things.
I sent you something the other day.
The adzuki-bean toast from Atami.
Remember it?
It's amazing!
Listen to this.
It's on Instagram or something.
And TikTok.
It's all over the place, right?
They're all looking at the same thing.
I said, "Isn't this place nice?" And I say.
And they're like, "I was just looking at this..."
I'm just looking at it.
There are a lot of things that come up as recommendations.
Right now, it's adzuki-bean toast. -It's in Atami.
It's in Atami.
Is it a restaurant where you can eat and walk around?
It's already like this.
A lot of azuki beans and butter
toast topped with azuki beans and butter.
toast with azuki beans and butter on top.
I want to eat that so bad!
I want to go there.
I want to go...
I want to go.
What kind of hot spring?
Is it a hot spring?
Like an inn.
It just came to me.
I was like, "I liked it, too!" Something like that.
That kind of place.
I want to clear all the places where I said, "Let's go here."
I'd like to clear all the places where I said, "Let's go here.
That's a lot.
You've got about five of them.
Yeah, I'd like to go.
I hope we can go this year.
Let's go.
Hot springs.
I want to go to a hot spring.
Open-air baths.
It's the best time of year.
I'd like to go.
I'd like to go to a private one.
Soak in an open-air bath like this.
We can talk about the future.
I'd love to!
It won't take long.
"Ah! I'm out of shape!" "I did it!
Repeat that a few times.
In and out.
That's great!
I want to do it!
Take it easy!
You know, when I was growing up...
I've come to enjoy playing with them.
I've come to think of it as fun.
Until a while ago, I was like...
I wanted to go ping-pong.
You said you wanted to play ping-pong.
Until about two years ago, right?
He likes to be active.
He was saying that.
But lately...
Food, scenery...
You know, the kind of fun where you pay for the experience.
Oh, that's been going on for a while?
It's nothing!
I'm the one who came as a guest.
I've heard this from everyone.
Yasumoto-san.
What's your motto?
My motto?
Well, I don't know.
I think it's very difficult to choose a motto.
It's your favorite word, isn't it?
I don't know any beautiful and difficult words.
I love the phrase "I'll be fine.
There are two patterns, aren't there?
The "I'm fine" that you say to yourself.
The "I'm fine" that other people say to you
The "I'm fine" that I say to myself
There are a lot of them.
I don't know...
I'll be fine" to say (to myself)
If you change the endings
There are many ways to say it
Anyway
I like "It's okay" that I say to myself
I also like "it's okay" when someone says it to me.
I like it when people say "it's okay" to me, and when people say "it's okay" to me.
used to say to me when I was little
She used to tell me, "It's okay.
whenever something happened to me.
I was impressed by the way she always told me
It made a big impression on me.
So, even if it's just for a few days
Whenever I feel anxious
I try to tell myself "It's okay.
Not only with the word "okay" but also with
When I say "It's okay" to myself.
I don't feel like I'm alone.
It's like we're working it out together.
Not just "it's okay."
Maybe it's, "It's okay."
Well, from now on.
I'm going to make that phrase my motto.
I'm often deprived of them.
Even with Mirei...
I forgot...
But she said something difficult.
She said something difficult about Mirei.
Like a piece of something.
What was it?
Love and Peace?
Does anyone remember? one
What is it?
It's not LOVE&PEACE.
Oh, there was something about it.
It's cool. It's a really nice word.
So from now on I'm going to say
"It's okay."
I'm going to make it my motto.
Please do!
To everyone who is watching
Is there anything you would like to recommend
I would like to recommend something to everyone who watches this page.
What would you like to recommend?
I don't know...
Recommendation
Is it "One Piece"?
That's what I'm into right now, lol.
I'm really into it.
I'm really into it, so I guess "ONE PIECE".
But that's it.
Everyone in the world knows about it.
I think it's a place that everyone knows and everyone has already gone through.
Even if I don't recommend it
I'm sure everyone already likes it.
Even if I don't recommend it.
Do you have any suggestions?
I don't know... one I'd like to recommend.
I recommended it to Maeko just the other day.
Do you want to recommend a highlight?
Is it okay if I give it away as a thing?
I have one right now.
Thank you very much!
I'll have my own talk.
I got a recommendation from Ayaka the day before yesterday.
Ayaka recommended it to me the day before yesterday.
I also clicked on it yesterday!
Bochi!
What's this?
I got it from Mayama, too.
Mayama recommended this to me.
Here it is!
This highlight
I honestly don't know how to read it
How do you read it?
C!
A!
T!
C-A-T-K-I-N!
Is this some kind of Chinese cosmetics?
Chinese cosmetics.
It's a highlighter like this.
I'm wearing it on my face right now.
It looks so natural.
It gives my skin a feminine glow.
It adds a little bit of color to my skin
I thought it made me look beautiful.
I bought it just like Mayama did.
I recommend it to everyone!
I bought it too, copying Mayama!
I bought it!
It's popular amongst the shrimp!
It's popular in Ebichu!
Let's all share the good things!
Let's do it!
What are you happiest when you're doing?
That's a very deep question, isn't it?
What is the moment when you feel happy?
What kind of moments?
I'm sure it's the same for you.
When I'm on stage.
I feel very happy.
I feel like I am the best I can be.
In a sense
In a sense, without thinking about anything.
I think the moment when I can just enjoy myself
I think it's on the stage.
That is the happiest time for me.
What is live performance like for you?
Happiness.
Isn't that what you mean?
Happiness!
(Live performance equals a happy place.
I think.
Riko, what makes you happy?
Me too, at a live concert.
I guess so, don't you?
Of course, live performances.
Of course!
Everyone says "live".
If you ask the members of Ebichu...
I think they'd all say "live".
Let's skip the live show, shall we?
Without Ligo!
I guess so.
What makes you happy?
When I'm meeting someone?
I know!
After the Corona disaster.
I felt it especially.
I think it's important to connect with people.
I think it's really important.
It's fun, isn't it?
After the Corona disaster, I feel like I've changed.
I think so!
You've changed so much!
Fans know that...
You don't really care about people.
You used to be a person who didn't care about anything.
But now you're so much more interested in the people around you
And you've started to approach people on your own.
And your energy has also improved a lot.
I'm more active now.
I really love being alone.
I was alone, alone, alone.
That's right.
I've really changed!
It's almost like I'm lonely without someone else.
I feel lonely without someone else.
I was thinking that there are some positive things
There are some positive things that can happen.
Speaking of Ayaka Yasumoto
the type who talks about things
That's right.
Even when we meet alone
I talk forever and she listens to me.
We have time, don't we?
Let's talk!
What's the theme?
The theme is.
"What kind of adult woman do you want to become?
I guess.
I am...
In my mind.
I want to be at my peak and shine in my 30s.
When I talk to adult women
I hear things like, "I used to shine when I was in my 20s.
"I was so happy when I was in my twenties."
They talk about their past.
That's why many of them say, "I'm looking forward to my 20s.
"I'm looking forward to my 20s.
I don't know, I just...
through the stories of such people's experiences.
I think that when I'm in my 30s or something
I'm going to tell young people, "I'm having so much fun right now.
I can say to them, "I'm having a lot of fun right now. "I'm having so much fun right now.
"I'm having so much fun right now.
I think it would be wonderful.
I think it would be wonderful if I could say to the young people.
I'll be able to help them imagine a brighter future.
I can help young people imagine a brighter future.
That's the kind of person I want to be.
Of course, I'm having a great time right now.
And I'm shining right now.
But if I can keep on updating it, and keep on updating it...
I'll be the best!
That's why my current goal is
"I'm going to peak at 30."
"to peak at 30.
And when I turn 30.
I want to peak at 40.
I want to think
I want to be a woman who is always pretty
I want to be a sparkling woman.
The theme is "sparkle," right?
This year's theme is "Kira Kira".
Kira Kira.
What do you think?
I wonder...
Maybe it's similar.
I still can't picture myself until I'm 30, but...
than when I was a teenager.
I'm in my twenties.
I'm only 21.
I'm in my first year of my twenties.
It's fun
So much so that I barely remember my teenage years.
So
To be honest, I don't really think about the future
I don't think about it until about 3 years from now.
And after that, you haven't really thought about it at all yet.
So...
I just want to enjoy the moment.
We'll be together.
But you know what, I can't even think about the future.
I can't even think about the future.
It's a good thing, right?
Isn't this moment fun?
It's fun.
It's fun, isn't it?
It's fun, it's fun!
Because we're the two people who think it's fun.
We're the kind of people that say, "Let's do this" and "Let's do that."
I wonder if we're on the same page in terms of what we want to do.
While soaking in the hot springs.
I think they talk about this kind of stuff all the time.
They do.
That's true.
"What will you do when you're a grandmother?" Or something like that.
They seem to talk about it.
Thank you for coming to Riko's Room today.
Thank you very much!
Can we decide together
Can we decide together?
Sure.
As far as I'm concerned.
Riko seems to love her the most.
I think Nonoka is the one you love the most.
I hope you will talk with your junior
I hope you will have a talk with your junior who you love so much!
Next time, let's have Nonoka come!
Take care~!
It's not like "Have a good day!" or something.
Oh, it's "Gozaimasuyou".
Have a good day!