Ebichu's video
Hello everyone, how are you?
We have a lot of requests for RIKO's
room.
We have a guest who has come to our
test.
Please introduce yourself.
I'm Yasumoto Ayaka, the number 5.
Thank you for coming.
You finally came.
Thank you.
You are the last member of the NAYSAN
group.
Thank you.
I wanted to come out, too.
Thank you for coming today.
This time, RIKO's room is a bit like a
curse.
I'm carrying a scary feeling.
I'm carrying it.
As usual, we will have a free talk in a
peaceful way.
The first question is,
How do you spend your day off?
It's a normal question.
I understand.
I'm going to talk about this.
I'm normal.
I'm going to talk normally.
I've been watching ONE PIECE recently.
I've been watching the anime.
I'm addicted to it.
There are dozens of series.
There is a great series.
I'm watching it every day because I
can't catch up with the latest episode.
I've been watching it.
I'm addicted to it.
I'm addicted to RIKO's series.
I watched the Tokyo Revengers series.
I was addicted to it.
I watched the famous series.
I want to go to the movie.
I don't know what the movie is about.
I want to go somewhere.
I was addicted to the movie.
I was happy to see the movie.
I understand.
I want to go to the movie.
You often play with me.
Do you have anything you want to do with
me?
I want to go.
There are many things I want to do.
I want to go to the azuki toast I sent
you the other day.
I'm sorry to hear that.
I'm curious if you watch the same thing
on Instagram and TikTok.
There are many recommended things.
I want to go to the azuki toast I sent
you the other day.
I want to go to a restaurant that has a
lot of azuki beans and butter on it.
I want to go to a hot spring.
I want to go to a place like that.
I want to go to a place where I can
smell the good smell of azuki beans.
There are a lot of places like that,
right?
I want to go there.
Let's go there this year.
I want to go to a hot spring.
This season is the best.
I definitely want to go there.
I want to use hot springs and talk about
the future.
I want to go there.
I think it's going to end soon.
I want to go there several times.
That's good.
I think it's fun to play like that when
you're an adult.
I want to go to a table tennis a little
while ago.
I want to play bowling.
I was active until about two years ago.
I was very active.
Recently, I've been playing with food
and scenery.
That's a good thing.
This is what everyone who came to the
guest house asked.
What is your motto as an actor?
My motto as an actor?
I think it's very difficult to say as an
actor.
I like the word.
I don't know difficult words.
I like the word OK.
Is it okay to tell yourself?
Is it okay to be told by others?
Is it okay to say it yourself?
Is it okay to tell yourself?
There are many words that change the
word.
I like to be able to say it myself.
I like to be able to say it to others.
My mother always tells me that I'm okay.
She always tells me that I'm okay.
That's my impression.
I tell her that I'm okay when I'm
worried.
I understand.
If you put it on the word, it's not just
one person, it's a feeling that you can
solve it alone.
It's not okay, it's okay.
Then I will also use that word as a
substitute.
I often write in double letters.
I forgot.
I said something difficult.
It's like a piece of English.
Do you remember?
What is it?
What is it? It's not Love and Peace.
One Piece.
There was something cool.
I see.
From now on, I will use the word, it's
okay.
I'm looking forward to it.
Do you have any recommendations for the
viewers?
Recommendations?
What is it?
Do you have any recommendations?
Recommendations?
One Piece?
That's what I'm thinking.
I'm really into it.
One Piece?
I think everyone in the world knows
this.
I think everyone is passing through it.
I think everyone likes it even if I
don't recommend it.
Do you have any recommendations?
What is it?
I recommended this to RICO recently.
I will give you a highlight.
Can I take this out?
You can.
I will take it out.
I recommended this to AYAKA the other
day.
I was surprised yesterday.
I was surprised.
I recommended this to MAYAMAYA.
This is it.
I don't know how to read this.
This is a Chinese costume.
I'm wearing this on my face now.
This is a very natural and feminine
skin.
I think this will make my skin
beautiful.
I bought it imitating Mayama. I
recommend it to everyone.
I also bought it imitating Mayama.
Everyone is popular with shrimp.
Let's share the good things with
everyone.
What are you happiest when you do?
I was asked a very deep question.
What is the moment when you feel happy?
What moment?
I think RICO is the same.
I feel very happy when I stand on the
stage.
I feel like I'm the most myself.
I feel like I'm in a state of being.
I think the moment when I can enjoy it
without thinking about anything is on
the stage.
That's the happiest time for me.
What was the live performance like for
AYAKA?
I'm happy.
That's not it.
I think it's a happy place.
What about RICO?
What is the moment when you feel happy?
I also feel like I'm on a live
performance.
I think so.
Of course, it's a live performance.
Everyone says it's a live performance.
If you are an EPICU member, everyone
will answer it as a live performance.
I think it's a live performance without
a live performance.
I feel happy.
I think it's the time to meet people.
I understand.
I feel it especially after experiencing
the corona virus.
I think it's important to connect with
people.
I understand.
It's fun.
I feel like I've changed after getting
the corona virus.
I think it's amazing.
RICO has changed a lot.
RICO is really not interested in people.
She was a person who had no interest in
anything.
She was interested in people around her.
She was able to walk on her own.
Her activity was also improved.
I was alone.
I agree.
I was really happy.
I feel lonely when I'm alone.
I think it's a plus.
I think it's a time to talk about
YASUMOTO AYAKA.
I agree.
I have time to talk about YASUMOTO AYAKA
forever.
Let's talk about it.
What is the theme?
I want to be an adult woman.
I want to be the most beautiful woman in
my 30s.
I agree.
When I talk to an adult woman, I think I
was beautiful when I was in my 20s.
I think I was good at that time.
I look back on the past and talk about
various things.
That's why many people say that they are
looking forward to their 20s.
I talked about various experiences with
such people.
When I was in my 30s, I told young
people that I was having a lot of fun.
I told them to come here as soon as
possible.
I thought it would be nice if I could
become an adult woman.
I want to be an adult woman who can
imagine a bright future for young
people.
I want to be like that.
Of course, I'm having a lot of fun and
I'm shining now.
If I keep updating my life, I will be
the best.
My current goal is to reach my peak at
30.
When I turn 30, I want to reach my peak
at 40.
I want to be a cute and shiny woman
forever.
You are shiny this year.
I'm happy.
I'm not sure.
I think I'm similar to that.
I can't imagine my 30s yet.
I'm still 21 years old.
I'm still the first person in my 20s.
I'm having fun.
I don't remember my 10s.
I haven't thought about my future yet.
I haven't thought about that yet.
I want to enjoy my present.
I want to be together with my future.
I'm having a lot of fun thinking about
my future.
That's a good thing.
Isn't it fun now?
It's fun.
It's fun, isn't it?
We are two people who think it's fun.
I want to do what I want to do.
I think so.
You know, I talk about this while I'm
using the hot spring.
I know.
I'm talking about what I would do if I
were a grandmother.
Thank you for coming to RIKO's room
today.
Thank you.
Can I choose the next guest?
I think NONOKA is the most adorable.
I hope you can talk to your cute
juniors.
Next time, let's have NONOKA come to our
room.
Thank you very much.
I hope you are well.
Please subscribe to our channel.