I'm nervous about the dress.
I'll take care of it.
Stop it. I want to wear a uniform.
I want to have the best JK life.
How about 17?
I don't know yet.
The answer is...
There are two lies in the world.
Choose the real one and leave the lie.
If you clear the mission, you'll get a
prize.
I might know the basic idioms, but I
don't know the world idioms.
There are people who think in various
ways.
What is this?
It's like a trick.
It's a deep meaning, but I'll tell you.
I don't know the world idioms.
I'll start with the easiest one.
You have to be careful.
The world idiom I chose is real.
It's a sea shell.
The Japanese idioms have a similar
meaning.
It's a year later, and it's a year
later.
I'm in the 7th grade of junior high
school.
Show me this.
I'll choose this.
There are animals, so I'll choose a
scorpion.
I can't think of a hint.
The world idiom I chose is real.
Wah it's over!
Hit the stone bridge and cross it
Who is the member who hits the stone
bridge and crosses it?
Hinata?
Yes, Hinata
Hinata and Mayama
Mayama is the opposite of me
Mirai-chan is quite a strong person
Hello
Please choose the one you like
I was curious about the one with two
elephants
Then, should we choose from the ones
that we can find?
Yes
Let's go to China
It's like a game for the country
I thought that the monkey and the
elephant were like the country
The world I chose is the real one
It's India!
No way!
I want to know what it is
It's India?
It's a cat-nicovan
General storing is something valuable
I think it's a cat food
It's a win for people but not for me
Isn't there something like that?
Young Corn!
I think so too
I really like Young Corn
I really like it
Other members don't like Young Corn
Everyone gives it to Rina
Everyone around me
is a cat food
Even if I get Young Corn
I don't know much about Young Corn
I know how to get Young Corn
Which one do you want to choose?
This one
What is it called?
I want to be a mother
Ok, let's go with this
So fast
So quick
There are people from Italy
There are
There are men who are older than her
They say that girl is cute
Mom!
I want to be a mom
The word I chose is real
Why? Mom will be happy
I thought it was real
It doesn't make sense
It's really Fukayomi-chan
I was fooled
Let's wear this
Why did you think this was real?
I don't know, I'm just angry
I don't understand the meaning
We walk the same way, and people say
we're weird, but we're weird too
Oh, so you can't see yourself?
It's like you can't see yourself?
That sounds really possible
The world I chose is real!
Yayyy!
I'll look at the picture and do it
again.
I knew it.
Please open it.
What is it?
Let's go with this.
No way.
No way?
Really?
You are brave.
Brave action.
I don't know what it is.
Is it something to eat?
I don't know.
It must be a taste.
The world's phrase I chose is the real
one.
What is it?
It's a face.
I knew it.
I like eating food.
Is it about food?
I think it's about food. In Japan,
people who like birds don't like fish.
I see
What do you hate?
Food?
Insects
Insects, gross
And shiitake mushrooms
You eat eggs recently
I eat eggs recently
You can eat them now
I can eat oyako-don now
I hate the soft ones
Shiitake mushrooms are also soft inside
What do you hate?
I hate celery and Chinese cabbage
I hate them but if I have to choose one,
I can eat them
I like all of them
I like fried chicken
I like fried chicken more than takoyaki
I see
What do you hate?
Hakka-kun
Me too
I hate them
I brought them
I'll leave it to Ono
This looks like it
I'll take this
I'll take the senpai
This cloth looks like it
The world I chose is real!
Please!
Correct!
Do you have a strong family?
Matsuno's family is strong.
My father is the strongest.
I have an image that the three of us get
along well.
I don't have a strong family.
Look at me.
You are a woman.
I'm a man.
Mom, me, Moca.
Correct!
I'm a cat.
Dad, bring me juice.
Dad is kind.
He always welcomes me.
Dad, do your best.
Do your best, dad.
Are the two real?
Yes.
Is this a good one?
There are two real ones.
It's a three-year-old.
It's a sweet.
Which one do you want to know?
I don't want to know.
Countdown.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1
I'll go with this.
I can't be disappointed.
The world I chose is real.
Yeah!
Japanese idioms with similar meanings.
Yesterday was a person's hair, today is
my hair.
I was right.
Don't be careless.
The elephant has heavy nose.
The way of thinking is totally different
in the country.
I feel like I've learned a little.