Hello!
I'm Rihika Inamoto.
I'm Aeno Christy.
We are going to play a game today!
Yeah!
We played it last time with Riria.
This time, we are going to play a game.
Yeah!
Some of you might think that one person
is not enough.
I know.
This time, we are going to play a game.
We have a famous game commentator with
us today.
She has 1.4 million subscribers.
She is great.
She is really great.
Let's introduce our guest.
She is Kano.
Hello! Nice to meet you.
I'm Kanaiko.
Nice to meet you.
Thank you for coming.
I'm glad to be here.
I met you on a game show once.
You said that you play a game.
I thought you are a young girl.
But you are serious.
We are serious.
You two.
You are often on TV.
I'm sorry, but I heard that you are a
professional gamer.
I was surprised when I saw you two.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
I'm glad to hear that.
Can I say something?
I don't understand.
You said that you have 1.4 million
subscribers.
When I play a game, I get scolded by 1.4
million people.
I'm sure of that.
I'm not like that.
Where are you selling it?
I'm sorry.
I often watch your videos.
Really?
Your videos are really interesting.
Thank you.
We can play a game together today.
I'll tell you what game we are going to
play.
It's APEX.
Yeah!
How do you like it?
I like it.
Do you often play games?
I usually play games alone.
It's rare for us to play games together.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Are you okay?
Are you scared of the viewers of
NUGIZAKA?
I'm okay.
Everyone is warm.
I'm afraid I'll get in trouble if I pull
my legs.
I'm okay. I'm enjoying it.
You can enjoy playing games.
I'm enjoying it.
I want to set a goal.
We wanted to be the champion last time.
We couldn't be the champion.
I always say this when I play APEX.
I want to be the champion today.
Let's be the champion!
Can we?
Our goal is to be the champion of the
three of us.
By the way, what is your rank?
The highest rank is the diamond.
I've never been in the top 10.
I'm the highest rank.
I'm okay.
I'm bronze now.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Let's have fun.
Please.
Thank you for watching.
Let's get started.
Shall we?
Let's go.
You guys are quiet and calm.
We talk about strange things when we do
it in private.
We talk about strange things.
We are noisy.
We are like adults.
It's fun to be noisy.
Let's do our best and have fun.
I believe in art. And pinball is the
best.
I'm ready for the first moment.
I'm nervous.
I'll kill 749.
Thank you.
Let's go! Let's go to the champion from
the first round.
Let's go!
The first round. Where should I go?
Today is the second day.
Let's go to the second round.
I don't know much about the new map.
I know.
Here.
It's quite difficult.
I'm not used to it at all.
The Gyofu is too fast.
It's a Gyofu festival.
Gyofu festival?
It's always a Gyofu festival.
You should stop breathing if you're a
human.
Games are the most fun.
That's right. Let's stop breathing.
I want a bonus champion.
There are a lot of them.
Let's do it.
Let's go.
It's a war.
There are a lot of them.
I don't think there are many people
coming down here.
Give me the weapon!
What do you like Kano?
I recently got a 301. I like the
flatline and...
I agree. It's the easiest to use.
I like the Char-Rai.
Char-Rai is fun.
Char-Rai is really fun.
But I don't like being in the enemy's
team.
What should I do? I'll go with Kaomin.
I have a flatline.
I found a flatline.
Thank you.
I'll exchange it with Mastiff.
Where are the enemies?
They are over there.
I think so.
I don't want to be in the enemy's team.
They are fighting.
I'm fighting. I'm here.
Let's go.
Aya is the enemy.
Let's go. Everyone is white.
Are you going?
I'm just going to check the situation.
I'm the enemy.
I'm going to check.
In the middle...
There he is!
I'm scared!
They might be fighting here.
Okay, let's go slowly.
Are they doing it?
Yes, they are.
Horizon is blue.
They might be on the top.
Nice fuse.
There are so many...
Deathbots.
Where are they?
Maybe inside here.
Inside?
They have caught EVERYTHING.
Seal's authority!
They posted an official notifcation
here.
YES!
They posted.
I think there are 16 DEATHBOTS powered
up in this Tower.
Are they warning us?
They are warning us.
No, not at all.
Yes, they are.
Do you know what?
Bairo and Hard-mode.
It was like all that at the time.
We haven't crossed.
Well, they are a lot.
We will cross together for today.
Yes, we will.
We will cross together for the next
Babyman.
Yes, we will.
They posted it
It's pretty blatant.
I can't see the screen.
Something is coming!
Where are they?
One is down here.
Please subscribe!
Oh no! Sorry!
This way, this way, this way.
There's a Fuse.
He's getting healed.
Is it bad?
The screen is not showing anything.
The shield is showing, but...
Alright! One down!
Nice, nice!
Oh no! Oh no! I'm done for!
I'm done for! I'm done for! I'm done
for!
I'm done for!
Harami!
I'm being chased!
Oh no!
Oh, he's waking up.
The report, champion has been
eliminated.
I got my teammates' banners back.
Are they around here?
There they are!
I got them!
I'm throwing a cellbit!
Nice!
Wait, wait, wait!
This is hard.
Yeah, it is.
Well, well, it's just a warm-up.
I'm done with my warm-up.
Next is the actual match.
The map has changed.
I'm done.
Do you have a favorite map?
Me?
Yes.
I'm not sure. I like the place where the
magma is.
Oh, that place?
I think so.
The place where the magma is.
I see.
I like that place.
Wow, you can use the robot.
What? Me? Why?
Oh, no, no.
Me?
Let's go!
Yes!
Now, the real thing begins!
Do you guys put on badges?
I don't want to put on badges.
Why?
I don't know.
Do you think people will notice?
No, I don't want to put on badges.
I saw a comment on my live stream that
said,
I took a picture of this, so I'll put it
on.
I think it would be nice if it was a
double-hand.
I don't usually put on badges.
I don't put on badges.
I don't put on badges either.
Wow, nice.
There's only one person.
Olympus.
What?
There's only one person.
Bye-bye.
I can do this!
I think I went the wrong way.
You can do whatever you want.
I'm alone here.
Alright!
I can do this!
The screen is difficult.
Let's find a weapon!
Let's do whatever we want.
I'm alone here.
I can do whatever I want.
What should I use?
It's been a while since I played
Olympus.
Really?
Yeah, it's been a while.
I'm using a lot of new maps.
I love Olympus.
Isn't it the most beautiful?
I see.
I'll prepare myself well here.
Prepare yourself.
lok at the cap
The ring is shrinking.
I'll take this Evolved Shield.
Thank you.
Where is the other one?
Where?
The other one...
Oh, here it is.
Evolved Shield found.
Level 2.
If Renka comes, we can fight.
Yes.
Nice!
Let's fight the enemies.
There are no enemies around here.
Where should we fight?
I want a big bag.
Let's go.
There is someone.
Where?
Let's go.
Kill him.
I will.
Where?
Here.
What?
What was that?
Same team as me.
ahhh
Eh? I'm wearing purple psychologist
Korean
Wooh
One down
Nice!
I'm here!
Go! Go! Go!
Sorry! Sorry! Sorry!
Good luck everyone! Go! Go! Go!
Believe in yourself!
I'm breaking!
Nice!
Do I? Do I?
I'm taking one kill each.
I'm taking two kills.
Someone is...
I got purple!
Nice!
I'm taking the first blood.
Wait.
Do I have a good weapon?
I don't think so.
Survive Taemin.
ack ack akk.
Be careful.
Whatever.
I'll give you this.
Purple.
Is it okay?
Yes.
Thank you.
It's a present.
It's stylish.
I'm happy.
Let's be stylish together.
I'll return it with a result.
I'll return it.
He's coming towards me.
Good.
That's good.
Kano, do you play Keymau?
What?
Do you play Keymau?
I've played Keymau once, but I gave up.
You gave up.
I gave up.
Is it difficult?
It's difficult.
I see.
I think the pad is good too.
The pad...
I heard that the pad has aim assist.
Yes, it does.
Does it still have it?
I've never felt the sound effect.
I want it.
I have to tell IEI.
I want aim assist.
I want it.
Let's find enemies.
There are enemies.
There are many enemies.
Everyone, please hold on until I go.
I'm waiting.
There is a purple.
Please hold on until I go.
I'll watch here.
I think they are here.
There are three of them.
Three? What should we do?
Let's go. I'm wearing my ult.
OK. Let's go.
Are you going?
Yes.
Here.
There is a Charly.
Is there a Charly?
Charly, oh!
I'm sorry.
I need gold!
gold?
I need gold.
I need blue and purple.
I broke the bridge.
Did you?
Yes.
I broke the pathfinder.
It's hard to see.
I'll put a scan.
I don't want you to do that.
There is a Wato-san.
I'm sure he is a pirate.
He is a human recovery.
What should I do?
We have no choice but to go near.
I want a rifle.
Stop it.
Everyone, this way.
OK OK OK OK Nice!
Go! Go!
It hurts.
Where?
Here.
I can't see.
What should I do?
Did you run away?
I can't see.
This guy is a gold!
Gold!
Wato-san is really good at this!
You can do it, Yellow!
One of them ran away.
Don't run away!
Stop it!
I missed.
Let's go!
You're going to the right.
One more.
Nice!
Guys!
GG!
Nice!
There's someone behind us.
I killed everyone!
There's a coffee shop!
Isn't that amazing?
We have 5 teams left.
5 teams left?
Casual is fast.
Wait a minute.
I'm sure it's an alternator. Are you
sure?
Yea
Thank you.
Light Danger is really strong
I like Bolt recently. I feel like he's
in the Hamo prefecture.
Wait a minute.
Wait.
What?
Nothing.
I'm waking up the Hamo people.
Let's stop the people who are waking up.
Aren't they all over there?
Yeah, it's like a fishing village.
Wait a minute.
Sorry, did you want it?
No.
Then, let's go over here.
Okay.
Let's go.
Wait a minute.
There is!
Where?
Somewhere around here
It's close
There's a footstep 30 seconds before
Isn't it really close?
I'm scared
I heard a jeep
Here here here
I made a mistake
Purple
I can't hit him
I have two
I did it
Nice!
There's an enemy over there
Behind!
Behind you!
I think we should go behind.
Is this guy alone?
I got him!
Behind you!
I'm gonna die!
Oh no!
I got shot!
There are 3 people!
It turned red.
Wait, this is not good.
I think I can escape.
Nice! Nice! Nice!
Stop it!
But it hurts a lot.
I couldn't see anything.
That was close!
I went in all directions.
What are you doing?
That was close!
I'm in 4th place.
That was close.
That was amazing.
It was hard to get 1st place.
That was great.
I didn't know Tamina was wearing a fish
suit.
That was close.
I was scared.
I was watching hell.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Can I get a signal?
I'm sorry.
I'm the only one who's going to the
mountain.
I want to go.
I'm sorry.
I'll go.
I'll wait.
I'm sorry.
I'm the only one who's going to the
mountain.
We usually do it together.
We are the only ones.
I'm sorry.
It's been a long time since I played a
full game.
Me too.
I'm glad.
Last time, we did a live broadcast
together.
The comments at that time were very
warm.
I thought I would be told a lot of
things.
Games are too challenging.
The viewers were surprisingly kind.
They were very kind.
That's good.
I'm in the way all the time. Are you
okay?
Because I'm the leader.
That's right.
How about the enemies?
I don't think there are any.
Let's play!
Okay!
Until we reach our goal.
Let's play.
No enemies.
Yay!
This is ours.
It's a free-for-all!
Everyone, I have good news!
I found a purple armor!
Wow!
I'll be the special forces captain.
Please do.
Leave it to me.
I found a hop-up.
It's a double-tap trigger.
It's a multi-weapon heavy magazine.
I want a strong suit.
What do you want?
New gun leader has been created.
Be careful.
New expansion light magazine has been
found.
Level 2.
I found blue.
Oh!
Level 2.
Oh, there it is.
You want something?
No, I'm good.
You sure?
Yeah, I'm good.
Thanks.
I feel so much more private.
What?
Oh, no.
Wow, only 12 squads left.
Really?
It's too fast.
It's casual.
If you have a bag, please let me know.
I have one.
Thank you.
Where are the enemies?
We have all the clothes
Let's search for the enemies
I'm going to the enemies!
Please take off your bag
I'm waiting here
That's good! You guys have a good
teamwork
Teamwork!
Because we are a team
Yes!
Where should I go?
Should I go to the phase driver?
Yes!
Ok, let's go!
I'm going to drop it!
Ok!
It's going to drop
That's good! You guys have a good
teamwork
The flatline iron sight is trash
Please tell me if you have a scope
Flatline
What was it?
Flatline found
Throw watching angle
There's a spotlight.
...
I don't think so.
There's no footprint.
No.
Is it a bra?
What? Me?
Yes.
Aya is using a bra.
Thank you.
I think I should wear a bra more than a
pair of Olympus.
Thank you for watching.
I'm afraid that they are in the
terminal.
If they are all together, the location
is important.
I can hear the sound.
I don't think I can fight.
Shall we go? Or shall we go through?
Let's go!
We came here before we went.
Let's go.
I'm not good at seeing.
This way.
Okay.
I want to find something to buy.
Where is he? Where did he go?
Isn't he over there?
Where we were just now.
Here.
Yeah.
40 seconds left.
Oh, I see his footprints.
There he is! He's close!
The enemy is close!
Where are you?
It's dark around here, so there's a lot
of enemies.
I'm out of the map.
I found it.
Where is it?
I can hear something.
There is someone!
This way?
Search for enemies and get 3000 points.
Where are the enemies?
Is it in here?
I hear footsteps.
I hear footsteps. I don't think they are
here.
They disappeared here.
I heard footsteps on the right.
I think they are up there.
I think they are here.
I hear footsteps everywhere.
I see a gas station.
I think they are here.
I see a race car.
I see them.
I will scan the map.
Scan!
Nice job!
I broke the blue armor.
There's purple too.
One of them is down.
There's a lot of meat.
Okutan!
Oh no! I'm down!
Wait! I'm surrounded!
This is bad.
I think we should get off.
Let's get off!
Wait! There's one below us too!
There's a lot of them!
This is bad!
Where's Renka?
There she is!
You can do it!
3 shields, 6 shields.
I don't know which one is the enemy.
I don't know either.
I can't see anything.
Yeah.
Wait!
Where is that?
Wait, where is the enemy?
There is one up there too.
I'll hide.
Nice!
I'll follow you.
Good luck!
There's one here and one here.
There's one in there too.
I got shot!
Nice! Nice! Nice!
I got caught!
I got caught! I got caught!
Go! Go! Go!
Stop it!
I'm not shooting!
It's coming from above.
It's hell.
It's really hell.
I see.
I felt your ability again.
Great.
I'll continue this broadcast in the
second half of the video.
Please watch it.
Please.
Thanks for watching!