EVichu desu desu has begun!
This week's Ebichu Tastas is the second
episode of Ebichu Tastas trial.
The crimes of the idol who is addicted
to shrimp are being exposed one after
another.
Will Gundam also be in the strange face?
Gundam is a strange face.
Is it guilty or innocent? What is the
fate of the members?
Ebichu Tastas Start
injections
I'm so into you
What should I do with my heart?
Moratorium, moratorium, moratorium
Junior high school student
Add various things to your private Ebisu
junior high school
Ebichu Juskatsu
This program is brought to you by these
sponsors.
This episode of Ebichu Tastas is the
second trial
Here it comes
It's the first trial in a year
That's right
Please don't cry like Matsuno-san
I won't cry
Tears, laughter, and the cry of the soul
The Tastas trial that made the members
extremely depressed
Revival tonight
It's just a variety show.
Please do it.
Because, when this show started, we got
a line from the principal.
Yes, the principal sent us a line.
Today is the trial.
This is a variety show.
We were called.
Everyone is okay, right?
I sent a line to a girl who is okay.
Then suddenly
Everyone
Revival
One day limited revival
Thank you.
Kira Ogata
Yes, tonight.
Kira Ogata will also be a lawyer.
In this trial,
Takiyue will be a prosecutor.
He will investigate the members who were
convicted of various crimes.
The remaining members will be the
the remaining members will be the
The Tastus Court unearned apparent Pepsi
The first basic question is this!
It's a special question!
A very comfortable idol's slander!
What is that?
That's a very good thing!
Comfortable?
Comfortable!
It's not comfortable! It's comfortable!
It's not comfortable!
Then, the defendant, Hoshino Mirei is in
front.
What?
What? You're lying!
I think it's a comfortable idol.
I'm supposed to be a comfortable idol.
What?
The self-proclaimed comfortable idol
Hoshino Mirei is comfortable?
What? What?
I don't remember that.
According to the member's report,
Hoshino Mirei is an idol, but she is
very obsessed with food.
Sometimes she acts that she can be
comfortable.
Therefore, she is an idol, but she is a
comfortable person.
I'm sorry.
Please raise your hand if you have any
evidence or testimony about this matter.
Matsuno-san.
I'm a person who eats sashimi.
I was out of the frame.
What's wrong?
Hoshino Mirei, who has no interest in
food, is also a little uncomfortable.
I often eat fruits, but sometimes I'm
late to the fruit market.
Then Mirei will notice immediately.
I often eat mangoes, but when I notice,
I often think that mangoes are gone and
I can't find them.
You often think that you can't find
them.
Yes.
What happened?
This is not just me.
I often fight fruit.
You fight fruit?
Mayama-san and Hirota-san always fight
with me.
But I'm in charge of the mascot, so
mangoes don't matter.
Who eats mangoes?
Only that person.
I see.
I should have finished it with a bite,
but I started eating it after that.
I see.
Here is another testimony.
In addition, the judge.
Is there anything else?
The judge said that he is a glutton, but
he is a fool to others.
What do you mean?
He did something terrible to the
souvenir he bought at Okinawa Park.
What did he do?
He bought sea grapes as a souvenir for
school and home.
He bought one sea grape, opened the
envelope, tore it into two, and took it
home.
It's sea grapes.
It's dangerous.
He bought sea grapes as a souvenir for
school and home.
What is his idea?
I told my friend that I was going to
Okinawa.
He said, Okinawa is good.
He said, I want to eat sea grapes.
He said, I'll buy it.
He always says that to his friends.
He said that there were many grams in
the airport.
He said, I should buy the biggest one.
He bought 100 grams of sea grapes.
He bought it and went home.
His mother said, it's sea grapes.
He said, don't eat it.
He should have bought it.
He didn't have that idea.
I thought it would be enough if there
were 100 grams of sea grapes.
How much is 100 grams of sea grapes?
It's 100 grams.
That much?
But it's surprisingly a lot.
You don't know, do you?
You don't have to be surprised.
I understand the player.
The defendant, Hoshina Mirei, is being
cornered.
What will he say with the final
punishment?
I grew up in a single-parent family.
I can eat whatever I want.
What is that?
She is just talking about it.
It's the final punishment.
I think it's bad these days.
I try to leave some food.
That's all.
That's all?
That's the final punishment.
The final punishment.
Will Hoshina be able to get away with
it?
Everyone in the back, please raise your
cards.
The accused has 4 votes, and the
innocent has 3 votes.
The defendant, Hoshina Mirei, has been
convicted!
It's not a big deal, it's just a family
environment.
So the defendant Hoshina Mirei will not
jsemay all charges.
Next, the second trial is...
The next basic case is this.
Still too much of a weird face.
I got it.
Which one is it?
There are a lot of weird faces.
There are two.
The defendant Hoshina Kashiwagi is
wrong.
It's a mistake.
The defendant Hoshina Kashiwagi is
wrong.
Even with a song over, Henshin can still
be changed
The defendant Hina Kashiwagi has shown a
change that is beyond the level of an
idol
Even though she has received a lot of
attention from the agency, she still
hasn't improved
So, she still hasn't changed much
I'll give her a kiss!
Benben, please
I'm not as good as I am on TV, but I'm
still holding back
Holding back?
Holding back
Kashiwagi, who claims to be holding
back, has a new pursuit
Judge, I have proof of the VTR.
What?
Is that okay?
Scary!
Yes.
Please look at this.
Answer and of course, the general common
sense quiz!
It's out!
You're doing it!
It was completely Gundam.
Kashiwagi and Kashiwagi are...
It's so funny!
Really?
You're doing it!
What was that?
Kashiwagi, please answer the question.
It's supposed to be allowed to use
Gundam.
It's not allowed to use Gundam.
Will Gundam be in the Hengawa?
Gundam is Hengawa.
Until now, Gundam wasn't being watched.
I thought, please stop with the weird
faces.
In my opinion, Gundam isn't weird at
all.
If you say that, I'll be the one who
gets scolded.
Chue-san, you're not weird.
It's like that.
It's not okay.
What happened, defense?
Everyone does weird faces nowadays.
Kashiwagi's is a bit weird.
I don't think it's okay to have weird
faces in the cute range of idols.
But you don't say that it's weird.
Weird faces are weird faces.
It's not cute to be weird.
Your idea is a comedian.
Your personality is a comedian.
And here's a suggestion from Kenji
Takiwe.
What did you do, Kenji Takiwe?
He said there were two members.
When the suspicion was raised?
I'd like to put one of them on trial.
Who was the other member who was
suspected of being a weirdo?
I see.
It's a defendant, Kobayashi.
Please come forward.
Kobayashi is also suspected of being a
weirdo.
What does this mean?
By the way, how weird is Kobayashi?
I'm holding it down.
I'm in the middle of the song.
Hirota.
Here's a powerful testimony to support
the suspicion.
When I make people laugh, I perform
live.
The cameraman who's filming the monitor
says,
I can't show this.
So I change the switcher.
I do it on another camera.
It's often done in real time.
I think that's the case.
You leave the switcher.
Yes.
I'm like, this is dangerous. Switch it.
By the way, can we see the change of the
switcher?
Yes.
We'll judge it.
What's the strange face of the switcher
that comes out during the live?
From the time of the song
Because I'm a kid, I have a bright
answer
Yeah!
This is it
Thank you
Since it's a big deal, let's check the
strange face of the switcher
3, 2, 1, go!
It's super funny
Two people who are particular about
their funny faces
Their passionate feelings are finally
revealed
There are some families who say they
like funny faces
Please be careful not to exceed the
limit
I'll do my best
I'll try to improve my facial expression
I'll keep working on it
I'm trying to improve my facial
expression
I'll keep working on it
They are not able to understand the
color of their reflection
What will happen?
Please raise your hand if you think it's
a waste.
Go ahead!
It's a waste!
Please reply to this email, Kobayashi to
be döm t-h sollte MAN tracing!
Bunun
will defy gates
had been a
that
after
giving
ac H tent
Ebichu, the narrow road of the lyricist
Following the previous time, we will
make the original lyrics that match the
melody of the song Donguri Korokoro
What kind of lyrics did these five
people write?
First, the announcement of Nakayama
We are the shrimp. We are the shrimp.
There are also shooting stars.
Shooting stars.
There are more?
Yes. And today, Kaiki Okata...
Wait, I made it wrong.
Sorry.
Please follow me.
There are also shooting stars.
Shooting stars.
And then,
Today, Kaiki Okata will be there.
We will enter after the show.
Let's do it again.
Thank you for watching.
Wait, I can't sing at all.
I can't do the modi-sum.
You can do it.
That's what Nakayama does.
Next is Hirota.
Now that I think about it, this is
Hyetaniougher.
Qué always left my earItch N Book.
So I'm going to이 singing this song with
this song.
This time, a live concert.
Cute
How to make boiled egg
That's right
It's about making eggs, but it's
sparkling
Yes
There is a dream
This is amazing
Thank you very much
It feels like a world view
Next is Yasumoto
The story of love
Two of us, one love so sweet
You are my Miss My Friend
You've got it all in
You've got it all in but the entrance
was like
Why did you enter from the back?
I wrote the lyrics from the bottom
From the bottom?
But this is just a way of making it
Can you sing the story of the encounter
again?
The story of the encounter that I had
that day
Next up is Matsuno
Zuru zuru zuru zuru zuru rinko
Shin-chan's switch is so difficult
The wind at the last minute is
interesting
That was pretty good
Good
Oh, is it my song?
Yes, how was it?
What was the last minute wind?
That was the last minute wind
The last minute wind is a joke that
Takiue made up last year
By the way, it was cut off at the on-air
How was it, Kaeki?
How was it?
You call it Japanese?
Yes
It's good that it has a rhythm
Thank you
There's also English at the end
It's a class that mixes various words
The last one is Hoshina
Chue-chan, Shin-chan, Nagare-boshi
Which one is more interesting?
Let's have a competition
Shin-chan, I'm looking forward to your
funny story
Good
She got it right
I've heard of it
It was yay!
I said yay very loudly
Shin-chan, please show us the joke
I'm sure it's Ichu-A-san
Thank you
Who's not sure?
But you want to see Shin-chan's joke
right?
I want to see a new one
Go for it
Alright
This is the script exercise
Amazing
And when Takei was doing it, I didn't
see any of the characters
At least watch it
The old man is working hard
To be continued
This year's event is also coming
The annual event of the summer, Famiyan
Tonight, the live performance that was
just held on August 20th
Please come and watch it
Ebi-chuu Summer Family Concert
In other words, Famien 2016 Super News
Special
Famien is a concert of Ebi-chuu Summer
Night Out One-man Concert
which has been held three times so far
And this year
This year's Famien has started!
Morkino KZ
Thank you for watching!
You can take a flippingEOO
This summer was very rainy
However, a great stage that blew away
the weather was performed
I want to sleep
We are NiziU
I can't sleep
There will be hearts in these time kilos
There will be wisdom in these repair
tubes
There are things that even kids can't do
toys
Although I haven't had enough water yet
Can I ask you to have more
Rain gets stronger as it goes on head
on.
The ground feels like the last place!
Geleage Club
The melody
Go bang bang!
A black and pink ring
High tension mission
Let's go!
It's a little hot
A fresh fate
A
It's a mess
It's not over yet
M.A.M.A.M.A.
Who take you?
M.A.M.M.A.M.A.
The only thing I can do is to call you
I'm not going to cry, so don't look at
me
The only thing I can do is to go out and
play
I can't say it, so hurry up
The only thing I can do is to be a good
girl
I'm not going to cry, so don't look at
me
And the last one is...
I don't want to lose!
I don't want to give up!
No matter how hard it is,
believe in yourself!
You can do it!
No fear!
Do your best!
I don't want to give up!
I want to be strong!
I'm not afraid!
Today and tomorrow are the same!
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
The winner is Mike!
No matter how hard it is,
believe in yourself!
You can do it!
I don't want to give up!
I want to be strong!
Thank you for watching!
Next time, we'll have the second episode
of the Ebichu Tassai version.
Are you sleepy?
Yes.
The evidence that was brought to
Hirota's front...
What kind of crime did they get punished
for?
The Tassai version is getting more and
more popular!
This program was sponsored by the
sponsor you are watching.
That's the real thing.
Please subscribe to our channel!