Ebichu Toss Toss has started!
I, Yasumoto, will be in charge of the
day's work.
What is this?
It's like a CD jacket.
Yes, we are arranging the CD.
I see.
You guys have so many CDs.
You guys are young.
Which one is the first poster you took?
This one.
It's a bit painful.
It's a temporary contract.
It looks delicious.
Who is this?
It's Hoshina.
You are bad at laughing.
Hoshina, you are my girlfriend.
You are stiff.
Your smile is stiff.
Next is this.
It's still good.
It's still round.
Which one is Mayama?
Mayama.
It's starting to look like Yasumoto.
Hoshina is stiff.
Hoshina is still nervous.
Her eyes are still stiff.
How about Hoshina's smile?
It's still good.
Are you really doing this?
It's a temporary contract.
Can you do it now?
It's not a permanent contract.
It's quite hard.
Next is this.
It's the main one of Yasumoto.
It's the middle one.
It's still good.
What happened?
She is smiling.
She is happy.
Hoshina learned how to smile.
She learned how to smile.
When will you meet Nakayama?
I will join the match.
She is nervous.
She is still nervous.
She still has a long way to go.
Kobayashi's smile is natural.
She is nervous.
She is like Hoshina before.
She is stiff.
She is learning how to smile.
She looks like the moment when Chie was
making Gundam.
She looks like Hoshina before, but she
is still stiff.
She is still stiff.
They enjoyed the nostalgic poster, so
they will announce the theme of the day.
Yasumoto, what is the theme of the day?
This time, Ebichu Tastasu is a special
edition.
We will release the best album.
This time, Ebichu Tastasu is a special
edition.
The best album will be released next
week.
It's a special edition.
The best album will be released next
week.
100 times the frustrating emotions
Come on!
I'm so crazy about you
What should I do with my heart?
Moratorium, moratorium, moratorium
Middle school students, moratorium,
moratorium
Add a lot of things to private Ebisu
middle school
Middle school students
Ebisu Chatsaku
I'm totally dead.
This program is brought to you by the
following sponsors.
At this moment, I'm performing on stage.
We will now dig into the best album that
will be released next week.
I can read the kanji.
I'm a little nervous.
You're reading too much.
I'm nervous just reading the kanji.
We have a guest.
The sound director, Seto.
Welcome.
Seto has been working with us since our
debut.
He brought us the best album.
Here it is.
Seto, please take this.
This is the CD jacket.
Thank you.
That's all from Seto.
I'm not a decoy.
I'll keep it.
The album is a mix of cool songs.
The staff selected the exciting songs.
The complete version will be released at
the same time.
The jacket is wrapped in white cloth.
Let's hear the story.
Did you have any difficult episodes?
The white cloth was tight.
It was hard.
I think I should wear a jersey at my
wedding.
No way.
It's a jersey.
I wear 4 pieces of kimono.
There are many inside.
I can't take a selfie here.
It's a life-threatening selfie.
It's hard to breathe.
It was painful to the point where my
ribs broke.
It's terrible.
Here is the recording station.
Please look forward to it.
To Chia vote & Tomorrow Vote
The new song of Bihapia, SUDDEN DEATH.
What kind of song is this?
It's a song written by Mr. Taku Okazaki.
What is the song like?
At first, it's a little hot.
And the chorus is a little emotional.
And from the second verse, it's a very
emotional song.
What is emotional?
It's a song that makes you feel hot.
Mr. Seto, are you emotional?
I'm emotional.
I'm really emotional.
Here are the recommended songs for each
member from the best album.
The best of the best is announced.
First, YASUMOTO's Best of Best.
YASUMOTO's Best of Best is...
Fireworks, Cigarettes, Rock'n'Roll,
Remix.
It's a song that we sing at live shows.
We sing this song when we go to a fire.
We sing this song at a festival.
It's a song for recording.
There's a part where I shout.
The shout is...this!
Yeah...
I couldn't shout at all when I was
practicing, so I thought I would never
do it.
But I miraculously did it.
You did it on the recording?
Yes. And when I got the CD, I was
surprised that I was doing it.
The part of the shout?
I was really nervous.
Because it's a lucky shout.
It's a lucky shout, so I didn't really
do 100 shots.
I've never heard of a person who says
100 shots.
I was so nervous that I practiced with
my dad.
Your dad has a loud voice.
My dad is going to come out.
Next, Hoshina's Best of Best.
Hoshina's Best of Best is this!
Unconfirmed Middle Schooler X
Why is this?
This is the first song I sang at the
first Super Arena in Saitama.
This is the memorable live video.
There is a secret behind this song.
When I was choreographing this song, I
met Lucky Ikeda for the first time.
He choreographed this song for me.
He said, this song is good.
He shouted, this song is good.
But this song doesn't have that.
It doesn't have that.
But Lucky Ikeda came to my house.
It's more interesting to say this.
Lucky Ikeda came to my house when I was
choreographing this song.
I was wondering what he was saying.
I thought it was a lie.
Is that true, Seto?
Yes, I was told that while I didn't
know.
Next is the best of best chosen by
Kobayashi.
The best of best chosen by Kobayashi
is...
Butterfly Effect.
Why is that?
This was the first CD for me and Reko.
I was so nervous when we were recording.
I remember that.
It was the first song.
You didn't know anything, right?
I didn't know.
Did the recording go well?
Did it go well?
It went well.
I was in the same booth as Nakayama and
Kobayashi.
We recorded one by one.
You were nervous because you were alone?
Kobayashi was in Rinko's booth.
I was nervous at first and it was hard
to sing.
Kobayashi was looking at Nakayama in the
booth.
Nakayama was singing.
That's cute.
You couldn't sing alone.
That's right.
You're so good.
You were that nervous.
You're like a parent.
I'm a good parent.
You're a good parent.
I'm not good enough yet.
Next, the best of best chosen by Mayama.
The best of best that Mayama will choose
is...
This one.
Fluffy Sirenium.
It's used in the bus when you are in a
good mood.
It's used.
I'm usually in the second place and I'm
about to cry.
I like the moment when the lights are
turned off.
Let's see the moment when the lights are
I've never heard of it.
Please tell us the moment.
Here it is.
1, 2, 3. This is it.
This moment.
This is the fun part.
I feel like I'm doing a live
performance.
That's the most emotional part.
I'm so emotional.
Next, Kashiwagi's Best of Best.
Kashiwagi's Best of Best is...
Nazutatsu Jouni.
Why is it?
This is a summer song in the middle of
summer.
It's like a festival.
Just by singing or listening to it,
it's a song that makes your body move.
Oh, really?
Let's see if it really moves.
Let's do it.
Let's verify it.
Can't you dance with Seta-san?
I don't know.
I don't know if I don't sing.
Taki might be nervous.
No, I'm not.
Taki is nervous.
No, no.
I'm not nervous when I sing.
We're adults.
That's right.
So, let's verify if your body really
moves when you listen to the song.
Tere Tere
danced elegantly
Business trip
with the sound of success
Money, work want
Thank you for watching!
The Ashitaba Band is playing.
Seto-san's hands are all wet.
Next, Matsuno's Best of Best.
Matsuno's Best of Best is this!
Cinderella by Kari Kei.
What is this?
This is Ebichi's major debut single.
The first song?
The first song.
I said this song before.
Calm down.
Matsuno is so excited.
She made a mistake on the Tsuba-Dobu
part.
Matsuno's first impression of Ebichi.
I'm recording this again.
I'm recording from the beginning again.
The voice is very young compared to the
previous one.
I want you to compare it.
I want you to compare the current Ebichi
and the old Ebichi.
The voice has changed.
It's completely different.
You put a lot of effort into it.
It's different. It's different now.
I want you to listen to it.
The part where it's changed.
Let's listen to it.
Comparison of the first single and the
second single.
First, the old version.
Hey, Guild President!
... Like this.
I'm not sure if I should wait or not.
You're going to wait?
Yeah.
I have no idea.
I'm getting dizzy!
Why are you getting dizzy?
Let's listen to the new version.
I'm feeling better.
Who's next?
Me!
Oh!
Awesome!
Come here!
You're good at it!
Oh!
Eh, is it a weird sound?
It's a weird sound!
But, the middle schoolers' voices are
all very clear.
It's like an adult's voice.
And, there's a bit of playfulness in the
way they sing.
It's like they're having fun.
Oh, I see.
It's completely different.
Furthermore, there's an episode Matsuno
can't forget.
It was my first time filming like this.
And, this is Ebi-Tadan's...
Ah, this!
It's really like a kiss.
That's right.
I put a lot of red glitter around my
eyes.
The next day, I got a pigmentation and I
couldn't take it off.
I had to go to school.
I had to make it red.
You went to school?
But it didn't come off?
It came off.
It's red here.
It says Q here.
It says Q.
Did you go to school?
I was wearing a mask, but it was red.
Everyone asked me, what's wrong with
that?
But I said, cover it up.
But it's Q here.
How can you cover it up with a Q?
I went to school.
That's...
That's a cry.
It's scary to wash it and not be able to
take it off.
I was like, what should I do?
Did you cry?
I cried.
You were crying at the Q, right?
I was crying.
Next, the Best of Best chosen by Hirota.
Hirota's Best of Best is this!
I don't think adults understand me.
Why?
I don't know why, but I was really
worried about this single.
I thought it was really weird.
So I put it all in this song and danced.
Just like the title.
I thought I didn't understand.
Then I was surprised at my own style.
I was recognized.
Then someone came.
I also had a family member.
It's a song that I found a new me.
Here is the dance that Hirosa has opened
up a new territory.
It's a moment, so please take a good
look.
I'm going to do my best.
What do you like?
I don't know. I have to see it later.
It's the feeling at that time. For me,
it's over.
It's a repeat.
It's meaningful to leave it as it is at
that time.
But I don't want to see it.
It's amazing. It's like an idol or a
rock musician.
I'm sorry.
I thought it was a documentary program.
The last is the best of best chosen by
Nakayama.
The best of best of Nakayama is this!
It's a new song!
Why is it?
Let's talk about it together.
No, no, no.
What is it?
It's a bit difficult, so let's talk
about it together.
I'm really looking forward to doing what
I can say live.
Dance battle.
Dance battle?
Yes.
What is the dance battle?
I'm going to do it.
Don't leave it to others.
Say it yourself.
Don't use Hiroto like a web.
The winner is Hiroto.
Who is it?
Let's see.
Hi everyone, I'm Taku Okazaki.
Congratulations on the release of the
best album of Shiritsu Ebisu Junior High
School.
This is a very fun song.
I also sang it at the recording.
I was the vocal director.
The members were having fun recording
it.
I think it will be a fun song.
Please listen to it.
This was Taiku Okazaki.
How was the recording?
It was fun.
Did you have any problems?
I had a hard time pronouncing English.
Taiku said that you were struggling with
English.
That was amazing.
I was really trying to speak English.
I'm looking forward to seeing how it
will be after the recording.
That's right.
To wish for the best album hit, this
person has come.
Please come in.
Please.
To wish for the best album hit, this
person has come.
This is Wild Sui-chan!
Today is Wild!
Wild!
It's not about you, let me do it!
It's fine, you can do it.
It's a bit hard to do now.
It's fine, but...
It's fine, it's fine.
I want to see it!
I've been watching it on TV!
You've been watching it on TV?
You're not a past tense!
Watch it now!
You should be watching it!
I'm not, I'm not.
Are you a drunk or a drunkard?
I've been watching it!
You don't need to be honest.
Everyone's been watching it!
My parents said that too.
They said that they only watch it once
in a while.
No, no, no.
What do you mean by the cameramen giving
in?
Do it over there!
That's it!
Sui-san, do you remember?
That's the camera.
You're filming this?
Really?
Today, for everyone in Ebichu...
You're filming this?
Of course!
Let's go.
No, really, Sui-chan...
Actually, today, her pants are down.
She's wearing suspenders!
What?
But still, her pants are down.
Why?
Let me tell you.
Look at those suspenders.
It's because she's wearing them.
It's wild!
What's with this situation?
I can't see!
We can't see!
Why did Sugi-chan have to wear a hit-
kigan?
Let me tell you why.
This time, you're releasing your best
album, right?
Yes!
I...
This Daverned
But, you're wearing a vest, so you were
called.
It's a strange way of being called.
This was the best, right?
This was the best.
I didn't expect it.
After a strange casting,
all the members wore Sugi-chan's best at
the end.
It was a hit.
I'm not done yet.
I'm still earning money.
It's wild.
The second live special in a row.
The first one is...
Nakayama Riko's birthday solo live.
Rika, Sakana, Yokohama,
everyone, together!
The second live special in a row.
She's completely absorbed in her first
solo live in Nakayama.
16-year-old's birthday!
This program was brought to you by the
following sponsors.
If I was punished by him?