Wow, it's pink.
It's like the color of my eyelids when I
close my eyes in the bright sunshine.
It makes me feel energetic.
Close your eyes.
Oh, this color.
It's the same color as the color of my
eyelids.
I'm sleepy.
Who should I start with?
Hello?
Who is this?
Do you know who this is?
Is this your senior or junior?
Junior.
Junior?
Who is this?
We met about 10 days ago.
10 days ago?
Yes.
It's been 10 days.
Is that a standard word?
Who is it?
It's a very, very old, from Tokyo.
A junior from Tokyo?
A junior from Tokyo.
What?
Is it a band?
It's not a band.
How about listening to this voice?
What?
I'm always next to you.
Taiki-san is always there.
Taiki-san?
Yes.
I'm always listening to you when you're
talking.
When I'm talking?
You're a drone specialist, aren't you?
What?
Taiki-san.
Ryusei Yokohama?
No, that's the worst.
What?
Ryusei Yokohama?
No, no, no.
That's the worst.
Wow.
Wow, all of a sudden.
I was like, wow, that's not it.
So the drone is the drama?
It is.
Wow, I'm so happy.
You know, you wouldn't say this if it
was Ryusei Yokohama.
What?
It's not.
Who is it?
It's the courage of the Tosa brothers.
Hello?
Wait a minute.
The moment you said you were the Tosa
brothers' courage,
there was a mysterious time.
You cut it, right?
Yeah, I cut it.
Wait a minute.
I thought you were Ryusei Yokohama.
Stop it.
It's Ryusei.
I want to cut it.
I was really looking forward to it.
Wait a minute.
That's not good.
I thought it was Yuuki, the brother of
Tosa.
I was a little surprised and hung up.
Can I stop?
This was a great opportunity.
I wanted to get closer to Yuuki.
We've always been polite to each other.
That's right.
So I thought I'd be a little bit of a
I'm so happy.
Oh, really?
I'm just a little bit polite.
So you're saying I can go now?
Of course.
I've already settled so let me go and
get our
5th high school students. 5th high
school students? I'm 32 now.
Yeah, I'm 27 this year.
So 5th high school students.
I've wanted to tell you something.
What?
We talked about how we speak the same
language.
When Taiki and I were talking,
Yokohama Ryusei-san...
I'm a little younger than him, but he's
a super actor.
Super actor. He's the representative of
Japan.
I was like, should I call him Ryusei-san
or Ryusei-kun?
There was a stage.
And he was like, Yuuki-kun, call me
Ryusei-kun.
He said that.
I said it.
He said it was impossible.
I've been calling Ryusei-kun recently.
Oh!
Really?
So I thought Taiki-san would go after
me.
But he's just called me Ryusei-san.
I've been calling you Ryusei-san for a
long time.
Can you stop calling me that?
Why?
You're becoming like a very familiar guy
to me.
No, no, no. You're Super IU, Ryusei
Yokohama.
Yes, of course.
You can't say that he's Ryusei-kun.
A musician like us, or a comedian,
are being teased and forced to perform.
That's true.
It's hard to say that he's Ryusei-kun.
If he did it, seriously.
If he had a normal attitude.
If he had a normal attitude, he wouldn't
have done it.
Who doesn't have a normal education?
What's your first impression of him?
My first impression?
Yeah.
I mean, I think it was during our first
diving practice.
And I suddenly forgot about Divers Note.
That day.
I see.
I was forgetting about the Divers Note.
And the teacher was like,
Oh, you forgot about it, Eiki?
I was told that.
I thought he was a real loser.
Oh, yes.
Yeah.
That's right.
But I thought so.
But once I got into the sea, I could do
anything.
I was really good at diving.
But I wasn't able to participate in the
second half of the practice.
That's true.
And you leaked that to Fuwa-chan, Yuuki-
kun.
I got a message from Fuwa-chan after
that.
I got a message saying, don't skip the
practice.
That's right. Fuwa-chan's friend.
That's right.
I'm sorry.
I was visiting my house.
I was asked what I was up to today.
I went diving with Taiki Okazaki today.
He said, I really like you.
I said I was just watching the ocean.
I was like, Taiki Okazaki, you're a
baby.
He thinks everything is a baby.
Yeah, he's my colleague.
He's your colleague.
Fuwa-chan used to come to my live shows.
Oh, he did?
Yeah, yeah.
He really liked it.
Fuwa-chan...
I'm an entertainer, so I don't have many
people who let me exchange their LINE
messages.
Oh, really?
That's what I really like about him.
I'm becoming Fuwachan and Taikun.
Oh, really?
But you know, we finally did it the
other day.
The line group of the DCU members.
It was amazing.
All 6 of us.
Yeah.
Isn't it amazing?
It's too amazing.
Well, well, well.
Everyone's amazing, but...
Abe Hiroshi's line group is in it.
Thank you for watching.
That's crazy.
It says, thank you.
No, no, no. That's not how you say it.
Oh, I see. That's not how you say it.
It's a text, so it doesn't matter if
it's a voice or not.
Oh, well, it doesn't matter.
But it was totally that tone.
Thank you.
But that group line is amazing.
That's amazing. That group line will
never fall out.
Even if it dies, it won't fall out.
That won't fall out.
That's a legendary group line.
It's a legendary group line.
Thank you for watching.
When Taiki was the only one, we had a
lot of interactions.
We had a lot of interactions.
After Abe-san and Ryusei-kun joined, we
didn't really get a lot of messages.
Yeah, we were all doing our own thing,
and when everyone joined, we all said,
please take care of us, but that line
group didn't move at all.
Yeah, if Abe-san was there, we wouldn't
have gotten any messages.
But that was...
多分 もう 組み取ったのよ 自分で 何で今回呼ばれてるかを
決める 場を 和ましていくべき存在なんじゃないかと 僕と結城君で
Yeah, that's right.
I'm so happy that you found that out as
soon as possible
and actively
made fun of the camera.
Taiki-san, you're so cool.
Really? I'm so happy.
I'm an entertainer.
You're embarrassing me.
So, today, let's talk about something
serious.
We want to do something.
Yeah, that's true.
We're entertainers.
We can't drink alcohol, so it's hard to
talk about this kind of stuff.
But I think we can do something on the
phone.
So, you know, you're making songs,
right?
Do you always think about something?
Wow, you're asking like a bright-skinned
writer.
You're a bright-skinned writer.
That's the worst.
I'm always like...
People always ask me,
What kind of song do you think of?
I think I think of a lot of songs.
I've been asked that question a hundred
times.
That's the most troublesome thing.
I've been asked that question about 600
times.
I'm just curious about the artist's
style.
I see.
For example, there's a song called Call
On.
This is a song that requires a very
difficult call and response during the
song.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's like you can't do a hand clap or a
fast English lyrics on the spot.
I see.
It's a song from a long time ago.
It's a band that I used to work with.
I was thinking about how to make them do
a hand clap.
There was a band that was trying to make
the audience do it.
Oh, oh, oh.
In a call and response.
It's impossible, isn't it?
I thought it was impossible.
I looked at the audience and no one was
doing it.
I thought it was really fun.
So I thought of writing a song like
that.
And the song I wrote was called Call On.
So I think I have a lot of ideas for my
own songs.
You're really observant.
I try to see how people act and act.
Maybe it's something new at the set of a
drama.
Like the seeds of a song.
Yeah, maybe.
Do you have anything specific?
Something specific?
Not like a drama, but something recent.
Like, I want to make a song like this.
I wonder if there's anything recent.
But I thought about it.
Like staff?
Like on TV shows, on live shows, on
comedy shows, on TV, etc.
But ADs are pretty angry.
Yeah.
Like the directors.
Like, why are you doing that? The camera
is on!
They're really angry.
They're really angry. I always feel
sorry for them.
Yeah.
But on the set, there are people who get
angry.
I think it's totally different from the
way people get angry.
You're right.
On the set, there are people who get
angry, but I don't push them at all.
You don't push them.
yeah yeah n
I think it's a necessary role for a
cameraman or director to get angry.
I see.
I think it's important to get angry.
I'm thinking of writing a song for a
very angry director next time.
I want to see a director who gets angry
at the stage of a live performance.
I really want to see that.
By the way, it doesn't matter at all.
Taiki's song.
There's a song you want to do until you
die.
Oh, I know that song.
Yeah, I want you to watch that song.
I'm curious about it.
So, please make one of these 100 things
come true with me.
One of the 100 things?
Yes.
What is it?
It can be a useless thing.
Do you eat snakes?
No.
That?
You've seen snakes a few times, right?
I have.
You know, people don't really want to
eat snakes.
I wanted to do something cool with
snakes.
Like what?
Like going to Mt. Fuji with snakes.
Have you ever wanted to climb Mt. Fuji?
I've never climbed Mt. Fuji before.
Oh, never.
I wanted to climb the highest mountain
in Japan.
Yeah, because we're going to the bottom
of Japan together in the future.
That's true.
I'd like to go to the highest mountain
with the same members.
Yeah, it'd be great to go to the highest
mountain with the same members.
Yeah, that's a great idea.
That's why it's so high-class.
It's a top-ranking mountain in Japan.
The highest mountain with the same
members.
Yeah.
It's a great way to show off your human
skills.
Let's go to the top together.
Do you want to eat the snake?
You're going to make two of them come
true.
I'll make two of them come true.
Let's eat snakes at Mt. Fuji's summit.
Let's make a promise.
Okay, then. Let's make a promise.
Then, I'll just call out to the members
of DTU.
Just call out?
Yes.
I see.
Then, An-chan, Ryusei-kun, and Mitsuomi
might come.
Mitsuomi-san.
Oh, Mitsuomi-san. Sorry.
Stop calling me.
Oh, I see. Sorry.
Then, I'll see you again when we shoot
the next video.
It's early in the morning, but...
Thank you.
Thank you. See you.