Yakan and Idol
Now, we have a project for Yakan and
Idol.
Can you do the title call for this
project?
Yes, I'll do it.
It's my third project.
What is it?
What are the three things that make Aoi
Nuri?
Here it is.
I see.
Can you tell me one by one?
The first one is talking.
I really like talking to people.
But sometimes I feel like I'm alone
because I'm too into the world.
What kind of world do you mean?
I'm a fast talker.
That's a very comfortable way to talk.
I'm going to try to keep this up today.
Let's talk at full speed.
Really?
What kind of world is it?
I'm a fast talker when I talk about what
I like.
I can't stop talking, so I can't stop
when I'm stuck.
I'm a very fast talker.
What do you like to say?
What I like to say...
Do you want to talk to someone?
I want to tell them what I like to eat.
When you talk about that...
I can't stop.
You can't stop.
So you're going to talk about the rest
of the world.
That's how you talk.
You're talking fast, but you can't hear
anything.
I don't know if it's true at events.
I want to talk about what I like.
That's right.
I'm going to say what I want to say.
There are still three major elements
here.
What do you like?
I've been drinking a lot of tapioca
lately.
There was a tapioca boom a long time
ago.
Yes, there was.
I've been coming back.
I bought a little earlier than I was
supposed to go to the scene.
I bought it when I was on my way home
from work.
I drink a lot of tapioca.
It's cute.
I like tapioca.
I also like gold-plated burdock.
It's a little bland.
Why is it bland?
I like the gold-plated burdock that my
grandmother makes.
I can't eat other burdock.
I like the gold-plated burdock that my
grandmother makes.
You like the gold-plated burdock that
your grandmother makes.
If your fans tell you that, you can't
stop.
Do you get told by your manager?
I was told that today.
It's okay to tell your manager.
I'm glad you told me.
I told you to keep it a secret.
You're right.
YouTube is a fast-paced channel.
I'm a fast-paced person.
How many times?
I watch it twice.
You're in a hurry.
Can you promote your debut mini-album?
I'll do my best.
I'll wait for your announcement.
I understand.
I want to hear it.
Please look forward to it.
I'm a patty.
Really?
It may be hard to understand today.
Yeah.
This program is...
Manu Mitano
Keisuke
Takeshi
Bansan
Shuuji at Stabler DD
I have been sent by the offer
Today's recommended gummy is
It is the cola flavor of the Peta-Goo
gummy
Please try it everyone
Thank you very much