Ebichu's videos
Now, I'm going to start the blind test
of the road of Kashiwagi Hinata.
I'm nervous.
There are 14 kinds of meat.
I got it.
Let's eat.
Out of 14 questions, I got 10 right.
I got more than 10 questions right.
And the prize is a Yakiniku bento.
I'll give it to the members of Umitube
as a reward.
I'll do my best.
I'll give Yakiniku bento to the members.
I'm nervous, but I'll do my best with
this eye mask.
I'll put on my eye mask.
Everyone, goodbye.
I just thought it was orange and light
blue.
It's noisy.
I'm going to do it.
It's noisy. I'm sorry.
So, I'm going to start the Nixomelia's
road, the blind test.
What is this?
It would be great if I could tell by the
smell, but I can't tell at all.
I'll eat it.
What is this?
I don't know at all.
What should I do?
What is this?
Wait a minute.
It's red.
I know it's red.
I should have swallowed it earlier.
I should have tasted it a little more.
Oh my god.
It's gone.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait a minute.
Well...
The red one is the best.
I don't know.
But I should guess the order.
Wait a minute.
Sagari?
Let's eat.
Where?
Thank you for watching.
It's like a Kalbi.
But which Kalbi is it?
Which one is it?
But...
It's Jokalbi.
Jokalbi.
What is this?
I'm wondering the taste.
Is it Akamino Calvinsu?
I'm going to eat it.
Hmm?
It's good.
Which one is it?
What?
It's a tongue.
I don't know which one is which.
I found a lot of hair.
Jotan.
I'm sure.
It smells different.
Marucho.
What is this?
I know his feelings.
She knows what I'm saying, don't you?
It's a loin!
loin loin
It's loin
Itadakimasu
Thank you for your viewing.
What?
What is this?
I don't know this meat
I feel like I want to play Akami no Karu
again
But I answered it before
It's not this one, is it?
Kalbi is a speciality of Japan, and
Japanese beef is a speciality of Japan.
And Joe and Akami?
Did I eat Akami Kalbi?
Yes, you did.
But it's pretty...
It's Joe! Joe Kalbi!
I'm sure.
Joe Kalbi!
Itadakimasu!
What?
What is this?
Jorosu
What?
Harami?
Chagari?
Is it Jo?
I don't know what Jo is.
Hmm...
Joharami?
No derivation.
Thank you for watching until the end.
I'm lost.
Is there any speciality or Japanese beef
left in Kalbi?
I see.
It's either one.
Which one?
I wonder if I bought a lot.
I just ate it, but it was so soft and
delicious.
Which one is it?
Specialty.
Specialty Kalbi.
It's difficult.
If I were a member, I would know.
Who is the gourmet of the BBQ
restaurant?
I think so.
So Miyanomoto is the one who finds the
food and facts.
And Mine will seem to look for the
traces.
we get the other 4 dancers to help us.
Thank you for watching.
I think Ayaba knows the most about
tapioca.
What is the most memorable dish?
I suddenly remembered Yuasa-san.
This.
I remembered suddenly.
This is horumon, right?
No?
I will eat.
under eldest daughter
This is a treatment of granm
Why?
Let's play.
Thank you for watching!
This is Japanese beef kalbi.
No, it's not.
Japanese beef kalbi.
Next is The kavia pulled down by Watson.
Sagari.
Thank you for watching.
Drive safely
Please look forward to the next work
Explo dat
It was a tongue.
I'm scared.
I got half of it.
No way.
I got a lot.
I did my best.
Wait, I only got 6?
I was so happy that I got 10.
I got a lot.
I didn't know that.
I'm embarrassed.
I got 6 out of 14 questions right.
It's my first time.
I did my best, didn't I?
Congratulations!
Thank you!
I will study more about meat and try
again.
That's all for today. I'm Nekusomurieru.
I will continue!
Bye bye!
That's a shame.