Thank you for watching!
Now, it's time for the banana song of
the host of the show, Kojichi Nagazaka.
Hello, I'm Nagazaka.
Hello, everyone.
I'm the best in Japan.
I see.
Please announce today's project.
Let's go.
Go Kissey!
Mount Fuji!
The rock climbing hit group was over.
If I get a chance like that, I will do
my best to leave a mark.
It's nothing, but you can climb Mt.
Fuji.
I want to do it.
I like it.
The member who was there said.
Did you say it?
I said it.
First of all.
I will go.
Wow.
How can you go to Mt. Fuji with that
much effort?
You want to go to Kawaguchiko, right?
You said yes.
Yamashita.
You can't go to Yamashita now.
I can go.
You are enthusiastic.
Don't underestimate Mt. Fuji.
I can go whenever I want.
You are the most open-minded person now.
This time, the two teams will challenge
on a different route.
The final challenge.
The team is divided into 10 people,
including Okamoto, who is sick and
tired.
Team A and Team B
First, these 5 people will challenge the
Fuji mountain route.
It is for beginners, but it is a 4th
generation challenge.
4 out of 6 people have retired.
What will happen to these 5 people?
The challenge of these 5 people is...
the first challenge of Nogizaka, the
Subashiri route.
Subashiri?
It's hard.
The slope is different up to the summit.
It's known as a course for experienced
people.
Both teams are going to meet at the 8th
point.
From there, they all aim for the top.
I see. They meet and go to the Subashiri
route.
The 30th single, Hitokiga.
Hitokiga, Hitokiga.
Last time, Banana Man told me to climb
Mt. Fuji, but I really climbed it.
I heard that Aruna has climbed Mt. Fuji.
I have the only climbing experience
among the five generations.
But yesterday, my mother told me that if
I lick the mountain, I will die.
Today,erica climbed the mountain.
After this, Okamoto's help was entrusted
to Ogawa.
A little before, the climbing team
started.
The first climbing.
The first climbing of Mt.Hikoi.
Fuji-san climbed the mountain.
I should have asked my senior.
How was it, Mr.Fuji?
Kawasaki, don't you do figure skating
and bodybuilding?
I did a lot.
American's
Amazing.
I've been training hard.
I've been feeling the difference between
the clouds and the sun.
I don't feel any difference.
What kind of clouds do you think it is?
I think it's a giant spider.
They're talking about something
different.
I heard that giant spiders taste really
good when they're fried.
I want to try it someday.
It's too crazy.
It's ouch.
The five of them have to climb the steep
rock face from the beginning.
There are a lot of luggage.
But they arrive at the first mountain
hut in two hours.
The sixth.
We're at the mountain hut.
It's the sixth.
There are about five of them.
I'm satisfied with climbing the top.
What should I do?
It's still the sixth.
Yoshida's team is at the starting point.
I think there are interesting members of
Maoh, Miku, Kansai and Kyushu.
When we are feeling down, we can help
each other.
We can make people laugh.
I want to go to the end.
Actually, before both teams left,
a person made a beautiful comment.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Manatsu Akimoto, the captain.
Since everyone is going to climb Mt.
Fuji,
I brought this hat.
This rock ball...
It says rock.
I climbed Mt. Fuji twice.
I'm going to climb Mt. Fuji.
This is the legendary hat I wore.
I hope you will take this as a souvenir
and climb Mt. Fuji.
Thank you for watching.
So, the legendary item is a good excuse.
The five people of Yoshida Route also
started to climb.
However, the members who started to
climb and started to go around the
mountain in full idol mode.
Even the mountain of Fuji is my
experience.
I'm the character of the play.
I feel good.
I'm going to be a very good actor.
I think Ichinose is a little crazy
recently.
I think I'm in the position of Kimoto.
I don't think I'm in the position of
Kimoto.
Ichinose, who was so excited, made a
mistake.
Oh, no.
You're a bad girl.
Yoshida and Ruto, who were able to relax
on a calm road, are finally on a real
slope.
The weather is bad.
It's time to decide the team name to
increase the speed of the car.
Have you decided?
We're the team.
What? These five are going to the top?
OK.
Let's go.
Mr. Daigo, you're light.
OK.
Now that the team is united, the five
members aim for greater heights.
Mr. Aru, you two go first.
Meanwhile, the running team continues to
climb the steep slope.
What do you want to do when you finish
the run?
Aya is waiting for the regular test and
the A-key test
She is doing something sad
And 3 hours from the start
They arrive at the 6th zone at a good
pace
They check the things they want to bring
to Fuji-san
A photo with Tamura, who Sugawara
respects
Ogaa introduces the birthday present she
got from Okamoto
What is the present?
This is called Spoo-chan
I bought this for my birthday when I was
one year old
I've been sleeping with this stuffed
animal every day
Good luck
Did you get wet?
I got wet
Wait a minute
Stop it, Spoo-chan
During a break in a calm mood
Kawasaki suddenly...
He is not feeling well
He can't move at all because of the pale
face
As a result of consultation with the
guide
He decided to take a long break here
The running team thought it was going
well
Will the five of them be able to
complete the challenge?
Slowly
Can you go?
Are you drinking water?
Yes
Where is it?
It hurts
Meanwhile, the five of Yoshida's route
Arrived at the seventh station in 3
hours from the start
Check out the things they want to bring
to Mt. Fuji
This time, they couldn't participate
The photo of the hamster of the pet
appears
Ikeda brought
Genjiro Tanigaki
We went on a national tour together
I want to be the highest in Japan
I want to be the most beautiful duck
It's sad if Genjiro is gone
There are 55 more
After this, the five people who took a
short break
failed to meet the eight people who were
scheduled to meet
, but the climbing roads from here are
even more harsh like the past
challenges.
The members who are struggling on the
mountain road for the first time in
their lives.
The members who are getting tired and
losing the ability to speak as a
standard.
Can I keep up?
The members who are losing their energy
quickly.
They can't get up immediately after
taking a break.
And...
A morning meeting
The altitude is going up, and the oxygen
is running out.
The altitude is going up.
The pace is getting slower.
The arrival at sunset is desperate.
But we have to go to the top of the
mountain.
I'm going to do my best.
It's a rainbow!
It's true! It's a rainbow!
A mysterious rainbow is coming out like
a rainbow.
It's amazing.
Will they be able to reach the top after
being fascinated by the magnificent
scenery?
On the other hand, the running team has
been stopped for about two hours due to
Kawasaki's health problems.
It's amazing.
They haven't reached half of the meeting
point yet.
They are climbing again little by
little.
But the rock wall is getting steeper.
The water is getting steeper.
They can't keep up with the pace.
That's the 7th hut.
Oh, really?
Is it long from the 7th to the 8th?
It's about twice as long.
Please don't tell the reality.
To be honest, the members' feet are not
heavy because of the staff.
It's faster to breathe than before.
Suddenly, I feel a lot of physical
strain.
The number of members has increased.
I arrived at the 7th mountain hut.
I'm going to do a sluice.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm feeling better than before.
I'm not as strong as before.
Kawasaki's physical strength has
improved miraculously.
Everyone's fatigue is approaching its
peak.
Kawasaki should recover his late
portion.
He is increasing his pace little by
little.
It's a little hard.
Take it easy, Yohan.
You can do it. You can't take one more
step.
Okuda is close to the limit.
Now Kawasaki is encouraging him.
I've been working hard all the way here.
I'll do my best not to let you down.
This is what I was looking for.
Five people keep encouraging the members
who are in pain.
What's the point of this?
Everyone is in a good mood.
The five people's bonds are deepened.
They somehow change it into the power to
move forward.
And then...
We did it!
We're on the eighth floor.
It's been 10 hours since the start of
the climb.
The running team finally arrives at the
meeting point.
No one has ever been here.
I'm glad.
I thought it might be dangerous on the
way.
Everyone encouraged me, so I was able to
cheer up.
Here, the five people are waiting for
the rest of the members to arrive.
Oh, I see.
In addition, they wait for the sunrise
at Yamagoya and reach the top of the
mountain from the next morning.
On the other hand, the five members of
Yoshida Route continue to fight hard.
The fatigue has already exceeded the
peak, and the limit is close.
Mentally, I can't afford it, and I can't
hold back my tears.
I'll do my best.
Why are you crying so hard?
Even so, the five of them stand up and
join forces again.
These five are going to the top!
The five of them are going to the top!
They are back on the road and are
climbing again!
But the sun is setting and the condition
is even worse.
Rain and wind are attacking the members.
But they are still encouraging each
other in the dark and somehow moving
forward little by little.
Be careful!
I have thought about it.
What?
The weather in Mt. Fuji changes very
quickly, doesn't it?
We were able to take pictures in a very
nice view.
It was in a flash, wasn't it?
That's right.
So, I think it was a miracle that we
were able to take the audition together.
That's right.
That's good.
What a good thing.
Nobisaka 46 5th generation was selected
from about 90,000 people.
To prove the miracle of the bond, they
went to the place where their friends
were waiting.
You're back!
Thank you!
You're the best!
And so, without losing a single member
of the team,
they successfully made it to the 8th
hole.
There are now members who leave their
worries to the captain.
They rest a little for the next
morning's climbing.
We finally met on the second day of Fuji
climbing.
Good morning!
A beautiful message came again for a萬全
Once again, there's a beautiful message.
Hello, everyone. How are you doing?
I think it's pretty tough, but I hope
you can feel the sense of accomplishment
when you climb,
There are things that you can only
experience on the mountain, so I hope
you can climb with your family.
Thank you for your hard work. I thought
it was a little hard, but I relied on my
fellow climbers.
I hope you all enjoy it until the end.
I hope it will be a good memory for
Furi.
I'm rooting for you from here.
Good luck.
I'm so happy.
I feel so relieved.
I got a message from Manatsu yesterday.
She had a hat and she did her best.
I haven't seen Endo for a while this
morning.
I thought I had to see a beautiful view
from the top.
Let's do our best.
The second day starts when the members
are getting more excited
after the seniors' cheer.
Thank you.
After checking everyone's condition,
the Takata team gives up at the same
time.
The team goes 3km from the starting
point.
The 5 members are feeling good.
Then...
It's good here.
The members who have worked so hard are
welcomed by the audience.
There is no Hina now, but 10 people came
here.
It's a great fortune to see Hina today.
The remaining five people will face the
five guests at the Yamagoya in the 8th
episode.
Looking at this from here, the view of
the top is a little...
I've never seen anything like this.
The five people of Yoshida Route are
also starting their second climb.
It's so beautiful.
It's amazing.
It's the Earth.
There were five people who were pushed
by the view.
But at that time.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Who is it?
It's only been 30 minutes since the
start.
What?
Ichinose, who was pulling the team
brightly, suddenly fell down.
I'm relieved.
Suddenly, the captain was captured and
tears stopped.
As a result of the game with the guide,
Ichinose acted differently from the
team.
From here on, each of them will go to
the top while consulting the captain.
The five-star mountain that has been
challenged by 10 people so far.
Can everyone get to the top of the
mountain?
The first team to go first finally broke
through the 9th.
From here, you have to climb the steep
rock wall that continues to the top of
the mountain with the last strength.
The first team to reach the top of the
mountain is the first team to climb the
steep rock wall.
It's about 10 minutes.
Five people have been supporting each
other until the end.
This is not a goal.
The team has been supporting each other
for two and a half hours.
Team Tsubashiri arrives at the 15th
section of the summit.
I'm so tired.
I'm sorry.
It's okay. You did a great job.
And the five members of the Yoshida
route are almost at the summit.
You have to fight against your own will.
Yes.
Are you okay?
Tomizato and Ioki, who were sick the day
before, are also trying to get here.
It's nice.
And, Ichino, who was doing something
else, is also climbing alone.
She did it.
Finally, the five of them meet in front
of the 15th tree.
I'm scared.
And...
I did my best.
You did your best.
The Yoshida team also arrives at the
summit.
Finally, all of them conquer Mt. Fuji.
I'm glad I did my best.
I feel like I've grown up a little bit.
I'm so grateful that everyone came here
without any trouble.
Thank you.
Then, here's a statement from the guide.
Everyone is here now because...
Actually, it's the highest mountain in
Japan.
The highest mountain in Japan is the one
you see in front of you.
So, if you want to see the highest
mountain in Japan, go all the way up
there.
Are we going?
That's far.
It's even further up the mountain.
You can go to the top, but it's really
higher.
It's really high.
There was a request from a badminton
player.
The captain of the mountain that was not
aimed at in the past two challenges.
KENGAMINE is the goal this time.
A shocking surprise.
Will he reach the real mountain?
KENGAMINE is aiming for the goal.
What?
No way.
How can we go on?
It's over.
We're going to do our best.
It's the last battle.
Both teams move their legs with only
their muscles.
They move step by step to get to
KENGAMINE.
They move their legs again.
But they are encouraged each time and go
to the top of Japan.
And one hour after arriving at the 15th.
I have never seen a mountain like this.
They continue to walk along the edge of
Mount Fuji.
They are back at the foot of the
Kengamine.
After that, the first residents of this
mountain range are gathered.
They climb the stairs to the top of
Japan.
They finally arrived at the top of Fuji.
ーIt was impossible without you guys. ーI
agree.
ーI thought it was impossible or the
limit. ー
ーEven though people think it's the
limit, they can go further. ー
ーThe first residents of Fuji ー
have confidence and such rap. We finally
came here.
Now we'll be happy even more.
Their dream Touch me from the top of
Japan!
Ready!
It's 30 episodes song called 〇uffs,〇k
1990.
We'll represent the first resident of
Fuji.
My heart has been broken many times.
But, they have been supporting each
other for many times.
They have won the first Kengami in
Nobizaka.
Amazing.
You did it.
How was it?
I was about to win the 8th round.
I was about to lose my mind.
But I didn't know I would lose.
You wanted to win.
How was it?
本当の頂上はもうちょっと向こうですって言われた時の When you were
told that the real summit was a little
further away.
イロハとか本当に心折れて I was so heartbroken.
その後一言も喋らなくなった I couldn't say a word
after that.
もう絶望感がすごくてもう動けない I was so disappointed.
オアとかも小さいのにさすごいな It was so fun.
楽しかったパターンの人いるんだ I can see some of them
had fun.
でもフェジトザンを終えて五季星の絆も深まったし I was able to
make a deep bond with the five-star
mountain.
本当に今回登らせていただけて良かったなって思います I'm glad I was
able to climb it this time.
いいこと言うな Don't say such a good thing.
これ岡本行きたかったな I wanted to go to Okamoto.
上がったな I'm glad I was able to climb it.
気持ちはみんな持ってってくれたからね Everyone carried me
with them.
この人数登ったら大体高山病何人かなっちゃう If I climb this
many, I'll be in the high mountain
disease.
絶対登れないその後 I can't climb after that.
登ってないから I can't climb.
木口ヒナ卒業セレモニーの配信チケットが販売 Kiguchi Hina's
graduation ceremony delivery ticket is
on sale.
マナット全国世話2021のジャケット写真が完成 Manatsu's
national news is the completion of the
2021 jacket photo.
Tension MAX!
Please subscribe to our channel!
Bye bye!