Ebichu's video!
Ebichu's video
Let's go!
I'm going!
I'm Kata Puda!
Be careful!
No, no!
I'll do my best!
I'm going!
We fazendo what there is to do
Let's skip it
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
Let's take a picture.
Let's go.
Cheese.
One more.
Thank you.
With love.
Please look at the end.
I'm just singing now, but I'm a little
nervous.
Thank you.
I'll do my best.
Are you ready?
Let's go.
Thank you.
Cheese.
One more.
Thank you.
Then, spielen it by which No! 1 band
Good luck to tabloid
saben
The reason why this Yatsui Festival was
decided is because of TVK's Kannai
Reveal.
Kannai Reveal?
Yes.
Yatsui-san came to play as a guest.
It was my turn.
At that time, I was announcing the
Yatsui Festival.
Oh, really?
Yes.
It's too bright, so I can't take a
picture of 3 out of 5.
Oh, that's right.
I'm sorry, Masa.
I'm sorry to say that I'm not good at
it.
Thank you very much.
Yatsui-san, I'm sorry.
I didn't have a chance to do it this
time.
Please listen to Masa Yabichan's live.
That's all for today!
We were ShizueBishou!
Thank you!
Thank you everyone!
Thank you.
It's hot.
It's been a long time.
It's been a long time since the last
time I went to a holiday festival.
The festival is over.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
The online festival was held last year.
That's right.
We performed there for the first time in
a long time.
We couldn't have a good time because of
the emergency.
We finally got rid of the stress.
We will do this again after a year.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
It was fun.
Last year, there were no guests at the
festival.
I'm glad you're here.
It was fun to be at the festival.
The music was also fun.
We were a little aggressive today.
We only played a few songs.
Some of you may have noticed.
We collected the five songs on the
playlist.
We tried each song.
The other two songs were amazing.
It was a fun song to play.
Everyone's reaction was amazing.
It was fun.
It was fun to play the song.
YATSUI said she liked jumping.
I was impressed by her jump.
I wanted to raise my hand.
So I told her to come.
But she didn't jump.
I met YATSUI before the festival began.
I met her.
I was about to dance.
I was so excited.
She did it with love.
But she didn't jump.
She didn't jump.
Everyone was like...
I'm sorry.
I hope you jump next year.
Please come again.
Whose message is this?
Fans.
Please tell YATSUI the story.
Please look forward to it.
Last year,
I did it because I was so excited.
The part where I said the line was...
I was going to do the original sound
source.
I was going to do it with everyone.
I was going to do it.
When I went to the live show,
I couldn't hear the sound source.
I stopped at the live arrangement.
We all did ad-libs together.
I was like, what?
I have a story.
So when I entered, I was told that the
Nikonama was dirty.
It's dirty.
That's what it is.
Listen to the music.
I want you to listen to the music.
It's dirty.
It's really dirty.
That was really fun.
I was really impatient.
The person who entered was cleaning, so
it was dirty.
It's dirty.
Please listen to the music.
I'm only crying.
It's dirty.
We have a lot of songs.
It's fun.
And the first person to see it is FES.
There's a family around that person.
The family is dancing hard.
We don't know.
How many people are watching us dance?
It's been a long time since I've had
that feeling.
That was fun.
Number shot.
It's a dome.
It's a pipe-a-dome.
I was really nervous.
There's a family in the summer.
I hope you enjoy it.
I'm always nervous about the set.
Let's sleep a lot.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's a dome.
We'll do our best in the summer.