Ebichu's videos
Rikonoheya, the second episode
How are you all?
Uruwa-shu
Last time, Mayama-san came to the guest
room
This time, the second episode, the
second episode
After the last episode, I was chosen as
Hoshina-san
I was chosen as Hoshina-san
I was chosen as Hoshina-san and came
here in a busy time
Thank you very much
This is the guest
Today's guest is lucky seven's Hoshina
Mirei-san
Thank you
Hoshina-san, in this episode, you ate
peyoung in Ebichu's videos, right?
That was the first time you ate peyoung
in Ebichu's videos
So, is there anything you haven't tried
yet?
Eh, I wonder
I think I've eaten Matsuya before
I think I've eaten Ushinoya before
Eh?
I ate it for breakfast when I went on a
tour
You ate it together
And it wasn't beef bowl at that time
It was a special breakfast
I ate something like that
And then, Sougyo curry
It became a hot topic
Sougyo curry was something I really
wanted to eat
I think I ate beef bowl
You didn't eat it
I don't think I ate it
I didn't do a food comparison
Everyone was saying what it was
But I didn't know what it was
I want to know the difference
Let's do a food comparison next time
Yes
The time has been decided
Really?
This year, I want to know about the
fashion and make-up that you're
interested in
Make-up?
Make-up and make-up
Recently, tint cheek?
Tint cheek?
Oh, I forgot the name of the product.
Let's remember the name of the product.
It's a Chinese cosmetics.
The package is like Sailor Moon.
It's a very cute package.
It's like Sailor Moon.
It's coming out.
It's a Chinese cosmetics.
It's a Korean cosmetics.
It's called Amuse.
It's a soft cream cheek.
The part where you put it on is like a
star.
I said Sailor Moon.
Where is Sailor Moon?
I recognized the part where I put it on.
The color is very cute.
What color did you choose?
I bought a coral color.
It's a tinted cheek.
I don't know how much it will be
applied.
I don't know if it's too strong.
I chose a coral color.
It's easy to use.
It's very convenient.
I recommend it to those who wear a mask.
I have to take it off sometimes.
I bought it because I thought it was
good.
Please check it out.
I'm running out of stock.
I don't know what kind of character you
are.
I want to say that there are many parts.
I said it a lot.
This is the first time I say it.
Is it a star?
I have a little information.
I will show you this time.
This time?
I recently released information.
I like chili.
I'm going to do a video of Momotachi.
I saw it online.
I was surprised by the unique product.
I was surprised that I knew about GUNMA
PASTA.
I said that GUNMA PASTA was famous.
I was surprised.
It's fun.
I thought that I might have been
familiar with the streets and the
specialties.
I thought I liked it.
I didn't know that there was such a
place.
Is it okay to say it for the first time?
I've said it before, but it's a good way
to say it.
I drink a lot of water, so I buy a lot
of water during lessons.
1L of water in a convenience store costs
about 160 yen.
However, a 2L bottle costs 120 yen.
It's better to buy 2L.
I don't need a plastic bag when I drink
a lot of water.
I have a good idea.
I heard a good thing.
I will buy 2L from now on.
I heard it before, but what is the name
of the actor?
I will ask the members one by one.
My name is YOLO.
It's a word that means once in a
lifetime.
I thought it was cool when I heard it.
I want to live to be 100 years old.
I want to meet myself every day.
I want to enjoy everything that happens
to me.
I remember this word when I'm lost.
I think about it once in a lifetime.
It's a word that helps me when I'm lost.
I'm impressed when I hear it.
I thought you liked it.
I don't have a word for it either.
I don't know.
But it's cool, isn't it?
I like it.
It was really cool.
I was talking in English with my eyes on
the seat.
Suddenly.
I was thinking.
Really?
I was surprised that something really
cool came.
Can I have it?
Please.
Let's do it together.
Our name is.
Y.O.L.O.
That's right.
MINE is a toy.
I haven't been there yet.
When I went on a tour.
I was wondering if I was interested in
this place.
I want to go to this store.
But.
I often use the tab log or hashtag.
I use the hashtag TOKYO GURUME.
I'm looking at those two and I'm happy.
I want to go to a ramen shop in Fukuoka
called Genki Ippai.
When I went to Fukuoka last time.
The store doesn't have a signboard.
It's on the first floor of the building.
It's a very popular store.
It's popular and there are no noodles.
The store is closed because of the
store is closed.
The store manager recommended it.
I want to go there.
But I'm not lucky.
I don't have a chance to go to Fukuoka.
If you have been to this store.
Please tell me your impressions.
I want to go there.
Please practice for me.
Please tell me your impressions.
What do you think is the best position
for you?
I don't know.
I think I'm in a position where I can't
change.
I think I'm an idol.
I don't think I'm a star without it.
I really liked idols when I was little.
I didn't have any consciousness about
idols.
I thought idols were like this.
But when I got older, I thought it was
okay.
When I got on the stage and was pushed
by the switch, the switch was turned on.
I think I'm in a position where I can't
change.
I think that's what I'm doing now.
I like you.
Thank you.
I like your impression.
I thought you were an idol.
But I really like idols who are on
stage.
I was pushed by the switch.
I like you.
But I'm usually like this.
It's a gap.
When I say that I have an idol feeling
on stage, I say it in a cafe.
It's cute.
I like that.
This time, the guest was MIRUHA HOSHI.
Thank you.
Who will come next time?
Please look forward to it.