Yakan and Aizuku
It's an early ending.
Thank you very much for today.
Did you have any regrets?
Please see this.
This is an announcement from the Atten-
shou team.
Our 4th album, 9th anniversary, will be
released on October 19th.
As the title says, this album is a team
of Atten-shou teams that are packed with
Kyushu and Matsuri themes.
Please check it out.
We will have a live performance on the
26th of October.
The title is Matsuri Tawagi, Odore
Kokoro Tawagi.
We will have a live performance for the
first time on Nakano San Plaza. Please
come to see us.
We are waiting for you.
There are many things to see.
Please look forward to it.
Aizuku, I'd like you to drink tea from
me.
Is that okay?
I'll drink tea.
It's hot.
I'll drink tea and get ready.
Really?
I'll drink tea.
Would you like some tea?
I called you before I got the
announcement.
It's delicious.
Thank you.
I'm glad I got the announcement.
I'd like you to drink tea.
I'll definitely meet you.
Thank you.
How was it today?
I talked to the innkeeper.
Do you also go to the sauna?
I like the sauna, but it's popular these
days.
I can't say I like the sauna.
I don't know if there are rules.
I'd like you to tell me something.
Let's go to the sauna.
I want to go.
I'm blue.
Where do you usually go?
I don't know.
God.
I'm ready.
I feel great.
The innkeeper and the idol.
I'd like to thank you for the
announcement.
Thank you.
I'm AI KIOMO.
I had a lot of fun talking to the
innkeeper.
I'm full of these three.
Please try it.
Please enjoy the
nature and sauna.
Thank you.
The next day.
I'm MOSHINA MIREI.
I'm YUZUKI HACHIKO.
I thought it was a strange combination.