The nightclub and idols!
It's very important, isn't it?
Yes, it's really important.
I'm an idol who works in Kyushu,
so I think there are people who think
it's difficult to come to Kyushu.
So I think it's a very good environment
for those people to talk equally.
Do you have any people who watched your
stream and referred to it?
Do you have any favorite streamers?
I'm a little too much, but...
Basically, I like people who are playing
games,
and VTubers.
When I'm on my phone all day, I watch
videos of streamers on YouTube.
Are you interested in VTubers?
Yes, I am.
I've never been a Vtuber,
but I've always liked anime characters.
I like that anime characters talk with
their own characters.
This is different from voice actors.
That's right.
Maybe I'm already a Vtuber.
Maybe.
It would be interesting if I had a real
face.
I think there are many genres of VTubers
that people who like VTubers like.
If I have both sides,
VTubers will also watch it and think,
Oh, this person is playing it in real
life.
I think it would be interesting to play
it.
That's what's on the air.
I think it's a place where I talk about
what I like.
There are many parts that I can't talk
about.
When I'm on a live show, I talk about my
life as a Vtuber.
I don't talk about my life in that way.
I want to see you without the emitter.
There are some places where I talk about
my life.
I want to make a Vtuber character.
When people watch my live show,
they say that I have a different image
from Seta.
If you have a different image, please
check the live show.
I'm going to show you my morning
routine.
Good morning, everyone.
I'm Airi, the crown pop artist.
Today, I would like to show you my
morning routine.
I'm going to take a morning routine.
I was very happy when I heard that.
I saw a lot of YouTubers doing morning
routines.
I wanted to try it.
I don't have a chance to show it to
everyone.
I was very happy.