But you know, Mei...
Is she a
Eh? A boyfriend?
No, I don't think she's a boyfriend
Eh, seriously?
She doesn't have a boyfriend.
She pretended to understand and cried.
I'm going to ask you about the
interview.
You were in the same dormitory, right?
Mei was a part of the Paradise 2 group.
It's a gang parade.
Originally, it wasn't a complete split.
We were divided into two groups and did
a little bit of activity.
At first, I was shocked and panicked
when we decided to split.
I thought I had to do it.
I couldn't convey the fact that the gag
parade was over.
I was left with a future I didn't know
yet.
I was very happy that I could still do
it.
We haven't been able to go on tour for a
while because of the COVID-19.
We have a live performance in August
1st.
It's like a revenge party.
Are you having fun losing?
No!
Are you serious?
We're going to win!
Go!
I think that's the problem.
That's right.
Actually, that's right.
I'm sorry.
But you can talk about anything.
What is this?
Did you participate?
Yes.
Very funny.
What was the timing when you did the
100th time?
After the tour was over.
After that?
I was blinded by Effect!
Did you have a cold there?
Was it so Boude it made you frown
because it was too spicy?
I don't think I was spicy overwhelming.
I don't think so
But I've never been so spicy
I was like, is it going to be tough?
I was like, it's not a bad thing.
It's amazing.
I want to find the meaning of what we
do.
I was in a hurry because I thought I had
to find it.
How did you feel when you heard that you
were going to have 200 concerts?
Is it really possible?
I heard that.
There was a little conflict after
announcing 200 concerts.
What is it?
You want to meet them?
That's difficult.
I think I should have checked all of
them.
That's a little...
Thank you for watching.
What should I say?
Think by yourself.
I can say everything.
Then I'll do this.
Yes.
I was told,
I said yes,
I shouldn't do that.
I realized that I shouldn't think about
more than that.
Did you actually imagine that you could
do 200 on the way?
I believed in that and I said I would do
it.
I remember the season of our farewell
And again, I remember the season of our
farewell
I was like, I can't do 200 anymore.
I was like, I'm gonna do my best.
I don't think I could do it alone.
How do you feel about the Ego-recon?
How is it?
I'm going to tell you something that I
don't think I can use.
It's not about following the history,
it's about how to tell your partner's
story.
It's about how much the interviewer can
tell you about it.
You're not gonna say it, are you?
I'm gonna say I can't say it.
I was pretty upset on the way.
So I was like, enough.
I thought you were gonna spread it.
But you didn't say it, so I was trying
to figure out how much you'd hate it.
Did you feel the Ego-recon?
I was just getting angry.
What's your opinion about the Ego-recon?
I think she's gonna ask about the
history.
I don't think it's about the history.
I don't care about the history.
But I think you should tell your partner
not to get caught.
I think you should tell your partner not
to get caught.
I pretended to be stupid and gave up
I can't see the full star