A night time idol.
Thank you so much.
Next, we are going to play some music at
the basement!
And…
T-That's the third one!
Sleeping!
I can't sleep without it.
Really?
I want to sleep when I have a break.
You really like it.
You need it for your body.
Yes, I need it.
When I'm tired, I need it to recharge my
energy.
For example, I need it for anime, manga,
or games.
I need it to cheer me up.
I can sleep for 15 hours straight.
Do you have a favorite item, like a bed,
a pillow, or pajamas?
Yes, I do.
I'm asking you.
I like pajamas because they are light
and stress-free.
I don't know if I'm touching it or not.
It's like a pajama for old ladies.
Old ladies say they can't sleep well.
And they say their bed is heavy.
I want to wear pajamas like old ladies.
No, you're making my dream bigger.
You're old ladies.
I want to wear pajamas like old ladies.
I want to see it someday.
I want to wear flashy pajamas.
Flashy and stress-free.
I want to buy those pajamas.
I got a cover of a bed sheet from my
sister this year.
I'm going to sleep with it.
What else do I care about?
I have a bad sleeping habit.
Really?
You have a bad sleeping habit.
I'm a type of person who sleeps with a
bad sleeping habit.
So, I sometimes can't sleep at home.
I think you're thinking about a lot of
things.
Is that true?
I think so.
I move my head without my permission.
I can't sleep if I think about
tomorrow's schedule.
You're a bad sleeper.
I see.
I have a special skill.
I want to hear it.
I think everyone sleeps in a bed.
There is a bed.
This side is a pillow.
Then, I sleep with my head turned over.
I see.
I sleep with my head turned over.
I sleep in the opposite direction from
usual.
I can sleep well if I change my mood.
Please try it.
No.
I'm really doing the same thing.
Really?
I'm changing.
You're changing.
I'm told to sleep with my head turned
over.
But, I don't mind.
I feel good.
I think so, too.
I think you can't sleep.
But, you can sleep well if you change
your mood.
Do you understand?
I do.
That's your special skill.
I've never heard of it.
I'm a bad sleeper.
I think it's the first time for you.
Please watch again.
I thought it was a samba.
Is it a sound of a body?
No.
What kind of sound is it?
Is it a sound of a body?
No.
This program is
Lion-san, Kakkoii-san
Takashi-san
Meteora-san
Kanna-san
Lisa-san
I sent it to you with the offer of
Masaki-san!
Today, I'm going to put in some bathing
solution and slowly soak in the bath.
You can try it out! Bye-bye!