Let's move on to the next one.
OK.
The last one.
What is it?
I don't know.
I'm excited.
I didn't know about this game.
I'm announcing the ranking.
What is it?
I'm the fortune teller.
You did the face without asking.
I don't want to be told which photo is
the one with a strange face.
You were the first place last year.
Did you have a good thing?
Good thing?
I'm happy every day.
It's you.
You were the lowest in the fortune
telling.
I was told that I would be happy.
I did my best.
I was told that I would be lucky.
I was told that my ears would bring luck
to everyone.
Thank you.
This year, I'm the fortune teller of the
expert of the eye-catching.
I'm the face fortune teller of Eichi
Ikebukuro.
Rankings are from 7th to 10th place.
Finally, the person who is the most
miserable.
I want to be in the top 3.
I hate the top 5.
First, the 7th place is this person.
The person who is the most miserable.
I have a thick lip, so I'm very fond of
it.
The reason why her front teeth are big
is that she has a strong vitality
I've seen it
The other day, I had a cold in my nose
in Saitama
She had a great recovery power
She recovered quickly
The winner is
Mayama's 2016 fortune is this
It's pretty bad
Ruhiro-kun, 8 points
I can't hide it anymore
I'm going to show my girl power
You're convinced, right, Tomo-chan?
Yes, I'm convinced
If you don't, it will be closer with
penopets
The teacher comments
You can uncover yourself and luck if you
don't forget to try
Try and say it
Yeah, grasp confidence like that
This is the person in 6th place
6th
The invisible ears connected directly to
the sides of face
It has a strong sense of caution, quite
easy to ignore
Wow
Thank you for watching!
She has the best face in the world.
Wow, she has a strong face.
But, indeed, indeed.
Here is the detailed fortune of 2016.
Wow, amazing.
Riko, you have a good balance.
If you can show your personality by
watching yourself, your work will be
appreciated.
However, you can be a beauty queen, so
be careful not to overdo it.
What does that mean?
It's not good to say that you don't want
to do it to a member of 7-11.
Then, I'll do it to Shiro.
Studying is 6 points.
What is your goal for 2016?
I used to hate it when a makeup artist
did my hair when I woke up in the
morning.
I thought I had to dress up and wear
fashion properly.
I've been wearing heels lately.
You've been wearing heels a lot.
I'm going to do my best.
Good luck.
The fifth person is...
This person!
Oh no!
Bye bye!
Wow, I thought you were going to say
something like,
I always thought you were going to say
something like that
She has a strong image and a strong way
of thinking
She has a strong belief and is very
active in her life
That's great!
And she has a high nose, which means she
has a high ideal
But, Rina, you have a goal of being a
high-minded person
I think you are perfect for that
I'm so happy
If you become more high-minded, you will
be able to talk more
I'm going to be able to talk more
What?
You are going to be a man in front of
the TV
Here is the detailed fortune of 2016
What?
You are going to be a man in front of
the TV
No, I'm not
You are not studying for that, you are
studying for something else
I'm studying for my life
You have a long nose, which means you
have a tendency to forget small things
in the past
You will be lucky if you relax
Can in the morning, I lot of time in the
hotel
You should not be so self-conscious
I'm self-conscious
But, you are more like that on the day
off
Yes, I am
I'm always somewhere on the day off
I'm always playing
Because you are a man
I hate being at home
I don't like the feeling of being bored
I want to see the schedule
Do you dare to take a rest?
I'm self-conscious
But, it was good
The nose pickup was great
You were a very attractive nose
We are KINISHI
Who are the people who are not here yet?
I'm the first
The fourth place is
Kobayashi Kaho
I'm relieved
The roundness of the nose and the
glossiness of the nose are good
So, you are lucky
You may be a female entrepreneur in the
future
I'm the female president
The nose is sticking out to the side
It means you are lucky
You may write a novel like Matoyoshi P's
I'm a teacher
Here is the detailed fortune
The study luck is good
I'm a female teacher
I was studying to improve my self-
confidence last year
I'm a female teacher, but I'm not good
at studying
Do you have any feminine talents?
No, I don't
I have a lot of bad luck
When it rains in the morning, I buy an
umbrella and get sick when it's over
I have a lot of bad luck
I get sick when it rains
I bought an umbrella
You're good at it. You're good at it.
If it's Kaho, I can think of everything
as Kaho
Sounds good
In that sense, I'm lucky
Anyway, Kobayashi's nose is the best
I will challenge something new, so I
will go around the office with money
Wow, that's great
I don't like nose
Your nose?
Like this
Cute
My mom said I have good eyebrows.
I love your eyebrows.
I've been getting better lately, so my
nose is like this.
That's right.
It's a good luck.
You have to cherish it.
Make it more glossy.
It's good.
I'm going to miss you.
Thank you for watching.