2 minutes later
I was told to fill in 2 minutes, so I'll fill in 2 minutes with Nono, Ema and
Yuna.
What should I say?
I'm Ema Terai from Shiritsu Ebichu Junior High.
I'm Yuna Nakamura.
I'm Minonoka Kato.
I think I should have said this first.
I'm sorry, I forgot.
I'm Ebichu.
Nice to meet you.
Ema and Yuna joined us in October and became a full-time student.
How do you like Ebichu?
Ebichu has a strong personality and a great performance.
I suddenly became a Japanese person.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm always like this.
I see.
Ema is always natural.
How about Yuna?
Ebichu is a very kind sister.
She's a kind group.
Did you say that?
She's a kind sister.
She teaches us a lot.
We're all junior high school students.
Yes, we're junior high school students.
We're about to graduate and there won't be any more energetic junior high school
students.
We want to do our best as junior high school students for the next few months.
Let's keep bringing out the real junior high school students.
We just finished the free demo on the 17th.
There are many new free demos and live performances.
I'm looking forward to it.
I think we should have done it a little later.
I'm doing my best on the free demo.
I'm doing my best on many things.
Please support us.
This was Shiritori's Miss China.
Bye bye.