We're in no time.
The three newbies were
the usual group of teachers,
Koshiyogi Kobayashi and Nakayama.
I'm not going to be the teacher today.
I'll be the teacher.
When I want to create a different
atmosphere,
I often get a chance to teach a
different teacher.
I want to teach the teacher how to play
the instrument.
I want to teach all three of them how to
play the instrument.
Koshiyogi is not only an educational
staff,
but also a dance manager in Ebichu.
She has a big mission.
I haven't seen so many people in a
while.
I'm going to make this while I'm still
in bed.
Thank you.
You're absolutely welcome.
I'm basically the one who doesn't have a
teacher.
This is a dance formation arrangement by
Koshiyogi.
Ebichu is a song that Koshiyogi herself
was in charge of,
and the song that the choreographer
himself was in charge of.
As the dance director, she checks the
choreography and formation.
I'm worried.
Why?
You guys.
Yes boss.
The boss is so nervous.
He's nervous.
So, you know...
Do you know?
The members whose names I've mentioned
so far are
Kanji, Mayama,
Kaaho, Riko, and Mire.
And the new member is Hiragana.
I'm the only one who said B.
Which one is B?
The one from the boss.
B.
That's because they're auditioning.
They're looking at the new member
candidates with sharp eyes.
But the new member's eyes and the new
member's name are from the new members.
The girl from the band, Kina-chan, is
the most scary.
Kanyuji is now the dance director of
Kashiwagi, who was adored as the
shrimp's tail.
And...
Yes boss.
They've climbed to the top of the boss's
seat.
The boss's singing lesson starts now!
The song they're going to sing is...
The song is from their latest album
released in 2019,
Omekashi Fever!
It's a difficult song with a lot of
unique movements at an up tempo.
Please remember your own dance.
Yes.
Now, go to the side.
Dada dada dada dada dada.
And then.
Two times.
And the other side.
Dada dada dada dada.
And then.
And now, move your right leg to the back
leg.
And then.
And now.
When you are done, put your right leg
behind your body.
When you reach out your hand,
hold your left hand and put your right
hand behind your body.
Do your best to focus.
and then make some noises.
Thank you for watching!
Then...
I'm sorry.
I did a unnecessary act.
There is no such thing.
The lesson is given by the boss,
Kashiwagi.
She made a mistake in the chorus.
I'm sorry.
I'm not good at teaching people. It's
hard. In the song, there are many songs
with different choreography, different
angles, and different directions. So I
check the video and practice one by one.
I'm human, so I make mistakes. So I make
mistakes and tell the truth.
I'm sorry, I was on the right.
The choreography varies depending on the
member.
Of course, the teacher needs to put all
the parts other than herself in her
head.
In other words, the dance director is a
very important role that can't be done
by just remembering what you've learned
so far.
I'm sorry. I really lied.
YUNA and KOKO are on the opposite side.
KOKO is on the opposite side.
I was on the wrong side.
YUNA is on the opposite side.
Please step out and fix your posture.
Please dance from the beginning to the
end of the second chorus.
Check time by KASHIWAGI.
Here we go.
I'm not good at it, but
I'm good at it, I'm good at it, I'm good
at it
I want to dream
in the wind and in the rain
Please, please, please
Come on!
Thank you for watching!
The hand that wants something is...
What was it again?
It's a turn.
This is the foot.
Sorry, I can't do it.
1, 2, 3, 4.
Put your foot out like this.
Open your mouth.
And then...
Like this.
Thank you for watching.
Put your hands together and put your
feet together.
If you follow the same speed as before,
you can't catch up and the swing will be
lost.
So I try to do it one by one.
If you punch here,
your arms will be left over.
Put your hands together.
If you put your hands together, your
arms will be like this.
They are very polite and polite.
Kobayashi and Nakayama, who were
watching the swing,
support the boss.
Hey you!
fend over...
110th anniversary
One more time, again!
I'm fine, I'm fine!
I'm not going home yet.
The boss kashiwagi's lesson overflows
with fun rather than strictness.
But she has this feeling.
I think that the choreography is very
difficult because I use my head a lot.
I used to be like that.
So if you can do it with fun from the
beginning,
I think it's best to have more and more
choreography.
She does a full swing of about 5 hours.
Thank you for watching!
it iskehr also somehow exceeded
work
I wonder if it's okay.
We're going to have a performance
tomorrow,
so we can't dance with these people.
So, please check the video and
put the choreography and lyrics in the
video.
That's all for today.
Thank you for your hard work.
Boss Kashiwagi's lesson is over.
But, the blog of this day...
The boss's unwavering comments...
...are a source of anxiety for the new
members.
But what about the new members?
They're very easy to listen to.
They're very kind.
They know that you have to close the
door.
We're going to meet for sure.
We'll do our best.
The pragmatic sis-in-law Kashiwagi,
the encourager,
the three із았ittedu of boca-to-mouth
acquaintances continues!
Thank you for watching!