AHM moons Nice
Well
Once
linking
I'm not a final test, but I thought I
could only take this test because of my
age.
Wow!
Thank you...
It smells like the sea.
The sea.
Especially in summer.
When we all gather, we go to the beach.
We can go swimming,
or we can go looking for sea glass.
This is the sea in front of my house.
I'm playing with my dad, or is it a
stone picker?
I don't know because it's so far away,
but he's like this.
He's like a man of the sea.
And this is the one fishing for
blackfish on his dad's boat.
This is my brother.
I will read the name of the book.
The moon that rises in the night sea is
very beautiful and mysterious.
I wrote this book with the hope that I
would be a beautiful woman.
Thank you for your support.
The title of the book is 海がつく.
I have a cousin who is the same age as
my father.
Both of them are 海がつきます.
I love princesses.
Among the princesses, I love Ariel.
I wanted to be Ariel.
I used to shave my hair with a fork.
I didn't have any dreams when I was in
elementary school.
I wanted to go to the city, not to the
countryside.
This is the Shinnin-enoshima Aquarium.
I grew up by the seashore, so I decided
to come to the seashore in Kanto for the
first time.
I came to see the jellyfish in the
aquarium because it is called the sea
fish.
I was surprised by the amazing view of
the aquarium.
Wow, it's huge!
There are so many!
Amazing!
I was surprised.
There are many different kinds.
What is this?
It looks like a sea cucumber.
What kind of fish do you like?
I often see flying fish in the sea.
Wow!
There are so many!
Interesting!
My father is a fisherman.
He comes back from fishing for various
fish in the summer.
I'm like a man of the sea.
In the summer, it's pitch black from
April to May.
I walk for about 30 seconds and there is
a sea.
It's not unusual for me.
It's right there.
I used to like idols, and I watched a
lot of videos on YouTube and TV.
I just liked watching them, and I
thought they were cute.
But after I started to like them,
I think it was about a year later,
I saw the audition for the second
generation of Hiragana Kiyaki.
I really want to take the audition.
I took the audition for the second
generation of Hiragana Kiyaki.
I failed the second trial.
I was able to get a good result.
This is amazing.
This is cute.
I was able to get a good result.
I've never seen a jellyfish like this
before.
Wow!
This jellyfish is a little bigger than
the one I just showed you.
There was a time when polyps were in a
hurry.
Then a small Ephyra fairy appeared in
the video.
It's a little bit like a flower.
If the Ephyra fairy grows bigger, it
will be like this.
When polyps were first found, they were
usually 2-3 mm.
Really?
This is what we found.
This year, we grew up with earwax.
I watched the kids who passed the
audition on TV.
I thought, I can't win against them.
If I had these kids, I wouldn't have
taken the audition.
I felt so frustrated.
I had two auditions.
One was a high school audition.
I couldn't do well in all of them.
I thought I wouldn't be able to do well
after I became a university student.
I really thought I would do it if I
could apply for the last test.
I thought I would do it if I could do
it.
I thought I could only do it.
I've been dreaming of this slope for 5
years.
I don't know what to do with this
strange feeling.
I'm very excited.
There is a place called Megane Museum in
Fukuie.
People who like glasses wanted to go
there.
A friend of my college friend said,
I'm from Fukuie.
I was excited because there was a Megane
Museum.
What should I do?
One mitarashi dango.
One matcha.
Can I have one more?
One kinako, please.
One kinako?
Thank you very much.
It smells good.
This crab is also very small.
There are crabs, right?
They move around.
The crabs are coming out.
Is it scary?
It's trapped.
It's like me in the middle of a break.
Did it move?
Now, I will announce the final
candidates.
I've been saying I'm an idol for five
years now.
I'm an idol.
No.1, Hiraoka Mitsuki.
I'm really an idol.
I really wanted to make my dream come
true.
I really wanted to be an idol.
I want to do my best even if my body
breaks.
I was waiting for the coffee to fall.
I was happy when I got the pass.
I couldn't believe it right away.
I was so happy and I felt so relieved.
My mom was so excited.
She told me to go home as soon as I
fell.
She said she was relieved and relieved.
My mother and I talk to each other every
day.
I often get a picture of a cat from my
family.
Please take a note.
Thank you very much.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Thank you for watching.
Can I?
Yes, please.
Congratulations to Mi-chan.
You made your dream come true after a
few years.
You're cool.
Effort always pays off.
You proved it with your own power.
But this is not the goal.
This is the starting point.
Hang in there.
I'll be rooting for you.
If you're having a hard time, call me in
the morning, in the afternoon, or in the
evening.
To Mitsuki.
I never thought I'd write a letter to
Mitsuki from my dad.
But I did it because it was like a
dream.
I'll write a letter.
I've been working so hard.
I've been building up one by one with my
own hands.
As the name suggests,
I hope that the group will continue to
shine while I shine.
And I will continue to cherish myself.
I'm Miyu Habatake, a fan of Miyawaki
Nanakoro.
I love you so much.
I'm happy.
I want to keep surprising my parents
more and more,
and I want to keep surprising them.
I'm Mitsu Hirooka, 20 years old, from
Fukui Prefecture.