Night time and idol
The second element
The second element?
Yes
Game
This is
There are two
I couldn't fit in, so I put them
together.
If you really like it, you can put three
It's actually four different things.
I wanted to do it, but I thought I could
do it together.
What kind of game is it now?
The game I'm playing now is a long time
ago.
Didn't you have DS?
DS? I'm glad to hear that.
I love DS, DSi, 3DS.
I love it.
You can play games on your smartphone or
PC.
And both are really beautiful.
The graphics are really beautiful.
I'm worried about the capacity.
It's really beautiful and it's a very
high quality game.
And there are many things you can do for
free.
My favorite game is Project World
Colorful Stage Feat. Katanemi-kun.
It's a sound game.
So the character grows and gets items.
And you can play a lot of cute
characters.
Do you play games all the time?
Yes, I play games every day.
I see.
It's hard to play with a script.
That's right.
I'm lost.
It's hard.
That's right.
I like it, so I can't help it.
But I can't help it.
Do you do any manga?
Oh, yes!
I'm the type of person who reads manga.
The type of person who reads manga.
I see.
Well...
I'd be happy if I could.
Oh, really?
I don't really write manga, but...
It's a little difficult.
Oh, I see.
So I'm trying my best to read it.
Do you read it in a e-book?
No, I don't read it in an e-book.
What?
Really?
I definitely want to have it.
You definitely want to have a book?
Yes, I like book covers.
Oh, really?
Do you have a book cover?
Yes, I do.
Oh, really?
I feel like I'm going to fall off the
floor.
You feel like you're going to fall off
the floor?
That's a dream come true.
You're such a girl.
Yes, I am.
I've heard from people who like anime,
games, and manga.
You've done work like this before, on
stage, and stuff.
Do you do any work like making a voice?
I don't do it.
Do you want to try it out?
I love 2D, so I want to be able to put
my soul into 2D.
Oh, I see.
But I'm worried about whether I can do
it well.
You like idols, right?
I like them, so I'm worried I might
break them.
But I want to try it out.
You want to try it out?
Yes.
I see.
I want to try it out.
What is the reason you are wearing a
mask?
It's around the Sky Tree.
I see.
I always tell my mom to watch this anime
and that anime.
I see.
This program was provided by Okoyan-san,
Haster-san, Nano-san, and Ikeppe-san!
Thank you very much!