Ebichu's videos!
What was the most difficult part of the
dance?
There were many songs that I've never
done before.
At first, I had a hard time.
There were many parts that were
difficult to practice.
I listened to the choreography and the
dance to the members.
I was able to absorb the dance.
The dance lesson was hard, but I was
looking forward to it.
What was the most difficult part of the
dance?
There were three people in the group.
We showed the dance to the members.
We had many parts that were difficult to
sing.
We were able to do it well.
At first, I was nervous.
But I was able to do it well.
There were only three people in the
group.
But we were able to show the dance to
the members.
The second part was difficult.
I was the most nervous.
I was afraid of singing the high notes.
I asked the teacher to teach me.
He said that I could do it.
I was able to sing the high notes.
I was very happy.
What was the most difficult part of the
dance?
I was very nervous.
I think the people who came to the dance
lesson will understand.
I was very nervous.
I was smiling in the second half.
I was nervous from the beginning.
But I was able to express the feeling of
the stage.
I was able to express it from the
beginning.
I was like, I did it!
I was excited, excited, and nervous.
I had a lot of emotions when I was on
stage.
But I was like, I did it!
I was like, I did it!
I was so happy to be on this stage.
I think I did better.
And the fans were very high.
I think I was able to appeal to the
people who were higher up.
I want to be able to appeal to people
who are like a hair on and a dirty eye.
I used to be a dancer.
I was a jazz dancer who was good at jazz
dance.
I was a little short and had a different
expression.
I was a little different from the usual
dance.
I was a little different from that.
So I was happy to be able to show that.
Before I joined the team, there were
only non-member members.
I watched a lot of videos on YouTube and
I thought they were cool and stylish.
I thought they were artists.
But we are fresh.
We are refreshing.
We are different from the 6 of us who
watched the video.
We are very fresh.
We are idols.
We are very bright.
We are very good at being dyed by idols.
We are very different from the 6 of us.
I think there are many things that can
be adjusted.
What is your favorite song?
I have never done a song that I have
never done before.
I did a lot of muscle training.
I was impressed that Yuno had a good
muscle.
What was the most difficult?
I was most worried about the unit song.
Yuno, Naho, and Maema did it.
I was happy to sing the song that I like
the most in the music video.
I was happy to sing the song.
I like all parts of the song.
I was thinking about how to sing the
song.
I watched the live video of the past.
I was nervous, but I was more nervous
than at the debut live.
I was nervous that I would do it.
I watched the stage for the first time
on the day of the rehearsal.
I thought that I would be better if I
did it.
I was not sure if I was good at singing,
but I was good at making a good sound.
I went to see a doctor.
He said that I was getting better on the
second day.
I was happy.
It was the first time I had a one-man
live on such a big stage.
Thank you for watching.
When we were on the big stage,
the members of the family wrote to me
about the color.
I didn't know the difference between
green and light green.
When they gave me the color, I thought
it was this color.
I thought I was looking at the color
right.
I thought so.
It was fun.
It was like, it's over.
It was a moment.
At first, it started with the song, I AM
ONLY YOU.
And it ended with the song, Any Time Any
Where.
When I was singing Any Time Any Where,
I thought I was singing only the song, I
AM ONLY YOU.
It was an hour and a half of live
performance.
It was a moment more than the previous
F.C. event.
After the university concert,
I couldn't do anything
because I was so tired.
But even after two hours of live
performance,
I was still energetic and I couldn't go
home.
It was the first time I felt like that.
I think I gained some stamina without
the F.C. event.
There were a lot of songs that were
raised
such as Kichu Puri and Omekashi Puma.
I thought it would be better if I
listened to those songs more.
I thought I could show my own style more
easily.
There were a lot of songs like Hot Up
and Iroza Omedama.
I think it was a song that everyone was
excited about.
When the flame came out,
the fans said it was hot.
My mom said it was hot.
I think I can do better if I get used to
the heat.
I think I can do it.
I felt it a lot.
I thought I could do it.
I felt like I had to do this.
I think we all have our own spirit
and we have to follow it.
I talked to the members and talked to
them.
After rehearsing, lessons, and live
performances,
I think we got closer.
It was a great success.
I think I was able to do a lot of things
in the middle and high notes,
and I think I was able to do a lot of
things in the high notes,
so I think I was able to do a good live.
I think I was able to do better than
Haru-chan in the next spring tour
in the next spring tour.
What was the most difficult thing you've
done so far?
There were more songs than before,
so I had to learn songs for the first
time,
and I had to fix the songs I had done in
Akita High School,
and the formation changed a lot.
I think I had to do about 5 or 6 songs
at once,
and I was really confused at that time,
and I couldn't remember the 5th song at
all.
I was really worried about everyone,
and I cried for the first time.
But I didn't want to cause trouble,
so I was able to do it myself by
confirming the formation I had come
before I put in the formation.
I think that was good.
I thought it was over,
and I felt like the members of the band
were all united in the end.
I thought it was a good live
performance,
so I was happy when it was over.
I had a lot of things to do before the
live performance,
such as shooting for the live show,
and I imagined the live performance on
the day of the live show.
I was surprised that I had so many other
things to do.
Thank you for watching.
It was really hard, but I was able to
make time to calm down and relax.
I remember drinking honey in honey.
I think I was able to concentrate better
because I had been performing for a long
time.
I practiced hard to show my body and
dance to the highest of the audience.
I focused on showing my dance to the
audience.
I was able to get confidence.
I have a lot of shake shake formations.
I practiced singing and dancing at home.
I was able to show my dance to the fans
who came to see me.
I was able to show my dance with
confidence.
I was able to see the penlight from the
bottom to the top of the stage.
I was able to see so many fans coming to
see me.
I was very impressed by that.
I was impressed when I first saw the
scenery of the family in the middle of
the stage.
I think it was the first time that I was
shown to the audience at a live show.
I was able to perform in the middle of
the stage.
I was able to perform with singing and
dancing.
Until now, when Hina-chan was on leave,
we were still three new members.
I think I've seen a lot of people with 6
plus 3.
At the university conference, I got a
lot of comments that I felt like I was
the first to have 9 new members.
There are still a lot of skills and
things that are still different.
I have to keep up with the other
members.
I think I was the first to show a live
performance with 9 new members.