It's hot!
I'm going to fall in love with the night
view!
The night view is the best!
Please subscribe to my channel!
What is the element of Shirahama-san?
Do you want to read it yourself?
The second factor is the game!
Kachikachikachii!
Ah, sorry. Kachikachikachii, are you
okay?
I made a mistake.
That's right.
I'm playing a game.
I'm quite into games, like Switch.
I've been playing DS since I was a kid.
You know DS?
I know.
I have a sister.
I'm playing DS with my sister.
I was having fun with each of them and
communicating with them.
I've been playing games since I was a
kid.
I'm into Splatoon these days.
Yes, yes.
But now there's a 3.
I don't have the courage to buy a 3.
You're brave.
I'm saving money.
I don't have the courage to buy a 3.
But when I saw the ads,
Splatoon 2 and 3 have been evolving a
lot.
I thought I'd buy it if I heard about
Splatoon 3.
I'm thinking of buying it on Christmas
in December.
I see.
Do you have a 2?
Yes, I'm really into Splatoon 2 now.
Really?
Yes.
But everyone goes to Splatoon 3.
Is that true?
But I don't have any Splatoon friends.
You don't have any Splatoon friends?
Yes.
I'm sorry. I forgot.
Who is it?
I want to ask you.
Who forgot about you?
I forgot about the member Aoyama.
I'm sorry.
That's good.
I said I don't have a friend.
But
It's been 3 years.
NANO-chan
Before I joined BOLT
She was my best friend.
We were good friends.
We played games together.
We played Splatoon together.
We played recently.
We played together for 3 years
The first round was on a ship.
We played together on the ship.
We were communicating with each other.
3 years ago
I had just started playing
We lost in the game.
Now I'm in the opposite.
I won several times
I won the game and I was so frustrated.
I was like, let's do it again.
I see.
You won the game and forgot that you
were a friend.
I'm sorry.
What do you do when you're bored?
I do almost everything for my friend,
Nanaha Aoyama.
What do you do when you're bored?
This program is provided by
Maki
Aoyama
Korari Kashishi
Chabu
These are the gifts I have for you.
Please come to the live show of Bolt
again!
Thank you!