Good evening everyone, I'm Sakurai Yuma,
16th place
Good evening everyone, I'm Yuna
Nakamura, 17th place
The other day, the new members of Ebichu
were finally revealed
Sakurai Yuma and Nakamura Yuna
The new members of Ebichu, Nakamura
Yuna, and Nakamura Yuna
The two of them performed at the
audition camp this time
They will show you the special singing
scene before their debut
And
Also becoming a hot topic on live
broadcast...
A non- painters analysis of have a huge
outcome.
The first part of the audition was...
We will now do a test using Karaoke.
Please play your best song.
Karaoke Test
The two new members performed their best
with nervousness in front of the staff
and the members.
First of all...
I'm Emma, 14 years old. I'm going to
sing Marigold by Aimyon.
Emma chose her favorite karaoke song,
Marigold by Aimyon.
The wind is strong, it shakes my heart a
little
I miss you who looked at me seriously
You are shining in front of me
I'm happy
You with the hat look like a swaying
marigold
That is the sky is still blue, the
summer
The love of that day that I laughed at
Don't leave me anymore
I'm looking at you with tears in my eyes
With a gentle cloud-like warmth
I'll hold you tight and never let go
I, I, I love you
I don't have enough words to say, so
kiss me
The clouds still leave their shadows
I'll never, never let you go
I won't let go of you forever and ever
Thank you very much
Next is
I'm Yuna, 15 years old
I will sing Yorushika's Tadakimi ni Hare
Yuna chose Yorushika's Tadakimi ni Hare,
which she thought was the best fit for
her voice
I remember you from that summer
The dry hands on the night
The scent of summer stroking my cheeks
Until I become an adult
I'll keep smiling and sleeping
When I'm tired of playing
I'll look up at the sky with my birthday
cake
Even if the moon shimmers
I'll surely, surely remember
I'll become an adult without being able
to catch up
The night blooms in your pocket
I can't say it out loud, I'm alone
If that's okay, I'll give up
Thank you for watching!
Please subscribe to my channel!
Thank you very much.
The precious first performance video of
the two new members
How will their singing grow in the
future?
Please look forward to the first live
performance of the new members at the
end of the year
The special performance video of the new
members
masters of
l Coop
Nice!
Thank you for watching!
It's time for the audition
The members of EVY-TU who are familiar
with Karaoke are gathered on the stage
I'm not a problem!
I'm a problem!
And they will choose the song that they
can sing together
So
I'm looking for a girl with glass shoes.
My Lord, that's me.
Please make a contract with me.
Please make a contract.
What should I do to make you turn
around?
benz
Thank you for watching!
Please look at me only
Oh, oh, please
Please sign a contract with me
Are you looking at me?
I'm looking at you
I'm going to write a story with my shoes
on
And throw them away in the trash
Ah, the spell has been broken
I may look like an adult, but I'm
actually a kid
Ah, dreams don't end
I'm going to become a princess
It's not just a game
I want to be a princess
We have to dance more before midnight
If we love the night, we can't see the
number of hearts
Let's dance with a smile
Please, let's dance
Let's dance
Let's dance until the night comes
Hmm, not yet!
Yes, good job!
Good job!
The program went on with the
I feel that life has changed and it has
been a good four days
Next time, Emma and Yuna will return to
the dormitory