Ebichu's videos
I'm Rika Mayama, the third place.
I'm Aka Yasumotai, the fifth place.
I'm Rei Nami, the fourth place.
I'm Rinata Kashiwagi, the tenth place.
I'm Kaho Kobayashi, the eleventh place.
I'm Niko Nakayama, the twelfth place.
I don't know.
What's going on?
I know.
What?
I got it!
Don!
Totsugimasen!
That's it!
I think I got it.
Close!
That's so close!
That's a win, isn't it?
I think I'll get 0.5 points.
This is...
Kanbei!
No way!
What was it?
It's different! But it's the atmosphere!
Maybe it's right!
It's right!
The answer is...
It's totally different!
Yeah!
The same!
Wait!
Isn't it crazy?
It's totally different!
ifs...
Us going because
really
Lee
This for
It's totally different!
There's a lot of them!
Let's listen to the rest later.
Let's listen to it and calculate it.
This is amazing.
This is a good question.
It's interesting.
The answer is...
Wow!
Which one was it?
This is...
Wow!
Wait, wait, wait.
Mie-chan, Mie-chan!
I wonder if it's the opposite.
The answer is...
Yay!
I got it right!
I want it!
It's perfect!
Wow!
Yay!
So, it means that you haven't seen the
video properly other than me and Mie-
chan.
I saw it!
The answer is...
Yay!
It's a solo song!
Solo?
Wait, this is hard!
I don't know!
Tokushima?
To be continued...
I don't like it.
Hinata?
And Mirei.
I'll do my best to get all the questions
right.
I'll do my best.
Let's conquer.
The second challenge.
What is this?
What?
I can't remember at all.
Well...
What?
Wait a minute. I don't know.
Wait a minute.
I don't know.
What?
There was a Koroe.
No, it's not.
It's not Koroe.
What is Ebi?
It's not Koro.
Oh, my God.
What is it?
Really?
What?
I just need to write down the number I
like.
It's easy.
I just need to write down the number I
like.
It's difficult.
I wrote down the number I like.
It's not a song.
Yes.
Ta-da!
I'm going to write down the number I
like.
It was close!
I did it!
It was really close!
I did it, but I couldn't get it.
It was like a box.
Go! Go!
It was strawberry.
It was a strawberry.
I don't know this one.
I don't know.
If you watch the music video, you'll
know.
I think a lot of people don't know this
one.
I want the family to do a quiz later.
Q. What is the name of the person who is
the most likely to be a ghost?
A. Akiyama Rina B. Akiyama Ayaka C.
Akiyama Ayaka Rina D. Akiyama Ayaka Rina
A. Akiyama Ayaka Rina B. Akiyama Ayaka
Rina C. Akiyama Ayaka Rina D. Akiyama
Ayaka Rina
Wait, I'm not here.
Where was it?
I'm not here.
Do I have to write kanji?
I was shocked when I heard that everyone
was still at home.
I couldn't go home.
Everyone at the party gave me a seat.
I'm sorry I couldn't write kanji.
It was too late to go home that day.
It was the next day.
I was late.
That's right.
The next day.
The driver also thanked me.
The next day, I went to Akita.
That's right.
The next day.
I'm not sure.
Ready, go!
Wow!
Wait, I'm amazing, aren't I?
I can see it.
I didn't ride it, but I know it well.
I'm not sure.
Oh, that's it.
But Kaho, this is...
Kaho, it's not the same key.
Isn't it?
That's what I want to say.
Right?
What's the code for that?
I don't know.
0.5 points.
Is that right?
Yay.
It's the best.
Mie-chan is the best.
Great.
Evengreen
This is Mayama, right?
I went to the photo book.
I don't know.
I wrote a name I didn't know.
It's like a Taiwanese singer.
Wow!
Cha-cha-cha!
See you!
The answer is different.
I'm totally different.
It's difficult.
It's totally different.
I said Chaya.
9 minutes.
9 minutes and 3 seconds.
It's totally different.
It's a different answer.
Maya is correct.
But my kanji is different.
Yes, my kanji and Maya's are different.
So let's have a judge judge this later.
Yes, yes.
That's right.
The kanji is different.
There are too many judges.
I'm a judge.
I'm usually a judge.
Why?
This is not a shrimp-filling problem.
What does this mean?
It's not a shrimp-filling problem.
I don't know.
I don't know the answer.
I can only think of this.
I don't know.
I think the answer is the same as Kaho.
Is it two letters?
I don't know.
Wait a minute.
OK, I'm done.
I don't know at all.
It's different.
Oh, that's what it is.
I don't know.
It was a problem between Jean and
Ebichu!
It's a shrimp kiss question.
It's totally different.
I'm sorry.
I'm not the best at this.
I'm so embarrassed.
I'm embarrassed.
It's not a big joke.
I'm just trying my best.
Miren is amazing.
It's a good thing to have you.
I'm embarrassed.
I don't know.
What was the name?
Extra?
I remember my name, but I don't remember
the name of the person.
Tsuchiya has too many manga motifs, so I
don't know which one.
I don't know.
You don't know what Tsuchiya-san is?
I don't know what manga is.
I don't know what Tsuchiya-san is.
Is this a hiragana?
I don't know.
It's a hanimin.
It's a manga motif.
What's your name?
I don't know.
Let's go.
Thank you for watching.
I don't know.
I can't get the answer.
I see.
Let's take a look.
Riko's Doraemon is young.
First of all, there was a name called
Doraemon.
Shizuka and...
What?
Who was Doraemon?
I don't know.
Oh, okay!
How many surprise marks do I have to put
on this circle?
Is this right?
Wait a minute.
Hinata is good at song-related
questions.
Yeah.
I think it's okay, but it might be
wrong.
I wonder if there was such a question.
Huh?
There are three questions.
Isn't it 3, 2, 1 from the top?
3, 2, 1?
Maybe from the top.
It's the same.
To be continue...
No!
2 years old!
It's totally different!
It's different!
Riko, you're amazing!
Riko, did you have it?
No!
I'm happy!
I guess it's because you're a fan.
Riko.
That's right.
That's amazing!
I'm happy!
I didn't know that I was so surprised.
I thought so!
I'm glad.
You're cheering for us.
That's right.
We'll be with you forever.
The next day
100,000 light years is a long time.
I don't know.
Somehow?
Something like this.
Ta-da!
2 points!
What is it?
A clock?
Isn't it amazing?
I don't know how big it is.
I don't know.
Even if I get it right, I don't feel
like I'm getting it right.
I don't know.
That's amazing.
Which one?
I don't know. Let's put it here.
It's a photo album.
It's the yellow one, right?
Yeah, it's the yellow one.
It's the 5th anniversary of the major
league, right?
Is that so?
I don't think so.
It was a solid photo album.
Take a picture of me.
One, two, three.
No4 was the smallest.
If you got it right again one question
point becomes expensive.
See you next time!
Finally, we got the right answer.
Yay!
We went to the country of elephants,
right?
Did we go to Chiba?
We went to the country of elephants.
Chiba City Zoo.
Zoo?
The country of elephants.
Zoo is not a country of elephants.
Chiba City Zoo.
Chiba City.
I think it was Chiba City Zoo.
We went to a family restaurant together.
We went there.
We went to Chiba Station.
It was fun.
I remembered that.
Finally.
Congratulations.
It's a crazy-like question.
I can omit the conversation this far
because I can't be born an Asian
anymore.