I say yes, but I don't get it.
I don't like me being
Excuse me.
I'm going to do it.
Oh, no.
I got it.
What the-
Hello...?
Hellooo?
Hello!
Hello last flirtatio
Hellooo
Hello
, eh, eh, err?
Who are you?
Who are you, hey, yeah!
Ah!!! Let me think!
Thank you very much ammo
Hinata
Ohno
Hello?
What?
Do you need a hint?
It's been a while since we last met,
right?
Yeah, it's been about two years.
I don't know.
What?
I'm the same age as you.
I'm a middle school and elementary
school classmate.
I got it!
I'm glad.
You don't really know.
Yeah.
It's been a while.
How are you?
I'm fine.
I'm glad.
When I hear you on the phone, I feel
like your voice is different.
Yeah, but you don't feel that different.
I feel like...
I was nervous until just now, like when
I'm doing Ebichu.
I was like, hello? I was thinking about
doing it.
But I was more nervous than I thought.
Yeah.
And...
When I said hello, I was out.
I'm out of the frame now.
It's okay. Please do it like that.
Yeah.
I don't really call in the first place,
either.
That's right. Because I'm pretty...
Well, I don't really call...
You're not good at it?
No, I'm not good at calling.
You know,
when we meet,
we always talk about recent things.
That's right.
I think about it again,
but I don't remember much about when we
got close.
Really?
I'm sorry.
I remember.
Really?
That was the most refreshing thing that
could happen in 1998.
I really don't remember the old days. I
don't remember the time when I was a
child.
What?
Tell me!
I showed it to me!
Show me!
Let me remember it!
There is an article called ーBe Judith ー
When I was in elementary school, I was
bullied.
I was bullied properly.
When I was bullied, I was alone.
I was being together with my classmates.
I see.
I was bullied.
Do you remember?
I remember very well.
ーBe Judithー
ーYou couldn't say it? ーYeah.
ーBut you're doing something very
carefully.
ーIt's normal to be with friends.
ーThat's the image I have. ーI'm happy.
ーI'm about to cry. ーIt's okay.
ーWait. It's too early to cry.
ーEat more. ーI'm so happy.
ーSo...
Don't laugh at me!
Well...
After I got into junior high school,
I was pretty active in elementary
school.
But I was bullied because I didn't have
a good sense of
being noticeable.
That's right.
I was bullied because I was not good at
being noticeable in elementary school.
It's not bad.
Thank you.
You were always by my side.
After I got into middle school, we
became a club.
That's right.
That's the beginning of my otaku life.
I often see your otaku life.
But is it my fault?
Yes.
You and me, Yuckey.
Yes, yes, yes.
Nagisa-chan and so on.
That's right.
That's how it started.
But I really thought it was okay.
Really?
So I joined the art club and we were
together more often.
Yes.
When I was in elementary school, I was
bullied.
When I said something, he said,
Yeah, that's right.
But I was trying to stand out.
I was like, you're bad too.
You said that?
I did.
Really?
I was like, really?
But I didn't have any friends who would
say that.
Even if you're not from the same family,
you're really not Italian.
I regret it so much.
Really?
But I was really grateful for that.
I think I've been hurt by people without
knowing because I don't have any
delicacy.
I'm glad that there are people who say
that when I grow up.
But it's not bad to stand out.
No, no, no.
It's not bad at all.
Well, it's a detailed story, but when I
entered the agency, I was told to dance
in the class.
Oh, yeah.
And I was bad at dancing, but I was
dancing.
Yeah.
He said, I didn't say no to that. You're
bad, too.
But I think it was really the same.
I can't say no to that.
I can't say no to that. But if I had the
courage to say no, I would have been
able to get along with them sooner.
I think I can feel that elementary
school students were better for me.
But really, thanks to you, in elementary
school, we were together at the
automatic meeting.
Including that, I think I was able to
get along with them.
I was having a hard time in the
classroom, but
I had a lot of fun when I got to know
the school.
I'm glad to hear that.
I can't get back to elementary school.
That's true.
I'm talking about my old days.
I remember that.
I've been to a special event.
I mean, a free event.
I've been to a free event.
You don't remember, do you?
No way.
I haven't been to a special event.
When?
Cinderella in a temporary contract.
Cinderella in a temporary contract?
Kawasaki?
I don't know. You can see it from
behind.
What? At Korakuen?
But I don't know even if you tell me.
Why?
I don't remember.
At least remember that.
I don't know.
But I saw it from behind.
I remember it was a bit far from my
middle school classmates.
If I was a bit more mature, I would have
been in the top class area of the C.D.
But I didn't have that kind of
knowledge.
I would look behind me and think,
I'm doing it.
You'd think I'm doing it.
Yeah.
After that, I finished and
I sent an email on the way home.
stuff
I actually saw it today, but I'm glad. I
sent an email.
I remember the email saying, why don't
you say it?
I don't remember at all. I'm sorry.
I don't think you remember. I don't
think it's a place.
But I'm glad.
That's a good memory.
How was I at that time?
But that's a cute costume.
Really?
It's typical idol costume.
I'm impressed.
Really? I'm happy.
I was surprised by her back.
She was cute.
You didn't see my front.
No, I didn't.
But I saw her back.
But she didn't notice me.
I thought she didn't notice me.
Did you make her sad?
No, no.
I'm glad she didn't notice me.
Really?
I'm glad you did.
But you came to the concert a few years
later, right?
Yeah, I was invited recently.
Recently?
Didn't you say it was recently?
About two years ago.
About two years ago?
I haven't seen you much.
I don't know why.
I'm sorry.
Once, when I had a special offer, I
bought a scholarship, so it was a lot of
fun when I got hit by Ebichu's Taiwan.
That's true.
I texted you when it was announced. I
thought you'd definitely go.
I had a lot of fun.
I'm glad when I suddenly appear in my
own life.
I'm saying that I watch it every week.
That's right. I'm sorry, but I haven't
seen it in a while.
I'm sorry.
I thought it was the most enjoyable.
I'm watching it normally, and I'm sad
about the farewell with Jishu.
Suddenly, when Ebichu said,
Next is my part time job, I was like,
What?
Seriously?
And I actually had a ticket for the last
event.
Oh, I see.
So if it was held,
I would have to be in the audience seat
the whole day.
That was dangerous.
I'll watch it. I'm sorry.
Thank you for watching.
There are many things that happened in
the past.
There are many things.
I had a thing about Matsuno.
Did I say that?
I met him for the first time after that.
He is a family member.
Oh, I don't know.
Really? You didn't know?
Where were you going at that time?
I don't know. How many years ago? Sorry.
About a year ago? Maybe it was at that
time.
But it's pretty unexpected.
I'm spending most of my time in school
or in school.
I didn't go out with anyone.
I was lucky to have a friend who could
go out with me.
I see.
I was very grateful.
It was like a
mother to my daughter.
We are the same age.
We are the same age, but we are in good
care of each other.
I'm so happy to report that I can handle
it myself.
I'll listen to you when I have
something.
I'll do my best to be a good person.
You're the only one who says that.
That's not true.
Wait, I'm about to cry, so stop it.
Really?
I'm crying.
Don't cry.
But, you know, I was in college in 2019.
It was hard.
It's been hard since 2018.
I went to an educational training.
I'll go back to what we talked about
earlier.
You invited me to a music festival,
right?
I thought it was unusual and it looked
fun, so I went.
I've never been invited so I thought it
was unusual.
I'm always embarrassed.
I always said it like I was relaxed.
But it was really fun.
Really?
At that time, we didn't have much time
to talk.
That's right.
So I was really relieved that I couldn't
say it properly.
But it was really good.
What?
lol
That's what I used to do.
I used to watch it from time to time.
I used to watch it when I was about to
debut,
or when I was about to join the agency,
or when I was about to become a
producer,
or when I was watching the special
edition.
I used to watch it occasionally.
And it was a day of celebration.
And you were the person who was there
from the beginning.
I really ran through that.
Thank you for watching.
You don't always say such passionate
things.
I want to say it.
I don't know what to say.
I'm sorry I didn't think of it at that
time.
I think it happened and it comes
gradually.
So our live was a little bit of a type?
At that time, the music press was
already there the next day.
I'm glad.
I was able to get it back at a great
time.
Well, it's hard to...
Especially my local friends...
Yeah.
I'll show you how I've grown up.
Even if I say my hometown, I was born
and raised in Tokyo.
I guess so.
I was worried that I wouldn't be able to
do it.
I was really nervous and anxious that
day.
But I was glad to see my friends
watching me like that.
I was happy to see them watching me from
the back of the dressing room.
I'm glad.
I sometimes watch them taking pictures
of me when I get home.
Really?
Yes.
It's kind of embarrassing.
I'm embarrassed.
I thought I shouldn't have said that.
I was given a good present, and I was
thinking about working hard from now on.
I'm sorry I didn't say that.
Thank you.
I was talking about Nacchi in Ebichu,
and I was so happy to introduce you to
my friend and best friend.
I was so happy.
I'm glad I was able to say that today.
I'm glad. Thank you.
I'll invite you again.
Please visit again.
At the end of the year.
I see.
I remember talking about the song, but I
also watched the first take.
It's amazing. It's easy to understand
the song, so it's probably better.
Elchu's song.
Really?
I also heard a new song.
What was it?
The one that's coming out from now?
Any Time?
Any Hour?
Yeah, I heard it.
No way! We just heard it yesterday.
Why are you asking me first?
I got this information from the
information center.
Really?
I'm confident.
It's nice. It's bright.
It's a tropical mecca for nine people.
Yeah, it's a tropical mecca.
The cool thing I just heard was cool,
and I like the atmosphere of a little
older person in their 20s, but it's
bright and shiny.
It's nice, isn't it? I feel like I'm
getting better.
So, the other day, I was...
九人シングル? 青い衣装のやつもさ。 エアホンライオットだ。
あ、そうそうそう。あれもすごい明るくていいなって思うし。
あれだよね、青い衣装似合うよね。
え、本当?初めて言われた。 本当に? 青いのいいなって思った。
ずっと紫だったからさ。 あー。
エビ中の衣装って色んな色があってさ、あんまりこう青...
, 着る機会って割と自分が個人の時に青とかないから。 青いのもいいし、あとすごい
マニアックなんだけど、ショートブーツがお似合いだなって思った。
本当にマニアック。 いやでも本当ありがたいありがたい。
良くない時は良くないって言って。
良いと思ったら良いって言ってくれるの本当に無理し。
でも私もう大人になったからもうちょっと分け前って行きたい感じはしますよ。 そう?
うん。
I see. I'm lonely.
Really?
I don't think it's bad in front of me.
I might get hurt.
No, it's okay. Your mental strength has
improved.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
I can solve my own problems myself.
You can solve it. You've grown up.
Yeah.
Oh, no.
I was so young.
It's okay. You should still be careful.
Yeah.
You should've thought of it differently.
I want you to go. I understand.
I'm soaked.
That's good.
That was fun.
It was fun.
I didn't know you could talk on the
phone for so long.
I can talk.
I can do it.
I'll do it.
Let's do it. Let's really do it.
Let's do it.
Let's talk. Really.
I'm glad.
It was fun.
I'm getting sleepy.
Are you sleepy?
Aren't you too free?
Thank you very much.
Then I'm going to sleep.
Good night.
Bye bye.
That's kind of me in a way.
It's gone.
I'm a little lonely.
It was a very good time.