It's started! Ebi-chuu-tastasu!
This week's Ebi-chuu-tastasu is a
leisurely walk
Everyone is eating!
A private ship is moving
Start with a walk special
Please subscribe to my channel!
I'm so into you
What should I do with my heart?
Monotrium, monotrium, monotrium
Middle school students, monotrium
Add various things to private Ebisu
middle school
Ebisu middle school class
I want to do it
This program is brought to you by these
sponsors.
It's raining
Why is it raining at this time?
I wonder
I'm the most curious about this, Hirota
Before we start, there's something we
have to do
What is it?
Here, something has been handed over
Here it is
What is it?
Toots Yummy translates to bizarre
Wait a minute, let's organize the
schedule
What's with the 7th season?
It's the 7th season
It's amazing, we never celebrated it
before
We never celebrated it before, but we
finally celebrated it on the 7th season
7th season is a mid-term show
We've grown up
And, we're going to shoot in the room
Why are we shooting outside?
Today is the special episode of the 7th
season
We're going to shoot at the Kameido
Why Kameido?
It's Kameido
It's been a lot of championships, so I
thought it was dangerous
Badminton was out of balance
We have to fix it
We're going to fix it
Ebichu Tastas started in April last year
It's been a year and a half since the
start
We've challenged various projects
This time, we're going to try something
new
We hope the show will continue
To the Kameido of Gachaoji, Ebichu
Tastas Kameido
Let's move on
So we came to Kameido Umayashiki in
Koto-ku
Kameido Umayashiki
This is not a time slip, is it?
No, it's not
It's not
It's a motif of a house
I see
It's a good place to take a picture
I know
What are we doing today?
This time, we are going to take a walk
in Kameido town
We did it before in the mini-corner
Have you ever been to Kameido?
No
Have you ever been here?
No one has been here?
I've never been here
You've never been here?
Do you know where Kameido is in Tokyo?
For example, if you were in Tokyo
This is Ebisu
Yes, this is Ebisu
There is a mole here
A mole is Ebisu
If a mole is Ebisu
Kameido is...
Which is Saitama, Kaho?
Saitama is...
Is it this way?
Saitama is around here
Saitama is here
So Saitama is below Tokyo?
It's not below?
Saitama is getting lower and lower
Do you know where is above Saitama?
The clouds above Saitama
Oh, I see
You learned it
Where is Ebisu?
Where is Saitama?
It's strange
They can't reach Kameido
So they changed the topic
Hoshina, do you have anything you want
to do in Kameido?
I came to ask Ryo if he is here
Ryo is not here
What's wrong?
That's Kameari
I know
I know it's Kameari
Kame is wrong
What's the most embarrassing thing?
Being caught by Nakayama
It's so embarrassing
We are not in the same line
They can't continue talking
So they start walking around Kameido
Before that, they will divide into teams
Team Divide
We will wait for a while
The first team is
Mayama, Hirota, Hoshina, Masuno
Please line up
And the rest is
What's that?
By the way, there is a standard for
dividing this team
It's called car lane
The team that doesn't get drunk and the
team that gets drunk
The car will be divided into two teams
I see
The car that is stable
The car that smells
The smell of the car will be the first
one to be killed
So, the two teams will be divided
The leader will decide first
The leader will decide
So, the team that doesn't get drunk and
the team that gets drunk
They will decide the walking leader
The leader has been decided
The leader of the team that doesn't get
drunk is
Hoshino
Why?
Because she is the most free
Free
I want to go to many places
Good luck
Team 4
Kobayashi
Why is Kobayashi?
Because I get used to the city
You get used to the city?
I think she will look good in a cameo
I see
She will be a cameo girl
The leader has been decided
They are finally leaving
Each team will be divided into the west
and east side of the cameo
They will take a walk in the west
First, they took a walk in a car
They went to a shopping street
They asked what they want to do in this
walk
Let's play tag in the park in the rain
That's good
Ann in Nakayama is usually a bad person
I want to do that
I want to go to a cheap place
Where?
I don't know
I don't know if it's there
I have an image
It might be there
It smells good
Let's go in
Let's go
Who wants to go?
They go in with the smell of freshly
baked bread
It smells good
Wait, the sausage looks good
It's a special curry bread
It's freshly baked
There are many kinds, what do you want
to eat?
I've decided on curry bread
Kashiwagi curry bread
Freshly baked
I'm curious about this
Ham and cheese, croissant
Croissant is here
Among the leaders
Did you choose?
I did
Excuse me, do you have any
recommendations?
I thought you wanted to eat the bread
This is the Ancha Batta
This Ancha Batta is the first one
Ancha Batta?
What is that?
The most popular one is
Ancha Batta with a lot of bean paste in
a soft dough
Yasumoto-san, please try it!
I can't eat red bean
Are you kidding? I asked for your
recommendation
Wait a minute, I can't eat red bean
because you asked for my recommendation
It's popular after Anchan butter
Is there anything?
I want this, I'll try my best
Curry is bitter
I think it's better not to ask
You can't ask
Vegetable?
I like vegetables
That's good, let's buy this
Is it freshly baked?
I'll buy this
Italian vegetables
Looks delicious
I'm hungry
I want to eat
Margherita is coming
Wait a minute
It looks delicious
It's freshly baked
It smells delicious
Let's eat together
Let's buy one and share it
That's good
One and share it
After all, they buy one of their
favorite bread and one of freshly baked
Margherita
Thank you for watching!
It's raining heavily, so let's eat here
You suddenly changed your mind
I'll follow you, Master
Don't be shy, standing side by side
It's like a scene in Totoro, five people
are lined up
It's nice
Let's eat
Where should we start from?
Everyone is eating already
Let's eat
It's delicious
It's crispy
How about you, Yasumoto?
It's delicious
It's spicy and has a strong pepper
flavor
That was a good comment
It's good to have a food report like
that
How about you, Kashiwagi?
It's crispy outside and chewy inside
Are you a food reporter?
I'm talking with curry on my mouth
It's a tea-like taste
It's cute
Next, Nakayama
What is this?
It's like a cake
It's like a chocolate
It's delicious
It's fun to eat from crispy to sweet
It's fun to change the texture
Thank you
How about you, Kobayashi?
Look at this crispy texture
I want to eat it
I ate it already
I'm not good at it
Are you okay?
You made it yourself
Look at this crispy texture
You can't feel the crispiness
Let's eat this
With mayonnaise
It's good
It looks delicious
It's hot
It's like cheese
It's really hot
It's good
Yasumoto, everyone wants to eat it
Don't eat it
You're eating Kashiwagi
Nakayama started eating it
Yasumoto, let everyone eat it
Don't eat it
Everyone wants to eat it
Don't say that you don't know the taste
Thank you for watching! Please subscribe
our channel!
Kobayashi-san, the leader of the
walkway, found something
It says recycling, so it's a very cheap
shop
We have to go!
I think my dream will come true
Let's go!
Cheap shopping is the best!
Thank you!
I can see the price of 105 yen
105 yen?
Isn't it great?
It's very cheap
Before we go inside, we should get
permission from the leader
Please go inside
I'll go inside
Excuse me
This is a program called Ebitu Tastas
This is...
Where do you want to go?
Let's go to the next station
Let's go
There might be something over there
There's a cake
Looks delicious
There are so many good things
Happy birthday
Hey, hey, hey
I got permission
Why are you trying to go without
permission?
I was surprised
That was good
I forgot about the rain and came here
Let's go inside
Let's go
This is a fashion shop with 17 stores in
Chiba and Tokyo
They sell cheap items for only 105 yen
Yasumoto, you wanted to come to a cheap
place, right?
I wanted to come
How is it? It's actually cheap
It's cheaper than I expected, I'm
surprised
Since it's cheap, let's do a matching
battle
Matching?
It's 105 yen for a coat
Cheap
It's not like this
Face the camera again
Okay, let's buy it
Do you want to be filmed?
Let's start the matching battle
Ready, start!
It seems that the matching battle has
started
It's a coat bag
It's cute
Should we think about the season?
Yes, we should
Ayaka-chan, you didn't wear this
This dress
I didn't wear it
It's cute
Yasumoto, you bought it here?
It's my first time wearing it
This dress is cute
Let's look for it
Let's take a picture of it on our blog
Wait, you're pretending to be a regular
customer
Please subscribe to our channel!
It's my first time
But
Wait, I have this!
I found the clothes I have!
Honey! Honey!
Furthermore
I have this too!
Why do you have that?
Is it really the same one?
It's the same one!
Then, it's a regular item!
It was this tag!
As expected, it was a regular item of
Tanpopo House, Yasumoto-san
Why?
After this, the members will be shown in
their cheap outfits.
The winner will be decided.
The cheap outfits battle that started at
a fashion recycle shop.
It seems like the shopping is over, so
we'll announce the coordinates.
First, Kobayashi-san, the walking
leader.
Kobayashi-san, please.
Thank you.
The theme is...
The theme is a girl who looks like she's
in Kameido.
A girl who looks like she's in Kameido?
Yes.
By the way, what kind of image do you
have of Kameido?
Kameido is...
It's like this.
It's like you're going to hit the
patterns?
I see.
I'm not sure what Kameido is like at
all.
But Kobayashi-san!
Yes?
The total price is...
420 yen!
No, it's not like we're doing a
competition or anything.
Huh?
It's not a competition, but 420 yen is
amazing.
Isn't it amazing?
How is it? Are you confident that you'll
win?
I want to win against my teacher.
You're all very conscious of Yasumoto.
I'm a fashion leader.
What about Yasumoto? Is he good at
fashion?
He's good. He's really good.
Please be quiet.
Don't say it yourself.
We're listening to you.
He has a similar style to me.
You have a similar style to him.
Does Yasumoto like Kobayashi's style?
No, no, I can't see the answer.
You can't see the answer?
Next, Kashiwagi-san's lecture.
Here we go!
Thank you very much.
You all make the sound by yourselves,
right?
I thought it would be better to say it.
You are silent.
Yes, I am silent.
What is the theme of the rental car?
Co-operation.
What do you mean?
I chose it at first.
I came here once.
It was hard to find a place that fits
here.
So, my manager chose various things for
me.
So, it's a little different from the one
you chose at first.
It's different.
So, it's a co-operation with your
manager?
Yes, I'm almost a manager.
Really?
So, you didn't choose a rental car.
But I chose it.
Really?
Yasumoto is also good at fashion.
So, I don't want to lose to him.
I don't want to lose to Yasumoto.
Is Yasumoto good at fashion?
Yes, he is.
Yasumoto is good at fashion.
Here comes Yasumoto!
What's the theme of this?
The theme is the feeling of the season
The feeling of the season?
No, nothing
I took the winter first
You took the winter first, because it's
still October
It's a little hot
It's a little hot, isn't it?
Yes, it is
How do you actually wear it?
Oh, yes
In the summer
No, in the winter, it's like this
It doesn't change much
Oh, really?
Because it's a regular fashion here
I had a lot of clothes I had
And finally, Nakayama-san's outfit
Here is Nakayama-san, please
Here you are
Me?
This?
It was a set, 3 sets
Since you have some left, let's make it
a set
You gave me the rest
Oh, good
It's perfect
Let's go with this all the time
What's the theme of this?
Well, Halloween
I see
I decided on this at the very beginning
I decided on this
You started from here
I started and chose clothes
I thought this is my true self
So, you matched the color of this and
the T-shirt?
Yes, I did
I started from the top
You decided from the top
Wow, I'm getting bored of this
I thought it's embarrassing
I chose it myself
After seeing everyone's outfits, they
decided to win
Let's go!
Dome!
Yasumoto 2, Kakayama 1, Chuuei 1
The winner is Yasumoto!
Wow, amazing
How is it, fashion leader?
You suddenly became arrogant
I made a big mistake
I'm over 1,000 yen, even though it's so
cheap
It's almost 2,000 yen
You spent a lot of money, so you are the
winner
I'm going to win without any complaints
You are the winner, after spending so
much money
You are saying such a humble thing, but
your face looks happy
I'll be on the show
After enjoying cheap shopping
once again make aияium?
This time the fashion show was very
exciting
Here, Kashiwagi-san
Hey, there's a bun cha, let's eat it
Really?
There is
It's true
Where?
There it is
Turtle
Turtle?
Kashiwagi-san, you're fast at finding it
Why is it a turtle?
Turtle?
Is it a mark of a turtle?
Turtle
Let's go!
Thank you very much
Sorry
Monja's shop is only for Kameido
Let's do that first
I'll leave it to you, leader
Let's go
Can I ask?
Ask, ask
Can you get my appo?
Be careful
Thank you, Kobayashi
Good luck
I'll be waiting
It's okay
Okay
Yes
See you
I'm here
It's okay
Bye bye
Excuse me, can I have a MQ?
Let's go
Where should we go?
How about an electric store?
That's a good idea
We'll go to an electric store and ask
where we are going
It's a shopping street, so there are
many things to do
This is my second time today
Sorry, Kobayashi
I couldn't hear you because of the sound
of the truck
We got the information
Let's go
Next episode is the second part of the
MQ
Nakayama and Kashiwagi are showing their
special skills at the store
Kashiwagi is already out
This team is also taking a walk
Ouch!
This is painful!
This program is brought to you by the
following sponsors.