The new members of the debut group were
announced the other day
They are close to the stage
5, 2, 3, 4, 5, 2, 3, 4, 5
The new members of the debut group are
announced the other day
Thank you for your viewing.
Good morning
I'm a new member
I'll do my best
I'm 24 years old now
You have a lot of hints
Chiritsu Ebisu Junior High School's 9th
anniversary live show
Due to the emergency declaration, the
live show suddenly changed
On this day, a new member will be
announced on the second stage
Are you nervous?
Chiritsu Ebisu Junior High School's 9th
anniversary live show
How was it? When you got a call?
I was very happy
I cried a lot
I was surprised and happy
I was very anxious, but I cried a lot
until then
And on this day, for the first time as a
Chiritsu Ebisu Junior High School
member, they entered the venue
And the senior members...
Oh, the first day of class!
I feel like it's the first day
It's the first time I've talked to her
She's a really good girl
Kobayashi caught up with this kind of
rumor
That girl, Hina-chan
She's the most scary one
I heard it from the boss
I think she's the only one who's not
scared of her
I hope she can be scared of her
She's a cute girl
Am I cute?
Yes, boss
Is she the same age as when you joined
the company?
Yes, she is
She's so calm
When I joined the company, I was like...
I'm not sure if I'm the same age as her
But she's amazing, she's so calm
I'm looking forward to getting along
with her
I'm looking forward to seeing her
personality
And the boss is...
I've been thinking about it and made a
white mask today
I'm going to make a white mask today
At 2pm, the first live performance
starts
The first live performance begins
The new members are...
I'm back.
They dress up for the stage show.
Just at that moment...
Good morning.
We have a live show.
Thank you.
The new member, Yuno Koku, who was on
another event, arrived at the venue.
Oh, yes.
Thank you for your hard work.
Good job.
Is this your first time meeting the
members?
Yes.
It's not the first time for us.
Actually, it's the first time for the
three of them to get together since the
training camp.
I'm relieved that we're three.
It looks fun.
This is Nono.
Say hello to them.
Mino.
It's the first time for us.
Please look at the back.
I'm Ginata.
You're cute.
I'm Kako.
11, 12, 13, 14, 15.
Oh, it's here.
We're here.
We're in the second half.
11, 12, 13, 14, 15.
We're here.
Thank you for the rehearsal.
The rehearsal for the live show begins.
The new members are being checked.
Can you put your head down?
The head is different.
The yellow part here.
The floor will rise.
When it rises, you can put your head
down.
Let's go.
Standby, go!
Lina.
You're surprised, aren't you?
Let's do it again.
I'm scared.
Let's go.
Standby, go!
Wait.
Let's go.
Go!
Thank you for watching.
Welcome back
I'm so scared
Let's go back
Let's go at the same time
Let's go
Go!
The production team decides the pose at
the same time as they go up to the stage
What are you worried about?
I'm worried about the pose
You mean the pose?
Yes, I'm worried about the pose
It's cool
We have to make the pose that we can see
Yes
The first stage
Can they make a good decision?
The new members have finished their
rehearsal
Thank you
The second stage will be held at the
same time as the first stage
10 minutes before the show starts
The first stage will be held at the same
time as the first stage.
Are you nervous?
Yes.
You are nervous, aren't you?
The new members are also here.
We are Ebi-chu.
We are going to sing a song.
Where are we?
Odaiba!
We are Ebi-chu.
Fighting!
The new members are finally starting
their live performance
The three members are the last ones to
perform
sixth of July has taken us to the south
of Japan
This is where idols from the Japanese
Tele wink
this is
Fame
Celebrities who perform a
progressive
song
That's it, that's it, that's it
I'm waiting for the next god to come
I wonder if I can do it so far
I can't do it so well
You can do it
I have to do it, so I can't do it
I can't do it, but I can do it
The heart-pounding of the pre-contract
I can feel it from the hand that is
connected
I can't hide my feelings anymore
If I can say it without letting go of
this hand
How happy would I be?
I want to know how the prince feels
It's hard, it's almost over
The six-person shrimp stew is over
From now on, no matter how many people
there are,
I will always be your companion
Oh, it's over
It's over
Amazing
I'll do my best, I won't give up
No matter how hard the road is
I'm nervous
Yes, it's painful, it's painful
I'm not sure if I can do it
Not too long after the same song, the
match happened!
The first day of the training
Everyone, let's get better
Let's go
You guys are the real deal
Good luck
I'm the 8th place, 14th place, 14th
place, 16th place, 16th place
Let's go
Finally, the stand by
has arrived
Thanks.
You three line up here,
don't you?
Please, elephant this time.
Do you think I'm crazy?
Thank you for watching.
The last song on the set list, Trendy
Girl, has begun.
At that moment...
Let's move to the center.
The last song on the list, Trendy Girl,
has begun.
When you walked ahead, you were
the類avorite candidate for Beacon Era
Hall.
But now, one man is interested in every
available talent and gerne officially.
Artists suddenly emigrated to
Beacon Era Hall.
Thank you for watching.
The first day of the training camp
I'm nervous.
I'm 99% nervous.
I'll do my best.
I'm really nervous.
Are you nervous?
Which one?
I can't remember
Go!
Please wait
30 seconds left
The countdown VTR was played on the
broadcast
Actually, on the stage...
The last stage of 6 shrimp is over.
Finally, the last stage of 6 shrimp is
over.
Soon
5 2 3 4
2 2 3 4
3 2 3 4
4 2 3 4
5 2 3 4
6 2 3 4
I will do my best
And the new member is
still here
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10
Thank you for watching!
We are the morning chime, She's Ebichu!
From today, Ebichu will be a 9-member
idol group with these three members.
Thank you!
The three members have decided to come
out.
This is how the new members joined the
group for the first time in seven years.
Thank you so much for watching the Nico
Nico live broadcast.
So, that's it for today.
Everyone, have a nice day!
Thank you so much!
Thank you!
NEXT PARTNERS LEAVE AWAY
It's finished.
Thank you for watching!
Let's go to Aisha.
After this, we'll shoot for Aisha.
We'll shoot for Aisha.
After experiencing the stage during the
debut,
the new members who have been on the
stage themselves...
I've really become a member.
I finally feel like I've really entered.
I'll do my best to become a better
person.
Thank you for your hard work.
It was a very short moment.
I'll do my best as Sakura and Kokona in
the middle of the show.
I'll dance a lot and sing a lot.
When we said,
I was like, oh, I'm a new member.
In this way,
Shibitsu Ebisu Middle School has become
a new student.
I just thought that today was the 9th
anniversary.
Nine people made their major debut nine
years ago.
Nine people became nine people nine
years later.
Nine people.
I'm not leaving everything to the new
members.
We have to do our best, too.
We all do our best.
I remembered a lot when I entered.
We have different personalities.
I thought we could support each other.
I thought it would be nice if we could
help each other and make a good
relationship.
I met them today.
I talked to them.
I thought it would be okay if they were
the same age.
I want to get along with them as soon as
possible.
I want to open my heart to them.
I want them to be relieved.
I thought so.
I think the atmosphere will change if
it's not different.
I hope we can all enjoy the fun and fun
together.
I want you to focus on that.
When we were rehearsing,
I was thinking about what the three of
us should think about.
I thought I was like that, too.
I felt nostalgic.
I was excited to make a new story with
the three of us.
I don't know what it is, but I'm
relieved that it's over.
Cute.
This is the best. It's like a shrimp.
More, more, more shrimp.
New era of private shrimp middle school
opens the curtain.
It's the first time I'm shooting a
magazine.