Good night!
Today, we are going to have a
competition.
It's called...
Tokimeki Mini Sports Competition!
It's the first time.
So, now, Karin is holding a rope.
A rope.
And...
A rainbow.
It's a game that you can pass through.
And 10 seconds.
The person who can count 10 seconds with
the clock in their body and the closest
to the time wins.
We will do three tasks this time.
The person who can count 10 seconds with
the clock in their body and the closest
to the time wins.
How do you feel about the sports?
It's been a while.
It's been years since I jumped rope.
I'm good at Karamin and Julia.
I'm good at this.
How about you, Aoi?
I want to be a cameraman this time.
I think so.
I'm worried that I'll be sad if I don't
cry.
Please join us.
I got it.
I don't want to give you a cut.
Thank you.
I'm serious.
Let's get started.
The first one is the second one.
The second one is the second one.
Let's do it in order of numbers.
Let's start with Karamin.
110 cm.
I'll do my best.
It depends on your height.
Isn't this pretty low?
Soft.
Wait, you're tall, so you're the most...
I'll go!
How do you do this? I don't know how.
It's like a sidebar.
Wait a minute.
I'll go!
Ah!
Oh, you're so relaxed!
I'll lower it a little.
Next, I'll try to make it 105cm.
It's pretty low.
It's only 5cm.
I'll start from Kanami.
It's pretty low.
It's easy.
I'm ready.
You're out.
Wait a minute.
You're all 10 centimeters taller than
me.
Do you know that?
I want to go.
I'm scared.
I think I can do it.
I got it.
It means that you can do it.
I can do it.
I'm scared.
Don't let go of me.
I have enough space to go back.
I'm scared.
Don't let go of me.
Is this okay?
I'm crouching.
You're out.
I'm out.
It's pretty low.
I don't know.
I can't do it.
I'm tired.
I'm out.
Oh!
You're okay!
I'm totally fine!
Wow!
Yui-chan, stop!
I'm sorry.
No, no.
OK, cut.
That's it!
Yui-chan!
Yui-chan came out!
Wow!
I was surprised.
Next, I'll give you another one.
Yes.
Next,
100 cm!
That's huge!
It's pretty small.
Next is 100 cm.
It's a 15 cm.
Yes.
One person was eliminated.
It's a very meaningless person.
Good luck.
So,
Good luck with the five of you.
I think I'll be eliminated this time.
I'll go.
I think I can do it.
You can do it!
You're so relaxed.
It's about 5 cm.
It's low.
What should I do?
Wow!
You're so good.
Wait a minute.
Look!
You don't have to push yourself too
hard.
Be careful.
Wait a minute.
You have to be motivated.
You can do it!
It's a little difficult.
She's looking at the camera.
Your head is difficult.
Your face is difficult.
I'm scared.
Please subscribe to our channel.
I'm scared!
You're so cute!
I'm scared.
You're doing it!
I'm scared!
You can do it!
Just a little more!
You're doing it!
Wow!
It's like a living thing.
It's kind of funny.
How did this happen?
The first time I saw it.
Next is...
95cm.
95cm?
It's small.
It's a Kachan.
It's a big Kachan.
Do you think you can do it?
I don't know.
I think I can do it.
You can do it.
Pio can do it too.
Akitomo can do it too.
You don't have to be scared.
I can do it when I'm touching it.
Your long tail is so beautiful.
I'm like that.
Right?
I'm not used to it.
It's hard.
Let's do our best.
Thank you for watching.
The time limit is given in official
interviewin keepsake video.
I was surprised.
I'm...
So...
So... So...
So... So... So...
I was surprised.
I wonder if I can do it.
I can't do it.
Amazing!
I'm tired.
Let's go!
What?
What are you doing?
I'm going to drop it.
I dropped it.
And you were holding it.
It's so small.
My heart is beating.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Oh, cute!
I think I'm getting the hang of it.
Be careful.
I'm scared when I come here.
Amazing!
I'm nervous.
Was it nervous?
No, no.
Wow, you cleared it!
The last player is...
Isn't it great?
I'm glad.
Everyone, don't get hurt.
I'll do my best.
I can do it.
If you can't do it, give up.
I'll go.
It's low.
It's scary.
I was surprised.
It's different.
It was slippery.
It's scary.
I'm serious.
120.
It's a good way to check the situation.
It's impossible.
Physically.
I'm surprised.
It's impossible.
It's difficult to be tall.
Only one person can do it.
What should I do?
Please subscribe to my channel.
I can't do it.
I feel like my butt muscles are going to
collapse.
I can't do it.
I'm scared.
No!
I couldn't do it!
But you did great.
You did great.
I can't do it.
Hang in there.
I still have 10 seconds left.
I'm still far from the end.
I'm nervous.
I'm getting my butt cramped.
Hang in there.
You can do it.
You did great.
Correct!
kind of this
you your turn
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I don't know myself.
I'm sorry.
So, there are four people left.
It's 85cm.
It's low.
Can I wear it?
It's amazing.
So, one person will be given a chance to
wear it.
We'll do it with four people.
Please do your best.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for watching!
Yuka is cute.
She was cute.
I'm getting excited.
I'm surprised.
It was unexpected.
I'm tired.
I was tired.
I'm surprised.
Oh, I can do it!
Ah!
I'm hungry.
I can't hold it.
I was sitting in a stable position.
I'm relieved.
How many minutes did you move?
I can't hold it.
I don't know.
I'm good at it.
I thought I could do it.
You did it at once.
Only Kanami and Aki can do it.
Good luck.
Next is 80 degrees.
It's interesting.
The next is 80 degrees.
80 degrees.
It's amazing.
Isn't it amazing?
Amazing.
I'll do my best.
I want you to stand up.
I want you to do your best.
I will do my best.
Wait a minute.
I'm going to show my butt.
Oh!
So close!
One more time!
I wish they weren't shooting...
I won't laugh.
I'll start.
It's hard.
You can do it!
I can't do it.
Your back is not protected.
You are scary.
She is trying to do it.
Let's try it.
He is enjoying taking.
Please hide it?
We're a bunch of small, young
It's difficult.
This is difficult.
Kanamin and Aki won the game.
It's not as tight as it used to be.
It's totally different.
You two get 1 point.
Let's move on to the next game.
The next game is...
The game of the two teams.
The first game is...
The second game is...
The game of the two teams.
The third game is...
Please subscribe to my channel!
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to hurt you.