This time, we will continue from last
week, the 7th season's special, Ebi-Chu-
Tasu, Kameido.
We will walk around the town of Kameido.
What are they shooting?
Ebi-Chu-Tasu, Start!
Ikemo Nattemo Irarenai Modokashii Kanjou
Kakeru Hyaku
Maia powdered
I'm so into you that I can't stop
What should I do with my heart that's
filled with you?
Monotrium, monotrium, monotrium, middle
school
Add all kinds of things to private Ebisu
middle school
Ebisu middle school
This program is provided by the sponsor
you see.
The two teams are always separated when
moving cars.
The team that doesn't get drunk on cars
and the team that gets drunk on cars.
They are separated into mysterious teams
and go on a walk around the Kameido
town, Brali.
Last time, they were invited to smell
and eat bread.
At the recycle shop, they hold a cheap
coordination battle with Yasumoto.
The two teams are always separated when
moving cars and the team that doesn't
get drunk on cars and the team that gets
drunk on cars.
The team that got drunk on cars and
bought a lot of old clothes is the Monja
shop.
I like this kind of seat.
Excuse me, do you have any
recommendations?
The most recommended is the turtle
Monja.
Turtle Monja.
And the one that is popular with girls
is tomato mochi.
Hey, what's wrong?
Turtle Monja and red tomato Monja.
Tomato?
Choose one from each team.
Have you decided?
What's that?
Turtle Monja.
Please give me a T.M.
It's a T.M. for Daigo-san.
The one who is eating the red tomato
Monja.
Please give me a T.M.
It's a T.M. for Turtle Monja.
Please give me a M.T.M.
Do you usually eat Monja?
Yes, we do.
Can you make it?
Riko-chan is pretty good at it.
Can you cook?
I said no.
But she is good at it.
Nakayama?
I can make it.
I can make it if I have a good
technique.
That's a big deal.
Why can you make Monja?
I used to go to a lot of Monja when I
was a kid.
Nakayama is good at it.
Kashiwagi is good at it.
He is good at it.
He is called a monk.
He made everything for us when we went
to eat.
Can you make Kashiwagi?
I love Monja.
I didn't expect that you can't make
Monja.
I can't cook, but I can make Monja.
You said you can't cook.
I can't.
Can you cook?
Wait, you have a master.
Yasumoto is your master.
He made Monja for us when we went to
eat.
Can you make Yasumoto?
I can't cook, but I can make Monja.
You are clumsy.
Which one is better? Yasumoto or
Kashiwagi?
I want to say it clearly.
You should say it clearly.
I am a warrior.
But he is my disciple.
Here it comes.
It's a turtle.
DM! DM!
It's a turtle!
I thought it was a turtle meat!
It's a turtle shape!
Cute!
There's a small turtle and a big turtle!
Amazing!
Hello!
Thank you!
What are you doing with this big thing?
That's the Tomatomonja!
What are you doing?
Please make two groups of Tomatomonja!
Yes!
Let's go to see their skill of making
Monjayaki!
Toma-kun, how do you make it?
Like a UFO catcher!
Ta-da!
Oh!
Please add oil.
Please add oil a little bit.
Is it OK?
Yes.
It's not put, it's dropped.
Chie-san, please crush it.
Me?
It's OK to crush it.
No one wants to see me making it.
I want to see it.
Do your best.
Be careful, it's bouncing.
That's right.
It's OK because it's there.
It's there, but...
It smells good.
What kind of smell?
It smells like tomato.
Thank you.
Grilled tomato.
More, more.
You have to cut it more.
There is tomato underneath.
What is that?
It's like minced meat.
Minced meat.
It's hot.
It's OK.
You can do your best.
It's hot.
Is it OK?
Not yet?
How is it?
Please put the meat first.
Do you mix it with tomato?
The staffs are listening to you.
I'm listening.
It smells good.
Do you want to cut it?
What is that?
Please subscribe to this channel.
It's quite cut here.
You can do it.
Look, she's already using her arms to
cut the kashiwagi.
Because it's a kashiwagi.
You're making a donut.
I'm going to make a donut.
Look, she's almost done.
It's looking good.
Don't you have to mix it first?
Do I have to mix this?
Look, she's making a donut.
I'm making a donut.
The athlete is doing her best.
I'm doing my best.
Are you okay?
It's not like you're going to make it
faster.
I hope it's delicious.
That's right.
It smells good.
It looks delicious.
Can you say something to the other team?
I'm sorry.
I have to do it properly because I have
a clam.
Thank you.
I can't eat clams.
I'll eat it.
Thank you.
I don't need a box.
I'll eat it.
Thank you.
I'll eat squid, too.
The athlete is doing her best.
How can I make a donut?
You can mix it a little more.
Thank you.
It's going well.
I have to do it properly because I have
a clam.
I'm worried about the clam's fire.
The clam's fire.
It's true that the clam's fire is like
that.
I'm worried if I get a stomachache.
I'll put it in.
Then, hold it down.
I feel like they're really used to it.
I think it's going to be fine.
Please subscribe to our channel.
It's a mix.
It's good.
It's coming out.
Don't give up.
It's a mix.
She mixed it.
It's crispy.
It's a mix.
It's good.
She mixed it.
It's a mix.
There's no hole.
There's no place to spill.
It's meaningless to make a dote at
first.
She mixed it right away.
It's good.
It's almost done.
Both of them look delicious.
Let's eat!
It's a little burnt
It looks hot
It's definitely hot
It's how to take it out
It's delicious. It's just right
It's just right
It's delicious
Tomatoes go well together
Tomatoes are delicious
The burnt taste is just right
I'm curious about the tomatoes
Come here
It looks delicious
It's delicious
Please excuse me
Don't forget to record
This much?
Let's eat together
Bring it
Bring this one
What is it?
Monja
After eating, they went to Kameido
station
It was delicious
I want to eat it
You can't eat it anymore, can you?
I think I can eat it
Are you OK?
I'm totally fine
I think I'm fine
Look!
Kameido Gyoza
It's true
Let's go!
Really?
Can you still eat?
Yes, I can.
Can you really eat?
Yes.
You look more energetic than when you
were hungry.
Yes, I can.
Can you really eat?
I'm eating now. I want to eat dumplings.
I see. It smells good.
Wow, it has a good atmosphere.
It's good.
Kobayashi, please.
Please.
Take this.
Oh, no.
I think it's better not to take it.
I'll wait.
It's a program.
Let's go.
I think we can go to the station if we
go this way.
Let's go to the train station.
Let's hide there.
Good idea.
Let's hide here.
Hey, hey, hey.
They are gone.
They are not saying, Hey.
Really?
Where did they go?
The manager said,
Yo is going.
Yo?
I'm tired.
What are you doing?
Where is the manager?
He is going to the yard.
He is going to the yard? Can you go in?
He said wait a minute.
Let's go.
Can you go in?
I think I can.
Let's go. The crow is crying.
He is back.
He is not here.
Is this it?
Kobayashi-san who loves dumplings,
wanted to come here.
Kameidomo Dumplings
Here you are.
Thank you.
I haven't ordered yet, but it's already
coming
We only have gyoza
Oh, I see
We have two plates of gyoza
Two plates of gyoza
Wow
Thank you
It's good
We don't have rice
We only have gyoza
That's good
This is really good
It's coming
Let's eat
Thank you
Oh, no!
I've never eaten such a delicious
dumpling
How is it, Yasumoto?
It's delicious
It's the best dumpling I've ever eaten
You just said Kobayashi first
I imitated him
It's delicious
It's amazing
I've never eaten dumplings with mustard
It's soft
It's delicious
How about you, Kobayashi?
I had a stomachache when I ate dumplings
the other day
But I can't have this anymore
It's light
It's delicious
I'll be addicted to this
I agree
I want to eat it
I see
It's served right away
It's like a dumpling dumpling
It's a dumpling dumpling
I wanted to see it too
I ate it
It's amazing
Cool
Can you eat two?
Dancing dumpling
Surprised
Delicious
Kobayashi-san, how do you feel about the
Kamen-do Gyoza?
I haven't eaten it yet
What do you mean?
I ordered it but it hasn't arrived yet
I'm happy to eat the real thing here
It's been 60 years since it was sold
Thank you
It's delicious
There are sweets inside
As they eat and eat and eat
Group of getting in the car
They walked to the end
See you next time!
I'm full now
I'm hungry
If I ate 3 more dishes, I would have
been out
To be honest, I ate because it was
delicious
But I was full because I ate at Monja
Really?
But I ate because it was delicious
Let's go back
I think it's over there, let's go back
You know it well
I think it's over there
It was fun
Congratulations
After this, the team who doesn't get
drunk on the car started to walk
What kind of shooting is this?
The team that doesn't get drunk on cars
is going to walk around Nishigawa on
Kameido
First, they're going to Kuramae Bridge
lama
Do you go for a walk?
I love to go to Mayama Sanpo
Where do you go for a walk?
On my day off, I go for a walk from
morning to night
A walk?
A walk? Do you go to a shop?
I don't go to a shop
I walk around the park
It's like a boring day of a single
parent
Hoshina-san, a walk leader, found a shop
that interests him
What is this?
Fukuchi Photography Museum. It's
amazing!
It was established in 1920
More than 90 years!
It's amazing!
This is Fukuchi Photography Museum,
established in 1909
Can I take a photo?
Can you take a photo?
Yes!
Let's take a photo!
It's my first time taking a photo
Let's ask around
Yes!
Let's go in!
Thank you for waiting
Hello!
I saw the sign, and it says it was
established in 1920
That's right
My grandfather was in charge of it
I'm the third generation
The third generation!
That's amazing!
Let's take a photo too
It's a rare opportunity
Can I take a photo?
Can I?
Yes!
So, the members decided to take a
commemorative photo
Well, everyone's posters are closed, so
it's a little like a photographer.
That's right.
That's good.
It's different.
Founded in 1996
It seems that there is a formation that
the master is particular about.
I'll take this camera.
Let's take a picture together.
Not yet.
Wait a minute.
Smile.
Not yet.
There are various items.
Good.
The master took out the goods of the
popular character to make the members
smile.
This is for babies.
Thank you.
I have to take a picture.
I see.
Thank you.
I'll take a picture.
Smile.
What's your name?
I'm Taki.
Let's shake hands.
Shake hands.
That's good.
Is this good?
I'm looking forward to the finished
product.
How long does it take to take a picture?
It usually takes time, but this time we
made it a big one.
Thank you.
Let's go back to the town.
I'm looking forward to the finished
product.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you.
It looks like a shop decoration.
It's amazing.
Let's do this.
What is this?
I heard it suddenly.
From a popular brand, a rare item is
also a treasure.
I want to do a gacha.
It's suspicious.
Hoshina found a 1,000 yen vending
machine.
It seems that a high-class item is a
treasure.
What should we do?
We don't have money.
I don't have money either.
I can't do it.
Which bag did you put your wallet in?
Please subscribe to our channel.
I want to do it.
I really felt bad.
I asked the staff to take the prize.
I felt bad.
I want to do it.
I used the money for the first time.
What?
I lost the game.
I remember.
I did not forget.
I do not forget.
Please give me a good prize.
For example,
Camera.
This is a good prize.
3DS.
PS Vita.
I got it.
I can play with this glasses.
I can not do it.
Let's start with Mayama.
It's cheap for 20,000 people wearing a
mask
That's true
It's cheap
Can we do it now?
20 times?
Why do you want to do it for the mask?
It's coming
What is it?
There it is
It's small
What is it?
It's small and light
I have a bad feeling about this
Is it a glasses?
No
Is it a light?
I don't know
It could be a luxury watch
Maybe
I can't open it
Let's open it
What?
It's a lighter type cable
What does it mean?
It's a cable for cell phone chargers
It's a cable for iPhone
It's practical
Amazing
Mayama-san chose an item that is hard to
tell if it's a hit or miss
This kind of item
It's a shocker
It's a return item
Matsuno-san and Hoshina-san also got a
t-shirt that is hard to say
Finally Hirota-san
Of course the target must be right
You've got a small one
Add-san are the t-shirts written in
green?
How does it feel?
Stylish
It's like plastic.
What did you buy?
Did you win?
It's 1000 yen
What did you buy with 1000 yen?
I won!
I finally won!
Really?
A clock!
What kind of clock?
Well, it's a brand watch that I don't
know well
But it looks good on you
Let's wear it like Honda Seishi
Let's go like Honda Seishi
It's a great fashion point
It's fashionable
It's monotone, so it's fashionable
It's done!
We did it!
I'm glad we got a cool clock
Let's go to the next one!
We wasted 3000 yen and 4000 yen
4000 yen is quite expensive
I know! I know!
Where do you want to go next?
The leader decides!
So we decided!
Yay!
Where is this?
Pet shop!
I want to go!
Next, they go to the pet shop led by a
walk leader
Well, leader, negotiations are over
See you later
Have a good day
Hoshina-san goes to the negotiation
I want to record in the program called
Ebichu Tastos in Fuji, but it's okay
Which one is this?
It's okay if it's just the two of us
Let's be two
Two?
It's not good if there are too many
people
I see
I wonder if they'll be surprised
Let's decide by rock-paper-scissors
The two winners are
Hoshina-san and Matsuno-san
They go to the pet shop
See you later
Bye bye!
Next time, the 7th season's special
Ebichu plus Kameido, the final episode
I'm playing with my hair
So cute!
The members are all relaxed
And then, the unexpected guest appears
Kameido Sanpo, the shocking ending
This program was brought to you by the
following sponsors.
請 kidding me?
At least let us use their nostrils.