I'm Miya Mato, a 16-year-old high school
student from Fukuoka prefecture.
Today I'm at Hakata station.
I'd like to introduce you to Kouka and
myself.
Hakata station has an illumination,
I go there almost every year.
I come to Hakata station on my way home
from school,
so it's a place I'll remember.
I'm at Nakasu station.
It looks like this.
This is Nakagawa.
I'm Yua Kokuhaku.
I'm going to talk about my drawing.
I started drawing when I was in the
second year of junior high school.
I didn't join a club when I was in the
I didn't have any hobbies or special
skills.
I thought I was nothing if I was just
like this.
But I like art the most among the
subjects.
I think art is the most fun in class.
I thought I could spend the whole day
doing art.
That's how much I liked it.
I started drawing.
It was fun.
I still draw pictures that my friends
ask me to draw.
When I see them happy, I feel glad that
I'm drawing.
I have a lot of pictures.
The pictures I'm drawing now are also my
memories.
I like to see pictures that I could only
draw in the past.
I often see old pictures.
I'm in Momochihama now.
I've been friends with a friend who has
been my friend since I was in the first
grade of junior high school.
I have a friend who I love and I'm very
close to.
We went to a lot of places together.
We both like salmon and salmon roe.
We went to a lot of places and ate a lot
of salmon and salmon roe rice bowl.
We went to our favorite restaurants
together.
We went to a new restaurant when we
found a new restaurant.
We ate a lot of salmon and salmon roe
rice bowl.
When I was a kid, I was very dependent
on adults.
I've always been bad at communicating
with people.
I didn't want to talk to people as much
as I could.
I didn't want to do anything actively.
But when I was in elementary school, I
heard Silent Majority on a singing
program and I knew Mr. Kiyokizaka.
I realized that I was a brighter person
than I was in elementary school.
When I was in elementary school, there
was a 4-letter word presentation that I
liked.
I liked the 4-letter word, Shoshi-
Kantetsu.
I announced it as Shoshi-Kantetsu.
I think it's very difficult to do what
you've decided.
I think there are times when you can't
do it even if you try hard.
But I think the sense of accomplishment
after doing it is amazing.
I'm going to do my best to be a person
who can give energy to others.