Ready, set, go!
One, two, three, four, five, six.
Failed
I said four, five, six.
I counted the number of times I did it.
She's a genius.
The next day
I changed my nails yesterday.
Show them. I changed my nails.
The next day
I bought it on the same day. It's 10,000
yen.
I bought this advertisement.
Today is Miyagi Prefecture Quiz.
Oh!
I haven't worn it in a while.
Since we are talking about Tohoku, we
will talk about it.
First, we are going to talk about Miyagi
prefecture.
We prepared 20 questions to ask you.
Of course.
Oh!
You know it, right?
Yes, I do.
Yes.
So, it's okay not to do it because you
know it.
So, today's topic is...
Shichu-kun!
Thank you very much.
Please watch it again.
Question 1. Where is the most popular
place in Ieji?
I don't know.
I don't know at all.
Let's start over from the human side.
I don't know.
It's thin, so it's hard to make it
bigger.
It's a little bit.
It's a good answer.
Oh, I see.
It's embarrassing.
You have a variety of experiences.
Please answer at the same time.
Ready, set, go!
Sendai!
Shi!
See? I told you I knew it.
It's over.
What if you get it wrong?
I should have written Matsushima.
That's true.
Question 2.
How many prefectures are there in Miyagi
Prefecture?
I know.
I should have written Japan.
Prefectures?
I think it's okay.
It's Miyagi Prefecture.
It's a pain in the ass.
Okay.
3, 2, 1.
4.
3.
Kitami, you're the only one who got it
wrong.
I know.
There's one more question. Do you know
what it is?
Yamagata, Nibate, Miyagi Prefecture.
You didn't say one.
I feel sorry for her.
I remember Zoukoku Fair.
This is...
I got it!
Question 3.
That's right. It's Akita.
I'm sorry.
It's Akita.
Question 3.
What kind of sea is there in Miyagi
Prefecture?
I wrote it.
Here you go.
I'm doing my best.
It's the Pacific Ocean.
That's right.
Question 4.
I'm struggling.
How many stations are there in Miyagi
Prefecture where Shinkansen stops?
I don't know.
I should just say Akireru.
Miyagi Prefecture?
How far is it from Miyagi Prefecture?
I don't know. I only take Yamagata
Shinkansen.
I'm so tired.
Question 5.
What is the name of the train that comes
to the station?
I came to Sansabin and went to Yamagata.
I don't know.
1, 2.
I'm sorry.
The answer is 4 stations.
Is it Ichino Seki?
It's Shiroishizao.
Shiroishizao is from Sendai.
I'm not good at drawing.
Women are not good at drawing.
You are cute.
You are popular.
Question 5.
You can't write this on a whiteboard.
You can only write it in your head.
Okay.
How many squares is Miyagi?
Let's go!
First, Tohoku Shinkansen.
Tohoku Shinkansen.
Ready, set, go.
24.
Kitami.
What?
I'll try to write it down.
I might have included the payment.
Oh no.
I'll try to write it down.
Ready, set, go.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
I counted every day.
You can live.
That's right.
Question 6.
Do you know Oireo Miyagi?
I don't know.
I know.
What is the name of the official
character of Oireo Miyagi?
I don't know.
Hint.
I know if it's only the character.
Musubi Maru.
Keyaki.
Kitamisu.
This is also correct.
Question 7.
I can't say for sure, but that's what
most people think.
Yutan is famous in Miyagi.
What is the most characteristic of this?
I think it's normal.
It's normal.
I think it's crazy.
Then you can drink it.
I don't know what it means.
I've been eating beef tongue lately, so
I don't know.
One, two.
Question 8.
It's hot.
Keyaki.
I've never seen it.
It's very long.
I think there are various opinions, but
in general, it's hot.
But I've never eaten beef tongue except
for Miyagi.
I want to go to Tokyo next time.
Question 8.
It's a famous food made by grinding
edamame.
What is the origin of Zunda's name?
I don't know.
Zun-chan and Dan-kun.
It's like a princess who's been
spilling.
That's good.
Let's do that.
Zun-chan and Dan-kun's first
collaboration.
One, two.
Zunda.
It's Zunda from Da-Zun.
Zun-chan and Dan-kun.
It's a long time ago.
It's said to be one of the famous
stories.
It's a picture of a bean.
Beans?
It was named Zunda.
That's definitely true.
Question 9.
What is Miyagi's number one vegetable in
the country?
Do I like it?
Miyagi's favorite vegetable.
I don't like it because I don't eat it.
I don't want to put it in a food court.
This is also a hint.
There are two things that are number one
in the country.
You can write two and guess which one.
One, two.
Cucumber and cabbage.
Tomato and pepper.
Wrong.
Two are paprika.
The other one is a rice cooker.
It's a rice cooker.
It's delicious.
Question 10.
What is the noodle dish that originated
in Miyagi?
I know this.
I know this picture.
Why?
I don't know if it's a hint, but it's
not ramen or somen.
What?
One, two.
It's a national food.
Kitami.
It was really two days ago.
It's a restaurant that originated in
Miyagi.
I want to go there.
There is a restaurant called Ryutei.
I like the Eastern Chinese food.
Next time.
Question 11.
What does the sudden amazing mean?
It's a sudden amazing.
Correct.
It's been a while since I got the
correct answer.
Question 12.
What is the date of the famous Sendai
Hanabata Festival in Miyagi?
I don't know the date.
I think it's the day of the festival.
What is the date of the festival?
It's okay.
One, two.
It's the day of the festival.
The answer is number 2.
The correct answer is from August 6 to
8.
I've never been to the festival.
We always get caught in the arcade.
I'll say that.
But it's a fun festival.
I don't think so.
I'm trying to go to the festival because
I'm trying to meet you.
I wanted to go.
I'm thinking.
The 13th question is a flower festival
that you don't go to every year.
The flower festival starts on August
6th, but there is a night festival on
August 5th.
What kind of festival is it?
I don't know. I've never been there.
What festival?
Tanabata Jelly Flying Festival
Hanami Festival
I don't know if that jelly is
nationwide.
The 14th question is from the mayor of
Miyagi Prefecture.
Why do you ask such a question?
I don't know.
I'll give you a hint.
22.
I thought it was 22.
The correct answer is 35.
I don't know.
15.
Where is the smallest city in Miyagi
Prefecture?
I'm sorry.
I'll be caught.
Have you ever been to Fujitani?
I know.
Shizugawa.
I did it.
I'm so happy. I'll give you my
professional certificate.
Thank you.
Yay!
Question 16.
Ta-da!
What city is the Tengai Airport located
in?
I know.
I don't know.
Ready?
Rikuu.
Natori?
Oh, it's not Rikuu.
Kitami.
Five months later...
I thought it was a lift.
The direction is completely different.
I don't know! I don't know!
Question 17.
Subway Tozai Line.
The Yagiama Animal Park Station on the
Tozai Line is said to be the best subway
station in Japan.
I know that station.
What is it called?
Is it the best in Japan?
It's the best in Japan.
The best animal in Japan is on it!
Isn't it written?
Really?
It's written on the side.
It's written.
One, two, three!
Yagi-san is on it!
I'm glad I got it right.
Kisami-san.
I know this.
I think Yagi-san is on it.
That's right.
Yagi-san is the best in the world.
Question 18.
Miyagi Kenmin said that he somehow put
on shoes with holes in them.
What shoes did he put on?
I knew this when I was in the group.
Really?
I didn't know.
Yamakata didn't say that.
He didn't say that.
But Tohoku-san often says that.
Really?
Tohoku-san often says that?
Yes.
Good morning, I put on shoes.
Good morning.
I thought this was the first time I
heard this.
I see.
It's really only Miyagi-ken.
Good morning.
Question 19.
What does the word pero mean in Miyagi-
ken dialect?
I don't remember saying pero.
I've never said pero to Miri-chan.
I might say wow.
I've never said pero, so I don't know.
The hint is food.
I got it.
What?
Ready, set, go!
Nori! Men!
Kitami-san.
Men? Why men?
Men.
Why men?
I thought it was Capra-men.
I thought it was Capra.
Okay, the last one.
Okay.
Question 20.
Hiyoriyama in Sendai City is said to
have the lowest altitude in Japan. How
many meters is the altitude?
I don't know, but I wonder how low it
is.
I have no choice but to go.
It's 50 meters.
Ready, set, go!
Question 20.
It's hard.
The answer is 3 meters.
If it's 3 meters, then...
3 meters?
We don't have a good example.
If it's 90 meters, then...
If it's a family, then 6 meters.
I don't think everyone knows this,
but...
It's half of the mirror in our
messenger.
Isn't that low?
Low?
Low!
That's all.
We'll show you.
The winner is...
14 out of 20 points...
Tammi!
I'm so happy!
Hello?
I cook everyday.
I'm sorry.
Let's break up.
By the way, you got 5 points.
Why?
It's a funny story.
I'm curious about Tanabata jelly.
If you know any other jelly that you
didn't get this time, please let us know
in the comments.
Next.
1. Silence.
2. Bow.
Thank you very much.
It's not a summer vacation. It's a
vacation time.
I made a mistake.
Thank you for watching.