Thank you for watching.
Draw a circle with your well-developed
arm.
Let's draw a circle around the star.
The song I'm going to sing is called
BAN.
BAN is the most difficult dance song in
Sakurazaka 46.
The goal of the 4 nights and 5 days
training camp is to be able to dance the
short version of BAN perfectly.
On the last day of the training camp,
she performs in front of the
choreographer, Takahiro sensei.
Good morning, everyone.
Did you have a good night's sleep last
night?
You did.
I think this training camp requires a
lot of physical strength, so I want you
to eat well and sleep well.
The lessons are divided into 4 teams,
taking into account dance experience.
I'll be doing the short version from the
beginning to the end.
The reason is that Sakurazaka members
learn the whole thing in 3 hours.
Once you're in, it becomes a given, so I
want you to experience it now.
So I'll force you to join.
In Sakurazaka, the time to learn the
choreography, which is called the
choreography of dance, is 3 hours.
Basically, you have to learn all the
choreography there.
The first trial for members who have no
experience in dancing.
I want you to start with this song.
After jumping, put out your left foot.
I'll turn my hand big.
I'm a little impatient to analyze where
I'm not good at and catch up with the
two of them.
I'll do it a little faster.
I'm not good at memorizing choreography.
I've been a homebody, so I'm not good at
dancing.
So I'll do my best.
I don't know the moves.
You don't know? Do you want to start
from the beginning?
OK.
Let's do it again.
You're going to do the E.
Ready, go.
You have to do this three times.
One, two, three.
And then you let go.
Your legs are apart at this point, so
you have to close them.
And then your right knee.
Hey!
Let's do it again.
I'm behind you.
If you don't understand, come and listen
to me.
I want to do it again.
This lesson time is limited, so you have
to absorb it here.
I draw your fact after the competition
and concentrate on a 정부 VP GM.
I tried to do it in 3 hours, how was it?
It was hard.
It was hard, wasn't it?
It was pretty hard.
The members always do the full length of
the new song in 3 hours to 3 and a half
hours.
For those who have experience in
dancing, the performance of the band is
not easy.
I have noוכay of hanging on to the
train, ever.
I was asked by Akimoto sensei to create
the most difficult dance in the past.
It's difficult.
It's difficult for a child who has no
experience in dancing to do this.
But I think it's more important to keep
up with the dance than to be able to
dance.
If you try to keep up with the dance,
you will be able to dance.
I hope that people will be able to see
that in this training camp.
Do you have a lot of appetite?
Yes.
I'll think about it after I eat
vegetables.
Please wait.
Let's eat.
I understand that she wants to practice
again soon, but taking a break is also
important.
Let's eat.
One, two, three, four.
Open this up.
Riko, you have to peel it off firmly.
I always tell the members to remember
the cool shape of the dance.
Now you can look in the mirror, but when
you get used to it, you'll see the
audience in front of you.
Dance as if you are looking in the
mirror.
Thank you for watching.
Yes.
First, Taniguchi.
You can dance, but your movements are
still small.
You have to dance more dynamically to
stand out on stage.
This hand pose is really important.
If you say this is a Sakura pose,
I hope you never forget this.
I feel like you're not paying attention.
I want you to remember what I told you.
I didn't say this during practice today.
You can see it yourself.
I haven't danced at all.
I'm late alone.
I make mistakes in the same place.
I forget and make mistakes.
If you keep doing that, it's really
dangerous.
You have to be able to dance this intro
properly by tomorrow.
I did the intro part today.
I'll start with 1A tomorrow.
I think you'll get lost as soon as the
song starts.
Today's task is to think about the world
of the song.
And I want you to understand the meaning
of the lyrics.
I want you to take this task and work on
it from tomorrow.
I knew it myself.
I'm the worst dancer in this room.
I'm depending on you two.
I want to do what I said.
Riko said it's my fault.
Riko will check it and remember it.
All I can think about is dancing.
I'm desperate to keep up with the dance.
I can't stop thinking about dancing.
I can't convey the world of music
without singing.
I have to deliver the music.
It's my job to deliver the music.
I decided not to cry.
At the entrance?
I decided not to cry, but I thought I
was carrying it with me.
First of all, are you motivated?
Why can't you remember so much?
To be honest, I've been thinking about
myself all the time.
I'm always thinking about myself when
I'm announcing my music in a group.