È川沈 剛 clinic
3 new members were announced at the 9th anniversary of the major debut of
Shirito Ebisu Junior High School
I am the 13th, 4th grade student, Sakuragi Kokona
I am the 14th, 3rd grade student, Kokubo Yuno
I am the 15th, 2nd grade student, Kazami Nanoka
3 new members stood on the stage after passing the 3rd, 4th day of the school
camp audition
They were talking about this
I hope that I can blow a new wind
The feelings of Ebichu
This time, they will deliver an unreleased interview
Furthermore
I want to go home
Great performance by everyев pancakes Meev mu!
First, we have Sakuragi Kokona.
I am very happy that I got to know that you are a great senior that I respect.
I watched a lot of videos from that time and got into it.
I want to go to the singing and vocal training.
I really want to join you.
I want to be a cool idol when I join you.
I am good at dancing, so I want to show you how to dance.
Next is Nonoka Kazami.
I like singing and dancing since I was a child.
I like K-pop idol, Twice.
I remember and dance.
I heard from the manager that there is an audition for every girl idol.
Cute and cool are different.
I thought it was amazing.
I want to be an idol that people of the same generation can admire.
Next is Yuno Kokubo.
I like prose and Gagakara ideal and listen Então
I like idols too
They are cool and cute
I want to be an idol who makes people smile naturally
They have overcome many challenges to become the most admired Ebi-Chu
At this time, they didn't know that they would become new members
At the end of the training camp, they talked about this
I thought that I was able to finish without any regrets.
I had some parts where I missed the lyrics, but I felt like I could do it.
I was able to do my best until the end.
Through this camp, the three members of the group,
we were able to get along and teach each other.
We were able to do it together.
I learned that I can do what I'm good at.
I can't imagine it yet, but I'm really happy to be able to do it.
It was like we were together for a month or two.
Everyone was really friendly and it was fun.
Did you do your best?
I did my best. But I think I could have done better.
I was laughing even though I was bad at dancing.
I think that's amazing.
I didn't have any problems.
I just wanted to do my best next time.
And the youngest Nonoka is...
I have never done anything before.
I was taught to dance and sing by the same team members, like Kokona and Aika.
I think I did well.
I was able to meet the real Ebichu and talk to her.
I also learned her songs and dances.
I want to become Ebichu.
I will do my best to make a new wind blow.
With this feeling in their hearts, the three of them became the new members of
Shirito Ebichu Gakku.
In the next episode of ZEMO-RIMIX, we will continue to follow the new members.
Please look forward to it!
And this time, we will show you the unreleased footage of the training camp.
And that is...
Ebichu members who were watching the live broadcast comments.
I want to see the feeling of wearing the sneakers
We thought we would do it yesterday
We thought we would do it
We wore these sneakers
To meet the fans' request
We will show you the song of the training camp, Paita Teki
the pride this private version has never been shown
on stage
Thank you
The three of us are the trend
Paita and the other two go
thank you
Thank you
See you
undi Jennifer
BOMINTARU
E elle
H karao
おし that
Do you remember that
I love you, my love!
I don't hate you, I don't hate you!
I'm not scared of you!
I'm just scared of you!
No Crap!!
Taking my Zoneicano away!
Dating her in Twitch group!
I'm not scared of you!
I am not scared of you guys!
I'm scared!
The end
Everyone did a great job
Thank you!
I can't say I'm in love with her.
Next time
Let's go
This is the real Kiritachi
The new members are getting closer to the back of the live show
5 2 3 4 5 6 3 2 1