Night time idol
.
I like beauty.
You have a high sense of fashion.
I'm not a big fan of fashion.
I like to look for simple and effective
products.
But recently, I'm looking for products
that are good for my skin.
I'm looking for products that are good
for my skin every day.
You're doing it right.
I can't do it from a streamer.
I don't have time to remove my makeup
with a streamer.
You're doing it right.
Isn't that right?
It's just right.
I'm not aware of it.
It used to be very random.
I don't know.
It's one person's thing.
I like it, but it's a pain.
But you like it, right?
I like to try things out.
Korean cosmetics are cheap, so I can try
a lot of things.
It's also very effective.
I look at the ingredients and think
about the effects of the poison.
I'm going to use this because my skin is
red today.
I see.
I'm looking forward to it.
Is there any cosmetic product you
recommend now?
I was talking about the poison.
The sheet pack from ABIVE is very good.
It's good.
The poison pack is very good.
It can make acne and redness.
It's hard to get rid of it the next day.
If you do that, it will immediately have
an effect.
It keeps your skin elastic until the
next morning.
I recommend it to you before shooting.
There is a popular cosmetic product
among fans.
That's because you're doing it.
There is a soda pack called Soda Spa
Foam.
It's a pain to mix two types of liquid.
I don't like the basic one.
It's a pain, but it's a foam.
Just put it on.
It can remove swelling and pores.
It can reduce redness and acne.
It's good for fans who have a problem
with swelling.
It's popular.
Everyone is wearing a white face.
I saw the video of the fruit, Nakamoto
beauty salon.
Everything was healthy.
Nakamoto is healthy.
I went to the sauna in Nakamoto.
I couldn't stop sweating.
I was sweating from my bangs during the
live.
I was laughed at by the first row of
fans.
That's my recent problem.
You've been doing so well.
I was laughed at during the live.
I was laughed at.
It's been more than 10 years.
I'm fine.
Thank you very much.
The game that will be played by the two
of you.
This is the game that the writer is
playing right now.
It's like a sports day.
Yeah.
You can't eat spicy food.
You should put it in a game that's more
like you.
Oh, should I put it in?
What else are you good at?
I'm good at running.
Oh, you're good at running.
You should make a game that's mixed with
spicy food.
Let's play an insider game.
Yeah.
The game that will be played by the two
of you.
This program was brought to you by Drill
Sensei, Totomomo-san, Leo-san, and Okura
Risako-san.
This program was brought to you by
GamiGami-san.
Thank you very much.