Yakan and idol
So, that's the ending of this episode
Before we end, can you take a breath
before I give you some important
information?
Okay
I'm getting tea from you every time
What kind of tea?
Today, I'm going to make a lot of tea
Wow, that's a famous tea
I'm glad I got it from Red Bull
So, today I'm going to make tea that
will make you feel like you're a bird
I'm going to drink it
I've made the right choice
That's it
I'm glad I got Red Bull today
I'm glad you got it
I'm glad
Yakan and idol
So, can you tell us about your future
plans for your work?
Yes, we're going to have a show on 11th,
12th, Saturday at 7th, 6th, Saitama
Shintoshin VJ3
The title of this show is Rock the Bolt
If you haven't seen the show, please
come and see it
On 11th, 8th, and 1st, we're going to
have a show at Dance Hall Shunshi
Station
It's Chii-chan's birthday, so please
come and see it
On Friday, 23rd, 12th, we're going to
have a festival at Yokohama Bay Hall
What's this?
This is a Christmas gift that I've been
giving out since I was 20
I see
So, on 11th, 12th, it's going to be a
very important day
Yes, that's right
It's going to be an unforgettable show
An unforgettable show
We're going to continue from here
There's also a tour of the Bolt's 4th
single, 8th, 1st, 2nd, and 3rd
Please come and see the official website
for more information
That's all for today
How was it today?
I didn't have much time to talk about my
hobbies alone
I was very excited for the first time,
but it was really fun
I didn't know much about it until now
Really?
I hope the viewers learned a lot about
you
If you have any questions, please leave
a comment
The content of the show is about wanting
to be Paris Hilton
Also Instagram
Yes, I want to do Instagram
Don't make it blonde
Really?
Please do
Please close the show towards the camera
Thank you for watching until the end
See you again
This was LUNA LIGHT
Bye bye