Thank you.
The dance is getting more and more
difficult
I'm so tired
What kind of choreography is it?
The choreography for the future
I forgot
There is no choreography for the future
I can use it
The choreography for the future
Up up up...
What?
Ah ah ah.
Wow!
I can't stop eating!
Really?
Look! Look!
Look!
This is the best!
This is a must-have item for a bare
face.
Even glasses can be seen.
Wow!
Yay!
Thank you for watching!
I recommend it a lot.
Let's eat it.
It looks delicious.
It looks like a fake.
I was surprised.
It's shaking.
Hello.
You did a great job.
Thank you.
Wait a minute.
It's amazing.
It smells so good!
Smells so good!
It's so good!
We can't smell it.
Can we eat it now?
I don't think there's anything for me.
I didn't say anything.
I just saw a red and green person.
I was just passing by and I saw
something.
There was a drink and a lunch box.
I was wondering what it was.
I found it.
You found it?
Thank you very much.
This is the best.
Please have a seat.
This is not for one person.
Is this for one person?
This is a feast.
Thank you very much.
Let's go.
It's shining.
Please notice this shine.
It's a shiny one.
Please take a picture of me.
It's beautiful.
It's a portrait.
It's a portrait and a beef jerky.
It's the best.
Let's eat.
I'm going to eat.
Wow, it's the best.
Let's eat.
Thank you.
Let's eat!
Yummy!
It's soft and delicious!
Please subscribe to my channel!
I'm impressed.
I'm impressed. It's delicious.
It's soft and chewy.
It's a little bit chewy.
It's very oily.
And it's crispy.
I like the smell of charcoal.
It's so good.
It's the best.
It's like eating in real life.
It's a totally different store.
It's so good!
Can I eat it?
The sea urchin that you eat in the sea
is so good!
You look so happy!
I wonder what it is.
It was great.
How many times do we have to go?
We have to go many times.
It's really good.
There is a tail soup.
There is a cat over there.
How can I get there?
I don't know.
My eyes!
I can't see it.
I'm hiding it.
Driver, thank you so much for using my
carì
You Carnegie
I kh的時候
Thank you for watching so far. See you
next time with a delicious video.
Soup
Yay!
I ate it
This is good
Yay! Today I'm the first one to put on
makeup
I always put on makeup at the end, but
today I'm the first one
Sideburns
I know that everyone is nervous
Oh, there's soup.
Oh, what soup was it?
Haru-be-san, what soup?
Ponkotan soup. What was it?
What was it?
The one with meat.
Tamegetan soup?
No, I forgot the name.
I'm wearing a hat today.
I'm going to be a wetty.
It's a Pankaji of Tokisai.
Gray is cute.
A cat adopted.
I heard the voice of joy when I did my
makeup.
I wonder what it is.
Will it happen from now on?
I'm happy to know that it's a little
bit.
Because it's a little bit strange over
there.
I'll make you smell it.
I'll make you eat delicious soup.
Let's change clothes.
Where is the green onion?
Where is that green onion?
Oh, outside.
Outside?
Wow!
Awesome!
Akina's tree.
Wow!
It's good.
The end.
It's great.
It's being grilled.
Look at the smell.
Look.
It's great.
It smells good.
It looks delicious.
I'm happy.
It's great.
I was thinking that I would be happy if
I could eat a bento.
Everyone is hiding in the dressing room.
They are hiding when they are taking a
bath.
They are looking at us, so they are
looking at us.
When I asked her if it was delicious,
she said,
I ate a bento.
A fish bento.
When I asked her if the meat was
delicious, she said,
I ate a fish.
This is the final.
Let's eat beef tongue and finish it.
It's like a BBQ for the last summer.
Look at this.
I decorated it today.
Yes, today is the decoration.
It's been a while.
I haven't seen it.
I've done it many times when I went to
the festival.
Dango.
Make it a dango.
Not a dango.
Today, I'm going to do my bangs.
I've opened it.
The way you wear it is different.
Yes, it is.
Thank you very much.
It's very thick.
Is it spicy?
Everyone, please eat.
I did it.
Yay!
It's ready!
It's warm!
Thank you!
Let's eat!
It's so crunchy!
It's so chewy!
It's so good!
It's thick.
It's thick, but it's chewy.
It's so good!
I'm so happy.
I want to eat in my room.
Luxury!
Oh, it's a low-point camera.
I finished the first bowl of beef
tongue.
I'm wondering when I'll go to the second
bowl of beef tongue.
I already ate two bowls of tail soup.
Today, I'm going to eat beef tongue for
the first time in a thousand years.
I feel like I've eaten 牛 タン.
Something came!
I heard that you've finished 牛 タン 2 杯 目.
I haven't finished 牛 タン yet.
The tail soup is 牛 タン 2 杯 目.
Oh, the tail soup.
It's really delicious.
What about 牛 タン 2 杯 目?
I want to go, but I'm wondering when I
should go.
When are you going?
I'm going to eat 牛 タン 2 杯 目.
What?
When is it?
What is this devil's whisper?
I want to eat it too.
now?
It may not be now, but before it goes
away.
Let's go.
It's really delicious.
I was talking to Piyo today.
It's Katamin today.
Katamin?
Ah!
What?
You've met Sako-chan, haven't you?
I don't know.
Katamin
I don't remember her name
I met her in spring
I didn't know that
Today is Katamin
I was talking about that
I was wearing a skirt
Only on the left side
Katamin was in front of me
and we were in the back
I said it naturally
I was like
You definitely don't hit my head with
theChooni custume!
I'm Kanamin.
Don't get it wrong.
Kanamin is Kanamin.
Your eyes are so cute!
So funny!
Please look forward to when we'll go to
the second one!
Please look forward to it! Bye bye!
I'm done with my hair and makeup!
I'm done!
I'm going to drink the tail soup.
I'm done with my make-up.
I got my hair done for the second hour.
It's actually really long.
I'm going to make it a little bit
longer.
I think this is the next hair style of
the new girl.
I haven't made my bangs 100% firm yet.
I went to the music room and Julia said
she was going to get some beef tongue.
So I'm going to go get some.
I'm going to get some beef tongue.
I'm not done eating.
It's good.
It's so good.
The meat is good.
Can I eat it?
I ate about 5 pieces.
Thank you for the meal.
Thank you for watching.
2nd beef tongue.
I'm going to big it up again, again.
hebben NEVER SAID salty sirloin
From now on, forever!
There's beef tongue in the middle.
There's no beef tongue in the tail soup.
It's cold.
Do you want to eat now?
It's a rehearsal.
I'll be scolded if I don't go to
rehearsal.
It's a rehearsal.
The rehearsal is over.
Thank you for your hard work today.
Please look forward to it.
We are Hatsune Miku TV, the group of 6
members of Hatsune Miku.
Thank you for your cooperation.
The first performance of the second half
of the year
Everyone, please look forward to the
second half of the year!
Please look forward to it!
Thank you very much!
I'm not done with my hair.
It's the final.
Isn't it too early?
The final of the tour.
Oh my god!
I ate a bite of mochi.
Gat.
Got?
Oh, it's good.
It's good to have a good body.
It's amazing.
Thank you for watching.
I love the moon on my chin.
There's a moon on my chin!
Oh my god!
I'm so excited!
What's this?
Beef tongue.
It's a beef tongue stick.
It looks like a snack.
It's a canned tuna.
It looks good.
There's also a cruller.
I've never seen this before.
I got mine.
Look at this.
It's amazing.
It's neatly arranged.
It's detailed.
I want to eat mochi.
I love mochi.
I can't eat tomorrow.
What do you want to eat tomorrow?
I have a shooting tomorrow.
I don't want to eat tomorrow.
I'm talking about it, but it's the third
time I've had tail soup.
I love mochi.
It's called Sweet God.
I see.
Wow.
Get, get, get, get, get, get.
The pudding looks so good.
I'll try it.
It must be good.
Wow.
I'll eat a lot.
I found a pineapple-flavored jelly!
I shouldn't eat this here. I'll eat it
at the academy.
There were a lot of cold jellies.
I drank Zunda shake, ate beef tongue,
and drank tail soup.
I'm enjoying Sendai.
I brought a hair clip.
What do you think?
Something's wrong.
I'll fix it later.
This is coffee.
Let's eat.
It's a hotel.
I'm so excited!
Everyone, I'm not wearing any lipstick.
So cute!
I think this position is cute for Twin
Tail.
Oh, it's a little long?
Yes, it is.
Certainly, if it's this roll, it's cute.
This is cute.
Let's do our best.
It's the last one. It's the final.
Is it the final?
Yes.
Aki-chan is decorating her hair.
She is decorating part of her costume.
This time, it's all.
The ribbon of ankle and sleeve.
I'm wearing it.
Piyo-chan is done.
Cute.
It's the real thing.
I'm going.
Let's go.
I'm going to read the script.
Do you read it?
Yes.
I'm going to read it.
The worst.
Today, I'm going to read the script.
Thank you for coming to the Summer Heart
Get Tour 2022.
Lock on to your heart!
We are Chokimichi NEM!
We kindly ask that you stand in line and
stand in line to give your attention.
We will not allow you to take pictures
or videos of the audience.
Please enjoy your performance in your
own seat.
You are not allowed to jump in the hall.
Please enjoy your performance with your
hands in the air.
Please be careful not to disturb the
audience.
Please follow the instructions of the
staff.
We will start the performance soon.
Today is the final performance of the
tour.
Let's enjoy the show!
We will enjoy the show.
Please wait for the show!
It was really fun, this time.
Thank you for watching.
Please.
Kanami, Kiri, Katsumi, Mito, Aki, Miori,
Chiyo, Toki, Miki, Miki, Sato, Kan!
Thank you.
Okay, thank you.
Okay, then, please look to the right.
This is the fifth class.
Thank you.
Finally.
Final!
I ate a lot of beef tongue, so I will do
my best with beef tongue power!
I will do my best with beef tongue
power!
I ate a lot of beef tongue, so I will do
my best with beef tongue power!
Thank you for watching!
I feel a little sad, but I really
enjoyed the whole show.
I'm really happy and full of emotions.
Thank you very much, everyone.
Thank you very much.
We will have a one-man live at Makuhari
Messe on October 22nd.
Let's go! We are Makuhari Messe, the
super-technical live show.
Aiming for the stars.
Oh, I see. Aiming for the stars.
The star has been banned.
Have you listened to it?
Thank you very much.
If you haven't listened to it yet,
please listen to it at each music
streaming site.
Thank you very much.
We are the star.
Please look forward to the 22nd of
October.
Thank you very much.
So, I'm really sad that we have to say
goodbye now.
Wait a minute.
We have a final today.
Don't you want to get excited?
Do you have the energy to get excited?
Can you clap your hands?
Can you shake your hands?
Let's get excited!
Please listen to it!
Thank you very much!
Thank you for your hard work!
We did it!
We went to 6 places.
We went to many places.
This summer, we will be ranked as the
lowest in the range of travel in Japan.
We will be ranked as the top.
We went there and came back.
We did it again.
We are so happy to meet all the young
people in Japan.
Thank you for coming to see us.
We were able to collaborate with many of
our friends from Sanrio.
We were able to perform together.
The space was so cute.
Every time we performed, it was like a
healing place.
It was fun from the beginning.
Mars battery was really cute too.
We made a lot of friends.
It's so cute.
The pavling is...
Everyone is crouching down.
The pavling is so cute.
It's cute, isn't it?
It's so cute.
Thank you.
My legs are gone.
It was a very special tour.
Thank you very much, everyone.
Next, we have a live show coming up
soon.
We'll do our best to meet you there.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for the tour.
See you soon.
Bye bye.
That's amazing!
My favorite Pick Me reuse!
I hope to deliver this song to as many
people as possible.
Through this MAKUHARI MESHIA,
I want to make a step up to the next
level.
I want to show a good performance so
that we won't lose to this company.
I'm really looking forward to seeing the
smiles of the young people.
I want to make a lot of memories and
memories.
I think it would be fun if the six of us
could go to various places.
On October 22nd,
Let's go!
TokiSan MAKUHARI!
We're waiting for you!
Subscribe to our channel!
I wonder why?
When I smile, it's like the world is
shining
I can relax by turning the umbrella
Otherwise, I can't walk
Someone is crying somewhere
I'm getting wet again
Isn't it cold?
Someone is crying somewhere
I want to share my feelings with you
The scenery I don't know before my eyes
Let's go anywhere
Goodbye
Thank you for yesterday
The town after the rain is colored
I was painting a fragment of the future
on the canvas of my heart
I will guide you
The reason why I sang
When you get lost, remember it
immediately
Even if it rains
So that you can laugh
Let's go anywhere
Thank you for watching!
I wear a rainbow dress