Collaboration Project! Kaho Kobayashi of Log Log DIY
Collaboration Project! This time, we would like to share with you a video clip of the YouTube channel "Log Log DIY" which started on May 8, 2012.
How are you all doing?
How are you all?
Hello everyone!
It's such a beautiful day today.
Insects, too.
Insects are flying around... on such a nice day.
What a surprise!
This time
I tried my hand at DIY!
It's called "Log Log DIY."
It's my first time to try it.
I really want to do it right.
I'm going to build it by myself.
I do everything myself.
I'm going to do a real DIY by myself.
I'm going to do DIY.
I'm just...
I thought I'd start with the outfit.
I've equipped myself!
Look at this!
What do you think?
I've equipped myself with this outfit!
The shoes are really hard.
really hard, for example.
It would be save when things fall on it.
I've never worn shoes like this before.
I got it!
The tips of the blades!
Amazing!
Don't kick people's shins with these!
Anyway, I'm going to enjoy doing it!
This is my first DIY project
I don't know if I can make it well
I'm not sure if I can do it well, but I'm willing to give it a try!
I'll do my best!
Let's start filming!
This time
I'll be the first DIYer on this channel.
As a DIY first timer
I'm going to try my best
I'm going to give it a try!
My original helmet is completed!
The point is, of course, this!
It is a standing "K"!
This is "K" of "KOBAYASHI Kaho".
I wanted to make the "K" stand up.
If you turn around...
You can see the "P" in "P".
So, no matter where you are
I drew the "K" so that it is easy to see and find.
I drew this picture.
When I put it on
It looks like this!
I imagined it like a helicopter propeller
like a propeller of a helicopter.
I didn't imagine it at all! (lol)
You lied!
I lied...
Like this.
It's called a jaan.
You don't see people wearing this helmet very often.
You've probably never seen it!
Original Helmet
Please try to make your own helmet!
Check out the video below to see it in action!
Check out the video!
See you later!
Next up...?
Please watch while guessing what Mr. Kobayashi is making!
The moment the blade enters
I get really nervous when the blade goes in.
It's so much fun...!
Does it feel good to cut?
It feels great!
It's really spicier than I thought it would be.
Oh, it's just a...... It's like...
It's like when you go through a ticket gate.
That's how spastic it is.
It's a lot of fun!
Even girls can do it!
After this, I'll be back for more.
I don't know what I'm going to do or not...
You'll see what I do and don't do in the video.
You'll have to wait until you see the video to find out what we do and don't do!
A short break!
I made karaage bento!
Let's eat!
White rice first!
Here we go!
Looks delicious!
From the left corner of the white rice
I'm going to attack!
There were 5 pieces of fried bean curd!
Delicious!
What's been the most fun so far? Of course!
Sawing was fun, but
Personally, I enjoyed the sawing
Cutting it down to the halfway point
To clean up the bumpy parts
I used to use a tongsaw to clean up the bumpy parts.
I really liked it, and it was fun to do.
It was fun work.
I don't know.
When I did it with a hammer, it was like...
It was really like shaké flakes.
It felt really good to see the wood flattening out.
It felt really good!
Do you like DIY now? DIY a little
I'm a little interested in DIY!
I don't know if I can do it or not.
I'm enjoying it, but if I was doing it alone
But if I had to do it alone, I'd be a bit sketchy.
"Someday!" And then I'd do it.
I'm not sure I'll be able to put it together
I don't think I could do it.
But I was interested in it.
I thought I'd like to try it!
Here we are
Under a nice sunny sky
I'm eating well.
Would you like to share a meal with us?
Let's eat!
I love rice!
Delicious~!!!!
End of the break! Last DIY!
Please watch what Mr. Kobayashi is making!
It's just a little bit...
I'm getting used to it.
A little bit like this
I can cut smoothly and quickly now.
He told me a while ago that he got used to it.
in the blink of an eye.
He said he was going to start assembling now.
I'm already feeling
I feel like I've already done DIY!
Is there anything you would like to make as a DIY project? I would like to make a shelf.
I'd like to make a shelf where I can put books and stuff.
I don't read books that much (laughs).
Some kind of tiny bookshelf.
I'd like to make a shelf where I can put small things.
I'd like to make a shelf for small things!
How did you feel about the DIY project?
I really wanted to make a small bookshelf.
I said before I made the video.
I was really a DIY beginner.
I wondered what kind of things I could make today.
I thought I could do more than I imagined.
I had a lot of fun.
I'm a little bit like this.
Today, I had a mentor, Mr. Kobayashi
Mr. Kobayashi, my senior, was there to teach me.
I was able to make it without any worries.
I thought, "Next time, I'll try to make it by myself.
I thought I'd like to try making something by myself next time!
Tools and stuff.
Electric... screwdriver!
Impact driver!
I really want to get one!
I want to stop by Home Depot!
You improved in a day!
You really did.
When I was doing it
You showed me little by little how to do it.
I did exactly as he said.
I got better. !!!!
When I hit that screw
I was able to do it very smoothly
I was so happy!
I'll probably talk about it a little bit
I think I've already told you how it turned out
I'm sure I'll be telling you all about it.
Please check out the Log Log DIY video to see how it's going!
Please check out the Log Log DIY video!