Ebichu's video
How are you all doing?
Hello, I'm Kobayashi Kaho, 51 years old.
Today is a nice day, and the bugs are
flying around.
It's a cheap day.
I'm going to try DIY this time.
It's my first time, but I'm going to
make it myself.
I'm going to do it myself.
I'm going to start from the past, so
I've got it.
Look at this. I've got this.
The shoes are really hard.
It's safe even if the shoes fall.
It's my first time wearing shoes like
this.
I'm going to make a snow kitchen.
I'm going to enjoy it.
I don't know if I can make it well, but
I'm going to try it.
How to make DIY
I'm Kobayashi Kaho.
This is my first DIY.
Thank you.
I'm going to make a logo DIY.
Kobayashi's video
3, 2, 1
Hello, I'm Kobayashi Kaho, 51 years old.
I'm going to try DIY this time.
I'm going to paint it and make a helmet.
I'm going to try it.
I'm wondering if it's difficult to
paint.
It's a beautiful blue.
What color should I make?
Please subscribe to the channel.
It's hard.
I did it!
So the original helmet is done!
Ta-da!
The point is this!
It's a pole.
This is a pole for the Kobaishi Kaho, so
I wanted to make a pole.
And there's a pole behind it, so you can
see it anywhere.
I bought it, but it looks like this.
It looks like a helicopter propeller.
I didn't imagine it at all.
I lied.
It's like this.
Ta-da!
It's hard to wear a helmet like this.
I'm sure you've never seen it before.
Please try making your own original
helmet.
Please check out the video where I
actually made it!
See you!
The end.
3, 2, 1
Hello, everyone.
I'm Kobaishi Kaho, number 51 in the
Shizuoka City University.
I want to try DIY this time, too.
I want to do my best to make the
beginners feel sad.
Please subscribe to my channel and give
it a high rating.
So, what are we going to do this time?
I'm a little worried, but it looks fun.
I'm going to try it.
By the way, what is this?
This is a electric round saw.
It's a round saw.
I'll hold it firmly.
I'm going to cut it with a saw.
You're good at it.
Wow!
Thank you for your viewing.
It's not fun.
I'm so excited when I see the teeth.
It's so much fun.
Do you feel good?
Yes, I feel good.
It's a spot.
I feel like I'm going to do it when I
take a picture.
It's a spot.
It's so much fun.
Even for girls.
I'm going to do it.
I see.
I think I know what it is.
It's okay.
Wow.
It's amazing.
It's so much fun.
I'm going to paint it after this.
I don't know if I'm going to do it.
Please look forward to it.
I'm going to eat.
I made fried rice with fried chicken.
I'm going to eat white rice.
It looks delicious.
I'm going to eat from the left corner of
the white rice.
Fried chicken is also in here.
I'm going to eat.
It's delicious.
Of course, I enjoyed cutting the green
onions.
I cut it in half when I was assembling
it.
I used tongkachi to clean up the bumpy
part.
I like it.
It was a fun job.
I was doing it.
It was like a salmon flake.
The trees were beautiful and flat.
I was interested in love.
I don't know if I can do it.
I'm happy because I'm with DAIKU today.
If I were alone, I would have a big
problem.
I'm not sure if I can do it.
I think I can't do it when I'm done with
it.
But I'm interested in it.
So I want to try it.
I'm eating under the nice weather.
Would you like to eat with me?
Let's eat!
The rice is the best!
I'm hungry!
Let's cut the legs.
I'm scared because I have a lot of thick
wood.
I think it's okay to cut the same way.
I'll cut the legs first.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I cut it like this.
I'm getting used to it.
I cut it smoothly.
I feel like I'm doing DIY.
I want to make a shelf.
I want to make a bookshelf.
I don't say much.
I want to make a bookshelf that can hold
small things.
I'm done!
Thank you for watching!
Please subscribe to my channel!
I said this before I made the video.
I was a DIY beginner.
I was able to make something that I
didn't expect.
It was so much fun.
Today, I was able to make something
because my teacher told me.
Next time, I'll make something by
myself.
I also want tools like electric
screwdriver.
I want impact driver.
I want to open a home center.
What are the tips for making a home
center?
My teacher taught me some tips when I
was doing it.
I improved when I did it as it was.
I was able to make it smoothly when I
was hitting the screw.
I was very happy.
I'm going to tell you what happened.
Please watch the video.
Bye bye.
It was fun.