I'm going to get out of here.
I'm so nervous.
Come out!
I'm scared.
You're so good.
You're a fairy.
I didn't have a partner to play with.
I talked to my mother.
I asked her if she had a partner to play
with.
She said no.
You didn't have a partner to play with?
I asked her if she had a friend.
She said she had a friend to play with.
I was so surprised that I got a bad
feeling.
Who is the person who has a bad feeling?
I don't know.
I have a bad feeling.
I'm worried about it and I'm worried
about it.
I'm sorry.
The first guest is YAKAN.
YAKAN TIDAL.
I'm YAKAN.
I was born and raised in a high school
in STARDUST.
I'll call today's guest right away.
This is the idol.
I'm the star of the B-log.
I'm the leader of STARDUST.
I'm MIE FUJI TANEMIU.
Thank you.
I'm FUJITANI.
There is a lot of information.
Thank you.
FUJITANI.
The event in all over the country is a
strong event.
I'm FUJITANI.
I'm going to ask you a question.
What impressed you the most about this
year's event?
This is the first time I've been on a
nationwide tour.
What did you do?
I'm YAKAN.
I thought this room was a studio.
Is there a room over there?
There is.
I'm going to ask you a question.
That's good.
You are a fairy.
I'm sorry.
I'm scared of the devil.
Are you okay?
Did you do a nationwide tour?
I did it for the first time.
It was a tour called Tokyo Ikanai.
It was a tour that said you wouldn't go
to Tokyo.
I went to the last live performance in
November.
I was surprised.
You were surprised.
You were born in the year of the rat.
I was born.
I was born in the year of the rat.
I was in a hurry to get to the station.
The person who enters the venue is a
liar.
I'm a liar.
You're lying.
I like to lie.
Let's go out with a liar.
That's it.
What is the biggest venue in Tokyo this
year?
NAKA's Sun Plaza and Sendai's Sun Plaza.
I will do both.
I see.
Sendai's Sun Plaza and NAKA's Sun Plaza.
I will do both.
I talked about it.
When is it?
November 23rd and December 24th.
Isn't it Christmas?
That's right.
Which one do you want to do?
I want to do both.
Sendai's Sun Plaza and NAKA's Sun Plaza.
I will do both.
Thank you.
I'm always happy like this.
I'm a little busy.
I'm not playing.
Is it a joke?
I'm a little busy.