I will send you EBICHU TASASU Kobayashi.
This week's EBICHU TASASU is the second
half of the Kobayashi project.
This is a dumpling with wings.
The first part is a corner where you
just listen to the story of Yasumoto.
Then.
I've known you since you were a kid.
I feel that EBICHU has changed as a
whole.
I agree.
There are many good stories that warm
your heart.
In addition, a new project for the
Christmas college game festival has been
launched.
What will happen?
Don't miss it tonight. Start EBICHU
TASASU.
What should I do with the heart of a
chuuburarin?
Moratorium, moratorium, moratorium,
junior high school students
Add various things to private Ebisu
junior high school
Ebisu Chassaku
Your name is
This program is provided by the sponsor
you see
I want to be trapped in a house.
I sometimes lose.
Trick or treat!
Kobayashi does what he wants to do.
Emi-chutasu Kobayashi project.
Everyone, please say one thing.
It's a TV.
We don't care about the criticism of the
central government.
We will send you the whole world of
Kobayashi this time as well.
I don't care.
Last time, she flew a huge airplane that
she has been longing for since she was a
child.
She did what she wanted to do.
So, are you satisfied today?
I'm very satisfied.
So, your dream has come true?
Yes, it has.
Thank you very much.
Is there anything else?
There is one more thing.
What is it?
I want to talk to my master.
What do you mean?
You want to see your master, don't you?
I do.
I think she is tired of seeing him.
What does Yasumoto want to see?
At the meeting before the show,
Kobayashi talked about Yasumoto.
What is good about your master?
He is a bit stoic.
I respect his performance.
I wonder how he can be so handsome.
I will see him during the show.
She shines so much that she is
fascinated during the show.
She wants to feel more of Yasumoto's
charm.
So, the talk show of Yasumoto started
with Kobayashi's wish.
What is Kobayashi's wish?
Another send off
From now, I would like to talk about
myself with the Master
I made him angry a little
so I prepare something like this
I'm grateful
Ta-da
Saikoro
Yay!
As you can see, the contents of the dice
are
Kobayashi chose a narrow theme that only
the two who are close to each other can
understand.
The members of Ebichu are waiting in a
separate room.
As a viewer, they will watch from a
distance.
Let's start.
Shall we?
I'll start.
Yes, please.
What will come out?
The best 3 movies you watched together,
please translate
Emi?
Emi is a name of a person
We went to see 4 movies together
About 4
The first one is
Your name is
Orange
Sailor uniform and machine gun
Senior's girlfriend
Love story
I went to study
Yasumoto herself, she watches 2 or 3
movies a day
She watches 5 movies at most
How much does she have free time?
4 or 5
Your name is
This is definitely 1
I took you to eat Shorompo before the
movie
That was amazing
It was delicious
In Hong Kong
Shorompo
Taiwan
We came back to Taiwan
We couldn't forget Shorompo
We went to eat Shorompo
Then, we watched Your name
That was good
Your name is 1
Yes
What is 2?
2?
I am
Orange
That was good
Which one?
It's difficult
Kanna was cute
Sailor uniform and machine gun
What is this?
Are you talking about the level of OAS?
Is it a DVD special?
To the next theme
Aound the top..!
Gate Noble
about purse story turn upside down
Thank you for watching!
Gyobanashi
You can't do that kind of strong pose
without Gyoza
Cute
I recently got into Gyoza at home
My dad often makes it
We have to go to your house
Yes
Hane-tsuki Gyoza
Gyoza with wings
Gyoza with wings is delicious
It's like a snack
I want you to make it crispy and
delicious
I make it once every two months
You are a rare character
You should tell your mother
Mom, I can't move without eating gyoza
I'm Kobayashi's mother
Kobayashi's favorite gyoza
I hope you make it
Thank you
I don't make gyoza too much
You were so happy about gyoza
To be continued
I'm so happy
Yasumoto's grateful story
Hello
You're getting excited, Kaho-chan
We went to a strawberry farm with my
family
Strawberry farm?
Yes, my family, my brother, my father,
my mother and me
We went to a strawberry farm and we
stopped by a supermarket
It was near here
It was about my brother and my father
There was a very shallow bath
In a men's bath
There was a shallow bath
I thought it was a bath where you can
take a bath while lying down
I thought so
I went in and looked later
It was a foot bath
So my father and my brother
On the way back from the strawberry farm
I bathed my whole body with foot bath
Please subscribe to our channel!
End of story
It's a good story
Yatsumotoki is getting a punch
Thank you
I'm not grateful at all
It's a heartwarming story
It was a good story
What? What time is it?
I hear something
I heard a sound
Is that the sound of the members?
What?
I want you to do a talk with other
members and teachers
Not with Kaho?
What?
Yasu?
This is a name tag
There is a box
What?
They want to see Yasumoto's funny talk
from the outside
So they changed the members
Yasu is the burden
I will talk with Yasumoto
The new guest member is
Matsuda!
Bye bye! Thank you very much!
This was guest Kobayashi-san! Thank you
very much!
Let's start the talk show with Kobayashi
Kikake and Yasumoto!
I'm not scared!
I've been watching you until now
The next guest is Rina Matsuno
Nice to meet you
Kobayashi-san, you are not going to talk
with everyone, right?
No, I'm not
You're not?
I'm going to watch the special talk show
with my master
You're going to watch it?
You want to watch it, right?
I'm just a viewer
Yasumoto Matsuno's first talk theme is
Yasumoto's thankful story
Yasubana
Yasu, I'm only thinking about that
I'm moved
I'm going to cry
But the one I cried the most was
If a cat disappeared from the world
Ah, I wanted to see that
The movie
The movie again?
The movie again
I cried so much
I cried while making a face
At the back of the movie theater
I remember that well
That's my favorite
The back of the movie theater
At the back of the movie theater
I cried
By the way, did you know that?
The seat that the teacher liked the most
It's the first time
I'm going to sit there from next time
No, no, no
You can't sit there
Why not?
11th place
11th place next to me
That's good
That's the story
Next
OK
I don't like this
I'm sure
It's coming, everyone
Again?
Wait
What's the next guest?
It's coming
I'm sure you've been waiting
Maya
You were talking about it just now.
I'm so happy.
The next guest is Rika Mayama.
What kind of talk will she talk about?
The first theme is...
The place we want to go together
Futaba shop
It's a bit like sumo
I want to try it out
Oh yeah
Yasu is
Yasu is really
Elementary school student
She was really quiet
I know
She was talking to her mom
Her mom was here
I was on the train
I was talking to my mom
My mom was talking to Yasu
At that time, my stomach was really bad
Every time my stomach hurt
Basically
I was like
Yeah, yeah
What? Are you stressed?
No, no
I'm learning
I'm having a lot of fun
That's the best
Let's go somewhere
The food is good
Hokkaido is good
It's just right
The feeling of distance is just right
Thank you
I'm lonely
I'm waiting for another visit
Visit?
It's like a shop
It was a program, but it became a shop
It seems to continue
I'm happy
I'm very comfortable
Thank you
See you
Thank you for the viewers
The next guest is
Aika Hirota
No, no, Yasumoto room
What is the topic of their talk?
The good points of each other
In short
High
Oh, that's what you're talking about
What is it?
The good points of each other
Well, I'm
Yasumoto is shy
To be continued
Yasumoto is serious about her work
I can't prepare in advance today
I feel like I'm in a panic
She prepares for tomorrow's event more
than anyone else
She spends her time for Ebichu
I feel like she spends her time for her
members
Thank you
I'm shy
I'm glad
Yasumoto is shy
I'm shy
She is shy
She is shy when she sees shy Yasumoto
I'm shy
I want to learn from her
I admire her for not being shy
She is very shy
She has a lot of character changes
She was a vocaloid from the past
She suddenly changed
She became a charamoto
She has her own personality and her own
opinion
I admire her for being able to convey
her ideas to others
I want to be like her
She has changed a lot since the past
I feel like she has changed the most
since she was in Ebichu
I feel like the whole of Ebichu has
changed
I'm glad that I can say what I feel to
others little by little
But, I feel like I'm being held at home
I feel like I'm being neglected
I feel like I don't have to regret it
She has that courage
I think that's it
Hirota talks
She is like Tetsuko Kuroyanagi
We are in the same group, so I hope we
can create an environment where we can
all talk like that
Yes, that's right
Thank you very much
Thank you
This time, the room for Yasumoto was
closed by Hirota
It's closed?
What's going on?
Should we go?
Can we go in?
The Kobayashi project is about to end,
so all the members will meet
Thank you for the meal
Kobayashi enjoyed the appearance of
Yasumoto
How was it?
It was interesting
I think I can keep watching
What was Yasumoto like?
He was very cute
Did Kobayashi see that?
No
Why?
The students were also embarrassed
They were together
They were both good, so it was good
Kobayashi was very satisfied to learn
about Yasumoto's new side
Next, Ebichu's special information
University student news
Ebichu's annual event, University
student meeting
The university student meeting's
specialty, the unit project
This year, a new attempt that has never
been done before
That is the draft meeting of the unit
members
This time, the unit project is requested
by the three super-gorgeous producers
And each producer selects a member to
choose from their unit
The unit is decided in the form of a
draft meeting
The result of the draft meeting is as
follows
Now, the private Ebisu junior high
school unit member draft meeting starts
Producer, Kaiki Ogata
Yes
The first draft meeting, the member they
want to select is...
Riko Nakayama!
I see.
She doesn't know what kind of music
she's going to make.
She doesn't know either.
She doesn't know what she's thinking
about.
But she's so explosive.
Riko Nakayama!
Next, Kakuta from Tokyo 03.
The first selection of members is...
Aika Hiroto.
I see.
I saw her in the movie, Hirono
Sentozake.
She was in the movie.
So I think I know her well.
And I think her voice is unique.
So I chose Aika Hiroto.
Next, Tenkomori Satsuki.
The first selection of members is...
I'll go with Mayaba-san
I was in a team of 2 or 3
I didn't know what to write
I wrote the keyword, child-san
I think the youngest child-san is the
youngest, the youngest child-san
I think it's a good start, Mayaba-san
The draft meeting continued after the
second round.
Ogata chose Hinata Kashiwagi, Kaho
Kobayashi, and Riko Nakayama.
Takuta chose Aika Hirota and Mirei
Hoshina.
And Tenkomori Satsuki chose Rika Mayama,
Ayaka Yasumoto, and Rina Matsuno.
Actually, this combination...
I've never seen this combination before.
This is good.
It's getting better.
Yes, this is the first combination ever.
I think this combination is interesting.
I think it's better than my usual
combination.
I don't know much about idol groups.
I've never been on good terms with them.
I'm glad I'm not on good terms with
them.
It's embarrassing.
In addition, the theme and theme of the
song will be given to the unit.
It's a song called Ocean's Guide, which
is a college game.
What kind of theme will be decided by
lottery?
What is the theme of the song played by
Ogata?
and back to glass isn't hot.
Thank you.
Ito Gin-chan!
It's the same feeling.
Eh?
Isn't it something like a love song?
This is troublesome.
I can't say anything.
I've never had an emotional input into
Ito Gin-chan.
Next, the theme that Tokyo 03 Takuta
chose is...
Crab!
Well, well, well.
Crab, huh.
Crab, it's good, somehow.
I can't walk while facing forward.
I can't avoid it while standing
sideways.
That kind of feeling is...
It's a bit of a dull direction.
You're forcing it, aren't you?
Next, the theme that Satsuki and
Tenkomori chose is...
Fish!
It's cute.
It's a fish.
I got it right.
It's a pop.
It's a good match.
I'm glad it's a bear.
What kind of song do you think it is?
As you said, it's a pop song.
It's not that fast.
The color is shiny.
It's a fish with a main title, Ocean's
Guide.
I think it's a fish that's not strange.
I think it's easy to fit in.
The final result was decided by lottery.
Ogata is in a hurry.
The theme is the dance number that any
shy person will dance.
Rock'n'Roll
I think I can do it.
So I'm going to stick to the rock band.
I'd like to try it.
Tokyo 03 Kakuta's theme is a crab.
The theme is this cute shiny Christmas
song.
I'm going to wake up and go to the
police station.
I'm going to make it to the live show.
I want to do my best with the two of
them.
And Tenkomori Satsuki's theme is bear.
The theme is refreshing and crazy.
It's decided to be a party tune.
I think I can do the theme itself to
some extent.
I'm going to split it into different
sections to make it sound refreshing and
crazy.
I'm going to change the subject.
I think I'll be fine.
I'll do my best, so please look forward
to it.
What kind of unit song will be
completed?
Christmas University Theater, which will
be held over two days.
Shrimp-Chu Ocean's Guide
For more information, please visit the
Shiritsu Ebisu Junior High School
website.
Next time, we'll have a big announcement
of the serious news of shrimp-chu
Tastas.
The second day of this broadcast is my
birthday.
Just before the 20th, the members came
up with a new phrase for Mayama.
Gari Gari Ramen Junior High School
It's like a one-shot gag.
What will happen?
This program was brought to you by the
following sponsors.