Yakan and idol!
What is your favorite song?
I don't want to say this, but I like
listening to songs rather than singing.
I like going to various people's live
shows.
The other day, I was with Back Number
and Sekai Noari.
It's amazing to be able to sing in a
live show.
Do you give feedback to your own stage?
I noticed something when I was doing the
interview.
I was talking about the emotions I felt
when I went to the live show.
At that time, I thought, I'm not me.
I'm not me.
I noticed it as a performer.
That's where you first noticed. I was a
performer, too.
I remembered.
I want to see it.
I felt like I was receiving it.
It's completely different from the side
I'm doing.
I don't mean that again, but I
remembered.
It's a good story.
I'm the type to focus on the lyrics.
You focus on the lyrics?
Yes. The deeper the lyrics, the deeper
the lyrics.
Do you have any lyrics that you've been
referring to when you're lost?
Recently, I thought it was good.
There's a song called Kimie by Reaction
the Buddha.
What kind of lyrics?
I'm nervous and I can't think of any
lyrics.
Please wait.
My hands are shaking.
Your hands are shaking?
No.
When you think about the meaning of the
lyrics, the lyrics are important to you.
That's right.
It's a great meaning for me.
I feel like I'm going first and the song
doesn't go well.
I have to fix this.
I have to fix it.
But you know the meaning of the lyrics
and the environment.
You have to deliver it.
That's right.
It's not a beautiful song.
I don't think it's a good song, but I
think I have to balance it.
I always think it's too much.
I want to improve it.
I think it's a good song for a
performer.
I want to deliver the song.
That's a good word.
Don't use it as a good word.
I'm sure you shouldn't.
What kind of job is it?
I think it's a job that can do that.
I just thought you were a manager.
That's right.
I don't know what to say.
I'm sorry.