White bean soup with white rice.
It's like this.
It's a wonderful choice.
The next day.
Good morning.
Today, we're going to Nikkan Sports.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you.
Nikkan Sports.
You usually post articles, right?
Yes.
I heard that you have a lot of
questions.
So I'm going to do an interview.
I'm going to do a project in the
question.
What is it?
Sounds difficult.
How many sushi words can you say while
talking?
I see.
I think it's a little bit ambiguous.
It's difficult.
確かに
Oh, that's right.
For example,
Cute.
That's right.
If you ask a question and say,
I see,確かに確かに,
You can put your hair in it.
If you say確かに確かに twice,
It's one point for what you said once.
If you say確かに twice, it's two points.
I see.
But...
Oh, that's right.
I'm sure I'll get a lot of points.
It's a little bit weird, so don't let it
show.
I see.
On the contrary, if you let me say the
sushi story,
Three points.
I see.
It's difficult.
It's extreme.
What's your favorite sushi story?
Today, we will ask you a question from
here.
Please answer the question.
Thank you for your time.
Thank you for coming to our channel.
I'm always looking forward to your
questions.
I'm always reading your comments.
I'm also a fan of your channel.
I'm embarrassed.
I have a lot of questions.
I'm also a fan of your channel.
I've never taken a picture.
Please wait a moment.
I'm moving alone.
I see.
I'm working hard.
I'm in the photography department.
I've never taken a picture.
I've never used a camera.
I'm in the photography department.
I've never taken a picture.
I'm not good at it.
Really?
At first, I was in charge of taking
amateur baseball.
But I made up the winning scene three
times in a row.
I was so nervous that I couldn't see
anything.
I can't see anything.
This is a fatal symptom.
I have to take a picture of anything
that happens.
I can't go to a scary desk and take a
picture.
I was depressed when I was told that.
I wanted to quit.
I really wanted to quit.
What were your hobbies at that time?
My real hobby?
Did you like sports at that time?
Yes.
I love it.
Is that so?
Did you do any sports?
I went to the field.
On the field?
Yes.
I ran in the field.
Did you run?
I ran 1500m.
I was lucky to be a photographer.
I participated in the Olympics twice.
I participated in the summer Olympics
and the Nagano Olympics.
I like it.
I went skiing and jumping.
I was there.
I went there for about 5 hours.
I was there for about 5 hours.
I didn't think it would end so soon.
I was there for a long time.
It was cold.
How many countries have you been to so
far?
I have been to 25 countries.
Did you go to 25 countries?
I counted the countries once.
25 countries?
That's amazing.
I was surprised.
I had a lot of luggage in the beginning.
I had to bring about 1000 films.
I bought a lot of films from Europe.
I brought half of the film in the trunk.
What?
Film?
I paid 1 million yen for the mobile
phone bill.
I don't have such a film anymore.
It's compact.
It's very easy to carry.
I didn't have to bring such a large
luggage.
It's easy to carry.
You have been to many countries.
Which country was the most fun?
I went to Europe for about a month
before the Olympics in Atlanta.
I went to the Grand Prix series on land.
I interviewed the people who were in the
series.
I was interviewed by a reporter, a
translator, and Michael.
I knew that the Grand Prix series was
good.
I was able to interview it.
That was very good.
I went to Stockholm.
Stockholm?
Stockholm is a city called Ljöpja.
I went there at around 12 o'clock.
I went to the city after the interview.
I took a picture.
It was very beautiful.
I have only seen it in textbooks.
I definitely went there.
I want to go there again.
I really want to go there again.
I took a picture.
I have a picture of us.
What is the reaction?
There is a reaction.
really?
I also want to make a picture that
stands out.
I have a picture of me.
The picture is bright.
I can see it.
I can only see the information of TOKU.
I think it's good to see it.
I see it every week.
I think TOKU's column is the most
beautiful.
TOKU's column is very colorful.
I put a lot of colors on it.
I see the member color every time.
I want to see the color of the member.
I want to see the color of the member's
nose.
eyes.
I think it's very popular.
I'm very grateful.
I think it's very good.
I'm very happy.
I think it's a part of life.
It's amazing.
Do you have a favorite color?
I like red.
Do you like seafood?
Do you have a favorite seafood?
I like fish.
Let's go on.
I'm curious.
What kind of fish do you like?
I like mackerel.
Let's go on.
Let's go to the 5th place.
I like mackerel.
I like anything.
How do you like mackerel?
I like grilled fish.
I like grilled mackerel.
I like mackerel.
What is the content of the sushi?
I'm curious.
I like the shining one.
What is the shining one?
I like the skin.
What kind of food do you like?
I like tuna.
I like sea food.
I like seafood.
I like oysters.
What is the most delicious food in
Tohoku?
I'm curious.
I like mackerel.
What do you like?
I like salmon roe, octopus, crab.
I like sea urchin.
I like sea urchin, salmon roe, tuna,
scallop, mackerel, and mackerel.
I like many things.
I like scallop.
You went to Aomori in May, right?
Yes, I went.
I went to NOKKEDON in Kishima.
I can put my favorite food on it.
I like that.
If you could choose 5 things in
NOKKEDON, what would you choose?
That's a good question.
I like mackerel.
I like tuna.
I like salmon roe.
I like sea urchin.
Thank you for watching.
Next is...
I got flounder.
Flounder with white meat.
Like this.
That's great.
That's a nice choice.
I got this.
What about you?
I got tuna.
Tuna.
I've been making newspapers for a long
time.
I think the newspaper work is amazing.
How much do you think you can get?
Can I ask you about the annual salary?
I don't know if it's okay to ask about
the annual salary.
How much do you think you can get?
I don't know how much I can get.
I'll ask you.
How much do you think you can get?
I don't know how much I can get.
I want to get 3000 yen.
I want to get 10 million yen.
I want to get 300 yen.
I'll tell you.
I'm a p.
很金してくる あ beraberインスアします
1個だ
ます
だそう手紙やる sinceраー
夜ですねあのコロンはですね Today I have a water
festival
のいろんな表記があるんですけど
For example, if you feel like something
makes you elated, you need to change the
layout begins with HiraganaThat's
automatic?
Yeah. This worked perfectly now
The layout is a group assignment with
Fukokopo
Oh it's different from this?
I'll give you a manuscript to those
people.
And before that, I'll give you a note.
I'll write it like this.
I'll write it in 20 or 30.
I've done it many times.
That's great.
That's all for now.
Thank you very much.
Our article will be able to reach many
people.
I'll write it in the notebook.
That's right.
That's all.
Thank you very much.
I'll do my best.
Today, we had a short interview about
the article we always see at the Nippon
Sports Center.
Thank you very much.
It was a very interesting experience.
I don't think you need to be in the
picture.
I think you can see who won the
championship.
It was amazing.
That's great.
I didn't expect the staff to say so
much.
I didn't want to bother you.
I stopped buying it.
I'm looking for a person who can buy a
strawberry in a strawberry store.
I wanted to make it natural.
I couldn't do it.
It was difficult.
There may be some words that you don't
notice while checking the video.
If you find it, please tell me.
Thank you very much.
The winner is Otsubara.
Bye bye.