The next episode will be released on
December 3rd!
Ta-da!
I'm sure I'll watch this many times!
Because, because, it's the best!
Shiritse Ebishu Middle School Ebichu
Star Contact!
On sale now!
Butterfly Effect
The brilliant contrast, the end and
birth
The story of life
New single of Shirito Ebishi Middle
School
Butterfly Effect
Look at that, it's a
butterfly!
Chachachacha...
Kamo-chan, Kamo-chan!
Kamo-chan!
I'm not in a hurry.
The last episode of our first full-
length show, Solmi no Kaoriko, is today!
I'm not in a hurry.
What? The last episode?
The last episode of our first full-
length show, Solmi no Kaoriko, is today!
Zuko!
That banana!
No, I don't want to end it!
What are you going to do?
Oh, then we should ask the person in the
teaching department to come.
Yo! Ayaka-chan!
Ayaka-chan, I called you, so you
shouldn't come.
Well, don't mind the little things.
Ayaka-chan!
As expected of the reliable student.
Oh, that's right.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Kobayashi Kaho, number 11, a student
of Shireche Bisshu.
I'm Riko Nakayama, number 12, a student
Well, Ayaka-chan, you should introduce
yourself.
Well, I introduced myself in Osaka last
time, and you two introduced yourselves
for the first time.
I haven't seen the person who hasn't
been to Osaka yet.
Akgure School
Today, shall we debate?
Oh yeah.
I'll start first.
Please give me a second.
1, 2
Sorry for waiting!
I've been waiting!
I'm going to make it exciting!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Yes!
I'm Ayaka Yasumoto, the 5th member of
the girl group who loves tomatoes.
Thank you for your support!
Next is Riko!
Riko, let's go!
Everyone, together!
I'm Riko Nakayama, the 12th member of
タソリだ.
Thank you for your support!
Next is Kaho!
Everyone, together!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Turn around!
I'm Kaho Kobayashi, the 11th member of
歌う稲穂ダンシングライス. Thank you for your
support!
ソルミのカホリコ! This program is for everyone.
Please send your questions to social
media.
We will answer your questions at the end
of the program.
I will answer your questions, too.
Please send your questions!
OK.
Let's sit down together.
OK. Let's sit down together.
OK. Let's go.
It's a letter of power.
Where is it?
I think it's better to bring it from the
base.
OK. I'll do it.
Thank you.
Now?
That was close.
It's a habit.
A little more from the back?
Is it OK?
You went too far.
OK.
Ok.
So, on March 9th, at the Maguhari Messe,
last week at the Grand Cube Osaka,
Riku-chan and I had our first concert.
So, so, so...
Oh my!
Oh my god!
Stoooop!
We're going to show you the picture once
again.
See you next time!
We held our dreams and love in our
hands, and laughed together forever
I learned that our everyday life would
always continue
The time I spent with you, the goodbye
you gave me
You are in my heart
I wish I could take it in
I was sad, I was laughing, I was sad
But I was able to send it to the end
Thank you
I will never forget
These days
I will never disappear forever
Because we can meet again
Forever
I will never stop
Let's meet here
Thank you for all the memories
I will always wait here
I will never stop
Even if we are apart, we are always
friends
Really
Thank you so much
Let's meet here
I will never forget
Thank you for watching!
We'll meet again, no matter what
We'll never change, we'll never change
Let's dance together
We'll never forget
Because we'll continue to be together
For the rest of our lives
We'll never change, our bond will never
change
Translated by Releska
I'm looking for a girl who's perfect for
a princess.
Prince, I'm not the only one.
Please make a contract with me.
Please make a contract.
K.A.I.I.K.A.I.I.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
K.A.I.I.K.A.I.K.A.I.I.
I want to be a princess
If I do that, will you turn around?
The old lady who was a child
To the stage where I lived
I'm a princess
Thank you for watching!
even if it costs a
thousand
We're the same family
We share the same bloodline
K.A.I.I
Let's do it together
K.A.R.I
We're gonna ride the roller coaster
K.A.I.I
Let's do it together
Really, Kawhi and Riku worked hard
today.
Yeah, we did.
It was amazing.
I told them that I was a teacher, but I
couldn't teach them at all.
I was always watching them.
I made a mistake and made everyone
confused.
Yeah, that's right.
It was amazing.
Ayaka, that's not true.
It's fun talking to Ayaka.
It's fun.
Riku helped Ayaka, didn't he?
Kawhi, Riku, Kawhi.
What? What?
Everyone, this is the end.
That's right.
What? What?
This is the end.
Mom, mom.
We worked hard today. Ayaka, you did a
great job.
We thought about it together.
Ayaka, Riku, and Ayaka.
I cried.
Really?
Actually, I was thinking that they would
be moved.
I was doing it.
But they were crying and getting
stronger.
It was really amazing.
I practiced all night until the end.
Wait, Rit-tan, you're sweating.
I'm sweating.
Are you okay?
I want to be hurt.
Kawhi.
From now on, we will work hard as a
team.
Some people think that they are still
crying and that they are not enough.
But we will support you and grow
stronger.
Please continue to support us.
Thank you.
Thank you so much for coming to the 2nd
episode of the series,
Thank you so much!
Let's get stronger by shedding tears!
Next is Budokan.
And the tour will start soon.
Let's do our best!
I'm going to meet Natchan.
That's right. It's your first time.
I've never talked to you before.
That's fun.
Is it?
Yes.
I'm so excited.
It's fun.
That's it.
I want to talk to you, but Ayaka is
here.
Let's go to the corner.
It's the experiment corner of whether or
not you can see through Kaoriko's lies.
The story about Kaoriko.
There are 12 cards.
Ayaka-chan will get a guess of whether
this is a doubt or not.
If the answer is correct,
Ta-da!
What?
Marshmallow!
A reward!
I'll give you a marshmallow.
But for me,
It's easy to stop the two of you from
lying.
I'll give you a marshmallow.
You can read it.
The teacher at my school is a teacher.
Her name is Fujii.
Next, Riko.
Riko sleeps in a bunk bed.
She is trying to buy a robot cleaner at
her house.
Riko has been stuffed with mochi in her
throat on New Year's.
Kaho's grandpa is a Mitsugo.
Riko has been on the elephant's back.
Kaho's father used to record. He used to
be a singer.
Riko has been on the elephant's back.
サッカーゴン中山選手。 Riko is a distant relative
of サッカーゴン中山選手。
Kaho has scored 0 points in the test.
Riko has been on the bike's slope during
the test.
Riko has scored 0 points in the test.
Kaho is the same birthday as Hidiki
Matsui.
Riko's father and older brother are in
the fan club during the Ebi.
I think it's definitely different.
Riko's father and older brother are in
the fan club during the Ebi.
First of all...
I don't think this is it.
I don't know.
I don't think it's out.
I'll take this.
This is a doubt.
This means a lie, right?
A lie.
And I don't think it's Fujii who's the
teacher of the other person at the
school.
I don't know.
Maybe it's Mr. Fujii.
I don't think it's Mr. Fujii.
Then, I'll take this.
And... Ah, 0 points! I don't think
there's a 0 point test.
I don't know.
Then, I'll take this.
And I don't think this is a 3-word word.
I don't know. I don't know. I don't
know. I don't know. I don't know.
But it's probably wrong.
Rikuo didn't sleep in the second bed.
I wonder.
I don't know. Maybe he's sleeping in the
second bed.
It's not right.
I don't know.
I think so.
Really?
This is not a distant relative of Gon
Nakayama.
Nakayama?
I don't think so.
I think it's a very distant relative.
It's a very distant relative.
Let's leave it.
Have you ever stuffed your throat?
I don't know.
I wonder. I'll leave this.
All of this? Really?
I wonder if it's a trap.
I don't know.
But it's the same as Mioji.
But there are many friends.
I don't know.
If you're a relative, you should talk
about it.
I don't know.
But you might not know.
But think about Riko-chan's story.
Let's put it aside.
So all of these are true?
I think this is true.
What do you think?
Is this really okay?
What?
Final answer?
Then answer from the face.
This is...
This is the robot cleaner that I'm
trying to buy at my house.
It's true!
That's great!
I don't know if I'll buy it, but I want
it.
I want it.
This is true.
Ayaka, you're right.
I'll put this down.
I'll do this one too.
This is the same birthday as Matsui.
Right?
It's true!
I was told it was June 12th, so it's the
same.
That's great.
That's correct.
Riko has had a stick stuck in her throat
on New Year's.
It's a lie!
If it's a lie, it's going to be a
disaster.
What is it?
It's a lie!
It's a lie.
I was worried about this.
Riko is a distant relative of soccer
player Gon Nakayama.
It's a lie.
I should have taken it without
hesitation.
Riko has been hit by a folding bicycle
in a magazine interview.
It's true.
Thank you.
What happened to that bicycle?
Folding bicycle? It's still there.
It's still there.
It's still used.
It's still on.
This is true.
Let's go with this.
Riko's father and older brother are
entering the fan club of Aibichu.
That's true.
I've heard that before.
You've heard that before?
I thought it was a lie.
I see.
Riko has been on the elephant's back.
That's a lie.
It's a lie.
That's really not much.
There were only four.
Ayaka is the only one who's right.
No, no, no.
It's not true.
There's this one, and this one is true.
No, no, no.
That was dangerous.
Oh, I see.
So all of these are true?
So the truth is,
you got it right, but the lie was mixed
in?
Yes.
Oh, you didn't choose?
Oh, I see.
That's too bad.
Shall we move on to the next segment?
Let's end it here first.
Oh, right.
That was the experiment segment of
Kaoriko's Lies, Can You See Me?
Yay!
Now, the next segment I suggested...
What is it?
The segment is...
Arm-sleeves!
Are you happy?
I'm happy!
Let's clean up.
Let's do it on the desk.
Like this?
I'm done.
Let's clean up.
I'll do it.
Thank you.
No.
Let's do it.
They're good at arm wrestling.
They're good at it.
Arm wrestling is this?
It's not a bad thing.
It's a good thing.
They roll down.
They're a good match.
Let's start with KABUCHAN.
AYAKA-CHAN is...
TEI.
Let's do it.
TEI. Let's do it.
There's a cat.
It's the first time I've seen a cat in
an experiment.
No, it's the first time.
There's a cat.
It's the first time.
Oh, right.
You're making a good impression.
Then,
Ready,
No way!
I'm so curious!
I'm done with this!
Then, can we do it one more time?
Wait, wait, wait.
Do you want to do the next one?
Ayaka-san is...
Ayaka-san is not a good girl.
Riku is really bad at this.
I'm bad at this.
Well, then...
That's a funny way to end this.
Let's do the next one!
Then,
I'm done with this!
The 6th single of Ebichu Middle School
will be released!
Please listen to Butterfly Effect!
The moment I woke up
What is this? I've never seen this
before
Entry, take one yourself
All your work, guess I'm adventure
There's not much left in the world
It's like seeing something
The steps I thought I'd take
Make me a bluebird adventure
Thanks for watching!
I'm going round and round, and I'm going
to see you again
I love you
It's a cool song as usual.
It's really cool.
But we're running out of time.
So...
It's not good.
Something...
How was the choreography?
The choreography is from Butterfly
Effect.
Butterfly Effect choreography?
Can I talk about that?
I think it's better to have more people
enjoy it.
I'll show you a little bit.
I want people to see our formation.
It's not good yet.
It's not fun anymore.
The way we start is cool.
It's really cool.
I wonder if you understand.
But we have to do it properly.
I want to show you something cool.
Can you do it?
Let's make a cute face.
Cute face and cute face.
I don't know what kind of face a cute
face is.
It's old.
Who is good at it?
Mayama.
Rina is good at it.
Let's ask Rina.
Super modern Rina.
They were dancing.
It's really over.
The end of the experiment.
We don't have time.
So...
Okay.
What?
Today, we have come to the director of
Yasumoto Aika Education.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
Bye.
It's a mess.
How was it?
I was able to listen to Butterfly
Effect.
You were able to listen to it.
I also did a little bit of the dance.
I was able to watch a little bit of the
VTR of Makuhari Messe and Grand Cube
Osaka.
I thought it was reflected in this way.
At the beginning, there were two of us.
We were so close, but the glass shoes
were so tight.
So...
But...
Oh, right.
I think there are a lot of people who
haven't seen it yet.
We'll do the last episode on a different
day.
Really?
Really? Wait, so...
We can do it again?
Yes, again!
本当のラスト1回はまた違う日に...
もう!? えー!?
まあまあまあまあまあ...
何もないのに...
え?本当?
え、じゃあ今日は最終回じゃなくなるってこと?
なくなるってこと!
後1回できるんだよね?
後1回できるの!
やったー!
えー?
本当?
本当本当!
やったー!
え、じゃあ...
え、じゃあ今日は最終回じゃないから...
今度最終回...え?
本当?
えー?
Then... you got it right!
Yes, I got it right!
That's great!
Then... it's about time...
Sorry, I got carried away.
I got carried away. I jumped so many
times and got tired.
Okay, here we go.
Okay, everyone who watched until the
end, thank you so much!
Thank you!
Shirito Ebisu School, student number 11,
Kobayashi Kahoto
Student number 52, Rikon Nakayama
Solimiro Kahoriko
Bye bye
Please watch again
Next time
It's really the last episode
Please watch
Bye bye
Please subscribe to our channel