This week's Ebichu Tastas is Ebichu
Tastas photo part 2
A photo contest where members take a
photo of each other
Then
It feels good, oh no, oh no, oh no
What kind of photo will be completed?
Ebichu Tastas start
Ebichu Tastas
By measuring the length of the
It may dry well after 100 days.
It can be useful only when it has a good
equations.
Thank you for watching!
This program is brought to you by these
sponsors.
Continuing from the previous episode, we
will be separating into pairs and will
be holding a contest to take the cutest
photos of each other.
The members take pictures of the
students in a free setting and decide
the best one.
The pictures are taken by a professional
photographer, Mr. Kunitake, who is also
a professional cameraman.
The members who are the best are given a
camera as a prize.
Finally, the shooting begins!
The pair of Mayama and Matsu are taking
pictures in a free setting.
The cameraman, Mayama, is busy with
something.
Then he finds a bat in the
item.
She is not cute at all, so she doesn't
like bat.
She takes a picture again in front of
the cigarette box.
She checks the picture she took
immediately.
Then...
Let's go.
Are you okay?
You are fast.
Are you really okay?
Apparently, she took a picture of her
whole body.
Now, Matsuno is the cameraman.
She chose the rooftop for the shooting.
Please come in.
I want to be kind and warm.
Oh, you want to be kind and warm.
Matsuno, who is a model and has taken
many photos, gives more and more
accurate instructions.
Please come in.
OK
It's good, it feels like I'm going to
turn around
Matsuno has a secret weapon here
I'll enter here
The eyes
While Matsuno was going to the roof, she
borrowed eye drops from the makeup
artist
I like this one eye
This one?
Stop it
I'll enter here
What is the picture of a secret weapon
using eye drops?
It's good. Oh, no.
Meanwhile, Hirota and Hoshina are
shooting in the classroom.
There is a secret weapon here, too.
That is...
Ref-1.
Ref-1 with feeling.
What a surprise!
The strategy is to remove the cloak of
the costume and reflect the gloss.
Can they use the reflection of light
well?
Not at all!
It's not a
dragonfly!
Hoshina gave up on the cloak and took a
picture near the window where the light
gathers.
This is really good! I want to take it
again!
Apparently, she took a picture of her
favorite.
Next, Hirota is a cameraman.
Here, too, he gave instructions to
remove the cloak immediately.
I'll put it a little closer.
I don't know much about men,
because I'm alone with a girl.
What do you think about this picture?
I want to take a picture that comes out
of the story.
Hirota wants to take a picture with a
story.
Next, he went to the back of the school.
Then, he started to arrange colorful
envelopes around Hoshina.
What is the story of this picture that
Hirota is aiming for?
What kind of work will be completed?
On the other hand, Yasumoto and
Kashiwagi pair...
Oh, I was wrong.
Oh, the video has started.
Why?
Last time, Yasumoto was worried about
the camera's operation.
She changed the location after getting
used to it.
The destination is the castle.
Ready, go!
Why are you running?
Cute!
Good!
One more time!
Phew!
They try to shoot a model running, but
as you can see, the size and focus are
not good.
What is this?
Still, they keep shooting. What kind of
picture will they get?
Next, Kashiwagi is the cameraman.
It's like a club activity.
Don't look at me.
Be careful not to get bitten.
Wait a minute.
Let me go again.
Yasumoto is struggling with the
movement.
Will this pair be okay?
And the Kobayashi-Nakayama pair
Kobayashi was very particular about
taking a picture of Nakayama in the
flask last time
However, they finally realized that the
key point is not to show their faces
So the flask gave up and went to the
ground
When they found a yu-gu space with tires
In this circle, not in the circle, but a
little bit there
The first photo
They really want to put Nakayama in
something
What is this strong commitment?
It seems that the daughter is taking a
picture
Why do you think it's a daughter?
Eh, somehow
Thank you for your viewing. Please
subscribe to the channel.
Because it's cute.
I'm scared.
I don't want to be there.
For some reason, the mother bird has
started to grow.
Nakayama starts shooting.
Then Nakayama called me like this.
Please let me shake it.
The producer of the program said he
wanted to shake it.
Please subscribe to the channel.
Thank you for your viewing.
Kaho, close your eyes.
One more time.
To make her more relaxed, she takes
pictures of the girls.
One, two, three.
What's this?
Close your eyes.
It's better to look at the back.
Kobayashi closes her eyes at the timing
of shutter.
Then, Nakayama...
One, two, three.
No.
I took a picture.
I was late.
She takes pictures of the falling leaves
at the timing of shutter.
She uses her staff to take pictures of
the girls.
After taking pictures of each member,
the shooting is over.
After this, we will announce the work.
Before that...
Emi-Chuu Game Quest
Emi-Chuu Game Quest is in progress!
In the previous episode, we revealed the
characters of the members who appear in
the game.
In fact, this game has an episode part
where you can fight the enemy and talk
to the members.
In that episode, the members move with a
rich expression.
Furthermore, all the lines are the voice
of the person.
So, this time, the members of Emi-Chuu
will challenge the overflowing
character.
They have prepared a lot of lines that
match the character's movement.
First, Yasumoto.
Have you ever done overflowing?
No.
No?
I was a little nervous.
Yasumoto is the first to challenge
overflowing.
Ehhhhhh?
Thank you.
It's good, but...
It's a bit too much.
I think it's a bit too much.
Ehhhh?
Thank you very much
What is your first impression of the
first overflowing
When I say this line
I'm a little bit
It's like a little bit
I'm embarrassed to think that I'm
watching it
This is also the first challenge of
overflowing
Please number 32
Something different
Please do it once
Next is Mayama who has voice acting
experience in anime
Her skill is
After the bath
You look great. I'm surprised.
Thank you.
Next, number 8.
Mayama, fighting!
Mayama did it perfectly.
By the way, what's your favorite line?
Battle part!
I like the system voice more.
I'm Hinata Kashiwagi, the always smiling
toy boy in Ebichu, who is more cheerful
than sunny day.
A.A.O.!
Let's play!
Let's eat!
I.A. special!
This is the end of the pre-recording
that took advantage of the individuality
of the members.
How do you feel about the game? It seems
to be fun.
I'm really looking forward to it.
And finally, the game in Ebichu is
ready!
The game project is at the final stage
of completion.
We will announce the details soon!
Please look forward to it!
After this, the results of the Ebichu
photo contest will be announced.
Who will win?
Both members take the cutest photos
together.
Ebichu Photo Contest.
Finally, the photos taken by the members
are announced.
Let's start with Mayama.
What is the theme?
The theme is a simple photo with a
cigarette.
The theme of Mayama's work is a simple
photo with a cigarette.
What kind of side of Matsuno did he
bring out?
Let's take a look.
This is the photo I took.
The color is amazing
What is this?
Did you paint something?
When I was shooting, there was a person
who changed the color
I thought it would be like a school
uniform
I painted it like a school uniform
It's a sunset
By the way, do you have a face
expression or aim?
After all, I didn't make it
I heard a voice and looked at it
Like this
I can do that face
I took it with a very quiet feeling
I did my best because it was said that
it was natural
Next, Matsuno's work
The theme is a sad feeling on the roof
What is the one that was particular
about Mayama's expression?
Let's see
Thank you for your viewing
Good!
She looks sad
She's crying?
Yes
She used eye drops
No
She's laughing
She didn't say anything
She said she didn't borrow money
I see
She's crying
She looks sad
I see
Kobayashi
The theme is Ginjiro Nakayama
It's amazing
The theme of Kobayashi's work is Ginjiro
Nakayama
I can't imagine what kind of photo it is
from the title
What does it mean? I don't know the
title, but let's take a look
Here it is
I see
It's Jinomirya Kinjirou
It's Nakayama Ginjirou
It's a Japanese-style Gin
I know that
There were many other statues, but only
Ginjirou was left
I see
The other statues were also taken
The only one left is Nakayama Ginjirou
There is such a story
It's not a ninja training
Next is Nakayama Ginjirou's work
The theme is Rinanann pose evolution
Rinanann pose evolution?
What does it mean?
By the way, Rinanann pose
Please subscribe to my channel
The attention is here.
This is the hand.
NAKAYAMA SAKE.
RINANAN POSE.
Did she use the fallen leaves well?
Let's see.
I see.
What is this?
Is this a leaf?
I was asked to cooperate with many
people.
This is the result.
I feel like I'm in trouble.
What is this?
Did you ask the staff to do this?
This is a miracle leaf.
This is a good timing.
It's hard.
This is RINANAN's evolution.
I don't know if it's an evolution or a
experience.
This is amazing.
Next is YASUMOTO's work.
What is the theme?
Your charm.
Your charm?
That's amazing.
YASUMOTO's theme is your charm.
It was a shooting full of anxiety, but
the result is...
I don't know if this is just a theme.
Let's see.
This is.
YASUMOTO's work is a shooting full of
anxiety, but the result is...
The smile is cute, so I put a smile on
my face.
How did you get this?
I ran and ran and ran and ran and ran
and ran and ran and ran and ran and ran
and ran.
Even after running?
I'm chasing even if I run away.
While writing?
Especially at that time.
I see.
It's like a paparazzi.
Next is KASHIWAGI. What is the theme?
Let's do our best tomorrow.
KASHIWAGI struggled to pull out the cute
part of YASUMOTO.
The theme is, let's do our best
tomorrow.
I'm curious.
Let's see. Let's do our best tomorrow.
This is.
Let's do our best tomorrow.
That's good.
That's cool.
That's super cool.
That's not it.
I just said just walk.
I didn't practice because Aya-chan
suddenly did it.
I was shooting at that time.
I was shooting because I thought it was
dangerous.
That's amazing.
That's the first time I've seen it.
Superheroes come home after finishing
their work.
Let's do our best tomorrow.
Because here, the left hand is
different.
That's cool.
This is a cute picture.
I can't see your face.
The back is cute.
I see.
The back is good.
I'm talking on my back.
Next is HIROTA's work. What is the
theme?
I'm alone.
Alone?
It's like a mochi.
I'm alone.
You're thinking now, aren't you?
It's a little different.
I don't decide.
I want you to imagine it.
There is no theme.
I see.
It's a
The theme of HIROTA's work is a
A picture with a story.
I can't see your face.
I'm talking on my back.
It's a cute picture.
I'm alone.
I'm thinking now, aren't you?
I don't decide.
I want you to imagine it.
There is no theme.
I see.
Let's watch Hiro's work.
What's this color?
It's nice.
What's in your hand?
It's a letter.
It's a letter set.
The color of the letter set is cute, so
the background is cute.
I want to use it, so I took off my cape.
We took pictures with all our cape off.
That's the way you're going to do it.
I want to use the color.
But if you make the face more vivid, it
turns yellow.
That's difficult, but I think it's a
good idea.
I see.
Can I take off my cape?
I don't know.
I took it off in one shot.
I took it off in one minute.
I used it as a reference.
I see.
You used it as a reference.
That's great.
What's the meaning of the title?
It's a theme art.
I don't know.
It's a window art.
It's a little lame.
It's lame.
I'll use it as a reference.
Can I use it again?
If someone else has a good one, please
use it.
It's a window art.
What's the meaning of the title?
The theme of Hoshina is a window art.
Let's take a look.
This is it.
Thank you.
I see
From the window, I can see two faces
I wanted to make the eyes stand out, so
I made the back a little blurry
What are you going to do, Chiyo?
I've decided
Window art
Congratulations, you've officially
adopted it
Then, window art
Ebichu photo contest
Photos taken by the members
Finally, the work of the professional is
decided by the
final evaluation by the professional
Who will be the member who will be
honored?
I would like to announce
The first place is
Mayabasa
Teacher, I want to say that the soft
light of the shoulder is beautiful
Teacher, you look at different places
I look at the position of the light
It's now position, how is it, Mayama-
san?
Personally, I want to go to Kyoto with a
camera
You want to go to Kyoto? That's good, a
tourist attraction
It's a really good picture
That's good
Now, how is it, Matsuno-san?
I'm very happy
It's overflowing
It looks like a different person through
the photo
Is it the same person?
It's the same person
Matsuno-san, you are always in a good
mood
I was given a smile
Kyoto was a good photo
That's right, it was surprisingly good
I was surprised
Mayama won the prize
We will give you the prize camera
Thank you
So, Hirota, please say something to end
this episode
I'm glad that everyone is having fun
See you next week! Bye!
Next episode of Ebichu Tastas
It's been a year since we last saw
Tastas
That's fast
It's almost the 1st anniversary
Ebichu is talking seriously
It wasn't like everyone is talking about
their future
I think we can do something difficult
The three of us are looking forward to
it
Ebichu talks about the future
Ebichu Tastas will be back!
This program was brought to you by the
sponsor.
What was your wish?
I had a lot of misunderstandings and
thoughts.