This year's last Ebichu Tastasu presents
Mayama Rika's Birthday Solo Live Special
Delivering a precious live on the 20th
birthday
Mayama Tastasu, Start!
What are you doing to me?
Mayama Rika's Birthday Live Special
That's a frustrating level of emotion x
Solar!
So bodies like yours are so crazy about
you
What do we do with our heart conveyed to
the bellybutton?
Monotorium! Monotorium! Monotorium!
Middle School Mutual Friend!
Participate in lots of things just for
the private Ebisu Eller!
Emichu Goodbye!
This program is brought to you by the
following sponsors.
Ebichu members' birthday event, birthday
solo live
Until now, 5 members have held birthday
parties
and it was a great success
And the main character this time is
Mayama Rika
The oldest member, Mayama
She will be performing on her 20th
birthday
It's the morning of Mayama Rika's 20th
birthday.
Mayama Rika's 20th birthday party
Thank you for coming
What is waiting for Mayama who has just
entered the venue?
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday dear Mayama
Happy birthday
and more
Happy birthday to you
It was beautiful
A champagne present from a voice
training teacher
Thank you
Mayama became a friend of an adult on
this day
I asked her how she felt
How do you feel now that you're 20?
I feel like I'm in a different country.
Have you changed?
I haven't felt any change yet, but I
wonder if I'll know what it is if I do
it today.
I feel like I'm 20 years old.
What kind of live is Mayama thinking
about on this once-in-a-lifetime special
day?
I think everyone can see Ebichu's song
if you launch it.
I think you can see something that you
can't see in my solo songs.
I think Mayama is more fun than Ebichu's
Mayama.
A special stage full of solo songs. The
theme is to enjoy yourself.
I feel like I'm really making a fun live
show for myself.
I'm having fun doing it without thinking
about everyone.
I'm 20 years old, so I've been doing a
lot of selfish things.
For more information, please watch the
second half of the program.
20th birthday. A memorable special live
will open the curtain.
At 7pm, the live will finally start.
Today is the 20th!
Everyone's favorite,
Maenomachan!
I can't speak!
Maenomi!
Mayaba-chan!
Let's do our best together today!
Finally, a special live performance by
Mayaba in her 20s.
BubbleMoon
Mayama-chan's birthday in the middle of
the station!
Let's sing together.
Mayama Rika-chan is...
Mayama Rika-chan is... Hiroshima
prefecture station!
You think I don't know, right?
I'm just saying things I don't mean
Don't look at me like that
I'll hurt your pride as an adult
Oh, whiskey, smoking, sinking night
That's not ours
It's definitely not yours
I'm getting old
I'm a cool man who longs for you
It's not really about you, but
I'm a sadist, a liar, a human
I know nothing but
I'll find it for sure
So shut your mouth up, old man
So, what? You guys are born in Heisei?
You're young
Well, I'm not really that old
Oh, right, recently
Oh, shut your mouth
Shut your mouth
Everyone!
Good evening!
Mayuma Rika-chan's 20th birthday party!
Please come to Mayuma-chan's party!
Everyone, thank you so much!
The night has fallen.
I'm Mayuma Rika!
Thank you for watching!
It's amazing, isn't it?
It's like a dangerous night.
First, we have a song called Roshu
Breaker.
You know, we have a show called Ebityu
Tastas.
Ebityu Tastas is about 20 years old, but
not a girl.
I was told that, and I was given a new
catchphrase.
Speaking of Mayama's catchphrase, what
is it?
Ebichu's high tension girl
It's 20 years old, so it's called girl
20 years old is girl
No, it's up to teens, girl
So, since we have the chance, let's make
a new catchphrase
So, here is Mayama's catchphrase for
adults
Muscle, muscular, skinny, tall
3,2,1, Mayama
And
Ok, let's start
Muscle, muscle, muscle, skinny, skinny
3,2,1, Mayama
So, this is what it is
You can't get used to it
What are you doing?
Don't make me slide from the first round
An awakened warrior raises his guard
against love
Love drowns in low-heeled,
I love you with these hands
I will be so sweet, after you
Thank you for watching!
Let's go!
I'll cut off the sky that's blocking my
sight
High tension, high tension
High tension
Ah ah ah ah ah ah
Let's go!
Ah ah ah ah ah
Shake it, party, everybody
I'm going to love you
Jump! Jump!
Ah ah ah ah ah
Party, sing it, go!
I'm a PINPON
Dance!
High tension
Party PINPON
I'm a PINPON
Let's go!
Party Party Party
Don't you know?
Give me big big bang
Big big bang bang
A big party
Let's get together
Party
I'll be waiting for you
on the stage
Don't you know?
Give me big big bang
Until my heart goes
big bang
and their fashion has been changed
Next it's our corner's angle
The winner is Shinano-san!
Chuchuchuru churuchuruchu
churuchuruchuruchu
Musashi the Beehive died
On the sunken soil of the field
The distant mountain was more
It was a shining, swaying afternoon
The beeslime related to apples always
put me in a trance
I challenged the sun and lost
I was burned, I fell, and I died
The Musashi of the city died
Certainly, Musashi died
The sun was about to set, but the red
sunset was burning
Raise me up
Alrighty, one-two!
Did you enjoy it?
Then, here comes...
TARUZAKE!
Mayama wants to open a mirror to
celebrate her 20th birthday.
Let's have her do it!
Ready?
Happy birthday!
Thank you very much.
I'm an idol, but can I have a little bit
of a drink?
I'll say, yeah!
It's her first time drinking a drink.
How will it taste?
Itadakimasu!
I don't know
It's still difficult for me
Thank you very much Kyoushin-san
She is very satisfied with the mirror
opening
The next song is
The last song
The next song I'm going to sing is a
song that I'm really glad I joined
Ebitune.
I'm really, really happy that you're all
here.
I'm going to sing with such gratitude.
《Magic》
Hey, do you remember?
The magic we used to use back then
I can still use it
The wonderful magic
The magic we used to use back then
Even on a cold night, the days of toys
that broke
Even on a summer evening, just one word
can change it
Because, it's a wonderful day, look,
something is coming out
The song of joy resounds in the sky
What a wonderful day
No matter how sad it is
Ah, the song of joy
Yoro-de-ichi, yoro-de-i, yoro-de-i, yo-
ichi
Yoro-de-ichi, yoro-de-i, oh-oh-oh-oh-oh
I'm going to play the shimo-mo
Yoro-de-ichi, yoro-de-i, yoro-de-i, yo-
ichi
Thank you so much for today!
It's my first time celebrating my 20th
birthday,
but I'm really happy to be able to
celebrate my birthday.
I'll do my best this year too!
Bye bye!
Thank you for watching!
Thank you!
Well, that's all for today.
Everyone, good bye!
Bye-bye!
Thank you for watching!
Sure.
Thank you.
I'll sink into the dawn
With a face made up, I gently approach
I'll send what I believe into the
darkness
Like a wet cloth entwined with a thread
I'll just hold you tight and fly through
the sky
I'll sink into the dawn
A repeat melody, pale smiles after a
face
Nothing more, needs to be protected, as
the boulder histogram
Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
New Episode Coming Wed. 1700 JST
Yoruo här harーSorga attaYo!
Translations by zcatcracker
Thank you very much!
I'll end it with this.
Let's do our best together in 2020!
That's why Rika Mayama's 20th special
stage has closed the curtain.
I was nervous.
I thought it was hard to do a live show
alone.
But I was so happy to see everyone's
faces and their love.
Thank you very much.
The first episode of TASTASU New Year is
a special edition of the New Year's
party.
It's a great showdown.
It's coming from behind.
What will happen in the New Year's
party?
This program was provided by the sponsor
you see.