Vol. 92 "First Real Event in a Long Time!
The first real event in a long time! It's been a while since the last real event, the 7th album "Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku" release commemorative school assembly ~It took 5 minutes for you to get quiet~ This time we will report on the first and second parts of the event on May 11!
The first corner "It will take 5 minutes until we become quiet" is a corner where the members talk about themes related to the album. You have to finish it in 5 minutes without looking at the stopwatch. The member who is the closest to 5 minutes in all 8 sessions of this event will win a luxury item!
Yes, that's right.
There is a box with talk themes in it.
We'll start by drawing them.
Who would like to start?
Well... you know...
I've never done it before.
To be honest, I don't even know what this event is.
We don't even know what this event is.
You should know that.
You're my senior, aren't you?
Look at this. How long does five minutes last?
I can feel it.
Five minutes.
Kazami's talk theme: "Impressions and highlights from the live performance of the album's special feature.
Let's start!
Let's see.......the big show
What did you think?
I thought your voice was different from what I expected.
I guess it's just...
The voice I hear
I'm saying.
The voice.
I'm listening to the voice.
The voice I'm hearing and...
I mean... I'm listening to you on the air.
I don't understand.
I don't know what you mean.
Your voice sounds a little different.
I thought, "Oh, that's what I sound like.
Dance Inter
In the middle of the show, there was a dance part.
There was a part where we danced together or alone.
Yuzuno and I danced together.
I danced with Yuzuno.
But Aya, who came out first, was so cool by herself.
She was so cool on her own.
I want to work on my dancing a little bit more.
I want to be a better dancer.
I'll stop!
Pi!
Oh!
4 minutes 41 seconds!
Mayama's Talk Theme: Thoughts and highlights of watching "Shin EVERYTHING POINT 2/2
Trouble.
I haven't seen it.
I haven't seen it. I haven't seen it.
Talk on a hunch.
Because I don't know.
Because it's him.
Whatever they cut out of this, whatever it is.
I'm living my life, so what's wrong with that?
That's basically Mayama's stance.
Today, you know...
I'm sure that everyone who came to the event today...
I think that the people who are coming to the event today...
I feel that the people who are coming to the event today... are probably getting the message that it's fun.
There's something I wanted to talk to you about. .....
Well...
The other day at Da-ice's
at Da-iCE's live concert the other day.
Yes.
Can I talk about Da-ice's live performance?
You know...
You know, the way people... the way they take words...
The way they receive things?
There are so many ways to interpret things.
It's not easy.
You know what happened to me the other day?
There were so many girls in the hall.
I know a lot of them are here today.
Thank you.
So...
So, it was a different scene than usual.
I couldn't help but
I said, "Oh, it smells so good.
And then...
I don't know...
You know, they're coming to this event today.
Maybe they'll come.
Is there anyone? I don't know.
I was EGo-searching this morning
Mayama said we stink
I'll put on 500 ml of perfume today
Someone said that...
Oh...
I've hurt people needlessly again
I thought I'd done it
Today's venue is...
Excuse me.
It smells good. It's okay.
I've reached the end of my story.
I'm satisfied, so I'm going to go now.
Stop!
How is it?
Five minutes and 31 seconds.
You wasted time talking about perfume!
Yes, I did. Okay, last one, Riko.
Wait, wait.
I'll start with how to use a stopwatch.
Nakayama's talk about the recorded song "Kyurun
This song
I've been recording this song for quite a while.
It was released in March?
The release was in March?
It was released in March.
The recording was done in March.
The recording was done in
July 2
That's right.
We did it before that, during the production of the Famien EP.
The dancing is so cute.
I don't know...
I think it would be really cool if we could dance hard.
So please look forward to it!
Let's see...
Everyone!
Kyururun!
What did you think when you first heard it?
Waka
I can't wait to show it off
So I'll stop now
Ah!
What? What? Huh!
Five minutes and 18 seconds!
The second corner: "Let's decide the number one favorite song from the new album! This is a project to decide "Fans' favorite song No.1" from the songs of the new album. Voting will be done by raising hands up to 3 times per person. Points for each song will be accumulated throughout the event, and the winner will be decided on the last day.
Using the counter and binoculars there
Oh, you use these?
That's why some people are using them?
Is that right?
Okay, we'll start with the first song.
Each of you raise your hand up to three times.
Three hands each, please.
Okay, first of all.
Who likes Anytime, Anywhere?
Let's see...
Hmm?
I'm 29!
Yes!
Yes, 29.
21?
About 21.
Okay, last one.
Who likes Earphones Riot?
What do you think? Do you want to use the last one?
I'll at least use it at the end!
Good job, Waka!
It was...
You're so sad...
I don't think you should look at his hands!
I think you should look at his face!
Let's see...
About 23.
So... I'm sorry to inform you that
It's time for us to end.
How was it?
Well...
I finally understand what kind of event this is.
Yes, I did.
But it's like this...
I was able to meet everyone up close.
Hmmm...
It's...
Seeing you all standing up so nicely and listening to me.
I felt very happy.
I'm glad they've all grown up to be such good children.
~Part 2...
What do you think, after the first part?
It was better than the first part.
You know...
There are more people in suits.
After work.
Thank you for coming.
We've been here for an hour.
We ate Dorayaki.
Oh, they're not dorayaki.
Let's see...
We ate taiyaki
We ate taiyaki.
I had it.
Well, let's get to it.
Let's go to the corners!
Here is the first corner
It takes 5 minutes for us to get quiet~!
\ The first talker of the second part! / Nakayama will talk about the song "Uchu wa Sandagura" (The Hourglass)
Let's start!
Yes, "Uchu wa Hourglass" is...
You know...
The recording was done at the very end.
It was recorded at the very end of the recording of "Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku".
"Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku" recorded this song at the very end.
It's the last song we recorded.
I wonder what it's about...
I don't know...
It's really...
It's amazing.
You haven't seen it? Just now.
Wait a minute.
Objection, objection!
Now!
Now! LOL)
You're really unconscious!
You were watching the judges, weren't you?
No, I didn't.
My favorite is
Waka's
You know...
What?
Where is it? Where is it? Where is it?
Um...
No one knew me back then?
I don't know.
I love it!
And then, I like the part of
I also love the part of
and I also like the fact that Waka sings it.
I don't know. I don't know.
It's a strong song.
I'm so happy.
How is it?
I don't know... (laughs)
How is it? How is it?
How's it going? (laughs)
It's the part where we go from "YUNO" to "NONOKA" to "MAJAMA.
At that moment, there's a lot of notes.
Like the sound of sand.
It's like the sound of sand.
I love that part.
Isn't it very difficult to get the rhythm?
Yes, it's difficult...
You sang it at karaoke.
Oh my god...
It's so hard! I thought so.
It'll be my favorite song.
I thought it would become my favorite song.
It's difficult, but I thought it would become my number 18.
I really like this song.
I see you sing it at karaoke.
I sang it.
Yes, I did.
About the second song.
The first song is
"Koibito Gokko" by Macaroni Pencil.
Like how many places it got in the whole country.
to see if the melody is right.
I wanted to do that.
I wanted to do the one where we see how well we hit the melody.
It came up.
I thought karaoke was difficult these days.
Okay, I'll stop.
I'll stop!
Yes!
Yes! No! Oh no!
Four minutes and 52 seconds.
Oh, my God!
Wow!
Yes, I'm sure I'll be back soon. Okay, Rika-chan.
Let's talk about the talk theme.
Mayama's talk theme: "Anytime, Anywhere," the song included in the album
Anytime, Anywhere
Lately, I've really been thinking about Ebichu's...
Um...
Anytime, Anywhere
Like the last song of the show.
I don't know.
The position...
You're sitting in a good position.
Like...
Anytime, Anywhere
But...
This...
When was the last time you recorded this?
Around this
Around October.
It was October, wasn't it?
Well, a lot of things happen. Life.
So.
I've only lived 25 years.
I hope I can be there for you when you need me.
I hope that I can be close to your heart
I would like to continue to sing with that in mind.
Which one is it?
This one?
That one!
This way!
5 minutes and 14 seconds.
Ah, but!
It's shorter than before.
Kazami's talk theme: The secret story behind the shooting of the music video for "Earphone Riot.
I was so nervous.
I was so nervous about the part where I filmed alone.
Moreover...
The other members were watching from other places.
So...
I was really nervous...
I'm really...
They're really watching us.
The older sister members are really good.
They're really good.
Look at them.
I think I'm doing it, too.
"Let's try this a little bit more."
but I can't do it right, so I'm like, "Oh, wow!
But I can't do it right, and I'm like, "Oh, wow.
For about three more minutes.
Three minutes?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, if I show you.
If I show it to you, you'll tell me, right?
I'm not gonna show it to you.
You know what I mean.
Oh, well...
Okay, a little more...
I'll talk some more.
Uh...
Mmm-hmm.
Well, I don't know.
Well, the music videos...
I think it was posted on each person's Instagram or something.
I saw it there.
When I saw it
I thought it looked great.
I thought it looked great!
Stop!
Ah!
5 minutes and 21 seconds.
By the way, Waka...
How many seconds left? I was just saying.
It was just about 10 seconds left.
What was the number one song?
Sayonara (Good-bye)
is overwhelming!
It's overwhelming!
What?
Where, where, where?
It's not hot!
Wait, wait, wait!
Your eyes are glazed over.
Stop it!
I can't tell!
Oh, no!
It's not the same pressure. 39?
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know.
My eyes are watering.
You're making me all teary-eyed!
Raise your hands.
One more time.
I don't know if I'm doing it right.
Oh, you should definitely look at it this way.
Perfect.
What's your favorite song?
I'm overwhelmingly a Happi Sorekku person.
I love Happi Sorekku!
I wanted to sing "Doichiichi".
I'm old, but I'm still one.
I thought it was my part, but I was wrong.
The younger one is singing.
Yeah, well...
I'm sure you're all thinking it.
Then what?
I just said...
I think the universe is an hourglass
What about you, Waka?
Yes, I like Hourglass in Space too.
Lately I've been thinking about Sugar Glaze.
I like sugar glaze.
I think I like Sugar Glaze.
So...
It's time for me to go.
It's time for me to finish.
I was able to use the binoculars today.
I could see with both eyes
I couldn't see well.
I only looked at it with one eye.
Oh, I see!
That's right.
That's how I'll do it.
Next time.
Wow!
That's great.
That was fun. Watch.
how is it?
Too close...
Ah!
I'm in front of you!
It's invisible.
Riko is blurry.
I didn't think you were this good at counting.
I didn't think I was that good at counting, Mac.
It was a great event!
We're having another one tomorrow.
Please come and visit us!
Thank you very much.
Yes, on this weekday.
For taking your precious time out of your busy schedule.
Thank you very much.
I'm sure everyone has their own
Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku
is a group like this.
something
I'm sure everyone has their own feelings
I've always accepted that.
Through this album
I hope that people will accept the new Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku
With these songs from now on
I would like to make memories with everyone
I'd like to make memories with everyone with these songs.
So please make this one
I'd be very happy if you could put it on a page of your album
I would be very happy if you could inscribe it on your foot album.
I look forward to working with you again in the future.
Thank you very much.
~After the first and second parts~.
You look lovely.
~We'll start over and try again~.
The talk show is over.
How is it?
I think so.
What is it this time?
It took 5 minutes.
The title of the event.
I mean.
We had too much fun.
It took Mayama 5 minutes to shut up.
Really, the whole time
He talked all the time
He kept talking, didn't he?
Really, really
（Aren't you too good at that?
By yourself...
You guys, you're both on your own.
You both did it for 5 minutes.
I was using it.
I thought it was a bad idea halfway through.
I thought it was a bad idea.
So I gave it to you two, and it was exactly five minutes.
And then it was almost five minutes, so I owe it to them.
If I had said "I'm stopping" a little bit longer...
If I had said "I'm stopping" a little longer, it would have been perfect.
It would have been.
I saw it for the first time...
Yes, I looked at him for a second.
It was unconscious.
I swear!
You didn't see it?
It was 19 seconds.
I was looking.
You saw it.
Yeah, but only for 19 seconds.
What about this event?
What do you think? What do you think?
Fun? It's fun.
It's fun.
Well...
And it's your first MC.
First MC?
You were MC the other day, too.
Yes.
For this event.
I'm going to turn the senior members
You said you're going to rotate.
That's right.
That's the role.
How was it? That's all I asked.
That's not true.
Rika and Riko are great.
They talked a lot.
Thank you very much.
It's difficult to be an MC.
Backstage
The first part of the greeting
You were practicing.
You've been practicing from the very beginning.
You know...
But it was fun.
It was great.
I'm glad.
It was a lot of fun.
Yes, it was.
This "Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku"
For the album "Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku".
This was the release event for the album.
Has everyone enjoyed listening to the album?
Have you enjoyed listening to the album?
What do you think?
Through this event, I hope you will be more interested in the album.
to this album
I think it adds a lot of meaning to the album.
I think it will add more meaning to the album
and we will be able to deliver it with more love
I think we will be able to deliver it with even more love
and
I think everyone will be able to listen to it with love.
I think you can listen to it with love.
Please continue to support the "Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku" album
and Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku as well.
© STARDUST PROMOTION