Ebichu's videos!
So, there's a talk theme in here.
We'll start by drawing this. Who will
start?
Well, that's...
We've never done it before.
Honestly, we don't even know what kind
of event this is.
I know that.
But you're a senior.
I'm sorry to say that this is a
competition.
What?
The first round of the competition!
Okay, start!
Well, the university's limit is...
My impression is...
I think it's different from what I
thought.
Different?
I think the voice I hear and the voice I
hear on the air...
I think I'm a little different.
I thought I was doing this.
There was a dance between the two of us.
I danced with Yuno.
And Ayame was the first one to come out.
She was so cool.
I want to dance a little harder.
I'll stop!
4 minutes 41 seconds!
Wow!
I'm in trouble.
What do you think?
I didn't see it.
I'm going to talk to you.
I'm the person who did it.
I don't know how to cut it.
I'm doing my way of life.
What's wrong with me?
I'm just going to do it.
I'm not here today.
I think I've learned how much fun it is.
I don't want to talk about this anymore.
The other day, Dice...
I'm sorry.
Can I talk about the Dice live?
How to receive words.
How to receive things.
I thought it would be hard because there
were various interpretations.
What happened to me...
There were a lot of girls at the venue.
They said,
Thank you, you're very good.
So, the scene was different from usual.
I said,
Oh, it might be good.
Then,
Today, this event is coming.
I don't know if they're coming or not.
I was searching for it in the morning.
Mayama said,
It stinks of us.
Today, I'm going to put on 500ml of
perfume.
There was someone who said that.
Oh, I hurt someone again.
I thought I did it.
Today's venue is...
I'll excuse myself.
It smells good.
It's okay.
I'm satisfied with the magazine.
I'll cut it.
Oh, stop.
How was it?
5 minutes and 31 seconds.
What?
It's the closest.
I shouldn't have talked about the
perfume.
Riko, last.
Wait, wait.
Let's start with how to use the stock
watch.
The release date of the first album.
This album has been recorded for a long
time.
The release date was March.
March.
It was recorded in July.
That's right.
It was done at the production stage of
the FamiN EP before that.
The dance is also very cute.
I think it would be really cool if I
could dance.
Please look forward to it.
What did you think of the magazine?
I'm sorry.
I want to get started soon.
How long has it been?
5 minutes and 18 seconds.
The next day.
I bought a counter and a stock watch.
Is this the same?
That's why I like it.
That's right.
Let's start with the first song.
Please sing up to the third song.
First of all, who likes the second song.
1, 2, 3...
I can't see it.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9...
29!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12,
13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20?
21?
How many is 21?
21!
Yes, 21.
Okay, last one.
Who likes the earphone light?
How is it?
Can you use it until the end?
I can use it until the end.
You're so great, Nono-chan.
You look so cute.
I don't think you can see my hand.
I think you can see my face.
For now...
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12,
13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20?
21, 22, 23.
23!
Yes, 23.
So, it's time to wrap up.
Yes, it is.
How was it?
Well...
I finally understood what kind of event
it was.
But I was able to meet everyone like
this.
Seeing everyone standing together and
listening to each other's stories,
I was very happy.
I'm glad that everyone was raised well.
The next day.
How was it? You did part of the event.
There are more people than part of it.
I think they're working.
They're working hard.
We ate Dora-yaki for an hour.
Not ad-live. We ate Dora-yaki.
Yes, we ate it.
Let's start the first corner.
The first corner is this.
It will take 5 minutes for us to be
quiet.
5 minutes later.
Let's start!
With SunaDoki
she was recorded on the record for the
last expression.
What can I say?
she was really awesome.
I can't believe it.
I was surprised.
Did you see it?
I saw it.
I didn't see it.
My favorite farm is...
Where is it?
Nobody sees me.
I like it.
I like the part of the song.
I also like the part that I'm singing.
What is it?
It's a strong song.
I think it's a strong song.
How is it?
It's a part that connects to the Yudomo
farm.
At that moment, the sound of the sand is
increasing.
I like that part.
Isn't it difficult to get the rhythm?
I sang it in karaoke.
I sang it.
It's difficult.
I thought it would be a box.
It's difficult, but it's a box.
I really like this song.
You sang it in karaoke.
I sang it.
I sang two songs.
The first song is Macaroni's Love Song.
It's not in the whole country.
I was wondering if the melody was right.
I thought it was difficult to sing in
karaoke.
I'll stop.
How is it?
It's a song that's been playing for 152
seconds.
Next is Rika's song.
What is the song that Rika is singing?
It's like the last song of the Ebitube
live.
Thank you for watching.
It's like sitting in a good position.
It's from Anytime Anywhere.
When was the recording?
It was around October.
There are many things in life.
I've only been here for 25 years.
I hope you will be close to your heart
when something happens.
I will continue to sing with that in
mind.
Which one is this?
This one.
Yes.
5 minutes and 14 seconds.
But...
I was surprised.
The recording was over.
I was very nervous.
The members are watching from other
places.
The members are very good.
I was going to do it myself.
But I was told to do it like this.
I couldn't do it well.
Is it already been three minutes?
Is it three and a half minutes?
I can't show it.
You will tell me.
I know.
I will talk a little more.
What is it?
I think it was posted on Instagram one
by one before the MV was released.
The costume was blue when I saw it
there.
I thought it was good because it was
very popular.
Stop.
5 minutes and 21 seconds.
NONOKA said a few seconds, but it was
just 10 seconds.
Really?
What is the song number one?
Sayonara.
It's overwhelming.
Where is it?
It's not there.
Wait a minute.
It's serious.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
Wait a minute.
I don't know 11 seconds.
12 seconds.
13 seconds.
38 seconds.
I don't know.
My eyes are shaking.
Wait.
Raise your hands.
Again.
Again?
I don't know if it's correct.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12,
13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22,
23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 29, 29, 30,
31, 32, 33, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39,
39.
39! Perfect!
I'm a big fan of Happy Soremin.
I love Happy Soremin.
I wanted to sing this part.
I took the stars, but...
I thought it was my part.
I thought it was the Japanese version.
I'm sorry.
I like Uchisumonoke.
I like it.
I like Uchisumonoke, too.
I recently liked Sugar Glaze.
Sugar Glaze?
It's time to wrap up.
I used the binoculars well today.
I tried to look at the binoculars with
one eye because they didn't look good.
Really?
Yes.
I'll do that.
I learned a lot.
It was fun.
How was it?
It was too close.
I can see Momoka.
Momoka is in front of you.
I can't see Momoka.
It's Tico.
I didn't think I was so good at
counting.
It was a fun event.
I'll come back tomorrow.
Please come and play.
Thank you.
Thank you for your time this week.
I'm sure everyone has their own shrimp.
I think the Shiritu Ebisuchu Gaku is a
group like this.
I've been accepting that.
I hope you can accept the new Shiritu
Ebisuchu Gaku through this album.
I want to make memories with everyone
with these songs.
I would be happy if you could write this
one on the first page of your album.
Thank you.
Please.
I'm sorry.
I was filming it.
It's cute.
We finished the talk. How was it?
Yes, it took 5 minutes to finish the
event title.
It was so much fun that I couldn't stop
talking.
You were talking all the time.
You were so good at it.
We were talking for 5 minutes, but we
were so tired that we were about to
fall.
It was just 5 minutes late.
You were talking longer, but it was
perfect.
I watched it.
You watched it at first.
I really liked it.
I didn't see it.
You watched it for 19 seconds.
It was about 19 seconds.
How was it?
It was fun.
It was your first time as an MC.
You were the MC for the first time.
I only heard how it was.
Rika and Riko talked a lot.
It was a good thing.
It was hard to be an MC.
I practiced the first greeting at the
cafe.
You practiced from the first greeting.
It was fun.
This time, the album was released.
Did you enjoy the album?
How was it?
I think this album will add meaning to
the album.
I think we can deliver with love.
Please look forward to the album.