Thank you for watching!
The teaser MV of the new song of the
city of Ebisu middle school, Earphone
Riot, which was released the other day.
This time, we will be close to the
shooting site.
We will deliver the off shot to
celebrate the teaser release.
The new song will be released on the
11th.
IAFON LIOT
This song was made by a composer named
Katsuhiko Sugiyama who created the song
Cinderella
This is the first new song as a group
Of course, the new members are shooting
the MV for the first time
But...
For some reason, the seniors are also
here.
Good morning.
I joined Ebichu 7 years ago.
I should have participated in the music
video.
I was very nervous.
I was also nervous.
I was also nervous while playing the
piano.
I was nervous.
Are you nervous?
I'm fine.
I was very mature.
I think you are the most mature.
I think so.
Thank you.
You are very mature.
Really?
The first scene is a one-shot singing
scene.
It's called a lip-sync, and it's an
important cut in an idol's MV.
The new members of Yamabani suddenly...
She's soPE專 sh taller
Operation
They made very few mistakes, with
meanwhile completing the others becames
a performance on point
So how about Senpai Class?
Um...
Right now...
Geez...
It's our first time doing this, right?
We're all doing so well.
The three of us are amazing.
Butterfly effect.
At that age of 13, we were 2 people who
challenged ourselves to perform this MV.
The shooting of this lip scene didn't go
well for the new members.
When each of us is doing lip scenes,
I feel free.
But I can't do it.
Ayaka-chan is in front of me.
She's doing it.
I'm imitating her.
I'm not looking at the camera.
Next, they are shooting in the water.
It's hot.
It's a sunny day with a temperature of
30 degrees Celsius.
It looks like a shooting to make the
country look better.
This is an old scene.
This is a scene where a girl with a
makeup change.
She's wearing a makeup with a long-
distance.
I used it.
That was the hardest scene.
The adult was the hardest.
I was like an adult.
It was hot.
It ended pretty quickly.
We ate delicious food.
We ate.
We definitely ate.
We ate delicious food.
Hoshina has confirmed.
The hardest MV shooting in the history
of the debut.
The adult doesn't understand.
Thank you for watching.
Meanwhile, at the shooting site...
Yuno, who is becoming the most
mischievous child in the shrimp, is
messing up the shabon ball.
It's cute
It's like a magic sword
It's huge
This is an item used for shooting
They are divided into 3 teams
They will wrap the sword in a shabon
ball
I think it's a little too close.
I don't think it's going to be a good
time to go forward.
Yes.
Ready, set, go!
Wow!
I did it! I did it!
I did it!
Ready, set, go!
Wow!
Amazing!
It's perfect!
It's so pretty!
I think it's pretty!
Like this!
Amazing!
It's in!
Yay!
Amazing!
It's coming!
It's in twice!
It's in!
And the last team is?
It's like I'm not going to succeed.
Yuno said that it's a team that doesn't
seem to succeed.
You're making fun of me.
I'm still here.
Oh, good.
It seems that it is better to do it
yourself.
You're making fun of me.
We can do it.
When I was in the lesson,
I was in the mood of untying my
shoelaces forever.
I was standing up and untying my
Then I was told to take it off when I
tied it again.
They make fun of me.
I'm doing it even though I'm quite old.
These two are struggling with fate.
Will they succeed?
Ready, set, go!
Let's give them a high five!
You're a little bit difficult to react
to.
Let's do it again.
Ready, set, go!
They did it!
Yay!
Thank you.
The filming is over.
The filming was successful with great
teamwork.
Thank you for watching and plenty to
say.
Wow, nice.
Wow, amazing.
It's long.
Okay, cut. Okay.
Perfect.
Okay, cut.
Thank you.
The shooting continued until night.
And finally, the last cut
Thank you
See you again
inner is miracle
Thank you for watching!
I'll give you your milk
I'll show you my hands
I don't want it
Thank you
OK
Finally
Thank you very much
This was our new song, Thank you very
much
The new song, Gear Phone Riot's MV
shooting is in the ranks
The MV shooting is over
Thank you very much
Is it your first MV?
Yes, it is
How was it?
The weather was so nice
The sky was so blue and beautiful
I think we got a good shot
What are the highlights of the music
video?
I'm singing in the middle of the song
And the camera is zooming in
I want you to see that
I want you to see my favorite part
I want you to see the gap between the
cool and refreshing rap part
I really like the shabon dama part
You like shabon dama?
I've been doing shabon dama for the
first time in years
I want you to see the part where I'm
having fun with everyone
Please watch YAHO.LION
Please watch it
The full MV will be released on the 18th
Please look forward to it
Only I will take your advice