This week's Ebichu Tastas continues from
the last episode, challenging the
broadcast reporter!
Excuse me
She is fast
She is very fast ignoring the camera
She is doing a lot of free and selfish
reports
Wait a minute
Moreover, the interviewer of Nakayama
drama appears
What will happen?
Ebitu Tastas start
What should I do?
Moratorium, moratorium, moratorium,
middle school student
Add various things to private middle
school
Emi-Chu Justice
The weather is a little...
This program is provided by the sponsor
of the program
It's good, isn't it?
It spreads in my mouth
The second half of the showdown between
shrimp and chuu
First, we will start with the Kashiwagi
Nakayama pair who reported the dog cafe
last time
They are introducing the menu of the
cafe with Ten
Wait, wait, wait, why?
Nakayama's today's menu is actually
Welcome to Smile Cafe!
That's all for today's interview.
What's wrong with Nakayama?
I really hate this!
Previously, the interviewer who made
Nakayama fall into a pit of fear,
for some reason, has appeared.
I'm here again?
But now, she's being interviewed.
How will Nakayama overcome this
situation?
Today, you came to the cafe, right?
The manager?
Of course.
Of course?
Nakayama-san!
She's surprised.
Can you ask the manager about the menu?
The one you brought here.
What does this menu look like?
I have a request.
I received a lot of positive feedback
from overseas.
Do you often receive feedback from
overseas?
Yes.
That's amazing.
Then, shall we eat?
Sorry.
She remembered it so quickly.
She remembered it.
I thought she might have forgotten about
Nakayama.
Nakayama continues to report while
enduring the fear she feels from behind.
It's spicy.
Is it spicy?
Ten-kun, too.
It's spicy, but it's going well.
It's going well.
That's good.
If you add the sauce of the hamare, it's
more spicy.
It's going well.
What is it?
It's spicy. It's very spicy.
But it's really delicious.
It's going to be a substitute for the
hamare.
If you add this, it's more delicious.
Nagamasa, you're not making progress.
How was my report?
I think it's great.
I think you didn't eat the main part.
The main part?
I didn't eat the chicken part.
There's chicken.
Is it spicy?
It's spicy! Wait, it's more spicy than I
thought!
It's more spicy than you thought.
If you have a dog, you can walk with her
once.
So, please eat with her.
It's the same amount of squid!
While the cashew was being dried,
Nakayama was doing a face that shouldn't
be done in front of the TV
That was a pretty good expression
How was it?
I thought Hinata was really good
She was doing well
It felt like she was being helped by a
dog
Next, Rika Mayama challenges the food
report
First, she chooses the food by looking
down
Oh, it's Yaki-chan Ramen
It's Yaki-chan Ramen
The ramen looks delicious
Mayama likes ramen
It's a Korean restaurant, but she's only
interested in the noodles
It's like making bibimbap
Will she be able to convey the charm of
Korean food by suppressing the
overflowing ramen?
Now, let's start the report of Mayama
We're finally going to start the show
Next, we have a popular Korean
restaurant
Please welcome Rika Mayama
Where is she?
What are you doing?
Hello, I am Rika Mayama
I am the reporter for this show
What were you doing?
I was doing something negative
I didn't understand at all
Her voice is also loud
Can you hear it?
She is very calm
I am serious
This is the Korean restaurant I am going
to introduce
It is located in Lichong-en, Tokyo
There are many menus
It is a popular restaurant
It is open during lunch time
It is sold out
You can go up if you want to
Let's go inside
Please subscribe to our channel
So fast
Don't leave it here
The moment I entered the store, I could
smell the fragrant sesame oil
It's like a Korean restaurant
It's good to smell the scent
Do you have any recommendations?
This is a buffet you can make yourself
It's good
It's wonderful
I want to eat this too
Thank you
Is that rice?
Self service
All self service
You can eat a lot of things you like
You can eat it right away
You can freely add toppings to the
Pirinpa lunch
In a large serving
It's done
It's good
Challenge the food report
The smell of sesame oil is good
It's good
Then, let's eat
It looks delicious
You put a lot on the spoon
I put a lot on the spoon
At once
It's delicious
I can't speak
Delicious
It's just right hardness of white rice
Why do you praise from rice?
By putting all the ingredients on it
What is it?
Like a storage box
In someone's mouth
What does that storage box mean?
This is a set of Mimimba
Ignore it
Red rice soup
I can enjoy it
It's novel, eating and standing up and
bringing soup again
What about soup stock?
Is this just as it is?
It's a set of Mimimba, so you can eat as
much as you want
I see
This one too?
Yes
Wow
Here comes the wife
This is the best
If you bring your son who is a glutton
No matter how many times
It will be over in 1080 yen
It's good for the viewer's eyes
It's wonderful
This is really a good deal
How does the taste of seaweed soup?
There is a very good recommended menu
for beauty
Can I bring it?
Please
What?
Please tell us the taste of soup
It seems that there is a recommended
menu for beauty
How does the taste of soup?
It's seaweed soup
Very seaweed soup
I know
I'm hungry
The taste of seaweed soup is not
transmitted
The recommended menu for the boss
appears
Chorumen
It's spicy Chorumen
Everyone is looking at me
I feel like I'm going to be on the
screen
I want to go here
Thank you for your viewing
I like it
Please subscribe to my channel
You put too much at once
If it's spicy, you should drink the
seaweed soup
Yes, I'll drink it
It's delicious
Please tell us more about the taste
It's very delicious, but we'll eat it
later
Please come to the studio
What are you doing?
It doesn't taste like wakame soup at all
How was it?
It was delicious
The viewers liked it
I wanted to taste it together
I see
Last episode, please wait for the next
episode
2 people looking closely at what to
introduce
Bunny's first seems to be interesting
Please subscribe to the channel.
It is also important to find the
characteristics in your hands
It's a celebration, isn't it?
In addition
Please participate in the play
What are you planning to do by involving
the manager?
Now that the preparation is complete,
the broadcast starts!
Let's call them right away.
They are now in the popular shop.
Hoshida-san, Matsuno-san.
Ta-da!
Are you happy?
Aloha!
That's good.
We are here at the popular shop, Village
Vanguard.
We are here.
Today's product is...
Ta-da!
Ready, set...
Omochiro Ryokou Guz!
That's a sudden change of pace.
Hoshina Matsuno reporter introduces
Omochiro Ryokou Guz Best 5.
Let's go inside.
Then...
Oh, I found a suspicious person.
I'd like to talk to him.
You're going to turn around?
Hello.
Welcome.
Who is it?
Wow, they prepared it properly
First, from 5th place
Not even close
Ready, go
I don't need it
Moshina-san?
Mirei, what's wrong?
Are you okay?
Mirei, at that time, this!
With this mask, the wind...
I got the fun part!
I don't need the wind!
Let's use the wind!
I see, you're back to your normal self.
You're good!
So, the 5th place is...
The mask!
You're good at introducing the masks.
There are many different types of masks.
Please try them on.
Ready, set...
Bang!
That's good!
How is it?
It suits you!
Does it?
I think the wind will get better,
and it'll get better in the night.
And you can aim for the wind too, right?
You're talking like a child.
The mask suits you too.
It suits you too.
4th place.
This key holder is cute.
It's good for your skin.
But this is not a key holder.
What is it?
You can put it on your eyes like this.
It's good for your skin.
I see.
It's a good match.
You said it's not a key holder.
How about this key holder?
Let's move on.
3rd place.
You are not good at cooking.
I'm hiding it again
You can see it clearly
What?
My shoulder is getting better?
I won't show it to you
This is a massage that you can relax
your shoulder by using this.
It's a good thing!
And this part is a roller.
I see.
That's a good explanation.
You can relax your shoulder by rolling
it.
And this is convenient for carrying.
Matsuo's doya is so big.
I'll bring it.
It's perfect for Nekowasaki.
Matsuo, stop it.
Next.
The second one.
It looks delicious.
Ready, set, go.
Excuse me, this is not a food.
Good timing.
This is a neck pillow.
Neck pillow.
It's a sweet shrimp.
Sweet shrimp?
Only for shrimp.
I have it.
Good.
It's good.
Shut up.
By the way, Mayama has it.
And...
Mayama has it. Is it a shrimp?
She has it.
How does it feel to use it?
It's the opposite.
How was it, Kasumi?
It's fluffy, but it feels good to touch.
It's like it's slippery.
It's slippery.
It feels good to touch.
Can I go to the next station?
Yes.
Next station is Kiyonari.
Kiyonari, the first station.
The two people who are free to choose
the next station will announce the first
station of the travel goods.
Kiyonari, the first station.
Oh, I have to wear sunglasses.
Oh, wait a minute.
I can hear the sound of the train.
Wait a minute.
I'm sweating.
You can see the sweat.
The first station is...
Ta-da!
This is it.
This is the rucksack.
We're going to the transparent part of
the rucksack.
You can put your favorite travel items
and idol goods in here.
If you close the door, you can put your
favorite travel items and idol goods in
here.
You can make your own unique look.
You can appeal to people.
We want to show our goods to people who
are watching us on the show.
So we decided to put our goods in here.
Are you angry?
No, I'm not angry.
She is angry.
If you are interested in our goods,
please come to our shop.
Thank you very much.
We will return it to the studio.
I can see the progress of the show.
Wait a minute.
It was good to bring goods from the
seat.
It was good.
The four reporter battles are over.
Who will be chosen as the best reporter?
This is the announcement of the best
pair of reporter battles.
Please announce it to this person.
Please.
So, it's the manager of Sano. Thank you.
Long time no see.
Please announce it to the manager of
Sano.
Please announce the best pair.
The winning team is...
Hoshina Matsuno pair.
Congratulations!
Hoshina Matsuno pair. Congratulations!
The winner is Hoshina Matsuno pair.
And the special prize will be announced
by Sano manager.
Sano, please announce the special prize.
I will announce the special prize.
Team Nakayama.
Congratulations!
Why didn't you say your name?
Sano, what does this mean?
I thought you were doing your best.
I don't understand.
There was no reason why you didn't say
your name.
No, I was doing my best.
But, you have a grudge against him.
You have a grudge against him.
You cried.
Sano, you made up with Nakayama.
You want to make up with him, right?
Yes.
Do you really think so?
You think it was bad to make him cry,
right?
Yes.
You think so.
You have been sorry for Nakayama since
that day.
Yes.
You are a good man.
Do you want to make up with Nakayama?
Yes.
Thank you.
The legendary Ikon battle will be
decided tonight.
The moment of history is now.
I'll show you my best.
Please wait.
Thank you for watching.
Enichu Game Quest
The game of Ebichu, Ebichu High School's
own Ebichu High School's Armored Air
Force Association, is finally starting
its live stream!
So this time, the Ebichu members will be
challenging the Episode Part!
In the Episode Part, you can choose from
a selection of items and have a
conversation with the members.
If you clear each stage, you can get
useful items in the game!
First, Mayama will be challenging her
own episode!
I think everyone is sometimes glaring at
me.
That's right.
No, I'm not.
Are you not glaring at me right now?
No.
It's okay, I'm not glaring at you.
Your eyes!
You're the cutest!
I'm not glaring at you, I'm looking at
Mayama!
I'm going to run away!
As expected of me.
Wow, that's amazing.
This is really good.
You can keep it up.
Keep it up.
I'm done.
I think you need to read the atmosphere.
What did you think of the episode part?
I thought that I was a very troublesome
person when I was capturing myself.
Next is Hirota's challenge.
Hi!
Perfect match!
It's similar!
It's right, it's right.
Cute.
I'm embarrassed.
It's cute.
I can do it by touching.
If you can communicate well, you can
follow commands.
If you follow commands to stroke your
head within a limited time, you can be
closer.
Why can't I stroke?
Oh my god.
I'm so excited!
This is amazing!
Each member's episode will be added more
and more!
Please look forward to it!
Our game, Shitsugeki! Shiretsu Ebisu
Junior High School Usofuki Association
has finally been released!
Everyone, please try playing it!
Everyone, let's go!
A-cho-macho!
Next time, we'll give a refreshing
project to members during the tour!
Screaming out loud!
Tears flowing!
Big applause!
Will they be able to refresh themselves?
This program was provided by the
following sponsors.
Akie-chan is amazing.
I want to be a brunch reporter.