Thank you for watching!
Enjoy there
Thank you for watching until the end.
Have a nice day!
I was really nervous about what to talk
about in the first episode.
Yakan was very friendly and asked me a
lot of questions.
I don't have a chance to talk about
myself.
I often do live streaming, but I don't
have much time to talk about what I
think.
I had a great time talking with him.
It's different.
It's my first time, but I can't do it.
I'm sure you can do it.
When I gave you a few of my words, I
thought you were taking care of your
words.
I wanted to put my words in somewhere,
but I got stuck in it.
I always want my words to reach you as
much as possible without
misunderstanding.
I often talk to various people.
Sometimes I think that I can't reach the
feelings I want to deliver to each
person.
I try to talk to you as carefully as
possible.
I'm taking care of my words.
I've always liked sweets, but when I
first joined Crown Pop, I was reluctant
to bring them home.
But recently, I've been found out that
many people like sweets.
So I'm happy to bring my favorite sweets
to the school's school.
I wonder what the others will think.
But they're all reluctant to bring them
home.
I'm the type of person who says, thank
you.
Are you OK?
Don't worry, I'll be OK.
definetely
I was wondering about this.
I talked about the three major elements.
I think you know that this girl cares
about this.
The member, Tanaka Saho, has a
mysterious part.
I wanted to ask Saho a lot of questions.
Saho is very versatile.
She is good at drawing and cooking.
She is very good at cooking.
I've never asked her what she likes the
most.
I want to ask her.
Here, tap.
A series of...
I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm a bit of a
slacker.
A slacker.
Well, I'm not sure...
among the staff members...
What should I say...
I think there are many people who have
the same interests in music.
The other day, I talked about
UCCA's Riju Murahoshi and the World's
End's Dome Tour.
I want to talk about music.
I don't know which music you like yet.
I want to recruit you.
I want to talk about many things.
Please subscribe to my channel!
What was the summer like for you?
We did our biggest concert in the
history of Kurapo on July 24th.
The biggest?
Yes, we had a concert at Toyosu Pit.
What did you come to?
Toyosu.
You didn't get any money from Toyosu,
did you?
No, I didn't.
You didn't get any money from Toyosu.
But we did a live concert at a place
called Nite in Shinjuku.
We were invited to come to Toyosu.
I see.
We did a live concert.
When we came on stage, the first song
was already familiar to me.
It was a song of a crybaby.
I see.
We performed the last song for the first
time.
It's called Bokura no Atashi.
We were asked to perform our own
experience.
We are people of the eyes.
We performed it for the first time.
We were like, we made it for this.
Please listen to it.
I was nervous.
I thought I could sing well.
I thought I wouldn't make a mistake.
I made a mistake because I was nervous.
But I wanted to deliver the song the
most.
I wanted you to listen to it the most
during the live concert.
Our feelings were filled with it.
I'm happy to sing the song 落ちサビ.
That's a good point.
That's right.
Thank you.
I hope this song can be taken only by
you.
I'm singing it for those who are
watching me.
It may be for a large number of people,
but I'm singing it for each of them.
I'm singing it with the intention of
reaching you.
This is a masterpiece.
It's a masterpiece.
I'm talking to you now.
Thank you very much.
It was the first time we had a hot stage
at the Tokyo Idol Festival.
We did our best to deliver the live
performance to the audience.
If we get the opportunity, we'll do our
best.
The fans will be happy.
The fans who don't know us will be
happy.
We're very excited.
I think we're excited because we're a
group.
The members are excited.
We had to go to the rehearsal because it
was an emergency.
We also have a set list.
We have a set list that we have to
submit to the public.
We haven't had a set list for a long
time.
So we couldn't change the set list
suddenly.
It was a bit sudden.
We were able to put our proof in it.
We weren't supposed to do it when we
were doing the live performance.
It was a precious and grateful
opportunity to be able to do it on the
hot stage.
The timing is perfect.
It's because the wind is blowing.
I think so.
First, I always have sweet and salty
snacks.
I see, these are two main elements.
It's like, you're going to give it to
me.
Is this normal for you, Fujita-san?
Yes, I always have three types of
sweets.
So, sometimes I have a small bag.
Yes, there are girls who have that.
Yes, I always have that.
Oh, you have one at home.
Yes, that's right.
What are you going to bring today?
Yes, I have a day like today.
I can choose what I want to eat.
I can also buy what I want to eat at the
convenience store.
But, I usually bring it to you.
I think I've seen this before.
I think you bought the gummy candy
yourself.
Yes, I did.
I've brought it from somewhere else.
But, recently, I've been getting
information that I like sweets.
I've been getting information about it
from adults.
I eat it on the live stream.
So, I've been getting a lot of sweets.
The other day, I was singing a lot of
Jagariko on the game stream.
Really?
Yes, I brought it home.
Do you need it, Ayaka-kun?
Put it in, put it in.
Then, two are connected.
Thank you.
Oh, it's in, it's in.
Is it delicious?
It's really delicious.
The Jagariko that idols give me is the
most delicious.
I heard the fans' voice.
The fans are the staff.
They enjoy the sound of eating.
It's a great world.
Is this okay?
I'll take a picture with Binaural next
time.
I want to go there with them.