Night time with idols
Let's get started with the main event!
Please give a title call to Cute!
My three elements!
Thank you!
In this segment, we will introduce the
three elements that make up you.
Let's get to know more about the guest
idols in this segment!
So, what are the three elements that
make up you?
Here they are!
First, Fruits!
Second, Nakamoto!
Third, Beauty Mania!
First, Fruits Monster!
I get Fruits Monster from my members a
lot.
I get Fruits every day at home.
I get seasonal Fruits.
My mother loves Fruits.
I got them from her.
I started getting seasonal Fruits a
little before the season started.
I thought it was normal.
I was stressed out that I didn't get
Fruits.
But I didn't have any.
I was depressed and had a mouthache.
I see.
I got Fruits from her sometimes.
I couldn't stop eating them.
I was all by myself.
I see.
I was living a life of my own.
I could eat Fruits as much as I wanted.
I could eat cakes as much as I wanted.
I grew up like that.
You couldn't help it.
I wanted to keep seasonal Fruits.
But I couldn't stop.
I ate only delicious Fruits.
I got Mangoes as main.
I got Chai Mascato.
You didn't get Fruits as main.
I got some.
What did you get?
Pineapple.
You couldn't get Pineapple?
I couldn't get main.
I got Dragon Fruits.
I don't eat them.
You don't eat them.
You don't eat them at home.
I eat apples in season.
I eat them in season.
I don't eat them in season.
You don't eat them in season.
You eat apples.
I eat Monsters.
You eat Monsters.
You eat Monsters in many ways.
I want to keep Monsters in my car.
You become so energetic.
I eat them in stand-by.
I got a lower jaw recently.
I thought I didn't know that.
I got Kokubo Yuno.
Did you get her?
Yes.
What else?
I got Fruit Monster.
When I came to the studio,
I didn't get Shine Mascato.
You didn't get Shine Mascato.
I thought I knew her.
You knew her.
She is not single.
She is not single, but she likes fruits.
She likes them in season.
In season?
I like it.
I get fruits in season.
I'm grateful.
Thank you for watching.
I really like Mouko-tanmen Nakamoto.
Mouko-tanmen, right?
I thought I'd go eat it later.
You're going today?
I went to the store the next day to eat
it.
You're kidding, right?
This program is from Yume-chan.
From nervous Manchikan.
Hoshinami-san
We sent it by Ebes-san's offer
Thank you everyone!