Hello!
Hinata!
It's always like this!
For example!
We are two!
Everyone, look at the back!
The emblem is attached!
The emblem is not enough.
It's not enough.
My emblem, come on!
You are so shy!
Thank you!
Everybody looks different this time!
There is a shrimp inside!
Bravo!
Where are Kaho and Riko?
Oh, you're right
What?
Don't show your character
What's this?
I've never seen this before
A kit?
Hi, hello
We are
KONI's
Hatsune Miku
Girls
This is a quiz show where we answer how
much we know about our favorite leader.
You will be given a pair and answer.
The pair that shines in the championship
is...
The one with the most super media in the
universe.
The prize is added to the total.
OK, Paul.
So, Hustle Universe.
He laughs hard
Eng sub by BaconC parent
Shiritsu Enbisu Junior High School,
Kobayashi Kaho chooses
What is your favorite chorus in the
debut song?
I think it's the part of the song, Kura
Kura of Yuwaku Shitaia
The chorus of Do Shaburi Regret
The chorus of Shintsui is No! Suzo!
Ah!
The part of B-san
The correct answer is
I'm sure it's the part of Mugen Looper's
The last two lines of Chororo
The correct answer is Shintsui
Shiritsu Enbisu Junior High School,
Kobayashi Kaho chooses
Ebichu!
The second question
Shiritsu Enbisu Junior High School,
Nakayama Riko chooses
What is your favorite gesture among the
Ebichu members?
I got it!
Please think about it
Let's Pansu Universe
You didn't say it
I couldn't remember
I didn't say it
Do you have any hint?
Hint?
Hint is
How do you feel when you see this?
I feel like I'm a man
I think so
I love that
It's time to finish
I got it!
Is Matsumoto the answer?
The pink and green one
Ayaka's touching the drink
The green one
I'm confident with this one
Aika's chin-up
Wait a minute
We have the same answer
The chin-up
She's already looking at it
The answer is the pink one
Today's a success
Let's do the next one
What's the favorite gesture of the
EVICTUBE members?
This one
Hey, hey
The answer is the pink one
No way
Who?
Don't you know?
I know
Go ahead
Matsuno's Miburu
Correct
I see it often recently
Kudo
When it's winter
Yes, when it's winter
I see
It's cold
Then, Goho-nii-sama
You want me to do it when it's not cold?
You can do it
Ebichu
OK, Paul, the third question
Ta-da
I asked Kobayashi Kaho, a private Ebichu
student
What is your favorite part of Riko
Nakayama?
Part?
Please answer when you make a circle
with your hands
Lens
Universe
I don't know about parts
What about your face?
Anything
What part of Riko do you like?
From here to there or from here to
there?
I think it's from here
I think there are other people who like
this
I think there are
Did you get your thoughts?
Yes
Rika and Nina's pair
How you open your mouth when you're
relaxed
I don't know
When you're dancing, your neck and chin
I thought of that
I thought of that the most
Paul will change to Kobayashi
and give you the answer
What is the part of Riko Nakayama that
Kobayashi Kaho likes?
The answer is
The answer is the eyes when you smile
You're wearing a mask
I'm wearing a mask
When you smile, your eyes disappear
Like Mikazuki
Yes, yes
I'm so happy
I want to see Mikazuki
Smile, smile
Exquisite
By the way, what is Riko Nakayama's
favorite part of Sukaho Kobayashi?
The smile on her mouth
I know, I know
Smile
I see
Riko is so funny
Ebichu!
Oh, it's Yahoo!
Oh, I found it! I found it!
What is this?
Let's go!
I asked Riko Nakayama from Ebichu
What was your first impression of Kako
Kobayashi?
One is that she seems to be a sports
person
But what was the other one?
First! First! Universe!
When I first met her, she was in her 6th
grade
Right
It was in spring
Yes, it was in spring
Is everyone's answer correct?
Yes
She's cool
Why?
I think she's cool compared to her
elementary school days
Because Kobayashi-san seems to be an
adult if she doesn't talk
She's cool
I heard that she was originally a cool
beauty character
She has a charm in her ears
I see
Please
She has a tall figure and seems to be an
adult
Yaba!?
I see
What? I can't see the bag
I found the bag
No!
This bag is not allowed
What?
I mean
I saw something weird inside
It's so gross
Hey, that's not allowed outside of the
space
The answer is
It's a...
It's a short sleeve T-shirt
What's that?
It was my first acting lesson
I only wear it once a week
I always wear the same T-shirt
You always wear a dice
A dice of luxury
You always wear that
You always wear a dice
Ebi-chu
How was Hatsuru Universe Show?
Everyone is so proud of you
Yes
Paul, you're awesome
Who do you think I am?
You're Paul
Paul
I'm not a boy
Let's move on to the fifth question
The answer is
Paul
What?
Can you hear me?
Laughter Serving
Now, we are going to have a face-to-face
staring contest between Paul and Cori.
The winner will answer whether it's Paul
or Cori.
It's easy.
It's easy. Everyone has already
answered.
Everyone has already answered.
Wait, wait, wait.
We haven't done that yet.
Then, let's Hustle Universe!
Hustle Universe!
Wow!
I see.
Please go ahead.
One, two.
Ta-da!
Huh?
It's Cori, Cori, Cori.
No, no, no.
It's Paul, Paul, Paul.
I haven't trained at all.
No, no, no.
First, you can't make a face.
Ah.
Are you ready?
Hina-chan.
Yes.
Hina.
Ready, go!
Let's all have a face-to-face staring
contest.
If you laugh, you lose.
Up, down, up, down.
Yes, it's over.
Yes.
Yes, so the winner is
Kisa and Cori.
How was it?
Both of you were fast, but
you laughed at the moment you took off
your clothes.
I'll try not to laugh if I do my best.
Then,
Niko-chan will also
look at me.
Face-to-face staring contest.
The correct answer was dead or alive!
The pairs will get a random present
Hello!
The 6th question!
Who will win? Paul or Cori?
It's a towel fight!
This is fun!
It's fun!
I'm nervous
I'll tell you because you probably don't
know
There are two sides, the defense and the
offense
The offense will use the feint
If you get the towel, you win
If you don't get the towel, you win
The one who wins two times wins
Which one will win?
Think about it
It's me!
Ready, set, go!
Corinne
Paul Kobayashi?
Let's go!
Let's Hassle Universe!
Ready, set, go!
Korihiro wins
Let's do it again in reverse
The second round
Ready, start
Oh, you're almost there
You did it
Korihiro wins
The winner is Paul Kobayashi
We are good friends
I'll give you $1
We are in the middle of the game
Hatsuru Universe Show
There are two more questions left
So, the results so far are as you can
see
The winner is Paul Owakori
The match between the two is a draw
The doll is a drawing of a genius
artist, Mr. Kobayashi
He is a draw
His legs are so cute
To be continued
Can you break more?
Can you do it?
It's a battle of can you do it?
But what did you say?
Can you break it?
It's a battle of can you break it from
the bottom
The winner is Paul or Cori
Please think about whether it's a draw
or a draw and answer
It's a draw
Then
Let's
Hustle Universe
It's decided
Let's open the answer together
It's a draw
If there is an option, I will choose
that
I can't do either
Let's do it
Ready
Start
1, 2, 3
What is the result of the poll?
Ready, set, go!
Sorry!
What's that?
I was so nervous.
Ready, set, go!
Wow!
The winner is...
Cori!
Wow!
You did it!
We're editing!
The final question of the puzzle
universe show!
Wearing an apron!
Wearing an apron with a folded end
without making a mistake,
and shouting,
We're going to do our best!
Ready, set, go!
Huh? We're all wearing the same apron!
Yeah, we are.
Let's start the puzzle universe!
Start!
You're good at counting.
It's okay if you can't count.
But it's surprisingly easy.
It's smooth.
It's surprisingly easy.
It's a piece of cake.
Cori is counting.
Cori?
It's a perfect score.
Oh, cooking!
She's going to do her best in cooking.
40.48 seconds.
That's fast!
Ready, set, go!
Huh?
Calm down.
Oh, really?
It's 29.åŽ
I didn't have the energy to look at the
apron.
Ayako, what are you going to do?
Wait, wait, wait.
Go, go, go.
I'm lost.
Punch!
I'm going to do my best.
It's over.
There are two teams in the winning pair.
Please decide by rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors.
The winner is...
I'll give you a kiss on the cheek.
My heart is beating so fast.
I've never had a double-sided kiss in my
life.
Ready, go!
One...
Wait, Riko-chan.
Riko-chan, wait.
I'm sorry.
Riko's thighs are so big.