I'm an idol!
Second, friends.
Yes, friends.
I love spending time with my friends.
I feel like I live my life to spend time
with my friends.
I go to school to meet my friends.
I prioritize my friends the most.
I have a schedule.
I like to write it down.
I spend my free time with my friends.
I don't have any free time during my
schedule.
That's amazing.
I spend my time with my friends.
If I have time.
But most of my friends are college
students.
Oh, college students.
Most of my friends are college students.
We usually meet after the university or
after the lesson.
We meet at my hometown.
We meet at the workplace.
And at this age, everyone starts to have
a driver's license.
Oh, I see.
Yes.
So, I can drive to the store when I
can't meet my friends.
You can.
I see.
I have a lot of money, and I've been
driving with my friends lately.
Don't you study?
I want to study!
But I...
There was a go-kart at Disneyland,
right?
Was there?
There was.
It's a really simple one, but I'm really
bad at it.
That's pretty good.
Yeah, but I'm good at Mario Kart.
I'm good at Mario Kart.
I'm not good at Mario Kart, but my mom
told me I shouldn't get a driver's
license.
I'm a little nervous.
Do you have any friends?
I don't have any friends.
I want to be able to do it all.
That's nice.
Have you had friends since junior high
school?
I have friends from elementary school,
junior high school, high school, and
idol friends.
I see.
I have a staff idol.
Who is it?
The first one to appear was Fujita Airi.
We've been getting along really well.
I recently went to eat udon with Ayame
Kawata, who is a member of UUKKA.
Is that true?
Is Ayame in your family?
Ayame is two years older than me.
She's the same age as Moeka.
Moeka is sometimes on TV.
I have to keep an eye on her.
That's right.
Moeka is the one who does this.
That's her role.
I'm looking forward to seeing her.
I want to be the cutest girl in the
world.
I'm confident that I can be the cutest
girl in the world.
I received it from Ryo-san.
Thank you very much.