Yakan and Idol!
This is the last ending.
Suzuha, please tell us about the news.
Yes.
Super exciting promotion is
the release of the new single, Star.
Please check it out.
What kind of song is it?
Star is a song that gives you the energy
to chase your dreams.
We are also working hard towards our
dreams,
so I hope we can work hard together.
And?
And the live performance will be held on
December 24th, Saturday,
and December 25th, Sunday at Nakano Sun
Plaza.
It will be held at the Super Exciting
Promotion, Doki Doki Christmas Party
2022.
This is the first live performance with
a live band.
Oh, live band!
Is there a Christmas-like performance?
I think so.
I'm looking forward to it.
Has the rehearsal started with a live
band?
It hasn't started yet,
but I'm excited to see how it will be.
Most band members are difficult to get
along with.
It's quite difficult.
Is that so?
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm sorry.
I'm kidding.
That's not true.
All the members are kind.
Including you.
I'm looking forward to it.
When I went to Momokuro's live
performance,
I thought it was cool to have a live
band.
When we decided to have a live
performance,
we were all very happy.
I'm glad.
It's only at that time.
It's nice to feel like this is a live
performance.
Yes.
And the Super Exciting Spring
Performance 2023
will be held on April 9th, Sunday, at
Hibiya Yagai Music Hall in Tokyo.
And on April 15th, Saturday, at Osaka
Osaka Castle Music Hall.
Oh, it's a week apart.
Tokyo and Osaka.
Yagai.
Yes.
It's the first time for Super Exciting
Spring to have a live performance
outdoors.
Is it the first time for a live
performance outdoors?
It's the first time for Super Exciting
Spring.
Oh, I see.
So I think it will be a new atmosphere.
That's unusual.
You have a lot of ideas.
Yes, I have a lot.
I see.
And then.
And from June to September, we will hold
a nationwide Fall Tour.
Oh!
Hyogo, Kyoto, Hiroshima, Miyagi,
Fukuoka, Osaka, Niigata, Kanagawa,
Aichi, Tokyo.
10 places!
I'll go around.
Oh!
Yes, please check it out.
Thank you.
I understand.
So, finally,
I'd like to have Yagai-kun drink some
tea from Genki.
Yes, thank you.
You're from Saitama Prefecture, so today
you'll drink Sayamaccha.
Sayamaccha.
Yes.
Please.
I hope you'll enjoy it.
Oh, it smells good.
Do you drink tea?
I drink tea.
Oh, really?
I drink it at night or before going to
bed.
Before going to bed?
I don't think it's a good idea to drink
it in a cafe.
I think it's totally fine.
Please drink it.
It will calm your mind.
Yes, thank you.
Thank you.
It's good.
It's got a bit of a kick to it.
That's great. Thank you.
Thank you. That was comforting.
So, with that, we'd like to end the show
here.
So, please end it with a cute ending for
the camera.
Thank you for watching today.
Did you get to know more about Hanami?
We have a lot of activities planned for
the KineX show, so please check them
out!
Thank you for watching today.
See you later!
The night ticket entree!
This program is brought to you by
Wagamama Prince,
Shin,
Inasan,
Yuta,
and Akkun.
Everyone, wearing blue makes you feel
better!
Thank you very much!