Thank you for watching!
nerves
finally...
Thank you!
I am the hero!
Please announce the project to be done
today.
The Great Actress, Demi-sho Nogizaka!
There are more members who are active on
the stage, but they will be able to
respond to any play in the future.
Tonight, they will challenge a project
related to various performances.
The judge will decide the best actress
at the final stage.
People who are interested may come to
watch a drama or movie.
Or a TV show.
Maybe.
Maybe not.
Yamashita Asadora actress.
It's already started.
It's embarrassing.
Asadora is amazing.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's a work called,
I don't know.
I haven't seen it yet.
It's the main character's friend.
It's a childhood friend.
I don't think it will come out for the
first week or two weeks.
It's still a child.
It's Asadora.
I'm sure this will come out when you
become an adult.
It will come out from the 4th week.
It's a hard shoot because it's every
day.
I was in Osaka until yesterday and I was
shooting in Osaka all the time.
I came back to Tokyo for Nogichu.
I'm sorry for Nogichu.
But I hope you do your best.
It's hard every day.
I can't see it.
I'm sure.
What time is Asadora?
Asadora is from 8 o'clock.
I'm sorry.
I have a rerun from noon.
The best thing is to watch it all at
once on Saturday.
I hope you'll get a lot of fans.
I'm not sure if I'll get a lot of fans.
Let's do our best.
First of all, HimeHina.
One phrase player system.
First, check the short play.
Can they perform according to the
setting announced on the spot?
The first line is, I'm sorry.
It seems easy and difficult.
It's just this one word.
But it's good.
It's good.
After listening to the setting, the
performance.
First of all, Inoue.
Have you ever acted before?
No.
Are you nervous?
I'm very nervous.
Here is the station.
付き合い立てのデート. 少しだけ遅刻してしまって待たせた彼に可愛く言うごめんね。
いいね。 いいよ。
いいよ。 それでは行きましょう。井上のごめんね。
ごめんね。
可愛い。 可愛いね。
Oh, I see. She has it.
It's good. You did it so naturally.
You're right. It's cute.
Thank you.
That's good.
I was nervous.
It was a top-notch scene, so I think you
did well.
But if you put your hand on your face,
you can't take it off.
No, no.
It's a play.
I wanted to see your face.
But it was pretty natural.
Yes, it was good.
I think it was good.
Next, what setting does Tamura play?
She is childhood friend and close
friend, but she is rejected by a man she
doesn't want to date.
It's a sorry-ne.
It's difficult.
It's not just a sorry-ne.
She is childhood friend and close
friend.
It has a relationship.
That's right.
Let's start.
I'm sorry.
I feel that you are kind.
I don't think so.
But I want to continue to be in a
relationship.
I can see that.
We have been together for a long time.
I don't want to reject you too much.
I want to continue to be in a
relationship with you.
But you have to shake hands with me.
You are good at shaking hands.
I'm focused on the string.
I can't see it.
I thought it was a string.
I feel sorry for you.
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing? You apologize.
Inoue Tamura is good.
Next is Captain Akimoto.
Can he make a veteran taste?
Akimoto is not good at acting.
He is a variety show.
Do you want to do it when you come here?
I want to do it when I come here, but I
can't hear you.
Let's show it here.
Let's change it today.
This is the situation Akimoto wants you
to do.
When you tell your best friend that you
are a psychopath of evil.
I'm sorry.
This is a good question.
Please make a good question.
I'm a psychopath.
Let's see.
AKIMOTO's sorry.
I'm sorry.
Isn't it different?
Is it gone?
Go back to Maraichi.
I'm going there.
It's a one-shot game, so it's hard.
Himura.
What is it?
Himura is writing a sword, but Akimoto's
sword is low.
I did it with 100 points, but I got 20
points.
Imura's eyes are surprisingly scary.
I'm saying, well, well, well, but I got
20 points.
It's hard to laugh.
One phrase game test. Next.
The line will be congratulations.
It will be congratulations.
First, the vice captain, Umezawa, will
try to give a speech.
Congratulations on the wedding of your
best friend who couldn't get married.
This is a good role.
I think I'll be able to cool down when I
see this.
Don't give her pressure.
Let's go.
Congratulations
You are good
I am nervous
You were good
I remembered my best friend
Really?
Do you feel lonely?
I feel lonely
You are good
Next, what is the acting ability of the
4th generation Kanagawa?
Do you do something? Like stage?
No, it's almost the first time. I
haven't done much acting.
Then it may come from now on.
What?
Yeah
I will do my best.
Congratulations.
Here it is.
Congratulations on losing the game but
praising your rivals.
Oh, I think there is such a thing as a
youth.
Congratulations on Kanagawa.
Congratulations!
That was good!
You were a little frustrated, right?
I hate losing, so I tried to be
frustrated.
Was it difficult?
It was difficult!
It was difficult, right?
It wasn't bad at all.
But I can't trust you saying that it
wasn't bad.
It's a serious score.
Even if you say it's okay here, you
might get 20 points.
I don't usually wear such low-cut
glasses.
Next, Kaki will challenge.
What is her ability?
Kaki, what about you?
I'm a drama actress.
I play a comedian.
I know.
It's hard.
Congratulations to Kaki.
Congratulations to the game master who
tells the correct answer in the death
game.
Kaki is a comedian.
I think her voice has changed.
She is not suitable for young men.
I don't know.
I saw the last episode of the game
called IKA GAME.
There are some women who are young.
I see.
That's right.
What is the topic of the show?
Let's start the show.
Congratulations.
I could see it.
The winner of the championship should go
to the championship tournament.
I was like, is there still a
continuation?
That's the highlight.
I'm glad.
The winner of the championship should go
to the sea!
What?
From now on, we will verify it on
location.
If you are given a question about acting
in a situation called the sea,
what kind of acting and what kind of
lines will you say?
We will check your ad-lib ability and
acting ability.
The first question is
After being dumped by the person you
love,
A word in the sea
First of all, from the ad-lib ability of
4th generation Shibata Yuna
I tried my best to be brave.
I love you so much, but I didn't love
you.
I'll make you regret it.
It's too late to regret later.
Good.
Next, we'll see Ikeda Teresa, the fifth
generation actress.
You're thinking about it?
Wow.
I love you.
It's cute.
The ad-lib section is well restored.
I told you I like that kind of thing.
You're taking her with you.
That's amazing.
Suddenly.
Cute.
What should I say?
Aho!
Cute.
That's great.
Next is Gokusei Sugawara
How good is her acting?
Here comes the Shokichi
Wow
What kind of appearance is this?
I'll become cuter and definitely make it
public
Please watch it
Make it public
Hayashi decides on the live performance
Can she act well?
I got a converse and a watch
I can't throw it away
I need you
It's written as Yasukita
The youngest member Ogawa
What is her acting plan?
I will never show you my notebook
She is cute
What kind of acting will the girl who
can't speak Japanese do?
Why?
I can't do it.
It's nice.
There's a drama like this.
It's in the film.
It's a nice film.
I don't hate it.
I like it.
It's amazing.
The next topic is about a friend who is
enjoying a beach bath and finds a huge
shark fin.
He will have to do an ad-lib of the
situation.
There are many shark movies.
First, Yuna Shibata, a 4th generation,
finds a shark in the beach bath.
It's fun.
Oh, she found it.
Hey, shark! Run away!
Shark!
Next, 5th generation Sugawara found a
shark on the beach
Interesting
Beautiful
There is something behind you
Shark! There is a shark!
Run away!
Is it a reenactment of the movie?
Next, Hayashi
Don't be afraid, Hayashi Luna
Hey, do you have a ball?
Wait, look behind you!
I'm so happy!
It's a live-or-die situation.
That's terrible.
Next, the shark discovery performance of
the
shark discovery performance of the
shark discovery performance of the shark
discovery performance.
How well does Nakamura act?
The waves are bad and the wind is bad,
so let's go home
What's going on?
This is really bad
I'm sorry
Very shark!
He ran away!
Why did you say very shark?
The next topic is about a mermaid who
was yearning for a human for a long time
Please act as a human being who was
yearning for a human for a long time
There are many movies
First, the mermaid who was reborn as
Nakanishi
Do your best!
She became a human
She is very good
Foot
The next topic is about a mermaid who
was born as a human for a long time
To a world of free humans
The next doll to be reborn is Teresa
Ikeda
She appeared
She is a character in the movie
She is dangerous
It's her first time to run
I will run in 7 seconds at 50 meters
I will show you
No, I don't know about that kind of doll
The mermaid is Ren Nakamura
This is the earth?
This is the air?
This is the sky?
Ren Nakamura is the best
What kind of doll will Okuda play?
Okuda
I also want to play
I think I'm a good singer
I'm going to say goodbye today
I see, in the world of dolls
Where are you going to walk from now on?
Road
You can't say this
This is a bad writer
Can't you say this line?
Thank you for your viewing.
The road is terrible.
It's terrible.
Suddenly, I was taken to the sea and
wondered what I was doing.
The shark performance is amazing.
That is a very interesting subject.
Was it good to find a shark in Shibata?
Yes, it was good. Shibata is a high-end
shark.
Shibata's sharks are high-end.
The shark in Yumiki is the lowest point.
The shark in the forest in Yumiki is
also the lowest point.
I don't know the shark in the forest.
Do you want to try it?
If you have fun with your friends, you
can teach them that the shark is in the
forest.
If this is good, I will give you a
point.
This is a complete loss.
This is a loss.
The Akimoto rescue challenge.
Will he be able to do the shark
performance?
I'm ready.
Wait a minute.
No! You should run away! Come here!
Run!
Cut!
I'm sorry.
Your friend is really bad.
What is that?
It's like you cooked rice.
I thought so.
The first round of the pinpoint play.
The player who will play the pinpoint
play.
Congratulations.
In this game, you can play a natural
acting with the setting that is very
close to your daily life.
The first topic is this.
When the important material created by
iron work is completed, you can press
the enter key at the end.
Wow, it's done.
It's done.
Oh, that's good.
The important material created by iron
work.
This is likely to be.
The acting until you press the key is
also important.
First of all, it's a difficult
challenge.
I think so.
Kubo is said to be the face of the face
as much as he won the Kimegawa
Championship.
Let's get started.
Ready, start!
Good work.
Is that so? That's good.
You did it.
KUBO.
I'm embarrassed.
Are you embarrassed?
I'm sorry.
That's good.
That's very good.
Next, KAKI will challenge the same
setting.
KAKI was good earlier.
It was a death game.
That's right.
It was a fixer.
KAKI, let's get started.
I'm going to faint.
I see.
I feel like I'm a real iron woman.
You must have made a great material with
a real iron woman.
I put my life into the entertainment.
I've never seen such a play.
I've never seen anyone who can be such a
play from this topic.
This is also a little closer to the
Akimoto of the troupe.
Pinpoint Sangu's time. Next is...
The second time acting of a father who
has been separated from his daughter in
the city.
If you fail this time, it will be a very
strange second time.
It will be a joke.
It's surprisingly difficult.
Asuka Saito will try the difficult
second time acting.
Asuka is good at movies and dramas.
Let's start.
Ready, start!
Dad?
Did your dad come?
No.
Thank you.
You are good.
You came from behind.
I have a pattern.
What is the purpose of this note?
I may be able to get a morning call.
You may be able to get a morning call.
You are good.
Was it difficult?
No, not at all.
As expected.
She is a strong woman.
Everyone says they are nervous.
I'm not nervous at all.
I like her face when she turns around.
She doesn't get nervous.
Is that so?
Next, can Tomisa, the fifth generation,
perform well twice?
Ready, start!
What's wrong?
You were cute.
Cut!
Why are you laughing?
How many times did you look at her?
She had a lot of eyes.
I looked at her 5 times.
After looking back, I looked at her
eyes.
So I looked at her many times.
Did you hear the last line?
I didn't hear it.
You changed.
What are you doing?
It's difficult to do it twice.
AKIMOTO, will you take it back?
I will do it twice.
Thank you very much.
Can AKIMOTO do it all this time?
You can get a chance.
Please do your best.
You got 30 points.
Let's go.
During Miho and Michio, which Watcher
was medicine,
Dad?
Right?
Dad...
Long time no see. Do you remember me?
Cut!
You were laughing for a long time.
I was serious.
You were a dad.
Even if you say so, the line after that
is like a hair cut.
Yes.
It was a pity.
I'm sorry.
Higuchi Hina graduation ceremony.
The tickets for the streaming are on
sale.
Kabuki?
Please subscribe to my channel.
Thank you for watching.