This week's Ebichu Tastas is a special
edition! New song big release special!
A song of a large-scale production that
is scheduled to be recorded on the new
album of Ebichu released this year!
Deliver the latest information!
But!
Why is it a three-wheel race?
Where is the inside of the box?
Where?
I was surprised!
I want to go to the game tournament in
time!
Even so!
One, two!
The title of the new song that you are
interested in is announced!
Ebichu Tastasu Start!
Arrangement
Famicom
Verbal
Carrier
Seating
Mod жизнь
This program was brought to you by these
sponsors.
Are you excited?
We are Super Heroes
Everyone is God
Shirito Ebichu Middle School New Single
Super Heroes
On sale
Ebichu Tastas has begun!
Today, the girl who is into drinking is,
the extremely kind Maayama Rika!
Good girl!
What? You're going to say something that
you're into drinking?
I don't want to hear that
And you're so excited
Do you have more to say?
I don't need to
But today, you guys are missing a member
Is there something wrong?
What is it?
I don't know
Look at this person
Hirota
It's Oga-ta Kaiki
Why is Oga-ta not here today?
Oga-ta Kaiki and I are going to
collaborate on the new album that will
be released today
Last December, Oga-ta-san made a song
for us
What?
Oga-ta-Kaiki produced a song for the
next album
Is this really not a prank?
No, no, no
I already sang
Already sang?
I'm done with the recording
Done
Amazing
So, this time, Ebichu Tatsutas special
performance
New song, the first song, we will do a
special
We can't do this
Let's call the great teacher
Ready?
Great teacher
Are you really playing?
Amazing
Here it comes
He is playing
Let's Go Auroica
Thank you for the introduction.
Welcome.
He's not introducing himself.
Please come again.
Thank you.
Mr.Kai.
What was the song like?
Was it perfect?
It was perfect.
I heard from the members that you
recorded the song.
What kind of song was it?
It was a great explosion of talent.
It was a great explosion.
We only know the teacher who is involved
in the variety show.
By the way, you are in a band, right?
Yes, I'm in a band.
Of course.
In the program, he is treated like a
comedian.
He collaborated with Ebichu as an
artist.
He is a musician.
What kind of band was it?
We are in a band called Here.
Do you know the band called Here?
Yes, we know.
Great.
What do you know?
I watched a lot of music videos.
I watched the music video of eating
sand.
Eating sand music video.
Eating sand.
You are a comedian.
No, I'm not.
What do other people think of you?
I'm a burning person.
You are a burning person.
I watch you a lot.
I'm a fan.
Have you ever watched the music video of
Matsuno?
I haven't.
We are the same.
Wait, you guys are calling me.
Great teacher.
Let's watch the music video of Here.
There is a music video.
Great.
What kind of band is Here?
Please watch the live video.
I love CINICLRAVE.
After this, surprise day here comes.
It's so cool.
When is this live?
Let's go.
Are you excited?
Please make a bigger voice!
Let me introduce the members of HIA!
First, guitarist, Mitsuashi Hayato!
And the other one, guitarist, Takeda
Masayuki!
Thank you!
The next one is...
I'm sorry!
And...
Daisuke Miyano!
The next one is...
I'm sorry!
We were able to meet the members
What did you think?
After watching the live show, you were
excited
It was cool
This is the line from the beginning of
recording
He's biting it
It's interesting
Okada-san, do you understand that it's a
proper locker?
Yes
So, you were treating Ogata-san as a
very important person
That's true
He's not a very good character
Today, let's apologize to Ogata-san
Yes
We found out that Ogata Kaiki was a
famous musician
So we will apologize to the person who
has misunderstood this opportunity
Let's apologize to Ogata-san who made
the new song of Ebichu
Okada-san, you've been apologizing to
Okada-san for this
He'll reflect on his mistake and
apologize
Yes
There's a card that you can't forgive
Please show us
It's in lock mode
Can I be strict?
You can
That's right
I can't help it
Yasumoto
Yes
Actually
I accidentally called Okada-chan or
Kaiki-chan
I thought it was rude
I'm a person of the same age
I didn't notice
Let's apologize to Yasumoto
I'm sorry, Ogata-chan
She's out of her mind
Even though she's older, she's still
trying to get rid of Yasumoto
Will she forgive her?
Where is the criminal?
It was close
I forgive you
I want you to call me that from now on
I picked it up
Well, I think that Mr. Ogata is becoming
a comedian
I think he is becoming a comedian now
I'm sorry
I heard that you are a comedian
I'm a comedian
At first, I said rock star
I'm a comedian who makes that into a
joke
I see
I thought you were adding roses
I thought you were a comedian who made
that into a joke
Hirota is thinking of giving up singing
and going on a path of a comedian
I won't forgive you
I have a part that I can't forgive, so
I'll forgive you
That was good
She's totally forgiving
Next, Kashiwagi
When we first met, I didn't think you
were a rock musician. I'm sorry
I see
When we first met...
When we first met, we were...
Shrimp rock
She was wearing a dress
But then, you were already in the shrimp
rock and shrimp Amigo
But you were already in the camera
That's how it was
I won't forgive you, shrimp Amigo
Shrimp Amigo
We're rivals
What did you think Kashiwagi was?
A strange, arrogant new comedian is
working hard
In the end, you become a comedian
Kashiwagi, who thought that only
arrogant reactions were for the new
comedian
Will you forgive me? I won't forgive you
When I was about to announce this song,
Kashiwagi-san was the happiest, so I'll
forgive you
I forgive you a lot
Let's move on
There are so many
There are so many?
Yes, there are
Nakayama, let's go
I thought Ogata-san was the first guest
I'm sorry
I see, you're a single-minded person
Yes, yes
So when Ogata-san came again for the
second time
I thought he was this person again, I'm
sorry
You were
There are two, there are two
Even though he was the first guest, he
came again and again
Nakayama thought that, will he forgive
him?
Won't he forgive him?
I've been able to wear two
Will he forgive you?
It's a good thing
Will he come at the end?
I didn't think so either
I'll forgive you
I didn't think so either, I'll forgive
you
You did?
I've been able to wear a lot, I'll
forgive you
By the way, Ogata-san forgave all the
other members' complaints
Ogata-san is a musician with a deep
heart
We are prepared to see
So this means you have enough of variety
I will choose a lot of celebrities
Of course
Come on carried
I told you
Ok then, Ogata who now has the image of
a comedian
Let's have fun with a variety of
battles!
So...
Ebichu vs. Hiya, the third match of the
flame!
First, the three-wheeled car relay
match!
There are 8 people in the middle of the
game, so there are only 4 people here.
Everyone here will play 2 rounds.
I see.
Isn't the number of coins different?
What?
The number of coins.
Is that so?
Isn't that the same?
This is a competition between adults and
children.
It's a little bit different.
It's really different.
I'll start.
Then, it's a three-wheel drive.
Start!
Good luck!
Mayama!
What is Mayama doing?
Let's go!
Mayama looks good on the service car
Mayama!
I'm fast too
Maiki-chan is fast
Mayama is fast
Good luck!
It's a button touch
Let's go!
Mayama is fast too
unexpectedly
Take-chan
Take-chan is good
Take-chan chance
Skirt
Skirt is bigger than I thought
Take-chan
Everyone has a skirt
Go
Wait
Yasumoto
Come
Here
This is possible
Kiss
Take-chan
Come
Fast
Take-chan is fast
Mitsui is fast
No
Take-chan is good
Take-chan is fast
How many people are there?
5 people
Hey
Do we have to do this?
Yes
Go
It's dangerous
We have to turn around
It's fun
It's like a ghost
Here we go
So cute
How many people are there?
7 people
Go
So fast
No
3 people
Go
Take-chan
Are you going to turn around?
Yes
Take-chan
Take-chan is good
How are you?
I'm good
Thank you
Bye
Take-chan
Nakayama City is here
If you come back with this, you win the
game of Ebichu
Ebichu wins!
This is a close call
I lost by a huge gap
Aren't you embarrassed?
The rules are too different
This is a race between three-wheeled
cars
What happened?
Ebichu wins!
This is a standard version of variety
show.
The winner is the one who gets the
answer faster.
Ebichu, who will go first?
Kashiwagi?
Hiya?
I'm the leader!
Alright!
In the box of Kashiwagi...
Here it is.
Konnyaku.
The big box is...
Zari Gani.
The excitement of the contents is
different, but it's just a handicap.
The winner is the one who gets the
answer faster.
Let's start.
What's inside the box?
Start!
Please put your hands in.
Where?
It's a good feeling.
What's wrong?
Please touch it.
More.
Wait.
Please stop.
What's inside the box?
Konjac.
Correct.
Let's have Ms.Kaichi touch it.
Wait.
More.
After the second round, the two of them
are in the lead.
The last one will be the special rule.
The final round.
If you win, you get 100,000 points.
It has nothing to do with the previous
game.
That's the promise of variety show.
Please do your best.
Next is the same standard of variety
show.
The battle of the fast-eating curry.
Thank you.
After this, the final battle.
The menu of the big.
The drink.
And the title of the collaboration song.
The power battle of fast food curry!
Thank you!
It looks delicious
Where is it?
It looks very delicious
There are a few
Adults and children, so there are a few
Is it a little? Isn't it three times
different?
The one who will challenge is
Hoshina who is not good at spicy food
Musician Ogata
I will go
Spicy curry challenge
Start
Go for it
It's spicy
How spicy is it?
It's the spiciest in my life
It looks spicy
How spicy is it?
It's spicy
It's the spiciest in my life
It's so smelly
Are you okay?
It's a game
I have to win
You can do it
It's like drinking
It's so spicy
Let's stop eating rice
It's getting slow
I don't know yet
I can do it
I won the last game
Thank you
I'll get a kiss
You sweat a lot
So
In variety show
Ebi-chu is the straight win
The third game is over
But one question
It was exciting
What was it?
I don't know
The new song
That's right
The song that you made
Please tell us a song title
It's called
Hendik
I made the feeling of moving towards the
new year with a strong heart
It smells like curry
It smells spicy
Everyone in Ebichu recorded it, right?
Yes
How was it?
The sound was so cool that it was
recorded
The tension of the recording was very
high
Kaiki did all the recording
She did the direction
This part is more like this
It was different from Kaiki of TASTAS
Really?
How was it different?
The clothes were not like this
The face was not like this
I'm curious about it, but let's close
the diary
Next time, Kaiki Ogata will announce the
new song of Ebichu
Moratorium Junior High School
Please look forward to it
There is no microphone
Air microphone
Next time, finally
The whole of the collaboration song that
Kaiki Ogata of Ebichu has realized is
clear
The close-up document of the musicians
Ogata and the members who wanted to
record
It's a batch
It's the best
Before the album release, the new full
version will be released soon
I think it will be a exciting song
This program was provided by the sponsor
you are watching
Thank you for watching!