This week's Ebichu Tastas is a new song
special edition!
The completion of the new song that was
born from the start of the program is
completely attached!
Spring vacation moratorium junior high
school full version
First public release of the original
song! Ebichu Tastas Start!
Go fry some Heikakoi by an air fryer or
porch...
politique tour
Making fun of Kimi
Eating and drinking
centigrade
This time, we would like to see the
production of the song written by Kaiki
Ogata, which is included in the new
album Anarchy,
Haruyasumi Moratorium, a junior high
school student.
Then, please show us the VTR.
Last year, suddenly in the program,
The name of the song that was announced
that the new album of the Ebi-Chuu would
include the song produced by Kaiki
Ogata.
春月にボラボラやる 中学生!
番組から新曲が誕生することに 今回はそのレコーディングに完全密着!
遂に今夜 新曲の全貌が明らかに!
去年11月 スタジオでスチール撮影をしていた エビチューメンバー そこに!
Aikido-san sent me a demo.
A demo version of Haruyasumi Moratorium
was sent to the members.
Let's listen to it.
It's so cute!
The lyrics are cute.
Here are the cute lyrics of the member.
Haruyasumi Moratorium middle school
students performed a youth song before
the new semester.
This feeling...
It's like a set number. It's never going
to be divided.
The feelings of a girl are told by the
words of a middle school student.
A 100 times frustrating emotions.
I'm so into you that I'm so sad.
The feelings of one-sided love that
move.
I'm looking forward to it. I'm looking
forward to the recording.
After 10 days, the recording of the
Ebichu members was started.
The recording of the band was started.
The studio has a big figure.
The guitar sound is not like the
previous Ebichu songs.
It's more rock.
I'm particular about making rock rock
sound stronger.
Rock sound that is not in the previous
Ebichu songs.
To make that, the members of HEAR are
gathered in the studio.
Furthermore...
Special keyboardist, Hajimetaru.
Hajimetaru, who played in rock band
Midori.
He is currently active as a solo artist.
O-Gata has recruited a strong musician
for this song.
I'm the bassist, Keita Nishi.
Keita Nishi.
He is a talented bassist who has been in
the back band of Koteto Moyasu.
Actually, he is also in charge of the
arrangement of this song.
Let's hear about his impression of the
song.
When I heard the song in the story, I
thought it was a really good song.
There are many melodies that only Kaeki
has.
It's a wide range of the song that is
close to the color of Ebichu.
You are a good praise.
This is a strange praise.
Are you okay?
I'm praising you, but are you okay?
I'm sorry.
In the spring break, a strong rock
musician was gathered for the recording
of Latrium Junior High School.
And finally...
Mr. Ishizaki, the producer of Ebichu's
song, heard this.
It's really cool.
Cute lyrics and a strong rock sound.
What kind of song will it be?
Thank you.
Ebichu members' recording begins.
Ayaka Yasumoto is the top batter.
Let's start with the chorus.
Let's start with the most exciting part.
Each member is finally recording the
vocals.
The ciudpan Panро.
I'm sorry but I'm not in a situation to
be in a situation to be in
That was good
Thank you
I'm not in a situation to be in
I'm going from high to low
The pitch is low but the feeling is high
You can sing like you are right now so
you can put your feelings into it
Please do it
You can put your feelings into it
How will Yasumoto respond?
Tu ga share quand Mush51
Perfect!
After the recording was over
It was very fun
I'm always nervous during the recording
It's like a stick
I was able to do it comfortably
Next, the one who appeared in the flashy
clothes is Aika Hirota
I came to Hayaki-san
Hayaki-san was wearing black and white
clothes
I'm not wearing anything
Hirota is full of spirit
What kind of singing voice will he let
us hear?
Thank you for watching!
Moratorium Moratorium Moratorium Junior
High Schooler
Moratorium Moratorium Junior High
Schooler
It's pretty good.
Thank you.
It's suddenly good.
Ai, Ai, can you do it with a rock-like
feeling?
It's more rock-like here.
Please try it.
How will Hirota respond to this request?
It's really good
Thank you
Hirota returns the desired rock feeling
with a wonderful song
Expectations are high for the finish
I was able to sing like a live
I'm looking forward to how it will
change from now on
Following Hirota, he entered the studio
I'm going to go to the studio
I'm not the usual me
Really? But I heard that it was fun from
Ayaka
I heard it was hard
It was fun at all
Thank you for your viewing
The recording of the lyrics that made me
look forward to this day starts
Thank you for your viewing
Moratorium, moratorium, moratorium, it's
different
Here, the O-Gata is the direction
I'll try it, the emotion is 1.2 times
It's already quite high, so I won't say
it's 2 times
1.2 times, 1.2 times
1.2 times, please do it again
Moratorium, Moratorium, Moratorium,
Junior High School Student
Perfect
The 1.2 times better version of the
emotion is also completed
Thank you for the wonderful song
Thank you
Thank you too
Ishii who was watching the recording so
far
The finish is very fun
I think it's a very good recording
Kaiki-san is a singer
I think I understand the feelings of the
person who sings
And
Thank you for your cooperation
Unlike usual, for some reason, Kobayashi
with a frowning expression
Thank you for watching
Actually before recording
Is there anything you are worried about?
I'm worried about everything
She wishes for recording while having
anxiety
Is it okay?
Let's go
Perfect!
Today is really good
Really good
I've been listening to your voice for 2
years
It's really good
Please do as you want
In addition to Kobayashi's worries, the
singing voice of this day is excellent
Seimei-gi-au Seimei-gi-au Seimei-gi-au
Seimei-gi-au
It's really good
Kobayashi, who was in a good mood,
completed the recording by repeating OK
take
And
Mayama-san, please
Can you do it?
For some reason, Mayama can't stop
laughing
She has an important role
I will go from the top to the line
Mayama is in charge of this part
This song's title call
Please
Seimei-gi-au Seimei-gi-au Seimei-gi-au
My heart is
Haruyasumi Moratorium middle school
student
In addition, during the title call, you
mixed more breath
I understand
Seimei-gi-au
Haruyasumi Moratorium middle school
student
You're doing Moratorium
I'm doing Moratorium
OK, I got it
Thank you
Mayama's title call, which was done with
Moratorium, is also completed
The song's structure is gradually
completed
Beyond the toss
Riko-chan
Good morning
Thank you
Let's go
Interesting
Please
Thank you
I'm still in love with you
It's good, Nakayama-san
It's perfect
I'll do my best
Like Mayama, the lines are also in
Nakayama's part
Then
A-melody
Bye-bye
Thank you for watching
This is also a bright bye-bye.
Yes.
Please.
Bye bye.
Thank you very much
Even in the recording, Nakayama World is
fully open
Ogata finished the 6 members
It's wonderful
I'm leaving a good take
I'm going well
I'm really happy
After this, the emergency situation
occurred in Matsuno's recording
And finally, the new full version will
be released
Here we are
Thank you for your cooperation
There are two more to go
Hoshina's recording starts
Perfectly
Super perfectly
Then, such a request
Something like a burikko
While remembering Taki Ue-san
Can you think of that buri Ue-san?
Yes
To the request of burikko-like
I will do my best
It's OK
The rust is very cool
You know that you needed the power of
Buriuue, right?
I thought so
I thought the contrast was very good
And the last
Thank you, Chief Matsuno
Chief? Please
Please decide the last
I will do my best
Matsuno will be the last
I'll start with the B-melody
B-melody
I'm a professional singer
I'm the only one who can sing and dance
It's perfect
Thank you
It's good here
Matsuno is doing well in the recording
However
It's getting rough
It's good
The recording that took a long time
Something is wrong with her throat
The recording is interrupted
Are you drinking water?
Yes, I'm drinking water
I think you can relax after listening to
the high notes
As the same vocalist, Matsuno is noticed
Then
Let's go
After recovering, she takes the last
block
This is the last song, so please sing
with the highest tension
Moratorium, Moratorium, Junior High
School Student
Perfect
Thank you
So, 8 students from the spring break
moratorium school finished recording
A few days later
Chara, Radwimps and other top artists
have started recording
Kiyoshi Kusaka, a recording engineer,
has finished the mix
Finally
Thank you for your hard work!
Spring vacation Moratorium Junior High
School students are completed!
Then, the new song from Ebichu Tastas!
Spring vacation Moratorium Junior High
School students!
First public!
Today's publiced Oga Takaki Produce
Spring vacation Moratorium Junior High
School students
Pre-release on the album and decide to
deliver the fastest!
For more information, it is also on
iTunes, each delivery site or Ebichu
home page check!
Next time Ebichu Tastas is!
Spring vacation Moratorium Junior High
School students!
Ebichu Spring vacation special!
Spring vacation Moratorium Junior High
School students!
EE
Backstage
Ah!
I wi Milet
Thank you for watching!
In the middle of the debut, new album,
Hana-dora