Nogizaka is back!
Everyone, the great actress, Nogizaka
Demi-chan!
Nogizaka 46 will challenge various
projects to be able to handle any kind
of acting work in the future.
First, they will act according to the
set announced at the scene.
From the one phrase contest.
I will change the lines.
I will say, good morning.
Is there such a thing? There are many
good morning.
After listening to the setting, they
will act immediately. Tonight's top
batter is Endo.
Endo, you are doing various things,
aren't you?
No, but it's not much.
Compared to the old Endo, it was
really...
Ha ha!
It was like this, but now it's
properly...
What? There's no good one?
It's a weird Endo.
Well, let's go.
Here's the situation.
To the senior who is interested in club
activities, there are a lot of love
words.
I want you to decide this.
This is why the feeling of love is
overflowing.
Senior who is interested in club
activities.
I don't know.
Let's go.
Good morning.
Good.
It's a serious love word.
Now it's a love word of Endo.
It's a love word of Endo.
I like it the most.
I imagined it.
It was difficult for me to express a lot
of love words, so I just said good
morning and tried hard, but it became a
little small.
Great.
Next, the setting of the fifth
generation of Ichino Semikun is...
I arrived at the classroom late at
night, but I was told to be late for
class.
It's difficult.
I thought I was in time.
I was told to be late for class.
I see.
Good morning, Ichino Semikun.
I'm sorry university
But what happened when I first ran?
I was in a hurry
You were in a hurry
I wanted to run away
It's like Steve Williams
But you were pretty angry
I was pretty angry when I was a student
Oh, I see
That's good
Next is Asadora actress Yamashita's
challenge
I'm nervous
I think Asadora actresses say good
morning
I'm from Kansai
I say good morning
Yamashita's good morning
This is a sleepover prank
It's a young comedian's good morning in
the opening
Why?
Do you know what a sleepover prank is?
It's a room where an idol like Nobizaka
stays
Izyri is good at it
I'm not going to say it in a loud voice
But she's excited in the opening
I didn't expect Asadora actresses to do
this
Let's go
Good morning
Why can you do it?
Did you get it?
You did well
You were a good young lady
You were very detailed
I'll put it in tomorrow
That's great
You can do it without knowing
One phrase challenge
Next is Onii-chan
Onii-chan?
I'll do Onii-chan
The first phrase challenge is
When your favorite brother does a boring
prank
I'll do a straight Onii-chan
Onii-chan from Akanishi
Onii-chan
I see
It's real and the setting is higher than
I thought
I see
When I was playing games, I did
something
What did you do?
I put on gum
It's the worst
On your hair?
I'm sorry
Onii-chan
Wait, gum is dangerous
I have to cut it
You can do it, you can chew gum
Next, Okuda Iroha will challenge Onii-
chan
Okuda, do you have siblings?
I have an older brother and a younger
brother
You don't have an older brother
Here is the situation
Onii-chan who met his first brother
Good
I thought you didn't have an older
brother, but you did
I see
You know you have a brother, right?
Let's do our best
Onii-chan?
Oh, it's the real tension version
I thought so too
I see
Onii-chan?
You held it down
You're good
Next, the 3rd generation, Sato Kaede's
acting skills
How was it? Did you have any acting
experience?
No, not at all
Why are you so nervous?
I'm not
It's hard, isn't it?
I think I'm wrong
No, it's not
I don't know, maybe Kunoichi's role will
come
Then
It's tough
This is the situation
5 years old girl
is looking for her brother who was
playing
I see
She's 5 years old
She's been acting for 10 years
The last one
Big brother!
Oh, she's coming out.
Oh, no.
My voice is a little hoarse.
You're right.
I thought I could be a voice actor, but
I forgot my voice.
It's a little difficult.
It's difficult.
I'm alone.
I don't want to hear that excuse.
There's no one here.
Thank you for watching.
It's really low.
It's a little lower than the first
AKIMOTO.
Is that so?
Change the line again.
It's a yes.
Yes?
It's a good one.
A word to his grandmother.
This topic is challenged by Tomisato.
The line is short.
Yes.
The situation of yes is...
The first yes of the phone number.
It's a yes.
Yes.
I only said yes.
Tomisato's yes.
Yes.
Yes, that's right.
It's a bit like a horror movie.
There are a lot of young girls in horror
movies.
Yes.
It's like that.
She has a good expression.
Yes, it's good.
Next, the yes that Ioki will challenge.
Yes when you give a present to a senior
who you are interested in.
To a senior who you are interested in.
Yes.
It's a good thing.
But you are interested in it.
Yes.
You like it.
Let's go.
3, 2, 1, action.
Yes.
It was a bit of a mess.
It was a mess.
I was so emotional.
I was so touched that I thought I liked
her.
It was a great feeling.
Next, Iwamoto's story.
He was asked to go out with someone he
liked.
He replied with a lot of joy.
This is a good story.
It's a straight story.
It's difficult.
Please watch again.
Yes.
That's good!
She is good.
She is a good person.
She is laughing.
She is embarrassed.
Do you make videos with your feelings?
I focus on the camera.
That's great.
That's good.
Hibura-san, do you want to do an
exhibition?
Me?
So, the exhibition is held by Hibura-
PRO.
I thought you were going to pee.
Is that okay?
Hibura-san, please.
Yes.
Good.
You are a good person.
I feel sorry for her.
She is a person who is told to be a bad
person.
Yes.
Why am I the only one who loses?
Do you remember this?
I remember clearly.
It's been very popular on the Internet.
Really?
Yes.
From now on, we will continue to the
last episode.
What kind of acting will you do if you
are given various situations in the sea?
Check out the members' ad-lib acting
skills.
The first topic is,
I'm irritated by myself who can't convey
my feelings to my favorite person,
I say a word in the sea.
The 5th generation Okamoto Hina will
challenge this acting.
The last episode
I couldn't say it all the time, but...
I love you!
That's good
Next, Gokusei Sugawara will challenge
this sad topic
I want to spend this winter with my
seniors
Why can't I say it?
Idiot!
I think you should be more active in
your acting job.
You're a fool.
What does 15-year-old Ogawa think?
What does it mean to be like a little
sister?
Cute!
customers are
Ike Da Teresa
Ike Da Teresa is coming
What is that?
Stupid
It's 10 o'clock
Why don't you believe that you like me?
I don't believe it
Why don't you tell me that you like me?
My idiot
Good
It's a peaceful woman
Next, Hayashi Luna who continues to
continue the tricky play
I like you
I like you very much
I can't say it anymore
It's like a reality show
Let's do it again
I love you
I can't say it
Next is the ad-lib performance of Yumiki
Yumiki wants to perform at the beach
He smacks his forehead until the last
minute to challenge the edge weakness of
the eyes
Oh my god!
I got it!
The staff members are all wet with tears
due to the high tide.
The next topic is...
I got 10 billion yen in the lottery, but
I came to the sea without telling
anyone.
Let's go to Hawaii!
I'm going to use my money!
First of all, 500 million yen is from my
savings!
I'm going to use my money!
ーA lot of members who scream about how
to use moneyー
ーThe acting that shows the style of the
actressー
ーIs she aware of it?ー
ーNo way! Really?ー
ーNo, really!ー
ーI did it!ー
ーI'm so glad!ー
I can save my mom with this.
I won.
What?
It costs 10 billion yen.
This is dangerous.
This is interesting.
Ending?
What is this?
The next topic is
How many seconds do you spend on your
precious memories?
Before you forget your loved one, come
to the sea and say a word.
The person who will challenge this
challenge is the singing mermaid,
NAKANISHI.
This is strange.
No matter how many memories you have,
I love you.
That's good.
So it's okay.
I will also love you tomorrow.
That's good.
Something is coming.
Next is the 3rd generation of
heavyweight play, Nakamura Rena.
I want to tell you how much I loved you
and how much I was happy.
I'll forget it tomorrow.
No!
I don't want this!
Yeah, it's real.
That's amazing.
They're doing a stage performance.
I've never...
You can go in properly.
Thank you so much!
I agree.
I'm sure I'll cry if I laugh.
I'm crying.
Really.
If I really lost my memory,
I would be sad if I thought I would
forget my family and members.
That's right.
NAKAMURA and ITO are amazing.
ITO and LILIA are living in a tragic
world.
I'm a little bit of a
YUMIKI.
Please listen to me.
I was in the same group as NAKAMURA and
ITO and LILIA.
I'm the type of group that enters.
I thought I'd say a word to the sea and
end it.
The two of them are back very late.
I have to do something.
I'm not sure if LILIA is a dangle.
From here on, I will check if I can act
naturally in a setting that cuts daily
life into super pinpoints.
What is the first topic of the night?
It's a facial expression play where a
message is confessed to the smartphone
and a response is accepted.
I'm glad I got a reply that I waited
for.
How to show just with a face
Asatora Yamashita challenges
I'm going to start.
Thank you for your viewing.
Did I send him a message?
Thank you for watching.
He just told me he's here.
I see.
He's already here.
Oh, not yet.
What?
Thank you!
Good job!
You're good!
Thank you!
You're good at this.
As expected of Asadore.
Asadore?
Can I call you Asadore?
That was good.
You're really good.
I'm nervous.
You're not nervous at all.
I was nervous when Asadore auditioned.
I'm glad you're not nervous.
Why did this happen?
automatic
Thank you for watching!
The next pin point is
The expression of eating a hamburger
that exceeds the concept so far
Expression acting
So it's so delicious that it's
impossible
Ioki challenges difficult expression
acting
Ioki can go? Ioki will go
Ready start
Today I came to the famous hamburger
shop
I would like to eat immediately
Adding!
This is...
Umayuki!
Wait a minute.
This is an act.
It started with a food report.
I thought it was an act that was doing a
food report.
I thought it was a drama like that.
You don't say Umayuki in dramas or
movies.
It comes out when it's delicious.
Umayuki.
Can I get Umayuki again?
Umayuki!
Thank you very much.
It's cute.
The next act is...
It's an act where you call the clerk by
ringing your finger coolly.
It's cute.
There are such things.
It's a role of a cool woman.
If this is decided coolly.
That's right.
Sato will challenge this act.
Will it be revenge?
Sato has changed.
This block is dangerous.
Please.
Let's start.
Ready, start!
Please give me a fillet.
What is that?
Is it a philhonic?
Please give me a fillet.
What is that?
It's a one-word phrase.
Please give me a fillet.
What did you say?
I think it's cool.
You suddenly called the staff and said,
please give me a fillet.
Suddenly.
It's a foreign setting.
The sound is cool.
The intonation of your speech is like a
philhonic.
It's like that when you talk.
You put a robot in it.
No, I put a foreigner in it.
Foreigners?
So, this is the last time Higuchi is in
Nogizaka.
I'm lonely.
Especially for a first-generation child.
Higuchi may have had various conflicts.
I think there were a lot of hard things.
I'm happy to clean up.
I'm glad.
It was a fun Nogizaka life.
I'm glad you helped me.
You're like a color from the beginning.
I'm glad.
What is this?
I'm proud of you.
I'll prepare a room for you.
I'm glad.
Have you ever been left behind in this
program?
At first, I was afraid of the scene.
I was also very depressed.
But Mr. Hananaman made it interesting.
I thought it would be okay.
I was happy to record every time.
I think it was the best place to come
home.
I'm glad you said that.
Please send a message to the fans who
watched the program.
Yes.
Wow, amazing.
Thank you so much.
I was able to do my best for 11 years
because of the fans who liked me.
Thank you for your warm support.
Nogizaka will continue to grow.
I will continue to watch this program
and support you.
Thank you so much.
See you again.
Thank you.
Congratulations on your graduation.
I'm happy.
Thank you.
Do your best.
Congratulations on your graduation.
Thank you.
Nojisaka 46's 31st single will be
released on December 7th!
Also, the online meet and greet event
for the release of the single will be
held!
And next time, in Kouji, Nogizaka, the
31st single will be announced!
Higuchi Hina's Sosugyo Ceremony, the
delivery ticket is on sale!
I'm Higuchi Hina.
Which one should I choose? This one?
Oh, thank goodness.
The member's bakuro episode.
Maaya wanted to eat a sesame seed, so
she bought it for the dog.
That was Maaya's natural episode.
I wonder if I can send it to her.
I said this.
It's okay. We're friends.
Please subscribe to my channel!