Please subscribe to our channel!
See you next time!
Hello everyone, I'm Rina of Crownpop.
Yes, do you know me?
I'm Rina of Crownpop. Nice to meet you.
I think some of you have seen me for the
first time, but I sing and dance.
My feature is that my ears are big.
Here it is.
You can definitely see the hole in my
ears.
I don't have a hole in my ears, so I'm
big like this.
And my specialty is that I can fold my
ears in three.
Can you see it? I hope you can see it.
I have a specialty that I can fold my
ears in three.
I'm also tall, so I hope you can see me.
I'm about 167 cm tall, so you can
probably see me from a distance.
If you haven't come to my live
performance, I hope you can come and see
me from a distance.
Did you think of me?
Did you really think of me?
Please remember me.
This is Rina from FLAGPOP.
Don't forget me.