Ebichu Table Tennis Tournament
Yay!
Start!
Ha!
It's a pin.
Oh!
Ha!
Woww
Ohh
Really fun
Super fun
Let's at it!
What is that?
I got it!
You got it!
Congratulations!
I did it!
I got it!
I'll do it!
4 points
The game is striking with the ball
This is so fun!
Well done!
Oh wow!
You are really good!!
That was cheating!
Time's up.
Time up.
I can't believe.
21 minutes passed.
To be continued
Thank you!
I'll do my best!
I'm doing my best.
I'm the most serious.
I'll do my best!
Thank you!
I'm so happy.
I'll do my best!
Thank you!
If you're happy, everyone else will be
happy.
Thank you!
8, lower jaw
Too difficult
One more
The zaster doesn't come out
Let's continue
START
Please subscribe to my channel.
See you soon.
Ah!
What?
That was scary.
That's enough.
I'm scared.
It was a ping pong ball.
Everyone was playing ping pong.
It's amazing.
There's no ping pong ball in the bowl.
Our conversation is not in the bowl.
Watch out.
Did you fall down?
It's amazing that you fell down.
It's like making omelet rice.
I was hit by a frying pan.
I'm going to hit you.
I'm in trouble.
Thank you for watching!
Let's go.
What's going on?
Coach?
I'm going to do it.
I'm so scared!
Focus!
Wow!
I'm so scared!
Good aunt Swordㅠㅠ
Good teether Gfferent
Bye bye!
We've been filming really much, so..
It seems cold.
Thank you for watching!
I can't hear you.
I'll do it again.
Two more to go.
You did well.
Now is my chance.
Maybe we can do our best.
Thank you for watching.
You can do it!
I'll go.
Did you just do it?
Oh, no!
Wait a minute!
You can do it!
I'll do it!
I'll do it later.
You can do it!
I'm happy.
I can't remember my facial expressions.
That happened first?
Okay
I'm going to eat it.
It's delicious.
Please subscribe!
We will give the winner, Kashiwagi-san,
a special bento box of Yakiniku-Kuroda-
san.
We are Nami.
Nami looks delicious.
Please open it.
Open!
What is this?
that's what I told you!
It looks good.
It's shining.
We'll have it.
It looks good.
It's not red.
Thank you for the food.
It looks good.
It's soft.
It's good.
I'll have the one I like.
Wait a minute.
It's bread.
It's good.
It's so good!
It's so soft!
Thank you, Iroha-chan!
I'll eat it with rice.
Itadakimasu!
It's so soft and good!
It's so good!
It's the best!
I can't lose to you.
It's so good!
It's so soft!
I thought it's not good to watch it.
It's good to eat with rice.
It's good!
But,
It's so good!
It's different from watching it.
I'll eat it while watching it.
It's so good!
Thank you for watching!
Please look forward to the next video!
Bye-bye!
Let's eat!
Please subscribe!
Are you a member of the team?
What?
I'm just a regular member.
I think it's because I'm not good at
playing ball.
I like throwing the ball with my hands.
I'm not good at it.
I didn't learn it.
I just like it.
I'm glad I won the championship.
I think Riko is better.
I was afraid of Riko.
But when I played with Ayaka, she got
better and better.
So I was afraid of her.
I think Riko is better.
Not as much as I'd expected,
but how long has it been?
I remember that I did it a long time
ago.
I was so excited.
I went to a ryokan when I was in
elementary school.
I went to play table tennis twice after
I joined Ebiju.
I haven't been to a ryokan since then.
I'm a coach for everyone.
I started training my wrist.
It was fun.
I was more concentrated than I thought.
I was so frustrated that I couldn't play
with Hinata in the final.
I was so concentrated.
I got a miracle smash.
I wanted to do more.
I thought table tennis was difficult.
I participated in the fun Grand Prix.
I won the first place in the fun Grand
Prix.
It was fun.
Bowling.
We often go bowling on a tour.
I'm sad that I can't go bowling this
year.
I want to play table tennis with you
someday.
I'm so sad that I couldn't win.
I'm so sad.
I did my best.
I thought I was the best.
I thought I could beat you.
I trained harder than yesterday.
I was just imagining.
I couldn't beat you.
I couldn't beat anyone.
I will learn from the video of table
tennis.
I'm sorry.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Ouch!
Wow!
I'm a little scared.
I'm scared of the same thing as others.
You're so good at it.
I'm losing.
Wow!
I'm not good at it.
As expected.
Despite such