Ebichu's video
Nagaema Riko's baseball lesson
I'm Hinata Kashiwagi
I'm Riko Nagaema
We're going to teach you baseball
So today we're going to teach Riko
baseball
You know what baseball is right?
We're going to teach you baseball
You were the image character for the
2016 Koryu-sen
Did you learn anything from that?
I was just explaining to Hinata-chan
And then the next day
It's been 4 years
I haven't learned anything from that
Then I'll teach you again
You can write baseball in kanji right?
No, ni, kyuu
That's right
What's that in English?
I don't know!
No, no, no
I don't like it!
Do you use it a lot?
I hear it a lot
Handball?
That's a different sport
Baseball!
Correct!
Do you know how many people are playing
baseball?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5
The person who is standing there, right?
Yes, the person who is standing here
The person who is in the middle
The person who is in the middle?
The person who is throwing?
Yes, the person who is in the middle
I can't get it, right?
It's a different sport
How many people are there to make it
scatter?
5 people
There are a lot of people
This is 10 people
Not 10 people, but 9 people
Pitcher, catcher, and there are people
who protect here
There is a thing called Nagegaya
I play with 9 people
9 rounds?
That's right!
We will play 9 rounds
The total score I fought here will come
out here
The more people, the more wins
There is an inning
If you take 3 outs in 1 inning, you will
switch to the next team
I taught you the very basic things
I was taught well
Is the pitch system okay?
I can put it in for a moment
There are still a lot of this
Please remember
Thank you
Today is the defense
I want you to remember the names of the
positions
Where do you think the pitcher is?
In the middle
Correct
Catcher is?
Below
Correct
The problem is this
Riko's problem is this
I knew the first and second types
There are 5 home bases and there are 1,
2, 3 types
This is called Naya
Naya type
Gaya type
People who protect the outside
Naya and Gaya
People who protect the first type
Think from 1
English like a pitcher
It's not 1
It's difficult
When you say you put out the first
single
First?
First, second, third
Great
That's it
First, second, third
Only here is a little different
If you say it big
The name of the hairstyle
Small
I don't know the name of the hair
Long or short
Short
Correct
You're good at teaching
If you say it big here, it's like right,
left, middle
Right, left, center
Correct
Riko is amazing
Riko already remembered the name of the
defense position
This time, I remembered the name of the
position
I think that Riko's level has been
improved
So today was the defense
Today is the batting
There is a home run
How many points did you say?
How many points do you want to give?
I really don't know, so 5 points.
Oh!
3 points!
Then no one is here.
So I hit the home run and Riko-chan got
5 points.
3 points.
I only got 1 point.
Hey!
But for example, there is a batter here.
There was a person who hit a hit in
front of this person.
Then, if you hit a home run, this person
will also return together, so 2 points.
Oh!
Then let's say there is another person
here.
How many points do you get in this case?
I said now.
4 points?
3 points.
I'll hit it.
This person was also hitting a hit, so
I'm here.
You will come back together.
How many people are at the base?
Now 3 people?
Yes, so 3 points.
Then if you are here.
4 points!
Correct.
The 9 people from earlier are not here.
That's a defense.
I was talking about attacking.
Oh!
The defense is here.
Is that the enemy team?
Yes, the enemy team is here.
This is a defensive person, so there is
only one person attacking.
Oh!
I'm sorry.
It seems to be a heartless person.
Is it a heartless person?
I see.
Yes.
Did you understand it like this?
I understood.
Did you learn a little?
Then, here is the batting episode.
I would like to imitate the batting of
my favorite baseball player.
I'm a coach now, but I'm a very
distinctive player.
I did it.
Do you know who it is?
I don't know, but I did it.
From the opening of the foot, this is
only a field.
Then, today I would like to tell you how
to enjoy the baseball batting.
What did you see other than the exchange
game at that time?
I saw it once when I was in elementary
school.
Is there?
Maybe it's Jingu.
I went once.
When I first went to the baseball
stadium, I already liked baseball, so I
wanted to buy a uniform or a towel.
Riko-chan doesn't have a favorite team,
does she?
It depends on the stadium, but the food
is different.
Jingu is a fried chicken festival.
I've never been to a public school, but
I was told that there was a very
delicious food.
The stadium is open from an hour and a
half before the game starts.
I went there an hour and a half before
the game started, and I could see the
players practicing and warming up.
When you're an idol, you don't get to
see the rehearsal.
I was really happy about that.
And there's a cheering song for each
player, and I'm looking forward to
singing it with everyone.
For example, in the team, I often sang
Tokyo Ondo with an umbrella.
I thought baseball was similar to being
an idol, and I felt that the audience's
voice was very important.
The bigger the cheering, the more the
baseball players will feel like they're
doing it.
It's important to have a cheering song,
and it's fun to remember it.
The seats are also divided into inside
and outside.
Pearl balls fly to the inside, so you
can see the ball up close or catch it.
In the team, the players will throw the
ball to the inside seat and give it to
the other player.
The ball is a service.
For example, the mascot of Yakult,
Tsubakuro, puts a towel in a rocket and
shoots it.
In the team, the cheering style changes,
and the inside seat can't be standing.
I was an inside player when I was in
elementary school.
I stood up and shouted out loud when I
was an outside player, and I wanted to
cheer for the team.
I recommend the outside player.
It's interesting that the cheering style
changes depending on the seat.
I think it's good to look at both.
I drank lemon sour at Jingu Stadium.
I drank it at the Naya Saki Stadium.
After I turned 20.
I can drink alcohol at the stadium.
Uriko may be drinking beer at home when
she turns 20.
Uriko came to me and said,
Hey, Uriko.
Oh, that's cool.
Uriko may be doing it.
I can see fireworks at Jingu Stadium.
I can see fireworks with about 30,000
people at the stadium.
I heard a little and wanted to go.
It looks fun.
I'm glad.
I want to go with Uriko.
I want to go in the summer.
I agree.
Next year.
Let's go together next year.
Please.
I'll go next year.
It's a deal.
Finally, I'd like to talk about my
favorite Tokyo Yakult Swallows.
The most attractive thing about the
Swallows is that the players get along
well with each other.
Some players give me food.
I'm a fan of that.
I'm curious about what the players are
doing in private.
I'm curious about whether the players
get along with each other outside of the
game.
I'm glad to know that.
Yakult is weak.
I have the image that the players are
weak.
But that's not true.
The players are the best in Japan.
I'm a fan of the players, but I'm a
little worried about the players.
But the players are not weak.
The players are amazing.
The player I support is Munezaka
Murakami.
He is the same age as Riko.
He is really amazing.
I think he will be a big hit in Japan
someday.
I want to change the image of Yakult
that I lose to him.
I think so as a fan.
I'm glad if Riko is interested in the
game.
I want everyone to support the game.
Let's play together with an umbrella.
I will give Riko an umbrella.
Today was the last episode.
I talked about the game.
Let's support the game together.
Thank you very much.
I'm tired.
To be continued.
We will do 3 innings in total.
Let's do it.
What is this?
It's a foul.
I'm out with one more.
I'm out.
To be continued.
It was out.
But Riko-chan got one out.
She got one out from this batter.
It's a foul.
Foul.
Is this a right fly?
Two out.
Next time?
If I get one out next time, I'll change.
This is hard.
Out! 3 out change.
It's a one-time attack.
Here I go.
It's a foul, so I'll do it.
I moved it.
3, 2, 1.
It's a strike. I just moved it.
It's a 3-strike.
Really?
Yes.
I have no more.
One out.
This one?
Yes.
I did it.
3, 2, 1.
You're fast.
This one?
I'm going to ask you all.
I should have studied.
You're worried.
Ready, set, go!
Pearl.
Oh!
Picture.
Two out.
Ready, set, go!
Pearl.
Oh, no.
Ready, set, go!
Oh, it's over.
You blew it.
Three out, change!
I only have one more.
Look! Two base hit!
Base hit!
I want to make this girl run.
Good!
Isn't it good to hit two base from two
out?
I'll do it.
It's out!
It's frozen!
I came this far.
This is sad.
Riko's attack.
It's a hit.
Let's say it's a hit.
Riko, it's a hit.
This is it.
And?
It's a hit.
The next batter is...
The count is...
9?
It's gone.
It's gone?
Ready, set...
It's a hit.
It's not out yet.
What about this person?
This person...
First, I went over there.
And then...
I remember it well.
Ready, set...
It's a foul.
So...
Ready, set...
I hit it.
Out.
Yes, out.
I'll spin it.
Set, go.
Out.
That was close!
How can you be so fast?
I've never seen that before.
Set, go.
It's over.
I did it!
Good bye.
I'll go to the third round.
I did it!
You did it in one try.
It's out.
I'll do it again.
Go! Go! Go!
Which one is it?
I think it's a hit.
Hit!
Let me run!
I ran.
I'm here.
Just like Riko-chan.
I want to do my best in this situation.
And this is the last time.
Here I go.
Bye!
You're so good at this!
Come back here!
Ready, set...
Out!
It's a two-base.
From here?
What?
What did you do?
You cheated.
I cheated.
I'm scared.
Ready, go.
Out.
Out?
Yes, out.
Here I go.
Ready, go.
Hit?
It was a hit.
Yes.
What's this?
Ready, set...
I got it!
This is a manroi.
Wait, isn't this the first time?
I'm so moved. I've never seen a manroi
in the back of the third floor.
If you do a manroi home run with this,
it's a firework.
If I'm out next time, I'll be out.
Goodbye.
This is an ambulance.
It's a tanker. Don't be carried by a
tanker.
It's out.
This girl must have shaved her body.
She shaved her body and protected me.
I'm out.
I think she has a broken bone.
I'm sorry.