This week's Ebichu Tastas is a big hit
Mini corner festival part 3
Members are divided into 3 teams
They will challenge various projects
This time
I'm aiming for the sea
Sea?
Mayama who loves ramen will show her own
restaurant
What will happen?
Hirota and Hoshina will open the chicken
with terashugyo
Ebichu Tastas start
I can't be a good or bad guy
100 times more annoying emotions
I'm so into you that I can't bear it
What should I do with the heart of a
jubilee?
Moratorium, moratorium, moratorium,
junior high school student
Add various things to your private Ebisu
junior high school
Ebichu Tastas
This program is brought to you by the
following sponsors.
We will send you a video of the event.
Thank you for watching.
I'm the singer of today's song, Ginata
Kashiwagi.
What are we doing today?
I'm the singer of today's song, Takihei
and Chue.
Let's sing Trump with everyone.
What are we doing today?
Today is the third episode of the
popular show.
It's called Ebi-Chu plus Mini Corner.
Mini Corner Festival is a variety show
where Ebi-Chu members challenge
themselves.
It's a traditional festival of walking,
cutting, and talking to each other.
This time, we will be divided into three
groups and challenged a certain theme.
groups and challenge a different variety
show.
Actually, there is a theme in this mini
corner.
What is it?
What do you think is necessary for Ebi-
Chu to make it even more powerful?
That's the theme of this time.
What is necessary for Ebi-Chu to make it
even more powerful?
What do you think, Mayama?
After all, no one is in junior high
school this year, so junior high school
students are needed.
Everyone is scouting.
What do you think, Kaho?
I think it's a good idea to ask various
people and expand the circle.
You mean to expand Ebi-Chu's secret
circle?
Aya-chan.
That's right.
It's a high-rise.
It's a very realistic one.
No.
What is necessary for Ebi-Chu now?
Training.
Training?
Why?
Training is necessary.
It's true that it's a free program.
It's a relaxed program.
I think training is important.
What kind of group is this?
It's all shuffled.
It's all shuffled?
I see.
I'll announce it.
The first group is Hirota and Hoshina.
The next program is Hirota and Hoshina's
spiritual training.
It's a serious training.
It's serious.
That's why Ebi-Chu doesn't have enough
training.
I see.
You really go to training.
It's a serious training.
Hirota and Hoshina's challenge is a
serious training.
They train their mental strength to pull
Ebi-Chu.
The next group is...
Mayama and Matsuno.
What?
What is this?
Mayama and Matsuno.
The next program is Ebi-Chu Ramen.
That's good.
Mayama and Matsuno's challenge is Ebi-
Chu Ramen.
This is a perfect program for Mayama who
likes ramen.
Mayama's blog often shows ramen.
The comments are also about the
compatibility of soup and noodles.
They are very particular about how to
eat ramen.
Mayaba-san, who loves ramen, will train
Matsuno-san to discover new
possibilities in shrimp.
Is this training to make ramen?
That's right.
It's not something to eat.
Matsuno-san has such a clear face.
Because it's training.
And the last group is...
Yasumoto, Kobayashi, Nakayama, me and
Chu-Ei
The next group is...
X-Squad's Oogiri Club
I'm not going to be a part of it
Oogiri was just a training
The third group is Oogiri Club, training
the muscles of the audience
They are looking forward to the master
Nakayama
After the third corner, something
strange happened to Takiyue
I'm not going to be a part of it
This time, Takiyue will be a part of
Oogiri Club
I'm going to be a part of Oogiri?
Yes, please
Will I be a part of it?
Since the broadcast time is getting
shorter, we have a scout for you
I see
I'm not sure
If it's not funny, we will cut it all
Really?
Please do your best
If it's not funny, the broadcast time
will be shorter
This mini corner festival
The first corner is...
It's started, shrimp ramen bowl
But, Mayama is not here. Where did she
go?
Hey, Omochi!
What? I can hear something.
What?
I let you win.
What happened?
Are you working at a ramen shop?
No, I came here to make ramen
Are you making fun of me?
No, I'm not
Mayama is getting excited
What are their expectations?
I'll do my best to make delicious ramen
I'll steal Takumi's skill
I'll make the best cup of ramen
They are a little bit different
But they are ready to learn how to make
ramen
It's rude
This time, they will train at popular
ramen shop in Takadanobaba, Tokyo
The ramen that the manager Takamine
makes is
Pai Chi ramen, which is concentrated on
the umami of chicken
They learn how to make the best ramen,
which is a combination of the golden
soup and the very thin noodles
Hello
Thank you for coming
I heard you came here to train
Have you ever eaten our ramen?
Not yet
You haven't eaten it?
Then let's start with the food
Yes
Thank you
Shrimp ramen and training
Taste test
Good smell
Looks delicious
Let's eat
Oh, it's good
It's a light and refreshing taste of the
sauce
It's thinner than the usual noodles
It goes well with this light soup
Please leave a comment
Mayama noticed it
Normally, they don't put olive oil and
tabasco
They put it in the soup
Soy sauce, shichimi, vinegar, and sesame
It depends on the taste
Why do you think it's so good?
The soup is light
It can be used for any taste
As expected
That's right
Mayama is good at making the soup
As expected
I have to put chocolate on my hand
Thank you for your viewing
Is it delicious?
She is training seriously to run a ramen
shop
It is possible
It is not delicious
Shrimp ramen sort~~ option 2
First want to enter the kitchen
Wait A, We there No
this is a student
A the position of the customers
Stefan
A place that only God could enter
By the God we get the ramen
I'll eat it
Do you understand?
You can't enter here easily
I understand
I'm scared
Mayama's feelings for ramen
Ramen for you
Yes
Ramen for me
A moment of happiness
No matter how tired I get from work,
I came here today to eat that one bowl
of ramen
I can do my best tomorrow because I have
that one bowl of ramen
On the other hand, what is ramen for
you?
Ramen? I only eat ramen sometimes
I ate ramen the day before and ate soy
sauce ramen the day before
I like pork bone ramen the most
I like soy sauce ramen the most
But if I can eat anything, that's fine
What do you want to make?
I want to make and eat
That's all!
Please excuse me!
In Ma-yama Co., which is located in a
real kitchen,
The training they will do now is...
Preparing the soup and the young men
They will do it in pairs
Mayama has a suggestion I am aiming to
open a restaurant
Open a restaurant?
Yes, I am aiming to open a restaurant
Then, I think it's soup
I think so too
I'm sorry but can you look at the
noodles?
I understand, I will do my best
Mayama is preparing the soup to decide
the taste of ramen
Power
It's not working at all.
It's difficult, isn't it?
It's harder than I thought.
Matsuno is going to try the clear
surface of the water, which is facing
the rotation from evening.
Are you waiting for the clear surface?
You are waiting, aren't you?
I'm waiting for it.
I'm training. I can hear a great sound
from the other side.
I'm a little worried, but I have to
train with my eyes.
It seems that he is stealing the
master's technique by looking at it with
his eyes.
Once more.
On the other hand, Mayama is watching
the training of the ramen.
It's hard.
She puts the chicken into the
ramen.
I'm not good at making ramen, but I'm
good at making ramen.
I only make sweets, so I don't use
knives.
Mayama is serious about making ramen.
Shrimp ramen training 3. Preparing
ingredients
Two people prepare chicken char siu,
boiled egg, and three shiraga leeks
Mayama who cuts the ginger necessary for
chicken char siu
And Matsuno who makes seasoned egg
I entered
6 minutes 30 seconds
30 seconds
Mayama trains his technique
Matsuno is doing a long-distance trip
This is a ramen road
And the dream of the future that Mayama
talked about
I want to have a restaurant
You mean you want to go
I think so
I like seafood
I want to do a stall at a live show
Ramen stall
Sounds fun
I want to go to a restaurant
The dream is to have many people eat my
ramen
Two hours until closing time, the
training continues
Next, Hirota and Hoshina challenge the
real training
Hirota and Hoshina's spiritual training
I was surprised by the real temple from
there. We were in Wangan Studio, right?
We are now in the Wako-Oshi area of
​​Saitama Prefecture.
It took an hour and a half from the
opening of Fuji TV.
Two people who came to train hard.
We are ramen.
It's very good.
I think I'm eating ramen.
Let's go.
This is a corner.
Two people who often talk in the train.
They are training silently.
When they climb the stone stairs,
two people are waiting.
Hello.
Welcome.
They welcome the heavy food.
This is Seiryuji Fudoin.
This is a temple of training.
Yes, here at Seiryuji Fudoin, there is a
temple with a history of about 1200
years.
Various training and training can be
done.
There, Mr. Morita Eiryu works as a
priest.
What kind of training do they do in this
temple?
Today, you two are going to do zazen-gyo
in this temple of training
Zazen!
I've never heard of it
Have you ever done zazen?
I have, when I was in elementary school
From now on, they will start to train
their mind in zazen-gyo
zazen to prepare the mental disorder
They have made such a problem in the
program before
I'm going to do zazen-gyo
I think there is something like how I
want to be seen as this group
A conflict that must be suppressed
within the group
Our youth, you know,
We've been through a period of ten years
I want to break another shell
We're clumsy
They want to break their shells in a
clumsy way
It seems that they were worried because
they wanted to improve each other's
shrimp
The training begins! After this, the
real training begins
Can the two who are worried show their
answers in the zazen?
The training begins!
Their training continues
This spring, they have celebrated their
second year of broadcasting
Tonight, a new project will start
Hello
On April 5th, the members of Ebichu were
gathered without being told anything
Everyone is looking at us with a face
that they don't know why we were
gathered
What is it?
Actually, there is a new project
First of all, please look at this
This is it!
Yes, Ebichu's new single
What are you talking about?
We haven't heard anything
We just came up with it
The times are moving forward
Suddenly, they are confused by the
announcement of a new single
What is going on?
I'm curious
I'll take the title
This is it
It's not a song that says look at me
It's really look at me
The reaction was good
It's good now
Look at me
Let's go
Please stand up
Sweet headphone users, here it is
What? What do you mean?
You look at the title, the song, and you
say that the lyrics are yours
That's not possible
This is a song that is...
It's a very realistic story
I'm curious
I want to hear it
Mayama, calm down
The lyrics of the shrimp chuga
这里から新作を大発表!
The winner is...
Ebichu's songwriting!
Do you know our language skills?
What?
I don't think so
I know that you're stupid
But I think you should see the cheapness
of the tape
We use a strong tape
It's our second year
We're going to start a new project
But we don't think it's easy to write
lyrics
So Chuu-san
Don't underestimate the lyrics!
What does it say?
Ebichu's songwriting!
The world of lyrics is a narrow and
narrow road
But isn't it too cheap?
You should know that the quality of the
tape is the same
The possibility of making a masterpiece
is low
But if you have a heart, you can make a
masterpiece
Kai-ki's song is in the album
So everyone's song might be a
masterpiece
The members are writing lyrics
A new project to make a song
Ebichu's songwriting is starting tonight
What kind of song do you want to make?
I want to sing Ebichu's song in a rock
style
I want to say, wake up today
You can do that
Wake up today
I ate a bread
You can do that
But it's boring
I want to say, I'm happy
You want to be scolded
All the songs are the same
Kobayashi-san
I want to make a melancholic song
What?
What's wrong?
Wait, one person is making a song
It's too early
Today in a dream
You can say no
The prince riding a horse
Why are you making her go forward?
Sorry, Matsuho-san
You're overflowing with talent
You're overflowing
I saw Mary Gowland
I know
I saw it
I wanted to express that
Really?
You're making a sound
If you do that, the dance will be 8
people
The audience will get drunk
The end
Next time on Ebichu Tastas, Hirota and
Hoshina will open the chicken
The cloth will be burnt
And in the big meal, Goriya Fever
And Ramen Mayama will open
This program was provided by the sponsor
you are watching
Please give one to each of them
I'm in trouble
Because of the house