The members of Ebichu challenge the original 5 kinds of competitions at Round One! Which team will win?
At Round One! 5 kinds of team competitions! Photography cooperation Round One Stadium Itabashi
Ebichu Darts!
The 4th event, Ebichu Darts: Count up to win! Aim for a high score with your whole team!
20 triples means 60 points!
Aim for the BULL!
Center the dart in the middle of your index finger.
Hold it like this so that you can balance it
Grab it with your right hand.
Gently bend your middle finger.
Put your center of gravity on your right foot.
Pull straight and throw straight.
Ding-dong!
Oh, wow!
I just made a big face.
The fourth event, shrimp darts. The competition is about to begin!
START!
Do as I teach you.
What? Isn't that great?
Oh, yeah!
Yeah!
That's great!
Ah!
No, it's too hard..
That's great.
You're good!
That's good!
Good job, Cocona!
Wow!
That's great! That's good!
I'm catching up!
Yuno, hang in there!
Yuno wants to get stabbed, too!
Throw it straight.
Huh?
Go, Maya!
Yes!
Oh, no, it's hard!
The fourth event, darts among shrimp, the result is announced!
357 points
274 points
269 points
2nd place B team Yasumoto/Kashiwagi Kazami 3rd place C team Kobayashi/Nakayama/Okubo
Points are awarded according to the rank in each event. 1st place 10pts 2nd place 7pts 3rd place 5pts
Ebichu Bowling!
The fifth event, Bowling in the shrimp, triples the points earned! Aim for a big upset!
Start!
Wow! So close!
One more!
We're all in this together!
Whoa!
Oh no...
Shall we go?
Yeah...
I'll do my best!
Hold this hand normally.
When you release it, hold it here as if you're sending it out.
See you later.
With a "see you later" feeling.
Have a good day!
I'm getting better!
Pressure!
Ayaka Yasumoto of Team B is under pressure for her third strike in a row.
Yes!
Oh no!
Amazing!
Oh, no!
Yeah!
I feel like I can do it.
Cocona Sakuragi, Operation Get Rid of the Garter, that dominant throw.
That's good! I can do it!
Cocona Sakuragi, Operation De-Garter, part 2, right hand throw
Cocona Sakuragi, Operation De-Garter, part 2, two-handed throw.
Let's do this!
And...
I've improved a little.
At first, all I did was garter.
But now I'm a little better.
It was fun!
The three of us enjoying the replay of the game.
I'm pretty sure I'm going to jump after every throw.
The overall rankings were announced!
In second place
Second place was a close race!
2nd place, Team C, 45 pts, Bowling record, 2nd place, 205 points
1st place goes to...!
1st place Team B 67 pts Bowling record 1st place 258 points
3rd place Team E 42 pts Bowling record 3rd place 191 points
Member Interview
I had so much fun that I forgot I was filming!
I've been to Round One twice in my life.
I've been to Round One maybe twice in my life...
This was probably my second time.
I've always wanted to play Spo-cha, so I had a great time.
But you know what?
This ....
Basketball... Shooting?
Our team is so bad at it.
Hmm...
I used to play soccer.
Struck out for soccer?
I'd like to try that one.
I think we could have won that one.
I think it was the first time for the nine of us to have fun shooting on location like this.
I think it was the first time for the nine of us to have fun filming on location like this.
It was a lot of fun playing games with everyone.
The bowling game went well.
I got more and more excited.
I really wanted to play again.
I actually got to play billiards.
I'm not sure why...
I'd like to try again after practicing a little more
I want to try again after I practice a little more.
If I can learn how to play in various ways...
I think I'll be able to enjoy the game more.
I want to play again.
When I was in high school and college.
I used to come here a lot when I was in high school and college.
I used to come here during exam breaks.
It's been a while since I've been here, so it's been a lot of fun.
And I hadn't been able to bowl for a while.
I really enjoyed playing with them as if it was my own private time.
And I was really happy to collaborate with a place
I'm really happy to be able to collaborate with a place that I've been coming to for a long time.
I hope you all enjoy the collaboration with karaoke and bowling.
We're collaborating on karaoke and bowling.
We're collaborating on drinks and stuff, so...
So please come and join us.
And of course, you can enjoy Round One's amusement facilities.
And of course, enjoy the amusement.
I hope you can enjoy it with Ebichu.
Today I just want to
We were just playing.
I mean, the nine of us
We've never been to a party before.
So playing at Round One was the first time for all nine of us.
It was the first time for all nine of us to play together.
It was the first time for all nine of us to play together, so it was a lot of fun.
I played billiards today.
I'm really good at billiards games.
but it was the first time
I thought it was a little bit difficult.
But it was fun.
I would like to study and play again.
It's been quite a while since I've been able to come to Round One.
I came here just for the fun of it.
It reminded me a little of my youth.
We used to go go-karting at the beginning, right?
And then we raced at Pike.
Oh, and the bikes sounded fun, too...
I wish I could have done that when I was watching the go-karts.
I was thinking about it in the back of my mind.
But I thought, "Motorcycle sounds fun too! I thought, "Bike sounds fun too!
I've been to Round One.
I hadn't been to Round One since a few years ago
I hadn't been to Round One since a couple of years ago.
We were so happy to see 19 of us
We divided into groups and worked together.
We were like a group, working together, trying to win the championship.
It was a lot of fun.
The NC team was pretty good.
I was saying that the NC team was not very athletic.
But we ended up in second place.
I'm glad we were able to do that.
We were surprised even by ourselves.
Um... Billiards?
I'm terrible at it.
It was really difficult.
And darts?
I think it would be cool if I could play.
I'd like to try.
This is my first time at Round One.
I didn't know it was this much fun! I thought.
I'd like to come more often with the members of EBICHI CHUKU.
I want to come here a lot more with the members of Ebiichu.
When we played darts.
It was more than I thought it would be.
It flew better than I thought it would.
I felt like I had found a new talent.
Or rather...
That's all I could do.
Bowling I finally decided
Don't just throw it like a normal bowling ball
I was throwing like this.
I was throwing from the bottom.
I want to train a little bit so that I can throw normally.
I haven't been to Spo-Cha since I was in elementary school.
I haven't come to Spo-Cha since I was in elementary school.
It's been a long time since I've been here.
I've never been able to come here with all the members.
It was the first time we could all play together.
The go-carts...
I'm a very safe driver and I drive very slowly.
But today, I took the plunge and went really fast.
It was fun.
I want to try something else...
Roller skating.
I used to do it every day when I was in elementary school.
I haven't done that in a long time.
Bowling was a team of three, and I was on a team with Aya and Hina.
Aya, Hina and I were on a team.
And there...
First, Hina-chan made a strike.
Then I did.
Then Aya-chan made a strike.
Three strikes in a row.
Everyone was really excited.
We could replay the scene on the monitor.
And when I saw Aya-chan's
the way she jumped when she made the strike.
It was so amazing!
It was so much fun!
Round One collaboration video shoot!
We all gave high-fives to the people nearby
After that, we went to the camera.
Then to the camera. Yay!
Yay!
You have to say "Se-no".
You want me to say it?
Ready!
Yeah!
Yes! Okay!
Thank you!
Is it your favorite song?
Yes...
PLAYBACK
It's so core!
You're looking at it right.
PLAYBACK is the best!
What's up with the coelacanths! I love it!
We are collaborating with Round One for karaoke and bowling!
Please come and play!