Ebichu's video
Round 1
Team Taiko
Ebichu starts
This is 20 triple, so it's 60 points.
This is 2 times outside.
This is 40 points because it's double.
This is 2 points.
You're beans now.
That's the shoe color.
Right.
Right again
If you point the ball the way it is
moving, the ball exposes itself and the
ball is going upwardsall the way it
moves
Focus on right leg
and pull straight and throw
won hear ähæ psy mä bääååå
sensei, sensei...
Oh!
Ready 미안 TSUKA
Ah no No
Ah!
OK
I'll teach you how to do it.
Very good.
Great!
T
Tabut 해야
A
Ha
Sakura pink
I'm the only one who can do it.
It's good.
If you can't do it,
Ahhhhhhh
Yes!
It's good.
Ahhhhhhh
Amazing!
Wow!
Can you do it?
I did it!
You did it!
Good luck, Shintarō!
I want to support you!
Wait, throw it straight.
What?
Amazing!
Oh, no!
357 points!
274 points!
2, 6, 9!
269 points!
This means...
Finally!
Yay!
Congratulations!
Good morning!
Start!
Goal, and hit!
It hurts.
Come on!
She minds her own business!
Soon after...
Thank you for watching!
I started FC in April 2019.
I know.
I did it
I passed
I'm a little bit better now.
I was a little bit better at first.
But I'm getting better.
I'm happy.
I'm having fun.
I'm jumping.
I'm not.
I'm having fun.
The second is...
This is a new team.
It's amazing!
The third is...
The fourth is...
This is a new team.
Yay!
It was fun though.
The fourth is...
I forgot that it was a shoot.
I had so much fun.
I think I've been to the first round
twice in my life.
I think it was the second time this
time.
I really wanted to play sports.
It was fun.
It's like...
What is it?
Basketball shoot.
The game of throw-in.
Our team is a little bad.
I was learning soccer.
I want to try soccer's track-out.
If it was that, we might have won.
It was the first time that we had fun
shooting with nine people.
It was really fun playing games with
everyone.
Bowling was pretty good.
I'm getting excited.
I want to do it again.
I actually did it.
I want to practice a little more.
I want to try again.
If I can do it in various ways,
I think I can enjoy the game more.
I want to do it again.
I came to play a lot when I was in high
school and college.
I came to play a lot when I was on my
exam break.
It was really fun to play with you after
a long time.
I haven't been able to play bowling for
a while.
I had a lot of fun playing like a
private.
I'm really happy to be able to
collaborate with the place I've been to.
I'm collaborating with Karaoke and
bowling.
There is also a collaboration drink.
I hope you can enjoy the sports drink
and the amusement park together.
I was just playing today.
I'm going to play bowling with nine
people.
I've never been to a game before,
so I had the chance to play with nine
people in Round 1.
It was my first time, so it was a lot of
fun.
The billiards I played today...
I'm really good at games,
but it was my first time playing a real
champion,
so I thought it was a bit difficult,
but it was fun,
so I wanted to study again.
It's been a while since I've been to
Round 1,
so I was really looking forward to it.
I was reminded of my youth.
I played Go Kart at first,
and then I went to a race with a
motorcycle.
I thought,
I wanted to play Go Kart.
I thought about it in my heart.
I thought I could ride a motorcycle.
I've been playing with Kago for a few
years,
so it was fun to play with nine people.
Team C said they were a bad group,
but they got a second place.
I was surprised.
The billiards...
It was a bit difficult.
It was really difficult.
I think it's cool if I can do it,
so I want to try it.
It was my first time at Round 1,
and I thought it was a lot of fun,
so I wanted to come with more members.
When I played Darts, I felt like I had
found a new talent.
I could only do that.
I didn't throw the ball normally,
but I was throwing it like this.
I want to practice to be able to throw
it normally.
It was my first time at Sporcha when I
was in elementary school,
so it's been a long time.
I've never been able to play with all
the members,
so it was fun to play with everyone for
the first time.
national team,
I had a lot of fun today.
I want to try roller skating.
I used to do it every day when I was in
elementary school.
I want to do it after a long time.
I was in the bowling team.
I was in the team of AYA and HINA.
HINA was the first to strike.
I was the next to strike.
Next, AYA was also the first to strike.
We were all having fun.
I can replay the scene on the monitor.
The jump when AYA struck was amazing.
I had a lot of fun.
Everyone high-touches the person who is
closest to you.
Then I looked at the camera and said,
YAY!
I want to say it.
I don't have a sound.
I said, YAY!
Thank you.
What is your favorite song?
Playback.
I like it.
I like it very much.
Playback is a song that can be played.
I'm happy.
I like RIKU and SHIIRAKAN.
We are collaborating with Round 1 in
karaoke and bowling.
Please come to play.