Thank you for watching.
This week's Ebichu Tastas are looking
for a room for Mayaba who wants to live
alone.
I'm in the bathroom.
The members are excited about the unique
property. What kind of new life will
begin?
Stay tuned for the next episode.
Are you ready?
Ebichu Sastas, Start!
What should I do with the heart of a
chubby girl?
Moratorium, moratorium, moratorium,
junior high school students
Shiritsu Ebisu Junior High School is
trying out a variety of things!
Ebisu Justice
You're pretty serious about this, right?
This program is brought to you by the
following sponsors.
Thank you for watching!
Ebichu Tastosu has started!
Where is this place?
It's like a cafe
It's a cafe
It's a serious place
It's amazing, you can open it like this
It's like a room
It's like a cafe
No no no, I'm sorry, it was my fault
Don't close it!
See you next week!
That's amazing!
Isn't it?
Amazing!
What's the theme of this fashionable
space?
What are we doing today?
Today, it seems that Mayama-san from
Otona could do what she wanted to do
It's a special day for Otona
Let's ask her what she wants to do
Let's say it together
One, two
Mayama-san!
Bye!
I'm the only one who's on the table
I was forced to get off the table
Today, we are going to make Mayama's
wish come true
What do you want to do when you are 20?
Actually, I want to live alone
You are an adult
So you are going to look for Mayama's
room today
You are serious today
I'm serious
I'm coming
I'm already planning to sign a contract
So, for Mayama who wants to start living
alone
We are going to look for a property
together
I don't see him today
He's not here
Where did he go?
Are you looking for someone?
Who is that?
We were waiting for you
You are too excited
This way
Hello
What's going on?
Chie, what's going on?
I'm not Chuei
Nice to meet you, I'm Chuei from Chuei
Real Estate
This time, Chuei Real Estate will
introduce you to the perfect property
for Mayama
So today, really...
By the way, this is a property for 5
people to share a room
I'm going to introduce you to the
perfect property for 5 people to share a
room
Okay, Mr. Mayama, please make a decision
It's just right, isn't it?
Everyone in the house will live
upstairs, right?
It's good
But, since this time, you are Mr.
Mayama, what kind of room do you want to
live in?
I would like you to tell me the
conditions of this middle-class real
estate
Do you have a specific condition?
Yes, I do
Please write down the conditions here
What is it?
Is this really?
Yes, it is
What is Mayama's particularity about
real estate?
Mayama's particularity is this
A lot of space
The first is a large room
A large room
How large do you want it to be?
If it is this size, it is enough
This is quite large
Wait a minute, Mayama-san
Are you underestimating the real estate?
This is a big one
If it is this size in the whole
I see, including all the bus and other
things
Including all the bus and toilet
But it is large
It is large
It is quite large
And the difference between the bus and
the toilet
I hope it has a foot bath function
I want to enter the toilet
Is a unit bus not good?
If it is different from the bus, the
price will go up
Can I think about it?
It's OK
Let's do our best
Mayama-san
Really?
The middle-class real estate
You want to do your best
Yes, I want to do my best
And
There is a shop around
What kind of shop is this?
Like a shop
Like a supermarket
Yes, yes
Like ramen
Like a supermarket
Ramen
It is a super ramen in the suburbs
I see
Super ramen
And the condition of not having a
license
Is there a place where the building is
crowded?
Like a girl, she was also particular
about security
Will she find an item that suits
Mayama's particularity?
The first property to introduce to
Mayama-san is here
Super open designer's mansion without a
license
Mayama-san, you like big rooms, right?
Yes
But I'd like to introduce this open-air
property
Where is it?
Here it is
It's so stylish
It's full of grass
10 minutes walk from Minamisenju Station
Designer's mansion with high
expectations
It's already quite stylish at this point
I think you'll definitely like it
Do you want to sign a contract?
No, no, no
I'll sign it
How is it? Isn't it pretty good?
It's good, but I'm not done yet. Let's
see what's inside
I understand. I'll show you the room.
Everyone, this way
What kind of room is in the apartment?
Mayama could you open the door?
Mayama-sama, may I open the door?
Mayama-sama, open the door!
Excuse me
What's going on?
Look, look, look
This is not a house
It's not a house
Come on in!
What's this?
Come in and take a look
It's warm
What?
The bathroom is fully open
The bathroom and the bath are fully open
This is a room that is not qualified
according to Mayama-sama's wishes
It's not qualified
This room is a super open double room
There are no doors or walls in the room,
and it's perfect for Mayama's
particularity of not having a blind
spot.
I like this one.
This is Mayama's favorite bath and
toilet.
And the bath is big.
There is also a fan here, so it's a good
way to prevent humidity.
You can play music.
You can also take a bath in a hurry.
You can do it.
You can do it right away even though
it's a separate bath and toilet.
And all the members can come and play.
But I can't invite people.
I'm a little embarrassed when the
members come to the bathroom.
Then you can buy a partition.
It's 315 yen.
You can play by yourself.
For example, let's play like everyone is
here to play.
Mayama, Mayama.
Can you imagine that everyone is here to
play and I'm here?
Mayama, can I play?
So, the simulation.
When the members come to play in
Mayama's room,
If you come to Mayama's room, you can
play.
We came to see you.
Take off your clothes
Make sure you are all set
Yes
Ok
I'm ready
The sun is shining
Nice
I need to wash my hands
You are quick
You are holding back
I'm going to borrow this corner
You are going to borrow this corner?
I'm going to sit here
Wow, Aya-chan
Aya-chan, you need to wash the toilet
I don't have a towel
Yes!
Matsuno is already in the bath!
That's good.
What's this thing you're wearing?
A washing machine.
A washing machine!
You're wearing a washing machine here?
Do you always work out here?
Yes, we do.
We do.
Wow!
That's great!
Is that okay?
Is it okay if we don't go to our
respective places?
If you notice, everyone is already in
their respective places.
That's right.
That's probably how it'll be.
We're all connected.
That's right.
Can you go back to your respective
places, like the bathroom and the bath?
I thought it was really good.
Can you look this way?
Yes, yes.
One, two, three!
Ah, this is the next jacket.
This is the next jacket.
The next jacket is in Mayama's house.
The new song is in Mayama's house.
But you can't see Matsuno.
I was posing for him.
I can't see anyone.
You can't see Kobayashi either.
That's good.
And you can't see Yasumoto either.
This jacket is good.
I have to make this VR and move it.
I have to move it.
This is a wonderful room where you can
take jacket photos.
What is the rating?
How is it?
How is it for everyone other than
Mayama?
It's wonderful.
I want to live here.
Who wants to live here?
Yes!
Mayama is decided by majority vote.
I'm the one who's going to sign it.
Oh, really?
Is that so?
But, it's not just here.
What?
The recommended point of this property
is...
Let's go to the rooftop.
Rooftop?
This way.
Let's do it here.
I want to expect it.
What's on the rooftop?
This is the rooftop.
Everyone, please come in.
You can see the Sky Tree over there.
This is the rooftop temple.
If you make a reservation, you can use
it anytime.
It's a open-air bath for newcomers.
Mayama-san, are you in?
Yes, I am.
How is it?
It's spacious.
It's good.
I think everyone can go there.
Is it warm?
It looks like a bowl.
Shrimp bowl.
How is it?
You can see the Sky Tree.
It's so comfortable.
The night view is amazing.
It looks great.
The night view is really amazing.
It's bright.
We can see it while we are in the car.
You can see it while you are in the car.
You can see it.
We can see it.
Mayama-sama, it's time to make a
decision.
Thank you very much. This property.
I forgot to tell you something
important.
What is it?
How much is the rent of this property?
That's right.
It's not important.
The rent of this room is 68,000 yen.
It's a good deal.
It's very cheap.
10 minutes' walk from Minamisenju
Station.
This room is spacious and open.
This property is particular about its
design.
Will Mayama sign the contract or not?
Mayama, please sign this contract.
Will he?
I'm sorry guys
It was fun
Chui chui chui
I think it's too fashionable for me
It's not fashionable
It's too fashionable that I don't know
how to use it
And I'm worried about the toilet
But I think the first property of this
property has shown the seriousness of
Chuei Real Estate
I think it was fashionable
It's not a laugh
I'm serious and I'm getting good things
from Mayama
You're kind
Please understand that
It's unstable and scary
Let's go to the next property
The first episode
It was close, the first episode
It was close
The hurdle was high
I thought we were going to sign the
contract
But we thought about the show and
refused
It's the same, man
Tiger Oishi, Maya, Masa, Mon.
But I'll decide this one next.
The second property is this one.
It's a open kitchen with a very close
shop.
A mesonet.
All good conditions, right?
It's a very close shop, so there are
conditions of hope.
It's a shop with a lot of shops, and
it's a popular mesonet now.
By the way, where is this?
It's in Shimokitazawa.
It's a fashionable shop.
From old clothes to takoyaki, everything
is here.
And there is something that mayama-sama
will be happy about.
What is it?
After this, the retro name is Fubukken,
which is perfect for the conditions of
Mayama.
Good night!
The second room of Mayama is a mesonet
in the open kitchen.
There is something that Mayama is
impressed with.
They go to Shinokitazawa, where there is
a property.
Is this soon?
It's almost here.
Is that so?
You can see the property.
Can you see it?
Where is it?
There is a cat.
This is a good place.
You can see the property.
Where is it?
This is a good place.
Everyone, you are passing by.
You are passing by.
This is the property I will introduce
next.
This is the property.
Is this a room?
Yes.
Let's go inside.
Today is a holiday, so please enter
safely.
Today is a holiday, so it's a manual
door.
Today is a holiday, so please enter
slowly.
Thank you for your time.
This is a ramen shop.
This smells good.
This is good.
This is amazing.
This is a ramen shop that is completely
free.
This is the ramen that Mayama loved.
This is a room that suits Mayama who
lives 24 hours with ramen.
This is a ramen shop that Mayama loved.
Chie, do you sleep here?
Yes, I can sleep here.
But it's not a bed.
I thought so, so I prepared another
room.
I'm just going to sleep here.
Let's go to another room.
Welcome.
This property has a room in the back of
the shop.
What kind of room is it?
Is this a type of bed?
It's a type of bed.
How is it?
This is good.
I can sleep well.
On the second floor, there is a
Japanese-style living room with a
16-story building.
There is no such a big building in
Shimokitazawa.
I'm going to sleep here.
Let's go up to the second floor
Yes
Let's go
Excuse me
Yes
The bed is spacious
How is it, everyone?
Excuse me
It would be nice if we could come here
to play
We can eat together
Yes, we can
This is the living space
Yes, yes
I think it's very good
It's a Japanese style room
And this is the north-western side
So, when you go out of the store, you
can see the shopping street
I knew it
The north-western side has a shopping
street and a ramen restaurant
It's a must
Let's sleep once
There are many things
Yes
If you put a futon on it, it will be a
futon
Yes
It's good
If you put two futons on it, it will be
a waist-rest
It's good for the waist
96F jalonds
Good night!
It's like a paper in a pachinko shop
It's a room that's that calm
Do you know Mintei?
Hiroto from the show Kuromanions used to
work here
And Yutaka Matsushige who is famous for
his food
I didn't know that
Look at this, this is Yutaka Matsushige
He started from here
He said it's his signature but it's
actually a postcard
He used to live here
It's a postcard of his history
Hiroto from Blue Hearts
It's a postcard
Is it a postcard?
So he'll get his signature someday
Let's imagine what happens if the other
members come to play in this room
Then, it's time for the simulation
What if the members come to play in
Mayama's room?
Please come and play
Thank you for coming!
Wow, amazing
Then let's go over there
There's a menu of handmade food
Ramen!
Thank you very much
No, no, no, this is different
Gyoza?
Gyoza, Gyoza
This is not a back-cooking
It's a bean sprout rice
This is all object
Object?
It's fashionable
It's an object
It's amazing
It's a good combination
And this is a mezzanette
I wonder
It's amazing
It's fast
It's really fast
It's good, but Ms Hirota is using the
back side too
It's good
It's amazing
It's relaxing
If I can move this, I can practice
dancing
You can
But I think you can do it even if you
can't move it
You can
Let's practice dancing there
One, two, three, four
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven,
eight
Wait, wait, wait
Wait
It's shaking
The members are praising the expensive
object
What are the conditions of the body?
I asked the owner of this shop what the
conditions are
What are they?
If you shift in about three days a week,
it's OK
I'll do my best
You can live in a house
And during the day, you can work at your
favorite ramen shop
This is a great advantage for you
You can go to work because you have a
good job
But if you go to the next condition,
it's decided
Every Monday is a low-salary day, so you
can work in the shrimp business for
1,000 years
That's great
On the contrary, you can only work for
1,000 years a week
I agree
I'm curious about the rent
I'm curious about it
The rent?
With the deposit
It's 40,000 yen
That's a lot
5 minutes walk from Shimokitazawa
station
This is the dream property Mayama wanted
Will he sign the contract?
Mayama, do you want to sell this
property?
To be continued
Oshi...
Ma...
Sit!
No, no, no, I turned it into a real
estate company for real estate agents
all over the country.
But, after all, this ramen shop is a
ramen shop that I came to.
It's a ramen shop that I came to as a
customer, so it's a little bit of a
problem to live there.
No, it's no good.
It was delicious.
Well, it's a little bit too much of a
change.
The hurdle was too high.
I want you to live in Mayama.
Who wants to live in Mayama?
Who wants to live by yourself?
Next time, we'll look for Mayama's one-
man property.
Mayama is really moved.
I thought it was a contract at last.
What the hell is this?
And...
There's something there.
No way, a room share?
This program was brought to you by these
sponsors.