I'm sorry, I forgot to say it.
Who is it? I want to ask the person who
forgot to say it.
I'm sorry.
You think about us even though it's our
birthday.
I think about you.
Chii-chan, think about Chii-chan.
Chii-chan, I'm thinking about Chii-chan.
That's the way you talk.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Fans call me Professor Shirahama.
Why is that?
Professor Shirahama?
Yakan and Ainaru
One day, Yakan, who was sleeping in the
living room of the company, showed up.
His name is Yakan.
Yakan, who is interested in idols, will
make delicious tea for the people of
Stardust.
Please let me talk to the idols.
The people of Stardust who are kind and
like tea are OK.
Yakan, who was born in the living room
of the company, was born.
The program that talks to cute idols was
born.
Please watch again.
I'm Yaka, the cute child of STARDUST
born in VIVA HOME.
Let's call today's guest.
This idol.
I'm BOLT's Shirahama Ayano. Nice to meet
you.
Nice to meet you.
I'm BOLT's Aoyama-san. I'm the youngest
on STARDUST PLANET.
Is it okay now?
I'm the one who entered the shrimp.
How old are you?
I'm 14 years old.
14 years old.
You are still in middle school.
I'm sleepy in the morning, but I listen
to music.
You are popular.
I may be popular.
Do you have a favorite class?
I used to study math in high school.
I studied a lot during the test period.
I like science.
I like experiments.
When I have time, I like science.
Many people say that STARDUST students
are good at studying.
Shirahama seems to be able to do it.
If it's only science, please leave it to
me.
Fans call you Professor Shirahama.
Why is that?
When I was in elementary school, I was
into slime videos.
Slime.
I liked to listen to ASMR videos.
I was talking about making slime with
BOLT.
My fans called me Professor Shirahama.
At first, I was told that I wasn't a
professor.
Many fans call me Professor Shirahama.
When I was in the sixth grade, I was
called Professor Shirahama.
You can make slime?
I can make slime.
How do you make it?
First, put sugar in the bowl.
What is the essence of slime?
I put washing glue.
Washing glue.
Washing glue that is sticky to harden.
I also put iron.
Do you also put iron?
I forgot.
I put iron to color.
It's a display.
You are a world-class professor.
I was into making slime.
I'm looking forward to it.
Please make slime with Ryuichi Sakamoto
and Shirahama.
Thank you.
I want to show everyone my editing
skills.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I sent this video by the offer of Kaeru-
chan, Maki-san, and Chabu-san.
Thank you very much.