I guess Ebichu's tour is coming to an
end soon
The tour should be going well
Let's do a father quiz
Please open your clothes
Here it is
It doesn't look like you
It looks cooler
Father quiz, the first question
Mayama's father's favorite food is
sashimi and sake
What is his favorite food and what did
he fry?
Scallop
I think he fried it with butter and soy
sauce
Does he cook?
Yes, he does. My dad and my dad cook on
Sundays
The answer is scallop with scallop
Wow, that's correct
What's your dad's favorite food?
I like pork belly, so my dad cooks it
for me
That's good
My dad cooks meat
Why is your dad your dad?
It's on TV
If a 20 year old girl says her dad,
she'll think she's not a good daughter
I'm not a good daughter
Please cut this part
If your father was a member of Ebichu,
what would you do?
Why?
My mom doesn't do that
I don't know, but my dad is a Kyushu boy
So, I have a lot of blood type
Of course, the correct answer is
Gourmet report
I do that a lot at home
You do?
I want to hear
Today I made Mapo tofu
How do you eat it?
It's like, yes
Yes
Eat it and say something
It's spicy
You're close
Say something to your dad
Thank you
Say it properly
You say thank you a lot at home
Dad, thank you
Thank you
Thank you for watching!
Hello.
Are you confident, Hoshina-san?
I don't know. I don't know what I'm
thinking.
Hoshina-san's drawing of her father,
open.
Oh, it's similar.
The first question of the father quiz.
What do you want Mirei-chan to fix?
The second place is,
By the way, the first place is,
forgetting her cell phone at home or in
the car,
and she is busy.
The third place is,
It takes time to decide on clothes, and
she has to change at least three times.
What?
That much?
Three times?
I really can't go out on a really bad
day.
If I go out on a really bad day,
it's a really bad day.
No tension.
Sleep once.
Bao!
I want to take a bath, but it's a hassle
to take a bath.
But if I don't take a bath, I don't want
to sleep.
So I sleep once and wake up again.
That's amazing.
I asked Hoshina's father.
I asked him what he liked to eat.
He said he liked to eat with his family.
I got it!
I'm sure it is.
Ta-da!
Yakiniku!
He said anything was fine.
He made me feel like eating Yakiniku.
It's cute.
I thought it would be fun to eat meat
with my family.
It's a long-legged.
It's cute.
The answer is this.
I did it!
The unforgettable thing that Hoshina's
father said to his daughter was
When he talked about his high school
graduation
He said he wanted to go to university
for his future activities
My father thinks about it
I think so too
I always bother him
Hoshina got 20 points!
Hello!
Next is Rina!
Are you confident?
I'm so scared! I'm going to write
something weird!
The father that Matsuno-san drew
It's similar!
I drew this face as a man
That's right!
So, the first question of the father
quiz!
What is Matsuno-san's father's favorite
food?
I know this!
Wait, there are two similar answers
Is this a hint?
If you say it's similar, you'll know!
Tomato
Cute!
It's pasta
What is that?
What is your father's favorite food?
I like enoki mushrooms
So fashionable!
What does Matsuno-san's father always do
when he drinks?
He sleeps right away and gets a little
upset
I don't get it at all
He sleeps on the floor until morning
Oh, that's it
By the way, is there anything you want
your father to fix?
There's a lot of things, right?
He's like, what?
He does that all the time
That's cute
At first, he says, you did it, right?
I know he says that
But it's too much
I'm tired of it
I say
I want my dad to take care of me
What do you want your daughter to fix?
There are many things
By the way, what do you like about your
daughter?
She is honest and pure
She is strong
You are watching her well
I sometimes think I should fix my
daughter
She is in a bad mood
I want to fix that
I want to fix my dad's mood
I think you are similar to your dad
She is similar to my daughter
She gives me advice when I'm in trouble
She is very helpful
Thank you for watching
Ebi-chu!
The last one is Kashiwagi-san
Let's start with Kashiwagi-san's father
Sorry, my hair got longer
Oh my god, you don't look like Obama-san
Let's start the question
What is Kashiwagi-san's father's
favorite food?
I don't know
White rice
You are Japanese
By the way,
It's amazing
What do you like?
The answer is
It's difficult
Steamed pork
What is steamed pork?
It's steamed pork, right?
Have you ever eaten it?
Let's go home and ask
Let's go home and ask your father
Steamed pork?
Let's move on to the next question
I asked Kashiwagi's father
If you could bring one thing to a
deserted island, what would you bring?
What would I bring?
This is amazing
If it's a deserted island, there's
definitely nothing
What?
Then, open
Mother
Oh, by the way, why?
I can't do anything without my mother
Is that so?
What's the answer?
Correct
And, listen, it's not a mother
I want to love
What is that?
It's realistic
It's going to be something
I've never heard the word I want to love
before
I've never heard it before
I receive e-mails and LINE messages on
my birthday every year
I'm always moved by the content
I don't say the content of the past
Thank you for always playing with me so
that we can have fun
Let's play with your mother together
from now on
I'm not sure.
The winner is Mirue Hoshiguma.
Enjoy your meal.
Thank you for watching.