I want to be an idol who can cheer up by
showing the changing appearance to
everyone.
I came to Izu, which I wanted to visit.
Izu! Izu! Izu!
Where can I touch it?
There are also other animals such as
pig-toothed hippo and super-looper.
Hello.
This is a pet store, but it is a pet
store specializing in reptiles.
Do you like reptiles?
I love them.
I hope you can experience various things
and enjoy them.
Good luck.
Thank you.
Do you know what it is?
There are many small ones.
This is a water tank that contains
reptiles from Madagascar.
It's called a koshagame.
It's a herbivore and loves vegetables.
It's made of Komatsuna, apples, and
carrots.
I was lost in a turtle for an hour when
I was a kid.
I remember that.
I've loved animals since I was a kid.
I've loved them since I was a kid.
I used to play in the corner,
and I used to see bugs or grasshoppers
in the corner.
I was more interested in nature.
I took a water drop near me,
and I showed it to my friend's guardian.
She was surprised.
She was like,
water!
When I was in elementary school,
the people around me
gradually became adults.
I became an adult too.
I couldn't say I liked insects because
everyone was scared of them.
I had no friends.
I didn't have any friends after I became
a child.
I didn't have any friends who could
speak a little.
I didn't have any friends after I became
a child.
I finally had friends after I became a
child.
Everyone...
I'm a girl, so I don't play with bugs or
mud balls.
I think that's why I gradually locked
myself in.
I was the type to get along with others
and care about them.
I wonder if the words at that time were
okay.
I was worried about it later.
Do you know what this is?
URUBER RUBER
It's a catchy name.
It's a Mexican salamander.
It's not a standard salamander.
This is a female salamander.
It's running away.
Sorry.
Cute.
It's slimy.
It's cute.
Please hold it gently.
Please hold it with your arms.
I'll let go.
Wow.
It's heavy.
It's quite heavy.
Isn't it heavy?
It's heavy.
My nose is running.
It's cute.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I'm going to pick a bunch of vegetables.
I was about to give up on studying.
I was like, I don't care.
I gave up on studying.
I'm not good at memorizing, and I'm slow
at understanding.
I had to work hard to become the best
person, so I was running away from it.
I thought that the world where idols
live was different, so I had no idea
that I would be an idol.
I just thought that I was a fan of
idols.
I didn't want to be an idol when I was
auditioning.
I thought I'd accept it because it was
there.
So I accepted it lightly.
I'm not good at taking pictures, so I
thought I wouldn't pass.
When I forgot, I got a call from the
agency.
I was surprised.
I'm Kishihonoka, 17 years old, from
Tokyo.
Nice to meet you.
I love frogs.
I started to change frogs in this
audition period.
This is the frog.
This frog is named Hina-chan,
named after Hinata-san of Hinata-zaka46.
Hina-chan lives for 10 years.
If you take care of it, it will live for
20 years.
I want to be loved by everyone for 10 or
20 years with Hina-chan.
Where did you buy the frog?
I bought it yesterday.
Oh, you bought it at the store.
Oh, I see. I'm sorry.
This is Hina-chan.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I think I can jump.
No!
I couldn't.
Hina wants to jump.
I don't have any special skills.
I didn't have anything to do.
I thought I'd do what I like.
When I thought about what I like,
I made up my mind with this frog.
I said it.
The last scene.
The judges didn't react well.
I was trying to make them laugh.
I thought I was going to fail.
When I heard my name, I said,
I said,
Number 5, Onoka Kishi.
I was confused whether I was really
called or not.
I was really called.
I'm not good at singing and dancing.
I'm slow at remembering things.
I'm not good at remembering things.
I think I'm bothering everyone.
I'm worried that I might pull my leg.
I've been practicing all the time.
I'm not good at it, but I think I can do
it.
I'll practice more than anyone else.
If I do my best, I think I can catch up
with other people.
I'm still practicing a lot.
I think I have a chance to show it, so
I'm preparing for it.
TEPCO is a Japan entertainment company
affiliated with SOGO ABIL boots and
Aunquebu in Hokkaido.
Please look forward to a performance
video at TEPCO!
I found it!
Is it a thick-toed beaked shadow?
Yes, I know.
I like this one the most.
He is very detailed.
He is popular as a pet.
He is a thick-toed beaked shadow.
Thank you for watching.
Usually, you can't see the name of the
shop by looking at this.
I'll put it on the table and walk over
there.
It's amazing that you can touch it.
Wow, amazing!
I'll put it on my face.
This is tarantula.
It's rare to see this.
Amazing.
I'll wrap it around your body.
I'll do it.
It's heavy.
It's calm.
Oh, it's cute.
It's 12kg now.
It can't move.
Thank you.
I got it.
It's cute.
Thank you for watching.
I think I've never found what I wanted
to do, and I've never had a goal in my
life.
I think I'm the one who gave me hope.
I think I'm the one who found the
meaning of life.
I think I'm the one who gave me hope.
God gave me the strength to live a good
life.
I want to be an idol who can show
everyone how I change,
even if I'm not good at anything.
I want to be an idol who gives me
courage and makes me want to do my best.
I'm 18 years old from Tokyo, Kishi
Honoka.