The title of the night!
Fujitani, do you have any announcements?
Yes, I do.
Please!
On November 11, the second mini album,
Igino ni Meja Debu, will be released!
It has nothing to do with the release
date, but it will be released on the day
of the Pocky.
I'm sorry.
I'm not going to tell you.
But it's on the day of the Pocky.
That's good.
I said it in the opening, but on
November 23, Wednesday,
Nakano Sample the Hall and on December
24, Saturday,
I don't care what it is,
I'm sorry.
The Sample the Hall will have the
biggest and most important live
performance.
Thank you.
I hope you can come to the concert with
your night view.
Please!
I'm so happy.
I don't think I can bring it to the
venue.
That's it.
Is there anything else you want to say?
No.
No?
Thank you.
I feel like I'm going to die.
I've been touched by you in the talk.
I've warmed up.
Can I have some tea at the end?
I'm happy.
Is it okay if I drink it?
It's okay.
I prepared hot tea.
Is it okay?
It's okay.
This is the cutest shot.
I don't want to drink it.
I'm putting on a mosaic.
It's okay.
I'm going.
I went to see it.
It's delicious.
I'm glad you're smiling.
You're a little shy, but you're the one
who's going to decide the face at the
end.
I'm surprised everyone's drinking tea.
Thank you.
Can I have you close your eyes to the
camera?
Yes.
Thank you for watching my strange
program.
If you like this video, please give it a
high rating and subscribe to the
channel.
Goodbye.
I'm going to drink tea.
I'm looking forward to playing games.
I throw it.
I'm not bad at games.
I'm not good at games.
I forgot to aim.
I was.