The first performance of the second half
Hello, I'm Yuno Sakura, a junior high
school 3rd year in junior high school.
Nice to meet you.
I wanted to make everyone smile like
F-13, so I came here.
Thank you.
Good morning. I'm Yuno Kamae, a third-
year junior high school student.
I've been interested in BGM since I was
a kid.
I've been thinking about becoming a
13-year-old by participating in this
audition.
I've been thinking about becoming a
13-year-old by participating in this
audition.
I'm not kidding.
No way.
Yes, it's a hard encounter.
I can't see the end.
I'm afraid of the rain.
I'm afraid of the shadow.
Yes, it's a future boundary.
I can't see the end.
I can't hear the sound of the guitar.
After the audition, the new members,
Sakura Iema and Nakamura Ina, are
challenged in a 10-person formation.
I'm looking forward to the scene where
Emma and Yuna are following me.
I'm going to do a lot of directing after
this, but I'm looking forward to it
because they are doing it so well that I
can respond to it.
I think it's amazing that I've been
doing the same thing as Kaoriko for the
past two months.
The preparation period is very short.
Thinking about it, it's really fast to
learn the choreography.
I think it's fast to learn the
formation.
I'm afraid I'll be late.
We're in trouble, too.
The two are approaching the live
performance.
The reason is...
I'm still worried about the lessons.
I've been told by the members to
practice.
I'm still worried, but I'm looking
forward to it.
It's been two months since I made my
debut on October 1st.
It was a flash.
I've been practicing, and I've got
results.
I want to make the live performance a
good one.
I think Yuna is the one who gets the
most stimulation.
I can't lose to her. I should work
harder.
I'm glad I could join her.
I don't think I could do this much if I
was alone.
I could do it because Emma was there.
They are encouraging each other.
They have been working hard for two
months.
What was the motivation for their hard
work?
Thanks to Yuma and Yuna, I can grow up
with them.
I can make my seniors stronger.
I can think more about Ebichu.
We are able to do many things because we
have each other.
I'm excited and nervous.
I want to make it a stage where people
can cheer for me.
Ema and Yuna are very serious during the
lessons.
They learn very quickly.
I can tell that they practice in various
places.
I have to do my best because I'm afraid
I'll be overtaken.
I'll do my best to give you a live
performance that you'll be looking
forward to.
I'm doing my best.
I went to ask the members of the girls'
group what was going on.
I think it's really amazing.
I want to have as many people as
possible who will support me.
I think it's a good thing.
And these two, who have also experienced
Tenryu Live, have made a new decision.
Even if I go to lessons now, they are
two people who work very hard, so I hope
they can keep up the good work together.
Last year, I was very worried about what
would happen to my first junior.
Now that I've overcome it, I don't have
that anxiety anymore, and I'm looking
forward to it.
Nice to meet you.
I have two members.
I'm really worried about it.
But I can't stop.
I think I have to make this decision
right.
I'll do my best to make you look forward
to my live performance.
I want you to take care of me.
Mayama, Yasumoto, and Hoshina are
looking forward to the new system.
I've been going back and forth between
schools.
No matter how much people change,
if the subject of Ebichu doesn't change,
I feel that there is a private Ebichu
school there.
I think it will be the second day that
you can feel it.
I would be happy if you could say,
Happy New Year, Ebichu!
Anyway, I will do my best!
Many fans and people say that
Ebichu Pride is the same as the past.
But I think it's a little different from
that time.
Various situations have changed since
then.
I have grown up more than I did at that
time.
I'm confident.
I want to support them who are anxious.
I want the members to feel that live is
fun.
I want the fans to think that the new
Ebichu is fun.
I want to tell them that I'm having the
most fun.
No matter what the era changes, the
spirit of Ebichu is still the same.
That's what we want to tell our fans.
I think that by doing this, we can make
our fans feel at ease.
I think we have to do our best to do
that.
Our first stage is at a big venue for
the interview.
I think it would be great if we could
make the audience feel that the scenery
was fun and beautiful.
I hope everyone will enjoy the stage and
I hope we can go together.
The anxiety of Japanese high school
students
Of course, she has been watching over
the graduating Kashiwagi for a long
time.
I think the pressure is big.
I'm out, and the two of them are in, and
this is the first time they've been on
stage.
Trying to imitate someone.
I don't think about that.
I want to show the best of me, like Yuna
and Ema.
I want them to enjoy the stage.
I want to show them the best of me.
In the middle of a lost road,
in the light I was searching for
I struggled because I couldn't draw my
shining self yet
If I had noticed the strength in my
weakness now
I'm sure I have the future in my hands
I won't hesitate anymore, I'll be free
I'll swim through the sky
We can become stronger like the birds
One by one, we are boys
To the new days where the sky and the
stars meet
The story now begins
Finally, a message from Kashiwagi and
the two new members
Um...
I want to enjoy the last graduation live
with all my heart and love for 12 years
If you come to the site and watch it on
the live broadcast,
I hope you can enjoy it together and
laugh and cry
I will practice hard until the end
I want to show my gratitude to the
people who have supported me since the
audition
I will show you the performance of the
first live performance on December 17th
I will do my best to show you a
performance that will make you want to
support me
I will do my best to show you the best
live performance