But why haven't you changed?
It's been a while since I felt like
this.
Don't we all seem the same?
There were so many things going on in
2017.
You know?
Yes, you do.
You watched everything.
You watched with a smile.
You know.
Look, this band, this band, and this
band are all in the same place.
Wow, if you do it, it's 100%.
One, two, three, four.
I'm not going to tell you, I'm going to
tell you.
I'm going to tell you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Bye bye.
It's been a while since I danced like
this.
I had fun.
I had a lot of thoughts about the songs.
I had a hard time at times.
I hope I can put those thoughts on this
tour.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye!
See you tomorrow!
※The
instrumental version was composed by
※the
children's song
Leaving the time that I lived between,
Thank you for watching!
I'm going to say something that's idol-
like.
The goal is to make everyone happy.
But it's really true.
I've been doing this for a few months.
I have a feeling that I was doing a live
performance.
I was wondering what singing and dancing
were.
But I had to do it anyway.
The rehearsal was a bit of a hassle.
I forgot that I was going to enjoy it.
I want to have fun tonight.
The goal of the tour is to be an idol.
I want to be an idol.
The goal of the tour is not to talk too
much.
I talk a lot when I'm not doing
anything.
I haven't told the members yet.
I'm going to talk about this only.
This is the last episode.
I have a lot to say.
It's the last episode, and it's the last
spring tour.
I'm sure some of the staff and I will
understand how I feel.
I haven't told the staff and the
principal yet.
I'm sure the members will be confused by
the spring tour.
I want to enjoy the whole thing.
I want to enjoy being an idol.
I want to be an idol.
I want to be an idol for the first year.
I'm counting down 250 days.
I'm talking to you now.
I've been thinking about it all the
time.
I've always had that kind of feeling.
So...
But, the Ebitú will continue.
I think there will be more changes in
the future.
So, I want to leave the fact that I was
there.
I want to leave it in the remaining
period.
That's my only last wish.
I want to keep up the momentum of spring
tour.
I want to improve myself.
So, I think that...
Recently, I've been watching and
doing...
I think that Geneporo's spring tour is
not coming.
It's not coming.
I feel different.
I'm doing it one by one.
I'm far away from the people I see.
I want to talk about the reasons when I
get closer.
I want to talk about the after-sales.
This is after my birthday.
I've been thinking about it since after
my birthday.
There are many things.
There are many things. Like commercials.
I think it's good to do it early.
I want to tell you about it.
Some staff members know it.
That's it.
I like songs.
I like the songs that everyone knows.
I told the teacher when I was recording
the record of Haruno Arashi.
Haruno Arashi is particularly memorable.
The lyrics are different.
It's a song made in a completely
different meaning.
The song is very unique.
It's a song that I remember.
I like it because I feel like I'm doing
it.
I want to do my best because it's a big
song for me.
I was a little frustrated because I
didn't know anything about the sound of
Iyami.
I'll do my best next time.
I have a lot of thoughts.
I want to make my dream come true.
That's why I think this year will be a
very difficult year, but I really think
that everything is the best, so I want
to do my best.
I think everyone is the same as the
family, everything point.
So I think I know.
I thought I'd go to the consultation
after my birth, but I was a little late
because there were various things.
But when I was making the album, there
were various things, and I was asked to
consult when I was here.
Then I was like, is that how it feels? I
felt like it was okay.
I think that's what happens in Ebichu,
but everyone is here to make dreams come
true.
So I'm also very clear about what I want
to do, so there are parts where it gets
bigger.
But I want to do my best in Ebichu until
I can do it, and more than ever.
As an idol, I want to leave a part that
I want to leave firmly, so I think it
will last forever.
I was wondering how to do my best in my
heart, but I decided to do it myself.
I have a lot of things that I'm hot
inside, so I'm having fun from the
rehearsal.
So I want to run through it.
It's a pretty big tour. It's the biggest
tour so far.
It's Ebichu, too. I don't know how
everyone feels about it.
But I want to make it a fun place, and I
believe that the people who come here
need me.
I want to have fun. I want to do my
best.
I think that's the angle I want to go
from.
When I look at the everything point, I
feel like I'm in a different place.
I think so. I think I'm in a good place
from the timing of the concert in March.
I think I'm in a good place from there,
so I feel like I'm in a good place.
I've been doing this for seven years,
and it hasn't changed.
I think it will not change in the next
10 years or so.
I feel like I can't change anything.
So I went and listened to it.
And Ebichu himself, I'm probably gone.
Maybe it's different.
I think a lot of things will happen.
I don't know.
But I think it will be fun.
Everyone is in a difficult time.
Ebichu is the biggest thing in life.
But if you overcome it,
I think it will change as a group.
I think it's a time to change.
I want to enjoy that moment.
Please show some love to S Elise gonna
sing.
Thank you for watching!
I'm sorry, I'm totally fine.
Aika was wearing a skirt and she didn't
stand up.
I refused to stand up.
I made it mine.
I'm fine.
Thank you for watching.
It was close.
I did it once, but I was like,
Is this okay?
I was lost.
But the direction is really good.
I think this is better.
So,
I was so surprised.
Thank you.
I have to continue the next one.
I'm so glad.
The next one is
very good.
Thank you.
I'm so glad.
From now on, Nakayama-san will be on the
radio,
and I'm sure those who have listened to
the MPS episode of Ebichu No Ya will
understand,
but it's a project where we'll be
accepting requests from the members at
the final meeting,
and we'll be doing it at the Ebichu
live.
Nakayama-san's opinion has been passed
on today,
and we're going to make time to get
excited.
We're going to practice, Hajimata.
How was it?
It was my first time being accepted.
I was able to meditate well, so I'll do
one jump.
So you'll do one jump and one jump at
the same time?
I'll do one jump.
And if there's not enough time, I'll do
it alone.
But you'll be taking time for that.
I'll be taking time to meditate and
changing clothes,
so I'll be making time to get excited
like that,
and I'll be doing it today at the
request of Nakayama-san.
Ready, set, go!
No, no.
Sensei.
Let's do the jump.
One jump.
It's not one jump.
It's okay.
Is this really okay?
It's easy to get up.
It's fun, Riku-chan.
I'll praise the coach.
Jump.
Nakayama-san! Nakayama-san!
Why did you come in?
It's not close.
It's not that close.
Look.
What is this?
I failed.
Nakayama, you have to take three more.
I'm sorry.
Is it good?
It's very close.
Look at your face.
It's not that.
It's OK.
One more.
I'll get closer.
I failed.
It's OK.
It should be good.
Look.
It's OK.
It's not good to be close.
I'm sorry.
Mayama, please call me.
I want to ask you again if I fail.
I'm angry.
It's very close.
Thank you.
It's not good.
This is not good.
Is this a bot?
This is a bot of Tony.
Please call me again.
The film is gone.
Wait a minute.
I'll take care of it.
Thank you very much.
It's gone.
Mayama failed again.
The film is gone.
Will we be able to get it right?
I've been ready.
This is?
Yes.
Is this what it is?
No.
Your face is much better.
I'm sorry.
Do it together.
In front of everyone.
Do it on stage.
I'm getting tired.
They said it's okay to do it later.
Yasumoto is in a good mood.
I did it, and everyone stopped.
I did it.
Everyone is tired.
I'm getting tired.
What is this?
Let's just get out of here.
Please do one more.
The tone exercise is...
Ah.
Thank you for watching!
U-H-O
Let's do the jump.
Let's do it three times.
Three times? Today three times?
Ready, set, go!
One, two, three!
It's a bit shaky.
Is it okay?
It's okay.
Not enough.
Five people are not enough.
In the same way...
Nakayama-san, you go first.
Jump as much as you like.
This is okay, Nakayama-san.
It's not enough.
I feel like I'm getting excited.
I feel good.
Nakayama-san, you go first.
I'll show you the intro, lucky!
Did you get it?
I'll show you.
This is the lucky one.
Lucky!
Cute!
please check FB live too!
What's wrong with you?
Who is it?
I've never seen it!
Hello, everyone in the audience!
Hello!
Who is it?
It's a hat for the weekday!
What is this blue atmosphere?
I am the special guest of this special
corner in Nagoya, Isanji.
Everyone, please take care of me!
Please take care of me!
I don't know.
You don't know what the corner is, do
you?
I don't know.
Let's start right away.
We will send this to the members of
Ebichu.
Ebichu Ultra Quiz for Aichi people!
What is this?
I will explain the rules.
Before asking questions, the quiz will
be decided by the audience.
The quiz will be decided by the
audience.
Please be careful.
The person who gets the most correct
answer will get more lunch at Hiroshima
Park tomorrow.
No way!
It's okay.
You can get more lunch.
I will do my best!
Let's start the first question.
This is the first question.
Where is the most silver-plated
prefecture in Japan?
Aichi!
The second question.
Where is the most silver-plated
prefecture in Japan?
Aichi!
This is the correct answer.
No way!
Is it Mayama?
Is it the correct answer?
What is this?
Is it silver-plated?
I don't know.
If this is the correct answer, isn't it
Aichi?
Yes, it is correct.
Really?
I see.
Next is the second question.
This is the correct answer.
Koike Yuriko is the Governor of Tokyo.
Where is Oumura Hideyaki the Governor of
Tokyo?
Koike Yuriko is the Governor of Tokyo.
Where is Oumura Hideyaki the Governor of
Tokyo?
This is also a mission.
Hiroto, please answer this question.
Aichi!
The correct answer.
I feel a little...
The third question.
This is also a mission.
What is the first international white-
and-white event in Aichi Prefecture in
2005?
What is the first international white-
and-white event in Aichi Prefecture in
2005?
Hoshina, please answer this question.
Aichi white-and-white!
Correct!
Next is Kyoshusei.
Question 4.
The night festival is famous for the
music festival, but what is the summer
festival that started in 2013?
Fabia!
Correct.
The last question.
The place where the festival will be
held this year is...
Aichi Prefecture!
Everyone, please answer this question.
Let's go.
Please answer.
Aichi Prefecture!
Correct!
So, the family party that was held only
in Yamagashi and Niihata is finally
coming to Aichi Prefecture, west of
Tokyo!
On August 26, 2017, Aichi Prefecture's
Aichi Chikyu-haku Memorial Park will be
held.
We are waiting for you.
This summer, we will make Aichi
Prefecture the hottest summer ever!
It feels different every day.
It's fun to watch us.
The reaction of the new fans is always
different, so it's fun to watch.
It was a party.
I was surprised.
Something flew.
You can't fly.
A pen light flew from the party.
You held it with your hands?
Yes.
A pen light flew from the party.
No!
You can't throw a pen light at the
party.
I did it like a traffic light.
I threw a pen light at the party.
A pen light flew on the stage.
It's a bit tough.
I said it, but...
It's tough, but...
My body is a bit dull,
but if I can overcome that, I'm sure
I'll be fine.
We're the second time, but most of the
people who come here are new.
So we're trying our best.
I'm taking the bone of my shoulder.
The angle is good.
It's too stiff.
It's a nice andthy mess.
We've been here before.
Jump!
1 2 3
Let's go alright, everyone!
TheseLevel B negative fields
You can lead, here
Thank you for watching.
Wake up! Wake up!
Are you okay?
I'm fine. I'm fine.
Hmmm...
Oh haha sciences
Roger
Yes yes yes yes
Please do not miss the live broadcast.
There are many people on the bike.
Oh, many people are riding on the bike.
It's a
lob jar, isn't it?
Eh? It's a fish! A strawberry!
Is this heaven?
Delicious!
Amazing, right?
I'm going to eat a lot today.
It's Naka's turn.
Open your mouth wide.
Jump! Jump! Jump!
Don't you have to do a big one?
A big one?
Sorry, it's Naka's turn.
Please follow Kayama-san.
What's this?
It's like a robot.
That's Pirate più Hua Noi.
Here we are.
I'm sorry!
We have a lot of thoughts for this tour.
We have a lot of thoughts, but we are
the people who perform on stage.
We don't want to make the audience feel
uncomfortable.
But we have a lot of customers.
We are happy to have a lot of customers.
This is the first time I've ever done
this.
How do you write the first letter?
On top of the letter, there is Riku.
On the left side, there is Steve.
On the top?
Yes.
It's different.
What should I do?
Can I write one more?
Like this?
One more on top.
It's coming out.
Like this.
Yes, like this.
It's okay.
Is it okay?
There is a new one.
Yes.
I wrote it again.
I'm sorry.
I'll give this to the first-time
audience.
Even if my voice fades away
I give up
Because you were doing it
Yes, because I was doing it
That's right
Ready, go
The mouth is big, big
Ah
E
U
O
Okay, jump
E
U
Ready, go
Bum bum bum bum bum
Jump, jump
Jump
Big jump
Big jump, then three times
Ready, go
E
O
Three
E
In the end, it's a Amiaki-nus.
It smells good.
Thank you.
Which one do you like?
I like the one with the vegetables and
the one with the meat.
I like the one with the meat.
Which one is more?
The one with the meat?
The one with the meat is over here.
I'll bring it.
Thank you for your hard work.
Who said it?
I feel like I'm going to fall down if I
put the fruit on my side.
I fell down.
Oh, the tissue.
It's okay.
There's a tissue.
This is a tissue for the car.
It's a tissue for the car.
That's right.
This is it.
I'm sure you'll bring something.
It's not cute.
It's like a one-piece.
What?
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
There's a natto and egg.
I want to put it on the noodles.
I'm sorry.
Ban Ban Ji.
Ban Ban Ji and
What's this?
Ban Ban Ji.
Ban Ban Ji with all your might.
Isn't Ban Ban Ji pretty hot?
All Ban Ban Ji are popular.
Ban Ban Ban Ban Ban Ji.
Ban Ban Ji.
What?
I don't know yet.
It's probably a cake.
It's probably a bean sprouts.
Maybe it's good.
Ban Ban Ban Ban Ban Ban Ban Ban.
Ban Ban Ban Ban Ban Ban Ban.
It's probably a cake.
Ban Ban Ban Ban Ban Ban Ban Ji.
It's going to be great.
Ban Ban Ji is delicious.
Let's see the other one.
Let's see.
Mochi?
It looks delicious.
Mochi!
Is it a rice cake?
It's a rice cake.
It's different.
Please do it.
Mochi!
It's new.
Ready, set, go!
Open your mouth wide.
Ah!
E!
U!
O!
How many times?
This time!
Jump!
Make it reach.
How many times?
Four times.
Last time, big jump.
I know the answer.
Do it as usual.
OK?
Here?
I can see it well.
How?
To the far sea.
I can see the ocean.
A bear is swimming.
I came to Okinawa last year.
I came.
And there.
It's dangerous.
I'll do my best.
Recently, I thought that
There are many chase movies, drama and
manga.
place of Where, bear a bear full of
time.
I àgainst!!
Do not you get special什么能力?
Now, let's hear the members' passionate
voices.
What?
Chiaos!
K-Kuchimi!
What are you going to do, Chiaos?
Run, run!
Goodbye, Tessa!
Please don't die!
N-No way...
You...
Stop it!
Chiaos!
Dadosaaaaaaan
If we can't find it we can't check it
anyway, anyway, anyway
Hell!
It's not like the oil-based eggplant.
Delicious!
Spicy!
The eggplant is delicious.
The eggplant is refreshing.
It's delicious.
Thank you for your viewing.
Good!
Thank you for watching!
Everyone's so excited.
It's dangerous.
Everyone's getting nervous.
But it's okay.
It's okay.
Let's give it our all.
Today is...
Super Final!
We are H.U.K.!
Let's go, Debut!
Super Final!
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Good job!
Since that day, I've been making
memories with Matsuno.
When I'm really lonely, I sometimes
dream of Matsuno.
Everyone said they'd come out of their
dreams.
In my dreams, I've never had a
conversation with Matsuno.
But the other day, I was finally able to
talk to him for the first time.
The dream was that Rina would come back
to this world for a day.
Rina and the other members walked to my
house.
At first, Matsuno was walking on the
street.
But he came to my house and talked to
me.
It was my first time in my dream, so I
was very happy.
But it's been a long time, so I was very
embarrassed.
But I was really happy.
We all calmed down and decided to eat
together.
But Matsuno said he wanted to eat with
his parents because he had only one day.
He said he'd come back once.
We all waited for him to come back and
we'd meet up after dinner.
But for some reason, after dinner, my
gum stuck on my teeth.
I can't take my gum off.
I've been taking it off so many times,
but I can't take it off.
I couldn't go to the meeting place, and
my eyes were rusted.
I don't know why.
It was a very strange story.
I was happy to talk to you after a long
time.
Even though it's only a day, I'm glad to
see you.
It's a dream, but I'm glad to see you.
As I said earlier, we all met Matsuno in
a dream.
Matsuno is a very important person to
us.
We are friends, but we are also
important.
I felt it again when I saw that dream.
We love Matsuno, but we also love our
family.
On the day I said goodbye to Rina,
Rina's father said,
Rina, thank you for being born in our
place.
I was very impressed.
I thought he really loved me.
I thought that if I grew up with so much
love,
I would feel love and grow up.
I was proud of Matsuno.
I was very happy.
I'm really happy.
I'm so happy to see the mother who gave
birth to Rina,
and the father who raised her.
Thank you for letting me meet such a
beautiful woman.
Thank you for supporting me and Lina in
my private school.
And I was really happy to sing and dance
with Lina.
What should I say?
I was really happy.
I still talk about Lina with the
members.
I think it's the most fun moment when we
talk about Lina.
I think she is a great person.
She is not easy to be a hero.
She is a superhero for us.
She always helps us when we are in
trouble.
I am really grateful to Lina and to my
parents.
I want to tell Lina to many people.
I want to tell Lina's existence to many
people.
I hope we can be a group that can make
people smile.
Thank you for watching.
Oh, two days before the fan meeting.
You must have been shocked.
Were you shocked?
You must be kidding.
I can't fool you.
You were so surprised.
You looked so lonely.
Scary.
Scary? Is that scary?
What?
Well, then...
I, Hirota Yuka, will be performing on
January 3rd, 2018.
The thing I decided the most was
actually around March,
but there were a lot of things about the
spring tour,
and there were things I had to think
about before that,
and I was able to do them today.
The thing I thought the most was that
I've lived for 18 years, and there are
so many things I want to do.
And I've become 18 years old,
and I've been able to do things I wanted
to do,
and I've done things I've never done
before,
and I've done many things that made me
happy.
But when I was in the assistant staff,
there were things I didn't get to
experience,
and I had a lot of things I wanted to
try,
even when I was in my teens.
And I decided to do things that I wanted
to do
I wanted to be able to share my story
with my uncle.
I said I wanted to quit right away when
I first joined Ebichu.
I'm really bad at groups with a lot of
girls.
I really hated groups when I was a
student.
I thought I was bad at Ebichu.
I was surprised that I was able to join
Ebichu after 8 years because of
everyone.
I didn't think I would quit right away.
But I was able to do many things with
everyone.
I was able to do many things with
I really like it and I'm scared.
Thank you for watching.
I thought it was more about Ebichu than
about my dream.
I've been running all the way here.
I've found something I want to see more.
I think there are some people who think
they're in Ebichu all the time.
I thought I had to make my dream come
true.
I thought I had to get out of it
someday.
I don't know if I was right here.
I thought I didn't want to regret my
life when I thought about it.
So I decided to run here.
It's about six months left.
I have a year's preparation.
I'm going to the next stop.
I thought it was my last spring tour.
I was able to go around.
I thought Vietnam was the last.
I was able to go.
But it's all really fun.
That's why I felt lonely.
But I saw everyone getting together.
I thought it was a great thing to get
together.
I thought about it.
But there was something I couldn't give
up.
I thought everyone would understand that
I was myself.
I want to go to my mom and do my best
for my future.
I hope we have six months left.
I think some of you are surprised.
You've been together for a long time.
I think you know what kind of person
Hiro and Ayaka are.
I want to respect them.
One of the concerns to me is that I may
stop spending my career if I didn't want
to let 【Tесь przypadku】 continue on a
better path.
【.】 simplesmente held a
«Budokan》I gerne
We'll talk about him.
I'll keep thinking today and keep
growing.
I'll do my best, but also sad.
Some may wonder why I said that, but I
don't have any timing.
If I had continued working, I wouldn't
have had any timing.
I'll continue in that way.
Thank you, everyone.
I'll give you a little time, so you can
talk.
Did you hide it well?
Yes, I hid it well.
I don't know what it is, but...
I was in the bathroom, and I was in the
mirror.
I was in the mirror, and I was in the
I thought it was a mistake.
I was angry.
I'm sorry.
I can't say it because I'm lonely on
January 3rd.
I can't say it.
I'm sorry.
I think it's a good thing.
And thank you for your hard work.
I'll support you.
What is it?
I want to take a picture.
Please write a picture for me.
I'm glad.
I'm glad if everyone is in the picture.
I feel like I've pulled my leg.
I'll do my best next time.
I'm going to go to a family dinner every
year.
It's hard to go outside.
I often leave a big task behind.
I thought I wouldn't do that this time.
I still have a lot of tasks.
I want to pull everyone into the rhythm.
I think so.
Last year, it rained.
When everyone was in a mess,
I was a survivor.
I was crazy.
Everyone watched Ayaka's movements.
I'm glad that the rhythm has been
corrected.
I always relied on everyone.
I don't rely on others.
I wanted to make everyone feel that we
can rely on Ayaka.
I thought it would be nice if we could
do that.
I wanted to pull everyone to the rhythm
part.
But today I failed.
I couldn't achieve what I was aiming
for.
I want to be able to pull everyone to
the rhythm.
I was really excited.
But I think it's difficult.
I've relied on Ayaka.
I have my own personality.
I have no leadership.
I have no power to pull everyone.
I failed today.
But I think I've made a big change.
I'll do my best.
I saw everyone moving in the back.
I saw that everyone was enjoying it.
But I don't think everyone is interested
in this character.
Only Ebi Goro and Koromaru.
I think I'm the most favorite character
in Fumien.
I was looking forward to it every time.
But after the show, I was worried about
the result.
I was worried about the result.
But I think that's the best song I've
ever sung.
I think that's the best song I've ever
sung.
But from next week, it will probably
last as long as this album will go live
forever.
But I know I will be more confident
after a week.
And strokes of happiness will change how
I look
so I will be able to see what I look
like once there.
I felt the time limit as an idol.
I wanted to be an idol because I like
idols.
I was very interested in service and
monitor.
It was very fun. There were a lot of
cameras.
I was able to learn a lot from this fan
meeting.
I didn't eat much.
But next year, I'm sure it will be
different.
I'm looking forward to it.
The first day of the fan meeting.
Good morning.
I ate dinner at home on the first night
of the fan meeting.
I always go to the shrine at 8 or 9
o'clock.
I went to the shrine, but I couldn't go
to the shrine.
Was it too far?
I couldn't go to the shrine.
I came back.
I was eating at the shrine.
I couldn't go to the shrine.
It's the first day.
I often go to the shrine.
I usually go in the afternoon.
I usually go to the shrine at night.
I want to cook at night.
But it's already melted.
It's delicious.
It's a hot pot.
It's delicious to eat anything.
How is it?
It's delicious.
The broccoli part is delicious.
It's complicated.
It's a hot pot.
It's delicious.
Look at this.
It's a hot pot.
I want to sing two songs at the
beginning.
I want to scream.
You can scream.
It's a hot pot.
It's a game.
I thought the pre-shake was long.
I thought it would come.
I thought it would come like this.
What should I do?
It's okay, Kobayashi-san.
I'll tell you everything.
It's a heart-wrenching thing.
Let's go!
A, I, U, E, O
Ready, go!
Guri guri guri guri guri guri
Handai guri guri guri guri guri
Handai guri guri guri guri
Jump five times
Ready, go!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5
Iron iron iron iron iron iron iron iron
iron
I'm sorry for toiling over
Sorry for making you way out
That was no use for nuker첸
That was no use for nukermuffled
That was no use for nukers
That was no use for nuker
Don't brag
Just come up and forget the ice
So you gave me an advance
You surprised me
What are the plans?
Everyone enjoy themselves
Let's do it.
Where are we?
Budokan!
We are M2!
Forever!
I.O.I!
Hiroto, you can't do it.
Everyone, please go up the stairs.
Please go up the stairs.
Oh no, Mayama went to the toilet.
Mayama?
I.O.I!
I want to see you today, all of you.
I want to see you from now on.
Thank you for watching!
Please go home.
I'm sorry.
I see.
I only have the lines for the song.
I'm dancing, but I'm bored with the
song.
So I'll sing the first verse.
Oh, I see.
So don't get mad.
That's the point.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to the chorus part.
Oh, really?
What should I do?
I have a way to go, so I'm not sure.
I'm sure it's different.
Let's go!
I'm going to do it.
So cute.
I want to be the one to do it.
Yay!
I'm not sure if I can continue to have a
gentle voice.
I can't feel it.
I want to hear it.
I've been crying since before the
opening.
I'm crying.
I haven't told you guys, but I've been
in the Ebichu Family since I was in 6th
grade.
I've been in the Ebichu Family since I
was in 6th grade.
I've been used to being a little sister.
I watched yesterday's live.
What should I say?
I don't want to say it in words.
It's fun.
It's like I'm enjoying myself.
Thank you so much.
I can't say it's fun or amazing.
I'm watching it thinking, what kind of
feeling is this?
I thought that I really love Ebichu.
I think I can do anything for Ebichu.
I really got courage.
I thought I should do my best.
I can't say anything.
I couldn't say that I was a crybaby
yesterday.
I'm not a crybaby.
I've been able to do this much.
I think that I have a lot of talent.
I want to do my best.
I'll do my best, too.
Thank you.
I'm embarrassed.
2, 3, 4!
between the characters
oh no
right?
1 2 3 4
Thank you for watching!
1, 2...
Nanana! Nanana! Nanana!
We're from Takayama!
We suddenly came here!
We're from Madozuki!
Thank you!
What are we doing today?
What?
Where are we?
We're here!
We are here!
I'll be here!
Let's show our pride!
Where are we?
We're here!
Let's sing together!
I'm sorry.
Is it okay?
What was I doing?
I was going to say, wait a minute.
It's okay.
Please wait a minute.
I made a mistake.
Can I have a hug?
I'm sorry.
I'm happy if there's someone who thinks
that way.
If you think that's okay, then that's
fine.
I want you to decide by watching today's
performance.
Recently, I've been doing a lot of
things like fakes.
I've been polishing and
lain...
It's a mirror as well...
and...
I still get a lot of orders from
someone.
I think it's still fun to be with that
person.
BOY hahahaha
I'll think about it as strong as
possible and
If It's Fantastic!
If you want to meet the feel of it.
Yeah that's right.
Yes because I'm there.
Yeah.
And there's Mirai-san who's got
everything she wants.
I can't laugh!
And there's Hinano Koshiagi.
And there's Riko Nakayama who's like a
wild animal.
30 seconds left.
I want to be in the family.
But I can't.
I'm going to be in the family today.
I'm going to be okay.
I'm proud of myself.
Everyone!
Let's have fun!
I'd like to introduce you to the fans.
I want your heart.
I want your support.
I want you to be excited.
Thank you.
So, yesterday, I said that you were so
cute, but you changed.
The person who used that cute thing
yesterday, please write it in the back
of the text.
Thank you.
Let's all have fun together until the
end.
Thank you for watching!
I don't want to see you cry
I can't see my dreams
I don't care if you go away
I want to fly, cross the wall, and make
it
A path, a path, now
Time and important things are surely
Presents from God
Smile, smile, smile, look up
Just one step forward and walk
Thank you for watching!
I'm sorry.
Monster!
Do you want to do it?
No.
You're crying too.
We can't do it.
Recently, we can't.
Today was really good.
It was great.
We filmed too much.
I wonder how the shrimp will grow.
But I'm not known to most people, but I
was there.
As everyone knows, you were there too.
That doesn't change.
No, you're still in the shrimp.
So, please continue to take care of
shrimp.
And shrimp from now on.
To be honest, I've been in the group
since I joined the group.
I started from Mayama.
I joined the group and then another one.
I've never made a mistake in the group.
I've never made a mistake.
I think it was only good things.
I agree with the new members every time.
I don't know.
This is difficult.
This is the most naive.
To be honest, it was only good things.
Looking at the past, I think it's not
bad that new members are joining.
When Kaoriko joined, we had a fight.
We were worried about the members.
We were worried about how to accept
them.
But when Kaoriko joined, we didn't think
that way.
Because of them, the color of shrimp has
changed.
So, the members and the members are
different.
I don't know when they will join us
again.
But if we can continue to be a group,
I think that kind of shape will not
disappear.
For the time being, I want to be stable
with these six people.
But I think that's good.
I think that if we can continue to be a
group,
we will be able to improve our current
shape.
So if we can continue to be a group, I
think that's good.
What if we can continue to be a group?
But if we can continue to be a group,
I think that we will understand each
other.
I want to be with you forever.
I want to hear your voice.
Who is it?
Ayaka.
What is it?
Rikko.
Ayaka.
Everyone looks like a little bit of a
consent.
There is a little bit of a consent
overseas.
They look like something, but I don't
know.
Mirai-chan.
Mirai-chan and Kaho.
Hina.
What's wrong, baby?
Your face is getting red again.
My face is getting red again.
I don't care.
I hope the live show goes well.
Who is it?
It's okay.
My hair is not even on my shoulders.
This side too.
It's okay.
It's long.
My hair is getting longer because I got
my hair done.
Kashiaki, can you please keep your eyes
open?
I'm going to draw it.
Thank you.
It's gorgeous.
I'll draw Rina too.
Good luck.
Hurry up.
It's a sharp jaw.
There's time to erase it.
It's like a lord.
Rina.
I'll draw Ebichu too.
It's scary.
I'll draw it.
It's a natural look.
It's a little creepy.
Who is it?
It's a flower.
Okay.
Bye.
Go-chan, erase it.
I wanted to take it.
Really?
Then erase it.
Can I really erase it?
Thank you for your hard work.
Today, February 8, 2018.
I'll say it again.
Thank you for meeting me.
Thank you for coming to see me again.
If, if...
If you feel lonely from now on,
don't look down.
Look up like this.
Shirito Ebichu Junior High School.
I love the number 9.
The former number 1, Kano.
Don't make me say that.
I'm embarrassed.
See you later.