Hi, Kei.
I'm Ebisu Chugaku, a private student.
How are you?
I'm fine.
Have you changed since then?
I was just kidding.
You've changed.
Of course I have.
It's strange that you haven't changed.
I've been saying the same thing I said a
month ago.
But there are many things that haven't
changed.
I think there are many things that
haven't changed.
Let me talk about things I don't
understand.
Is that okay?
I have something to tell you.
I, Miyazaki Yuna, will be performing
Ebisu Chugaku at the end of the live
show on December 26.
I love the members and the staff, but I
decided to quit the entertainment
industry because I wanted to focus on my
career.
I have three more live shows to go, but
I'll do my best.
Thank you for watching.
I'm sure you're next to me
I've become a smile from my heart
Spring is the peak of the sky
A voice that changes the summer
The snow of winter is full of love
It changes into memories
I want to cry, I want to laugh,
If you're 뭐가udesed, such a distance
between us...
I will never forget you even when I grow
up
We will never change
We will never forget you
I was able to make a wish
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
I forgot to say goodbye
There's a hole in my heart
I can't stop it
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
I'm always here for you
I'll never forget you
I can't see!
I'm crying too much.
Everyone is crying too much.
But Natsu went to bed with Ayaka.
Natsu's bed is open.
We were talking.
So I said, Natsu, you can sleep in this
bed.
Ayaka said yes.
So I went to bed.
Ayaka went to bed for about an hour.
I went to bed.
You were angry?
Yes, so I was angry.
I was angry because it was so hard.
So I came here.
I thought it was magic.
Teji Aya
I'm showing you the magic.
You said you would show me the magic.
I forgot to bring the video.
I'm disqualified as a magicians.
Yes.
But there is that.
Teji Aya
I can't get out of it
My vague memories with you
Won't reach you
How can I catch your smile?
When our eyes meet
Time flies
I like you more and more
I feel wonderful
I love you, I love you but
I'm nervous and can't move
It's easy to be completely silent
I want to be by your side
The season of love is coming soon
I'm sure I'm better than you
I'll stop you
The wish I was able to keep hidden from
the website
Is a little bit painful
No matter how I try, the distance
between us
Can't be narrowed
Today again, I wish for the stars
To give me courage
Thank you for watching!
I want to tell you, I want to tell you
how I feel
Let's start the season of love with
courage
Let's tell you how we feel
I was really surprised at the three of
them.
Everyone was surprised, but somewhere...
No, it's not that easy to understand
each other's feelings.
I thought it was no good.
So the new two new students must have
been very, very anxious at first.
I'm sure the six of them were just as
anxious.
I think it's difficult, but I'll do my
best.
I'm not an educator.
No, you're not.
I'm a bit older than her, so I don't
know if I can keep up with her.
But I want to get along with her.
That's right.
I'm not sure what to say.
I'm a bit older than her, so I don't
know what to say.
I'm so happy.
Today, we played like that.
What?
Sorry, we didn't play like that.
I want to do my best.
We only played five songs.
Yes.
We played five songs.
I'm sorry.
If you are going to talk, please show
your face.
I'll show my face.
Today, I want to show you this ball.
I want to show you this ball.
Let's go.
We are Wichu Raku!
Bye!
Thank you very much.
There was a strange movement at the end.
I understand.
You were a girlfriend and a boyfriend.
In the future, if you guys are separated
and go to 3B, there will be a 4th floor
where you will be able to find a model
or actress.
I couldn't tell you today, but these two
people will enter the 4th floor.
They are related to record company, so
last November, they checked the audition
and the new audition.
They decided to come here together with
Fujii.
I wanted to say that if it was the case,
it would have been faster.
But there are various record companies
and various relationships,
and if it leaks, it won't be a problem.
I'm sorry to these children, but I
decided not to tell them until the live
ends.
I don't know much about the employees
who know this.
Because I don't want to leak.
I'm sorry to tell you that there is a
problem on the way home today.
I wanted to tell you because I didn't
tell everyone until now.
I want to tell you that next year,
I will be in my Fuji 2015, and I will be
a 3B junior.
This time it will be a group that aims
to be an idol group.
From that day on, next year...
I think you'll be working on a group for
my Fuji 2015.
I hope you'll do your best.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Then, let's say something.
I'm sorry for the trouble.
It's okay.
It's not your fault.
It's an adult's fault.
What is it?
Please keep getting along with me.
Please, I'm begging you.
I can't close it.
That's all for the report.
Thank you.
I feel refreshed.
Is it Riki-chan's?
It's Riki-chan's.
It's almost done.
I can't close it.
It's done.
Don't be afraid.
We're all friends.
It's okay.
We know each other.
We're friends.
Some want to be actors, some want to be
idols.
We have many things to do.
We want to be professional.
Please, work hard for your goals.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Everyone is kind.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Thank you.
I didn't see the live performance.
I heard it was good.
Thank you.
I want to clean up today.
I want to clean up.
Please.
Thank you.
Ayaka is wearing a lot of clothes.
I know.
That's good.
Let's do it like that.
You stand up.
Let's go, Hayashi-kun.
Yes.
Ready, go.
Go!
Yay!
Thank you.
Yeah!
Yeah! That's weird.
Thank you very much.
I'll do my best.
Bye bye!
Thank you very much.
You are welcome.
Yen is strange.
I bought snowboard.
Can you snowboard?
I can't snowboard.
Have you ever skied?
I skied.
Can you ski?
I can.
I'm in the Olympics now.
I'm re-signing for snowboard.
I want to snowboard.
I want to ski.
You want to ski?
I want to snowboard.
I'm not used to snowboarding.
You are used to it.
Yes.
I want to try.
Are you used to it?
Yes.
You are communicating with your seniors.
Are you used to your staff?
I'm not used to it.
I think you are not used to it.
I'm used to it.
Are you used to it?
Yes.
Who do you want to be the next producer?
I'm thinking about it.
I'm close to it.
We are very close.
You should be closer.
You should be close to your face.
You should be close to your cheeks.
You should be close.
That's it.
Who should I be the next producer?
You should be close.
Everyone laughs when I do it three
times.
I'm thinking about it.
Thank you very much.
I'm so tired.
What's wrong with you?
Hiro-san! Hiro-san!
Hiro-san, are you okay?
You're lying, right?
You're not a character.
I'm not a character.
Let's change the party.
This is the
one I'm going to draw.
I don't want to do that.
Everyone will stretch their bodies
and move forward from here,
so let's all laugh today.
Yes.
Everyone, you have to shout.
You have to shout.
We are the
Kizuna AI!
We are the Kizuna AI!
We finally got it!
Thank you.
Let's do our best.
Smile.
Thank you for your hard work!
Good job!
One more!
Thank you for your hard work!
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I can see your eyes are small.
Can you see them?
I can't see.
I'm sorry.
I'm writing a message at this distance.
No, I can't see the boys.
I can't see.
No.
Then, let's toast.
Who?
My sister is going to do it.
That's why I'm waiting here.
As expected of Yasumoto.
What's going on?
Let's do our best tomorrow.
I want to drink a lot of water.
Stand up.
Don't need to raise your hands.
No, no, no.
I don't need to raise my hands.
Then, let's do our best tomorrow.
MAMAMOO!
What about Masuda?
I can't drink properly.
I want to spread my feelings to people.
Let's do our best!
I want to hear more of your words!
I want to eat vegetables.
The
Let's eat.
You can eat it.
The
Let's eat.
It tastes good.
Let's eat!
Avocado.
The sake made with salt is more rich
than sake ofIMAGR DYкаK Uhul
labs
I can't eat this.
The salad is really good.
Let's eat, everyone.
Thank you.
Ignore it.
It's good.
Let's eat.
One, two, three.
One bite.
It's good.
How is it, Abe-kun?
Oily!
I'm surprised.
It's really good.
I don't know. I only know that.
Carrots are delicious.
When I was in elementary school, my
grandmother used to say,
If I didn't have sweets, I would have
eaten carrots raw like a rabbit.
So, carrots are...
I think...
I think it's better to eat carrots raw
than to eat them cooked.
I think it's more memorable to eat
carrots raw.
It's a story of carrots.
That's all. It was Orange.
I'm sorry.
It's a big day.
It's amazing to see it from here.
Pocky is a human.
Pocky is a shrimp.
What is it?
Isn't it a shrimp?
What is this?
Is it in your head?
It's in Pocky.
Come out, Pocky.
I want to get in too.
It's popular.
It's like it's coming out.
It's hard to breathe.
I'm going to get off, so I don't have to
do that.
Turn the key, that number is my favorite
It's getting cold, my hands are shaking
I want to keep dancing, but now I'm
always in a trance
I'm going to eat hamburger.
It's a little bit soft.
What is it?
It's like a hamburger with a fried egg.
It's a little bit soft.
How you ready?
Thank you for watching.
I'm sorry.
I didn't get any medicine.
But I'm feeling better.
I've been getting some medicine.
I'll do my best.
Cheer up.
Don't laugh!
Matsu, stop it!
It's funny.
I only noticed your smile
I want to see you again
I want to be with you again
I want to throw it away
And then, they became eight shrimp-
chewed.
These two are amazing.
Really amazing.
It's time for the two of them.
Ouch!
Don't hurt!
It's a helicopter.
This is Ehime, right?
Aichi is in the shape of kangaroo.
The shape of the turtle.
Aichi is...
Aichi-ken is kangaroo.
Thank you.
I'm so embarrassed.
I'm so embarrassed to be a guest.
I'm really embarrassed.
Wait, you're talking about me, aren't
you?
I'm talking about you.
Aya-chan, you're a liar.
You always say that from Aya-chan.
I always hear that from Aya-chan.
You touch her hair and do this under her
nose.
I'm going to do it.
I can't use this, so I can't say it.
It's amazing.
I'm embarrassed.
No, Aya-chan is also dangerous.
I've never done anything like this.
I'm going to do this under her nose.
I've already stopped.
I'm not doing it anymore.
It's annoying.
I'm embarrassed.
It's annoying, Aya-chan.
Aya-chan is the one who's embarrassed.
I'm embarrassed because I'm trying hard.
I'm going down now.
I'm going down and down.
I'm going to calm down again.
I'm going to sleep at night and go home.
I'm so happy.
I did it.
Did you see?
Thank you.
I'm so glad I didn't die.
Aya-chan is cute!
I slept a lot.
I sang a lot.
Good morning.
I was sleeping.
It was our first time on a tour with
Kamoriko.
It was a tough tour.
But you were smiling and talking about
the tour.
Do you remember?
What did you say?
I said I thought it was more painful.
You remember!
It's more fun than I thought.
I was worried about the tour because it
was a tour.
I was able to sing and sing.
Ayaka was the only one who taught me.
Everyone was happy.
I'm going to cry.
I'm happy. Riko-chan, how was our
education and training?
That's not true!
Don't say that!
Aya-chan, I want you to praise me.
I want you to praise Riko-chan.
I understand.
I'm sorry.
You can say anything.
Thank you for always coming to the
lesson.
Thank you!
Stop it!
You can't run away from me!
I'm embarrassed
You'll be embarrassed
It's a telepathy
Should we change the name?
I think that Hirata has grown up
When she taught Kaoriko dance
When she cheered her up
I think she has grown up so much
Really?
Before the show, I was so nervous
Thank you for watching
She hugged me all the time
She was so nervous
You became a big sister
I did
I became a little bit
Then, from the oldest
This girl's part changed
I heard it
Yes, you did
The oldest
I like the oldest at times like this
But
I can't say it back
But I think Aya-chan has grown
I see
I'm serious when I talk about this
I don't want to make this atmosphere
But
Of course, Kaohsiung has gotten used to
it
And she can show herself in front of
others
So Aya-chan can show herself in front of
I've heard it before
But she can stand on the same line as me
She can stand on the same line as me
And Hinata
She was always strong, but she's seen
more people around her
Rina
Today was hard for her
She was always nervous and cried
But she didn't cry today
So I think she's gotten stronger
And Ai-Ai
She's gotten better
I like her
She's gotten more freedom
More
How should I say it
In the middle of the show
I respect her because she's always
expressive
But she's gotten more expressive
I think she's cool
Thank you
Mirei
She's got a lot of confidence
She's become a big sister
Maybe Mayamaru is the big sister
Today
I think I was the one who cried the most
When you were doing the hair
Mayamaru was so excited
It's like
I know
She was so happy that she cried
It's a wonderful thing
I was so happy today
So in that sense
Everyone is getting stronger as I get
weaker
Thank you
I have to train more
Because you got stronger, tears came out
As expected of onee-san
Everyone, little by little, did you get
stronger?
Did you get used to it?
It's good to get used to it
You have to do better, Bichu, even
further
Sorry, it's like a reflection meeting
You talked seriously
But everyone has grown
It's thanks to everyone who always
supports us
Thank you very much
We'll give you more performances until
summer
We'll do our best to make you think, oh,
that's amazing
Thank you
Then, I'll say it in order
Yasumoto-san...
Okay, okay
37 Biusho
No
Yasumoto-san, 37 Biusho
I can do 37 Biusho
I'm sorry, I made a mistake
Then, I'll say it in order
Tere-moto-san, please
Everyone, please give me your hands
Ready?
This!
Wow!
Te-he
Tere-moto?
Thank you!
I'm worried about Rina
I'm a little weird now
I said congratulations
I feel happy
Do you understand Ayaka?
Everyone, who?
Absolutely
I said congratulations to Aya-chan
Thank you, congratulations!
Thank you!
Congratulations to Terumoto
Is this the end?
This is the end of the story
Right?
So Mirei-chan, please say your ending
Yes!
So this is the end of the story
Please say it together
So today, everyone
Have a good day!
I'm so tired!
Thank you!
Please leave a comment!
Please wait a little longer!
Everyone, please wait a little longer!
Thank you!
Please leave a comment!
Please wait a little longer!
It's over.
Thank goodness.
I'll be back later.
I'm so hungry.
It's over.
It's starting.
What?
I'm sorry.
Say it again.
It's over.
I'm sorry.
Thanks for watching.
Please check it out on the other
channel.
Please subscribe our channel and click
the button.
One year has passed so quickly.
This is the second time they've been in
a tour together.
They're getting used to the current
shrimp fishing.
But they realize that it's not natural
at all.
But no one says anything.
They don't want to change.
They just want to continue forever.
The first day of the tour
Good morning.
We'll do our best until the first day.
The first day of the tour
Good morning.
It's time for the morning.
I'm Chihiro.
I'm Chihiro Ebichu.
Thank you for your continued support.
We are Ebichu!
Where are we?
Sentai!
We are Ebichu!
Let's do our best!
This is a secret secret
I'm going to go
Then open your heart
Because there is a love
Oh, this is
Let's blow up the world of the two-faced
people
Come on! Come on!
Let's do whatever we want
Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on!
Chichi-Chichi, Ume-Uke, Pokemon
The power of the two-faced people
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Let's do whatever we want
I'm going to dance, bye bye bye
I don't need your answer anymore
There's a answer to the question
I'm going to dance, bye bye bye
Thank you.
There is no MC of FURUTOKU.
That's true.
That means that.
First of all, MC.
Is it serious?
Yes.
Everyone.
Why is it serious?
Please cut it.
Yasumoto is here.
I do not know.
Everyone, please drink water.
It's hot today.
It's hot.
It's getting cold.
And the sweat is flowing like a
waterfall.
What is this situation?
Do you know that everyone is running
like a waterfall?
What is that?
What are you doing?
Because it's MC, it's MC.
Because it's MC.
Thank you.
Come on!
Music
I'm so happy
If I can hold your hand
I'll be so happy
I want to kiss you
I can't stop, I can't stop
Kiss you, kiss you
Kiss you
Thank you for watching!
Yeah, not yet!
Yes!
Let's go!
How was it?
It was hard from the beginning.
It was hot and you were on the ground.
You were in a hurry.
You were cold and you were tired.
Was it hard to stand up?
It was hard to stand up.
Even if you were to come back,
you couldn't get into the 2nd song.
If you can do that, you should come
back.
If you can't do that, you should take a
break.
If you come back, you can't come back.
Everyone thinks it's okay.
There's still time.
There are 5 songs left.
Thank you for watching.
I'm saying, Ayaka!
I don't like this kind of thing. It's so
touching.
This kind of thing makes me cry.
Ayaka.
I'm saying Ayaka.
Yasumoto.
Yasumoto, I'm saying Ayaka.
I have to go.
Thank you for coming to the show!
Thank you!
I'm so happy!
Everyone, it's morning!
Good morning!
But, for now,
I'm doing this as eight people.
During the concert, even if I'm not
there,
I hope the eight of us can do it
together.
I hope that's the case for me too.
I think I said something good just now.
I'm sorry.
It's okay, isn't it?
It's close, so I'll go.
Oh, that's right.
OK.
Goodbye.
Bye-bye.
It's gone.
It was here.
Awesome.
That's right.
It's good to fix it.
It doesn't matter where it is.
It's laut.
It goes along with everything.
They're иeat, bytes eaIIyever ehk
Wow
us
BoIbl
y
The
good
It's delicious.
Corn cheese.
Please star in the Magikarp.
That was cool.
I got my mom to eat ramen for me.
It was delicious.
Didn't you get her to eat it?
We were going to Magikarp.
I was pulling it hard.
It was scary. It was a jibigyami.
It was amazing.
I was like,
I got it! I got it!
I was pulling it hard.
I was like,
I got it!
I was crying.
I want to say sorry.
I heard it in the Japanese.
Aiko said,
Let's go eat ramen together.
I was like,
I was watching the family.
I started crying again.
It was really good.
It was delicious, right?
You ate cheese dumplings, right?
What was that?
It was delicious.
I drank the milk tea.
I drank it, but I drank it.
It was cute.
It was really good.
If you cry, you'll get angry.
I'm sorry.
Why are you saying sorry?
Where are you sorry?
I'm sorry.
What are you sorry for?
It's over.
It was delicious.
Don't say that.
I'm sorry.
It's not bad.
It's good.
Let's talk seriously.
I want everyone to listen to me.
It's a difficult problem.
You can cry.
Everyone wants to eat this.
I don't like it.
I've been thinking about what to do.
What should I do?
I don't think I can decide that.
I think everyone should think about it.
But I don't want everyone to act
separately.
I don't want to.
Keisuke said that he was only bad at
eating.
I was thinking about how to do it.
I was doing it alone.
It's cute.
I was thinking about what to do.
No one is bad at eating.
I was doing it alone.
Everyone wants to eat it.
It's a difficult problem.
This is a similar story.
It may come out in the future.
This is not Hokkaido.
I can't eat it.
I thought it was bad for everyone.
I don't think it's good for the mental
health of the past.
There is no problem with the fact that
there are things I don't like.
I don't think I don't like it.
Everyone can eat what they like.
I think it's easier to go to the staff
and eat what I like.
I think everyone's behavior may be
different.
But I can't eat what I can't eat.
I will eat with the staff and meet
everyone again.
I think that's a good way to do it.
You don't have to be in a relationship
with each other,
and you don't have to be in a past
relationship.
There may be some things you think
about,
but you don't have to worry about it.
It was just a past relationship today,
and today was a day where Mirei couldn't
eat.
Mirei can only eat fresh fish.
It's impossible to eat fish like this.
Then, will you go to ramen?
You can't go to ramen when you're alone.
I want to go out with you.
I was the first one to invite you, but I
refused.
I want to cry the most.
I'm sorry.
I'm the one who's hurt the most.
This is my third time.
This is really good.
I'm going to eat.
There are few people, but there are few
people.
Yes, there are few people.
Yes, please.
Yes, I have a question.
I have a consultation.
It's not a consultation, but I think
it's the first time to have a live
viewing today.
That's why I was thinking about Johnny
Matsukashi.
I talked to the director of Fuji Jutsu.
Honestly, I thought it would be good to
have a first show with eight people.
I thought so, and I asked the staff and
everyone to prepare it.
Actually, there was a contact from the
end of the day in the middle of the
night.
But the audience is also expecting.
If we miss this, we will have to wait
until the show is over.
We will not do the massage Johnny.
We will get the CD of the audience, but
we haven't seen it yet.
I got a call from the audience that I
was wondering what it would be like.
At that time, I didn't change my mind.
I talked to the director this morning.
There is a live viewing.
I want to see it.
I'm sorry to say this, but I'm
responsible for the hospitalization.
I'm on leave, and it doesn't matter to
the audience.
So the audience is Johnny Matsukashi.
I missed it.
I'm still wondering what the audience
will do.
I want to see it.
I'm listening to the story now.
I'm sorry.
I think Eri-chan has the longest part.
Yes, she has the longest part.
So, what do you think?
I want to do it.
As I said,
I think it's difficult to write a good
story
because Yasumoto is not here.
Johnny is necessary for this situation.
It may be incomplete,
but I think I can show Johnny who came
to Yasumoto to other places.
I think the seven-person Johnny is
valuable.
I said I wouldn't do it if I didn't do
it.
I said I wouldn't do it if I was last
year.
This year, I'm going to say the opposite
that I wouldn't do it if I was normal.
I'm going to be more active.
It's fun to be Johnny.
I think it's necessary for today's set.
There are places where there is no
Yasumoto,
but there is no Yasumoto today,
and he will come back.
If Johnny didn't come out today,
I think the place to put Johnny is not
good.
I want to do it today.
It may be difficult for everyone,
but I want you to be satisfied.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I think it's better not to do it.
I think it's better to do it.
What is it?
I like Ayaka's part.
Did you hear it?
I like the CD sound.
For example, if I'm in the family,
I can cover it up, but I'm sad that
Ayaka's not here.
Even if I'm particular about Nana.
I want to sing with everyone, but I want
Ayaka to be mixed in.
Today is the first time we're performing
together, so it's 7 people, but it's 8
people.
I understand. I'll ask the music fans.
I think there's a way to make Yasumoto's
voice come out without touching the
stage.
I don't think there's one without it.
I'll ask if there's a way to do that.
So, I'll ask Yasumoto to do it today.
Thank you for watching.
We can understand the part of the song.
Please tell us in advance.
Let's see if we can do it in the form of
Ayachan.
Let's have the music team to judge.
Let's go.
Then, in that direction.
Yes, please.
Let's go to the switch.
Let's do it.
I'm sorry.
You're like a grandma.
I'm like a grandma.
You're a grandma.
You should say it.
Why did you move this stone?
I thought this way, but I wanted to know
what everyone thought.
It's easy to do this here.
I'm an adult, so I'll do this.
But I heard it because I wondered if
there were people who thought that way.
It's okay for you to think that way.
You can say it before I say it.
I think it's better to think this way.
You should say it.
Why did you move this stone?
I was watching.
It's okay if everyone thinks that way.
I think this way.
If not, I shouldn't have moved this
stone.
I heard that you should do it.
I thought this was a wet story.
I think this way, but the members and
Ume are the same.
I think this way, but Maya thinks the
same.
You can say it first.
There is no problem.
It's 50-50.
I think it was good.
It's been a long time, so I don't feel
like a tour final.
And there was an additional performance.
So it was like 3 months and a half.
I thought it would be lonely if I didn't
come next week.
I'm sorry.
What is it?
Soba!
What?
Thank you!
I'll throw it away if I see it today.
No!
What is that?
What?
I wonder how many times it tastes good.
It's good.
Soba?
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
It's delicious.
I'll eat meat.
Meat looks good.
It looks delicious.
Soba is here.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
How many times?
Soba is here.
When you say that,
you'll realize that it's your birthday.
It's seasoned.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Let's make a new reaction.
When you say that,
I'll eat it.
It's delicious.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Is this seasoned?
Yes.
What is it?
Soba.
Soba?
Soba with okura.
That's amazing.
Christopher,
you have to do something good.
That's right.
This time,
you'll do this, right?
Do your best.
Will it be okay?
I'm worried.
It's fast.
I wonder if we didn't make it in time.
What's wrong, Christopher?
That's right.
Huh?
Oh!
Yeah!
Thank you!
Huh?
Seriously?
I didn't know!
What?
You!
You're in the middle!
What?
Amazing!
Happy birthday!
Wow!
Um...
What?
Congratulations!
Can you sing it properly?
Huh?
Um...
Since there's no candle,
I'll use an air candle.
Okay, that's a good idea!
Really?
Yeah!
That's a good idea!
Please!
Let's sing together!
Aika, please!
Huh?
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday dear Aika!
Congratulations!
Please blow out the candles!
I'm ready!
You have 17, right?
At once!
One, two!
Congratulations!
Thank you so much for coming to this
tour.
I'm so scared that the ABCs will give me
points.
Aika-san is really talking in a sluggish
way.
I'm told that I shouldn't talk because I
talk too much.
But she's talking a lot.
I'm talking a lot.
She's always talking a lot.
Why? Why?
But...
Well, it's amazing.
The current Ebitube is like this.
Everything points.
One, two, three.
I think they're all different colors.
I think that's the growth process of
Ebitube.
I hope you enjoy it.
And I think this will be the last time
you see this.
So, I hope you watch it again after you
see it.
It might be interesting again.
So, I hope you watch it again and get to
know it better.
Thank you for coming to the tour.
It was really fun.
We were 8 people.
I wanted to improve my performance.
I was worried about what I could do.
I was in Kanagawa.
My teacher said that I was good at my
performance.
I knew that.
So, I felt like I exploded.
But, I was in Kanagawa.
The last time was this time.
But, the performance started from
Sendai.
I think everyone...
I think everyone had lessons.
I couldn't do lessons.
I remember what I learned and I know
that everyone can do it.
So, how should I put it?
So, the performance power from April has
increased with each tour.
And I think that I've learned everything
I've learned on this school tour.
I think I've been able to show
everything.
Personally, I think it's a great tour
final.
I don't want people to think that I'm
being a
mischievous girl, but I don't.
I feel like I'm in my youth only when
I'm in my prime.
I'm trying to be a youth in Ebichu.
I'm not saying it myself, but I love
Ebichu.
Let's eat this cake later.
Can I take it home? Thank you.
Can I take it home? Sorry, thank you.
Thank you, Christo-san.
Christo-ha, are you feeling down?
Are you feeling down?
I'm sure we'll meet again.
We'll meet again?
Shall we sing?
What?
Thank you for today, it was really fun
Your rice balls are too much
Did you notice? You've been laughing all
this time
This smile of mine is a gift from you
If you could become a star, you could
see you from the night sky every day
But it's too far away, so I want a
flower that blooms by your side even in
spring
Can we meet again? Can we meet again?
I can't let go of our feelings
We're surely together, aren't we?
Forever and ever
I want to be like this forever
I wish time could stop like this
After saying goodbye, I'm all alone
I'm lonely here, but the most important
thing is
that you gave me my smile, and that I
won't lose it
I wonder if we can meet again
I can't even hold hands with you
We'll always be together
Translated by Releska
I wonder if we'll meet again
The feelings that can't be said with
hands in hand
We're surely together
I wonder if we'll meet again
Let go of our hands that are tied
I'm sure we'll be together
in the future
The story of the first love
Congratulations!
Let's take a picture!
OK!
Ready, set!
I still think of everyone as my friends.
Friends who have overcome a really big
event called small changes.
I'm not a representative, but for now.
The former representative of the
transfer student, number one, Kannon.