And even without the award for being a
partici
ite
Must be Urdg v
not
Yakan and Idol
One day, Yakan, who was sleeping in the
living room of the Star Dust
headquarters,
showed up. His name is Yakan.
Yakan, who is interested in idols,
asked the people of the Star Dust to let
him talk to idols
because he would put delicious tea in
it.
The people of the Star Dust who are kind
and like tea are okay at once.
So, Yakan, who was born in the living
room of the Star Dust,
was born with a program to talk to
idols.
I'm Yakan, who was born and raised in
the living room of the Star Dust.
Today's guest is an idol.
Hello, everyone. We are Orono.
I'm Naito Luna, who was born and raised
in the living room of the Star Dust.
Nice to meet you.
Thank you.
Naito, thank you for coming.
How old are you now?
I'm 21 years old.
Your age is 25 years old.
How old are you now?
You are older than anyone in the Star
Dust.
I'm really happy.
I'm really impressed by your comments.
Thank you for coming today.
I'm a big senior.
How is your autumn life these days?
Autumn life?
I'm talking about summer.
Let's start with the summer story.
I'm an Indian.
Really?
Everyone says I'm surprising.
This summer, I set a theme and goal as a
footcar.
What is a footcar?
It's a footwork.
I see.
So I went outside a lot.
Which country did you go?
I went to the dream country twice.
I went to the beach to see the
fireworks.
I also went to Osaka.
Osaka?
Yes.
It's a lot of work.
I look like a free person when I talk.
I didn't think so.
I suddenly became very negative.
I think it's a summer where I can enjoy
private life while touring with
LilyBet1man.
That's good.
Are you wearing a footcar in autumn?
I think it's good if I can go.
I can't go in winter.
Why is that?
I can't get out of the bed.
It's cold.
I'm weak.
It's a good footcar keyword.
I will go.
Nightclub and idol.
Naito.
You are active as an Instagramer.
I heard it for the first time.
I feel like the antenna around that is
very active.
I like to go to the cafe and take
pictures.
I like to wear a swimsuit.
I want to wear it all over my body.
I agree.
You have a fashionable image.
I just like swimsuits.
You are very active.
What is the most important thing in a
sauna?
My father has been in the sauna for 50
years.
You are very active.
I love my family.