Thank you for watching!
Night-time Idol
This is the end of the show!
Do you have any announcements?
We will be holding a festival on
February 25th at Line Cube Shibuya!
What is this? It looks like a fun title.
It will be held in Shibuya, Tokyo.
It's the first time to have a one-man
live with Carnival.
I'm excited to take off my mask.
I'm going to take off various masks.
What do you mean? Take off the mask?
And I want to show you various scenes.
Carnival is a festival that is a little
mature for us.
Is that true?
Yes, it is.
I don't think I've ever heard of it.
It's like a samba.
I don't think it's a samba.
Oh, that's right.
Is a hoho banda a physical sound?
No.
What do you mean?
Is a samba a sound?
No, no.
It's not like, wasshoi!
It's a little foreign.
No, I like samba, too.
I don't like the samba feeling.
Everyone likes men.
I don't take off my samba.
I'm not saying that.
I wonder who will come out like a
commercial for the end of the year.
I'm looking forward to it.
Please come and play.
A mature carnival.
I see.
Thank you.
I have a tea that gives you energy.
Can I drink it?
I like tea.
Thank you.
Today, I made a tea with a blend that
hurts my throat.
There's nothing weird in it.
Are you okay?
It's suspicious.
I'm being told.
I've never been told that.
But I think I'll understand if I talk.
I'm fine.
I didn't think you'd doubt me.
It's delicious.
How is it?
I blended various things with orange
peel.
It's a citrus flavor.
It's refreshing.
It's good.
It smells good.
Do you drink tea?
I love it.
I drink three cups of hot tea a day in
winter.
I see.
Please try it.
Thank you for watching.
I was suspected of something.
You're used to being a double-sided,
aren't you?
That's right.
It's terrible, isn't it?
It's not easy.
I'm getting older.
You too, Sakura-san.
Well, that's it.
Finally, I'd like you to close the
program.
As an idol, I'd like you to close the
program with a cute face.
Please do so.
How do I close it?
I'm going to leave it to you.
You're used to doing that kind of work.
Thank you for watching.
This was Sakura Nao from Team Search!
Bye bye!
This program is brought to you by
Amitaro, Toshikazu-chan, Kazumi,
Hidepio, and Bocchi.
My hair is growing and I'm not sure when
to cut it. Bye bye!