..."Yakan and Idols."
Game 3
Event or animal​
I was torn between the two, but I think
it's my 3 favorite things​
When I think of things I value​
I've always thought that I should spend
a year with my family​
Ehh?​
For example, of course New Year's Day​
Or the Lunar New Year's Day​
Or the Hina Festival​
Yeah, yeah​
Or the Golden Week, or Easter​
Or Halloween​
Or Christmas, or my mother's and
father's birthday​
I've always thought that they're
important​
So I think they're one of my 3 favorite
things​
You still value them this year, right?​
Yeah, I think for New Year's Day, my
family​
My relatives gather and have a big
party​
Yeah, yeah​
I think I'm doing that now​
I see, so you're doing that now​
I hope you become a TV personality​
Or animals​
The same​
I like animals the same​
Yeah, yeah​
If I have time, I watch animal videos
and smile by myself​
And my mom would tell me off​
I also have Zecchan​
I like animals​
I want you to tell me in the comments​
Like, which zoo is good​
Or which zoo is good to see animals​
There's a lot​
Especially this year, or last summer​
My family went to the Himawari field on
Soreiyu Hill​
Where is it?​
It's in Yokosuka​
Oh, it's in Yokosuka?​
Yeah​
We went to see the Himawari field​
But there's also a zoo where you can
touch animals​
You can touch capybaras there​
You can touch capybaras?​
Yeah​
With alpacas at this distance​
Alpacas and capybaras?​
There's kangaroos where capybaras are​
Oh, really?​
It's a fun experience​
Kangaroos?​
Yeah​
It's a fun experience?​
They're small, right? Like, warabi?​
No, they're big​
They're big? There's a real kangaroo?​
Oh, that's cool​
So be careful​
Don't stand in front of kangaroos​
You could get hit​
Right?​
But you can go in there​
Oh!​
Soreiyu Hill in Yokosuka​
Yeah, I recommend it for family outings​
Family outing...​
Today, we're looking up staff members​
We're looking up staff members​
Including the ones in the anime​
We don't know anything about this place​
You don't know Soreiyu Hill?​
I don't!​
You're from Kanagawa, so you'd be
embarrassed if you said that​
You're from Kanagawa?​
You don't know Soreiyu Hill?​
I don't!​
That's weird!​
I've met capybaras and kangaroos​
There's a mini-event in Soreiyu Hill​
Oh, yeah​
How is it?​
Is it a house?​
It's a house​
I'll go there​
Please go out​
Oh, really?​
I can go in there​
Okay​
This is amazing​
You can go in even if it rains​
There's still a lot of room for events​
Please​
You can​
If you have the opportunity, please use
it​
Thank you very much​
Please​
Please subscribe to our channel​
We're waiting for your tea commercial​
That's the bad part​
If you keep doing that​
You'll end up like this​