Lesson Day 2
I'm so excited.
I used to do it with this suit.
It's always been a long time since I did
it.
I was absent yesterday.
I will join quietly today.
I was so excited.
I got advice from my senior.
I'm a muscle trainer.
I'm going to go up and down.
I was half-assed.
I'm going to do two-times pull-ups.
The new formation lesson has started
with the new members for the fan meeting
Today, they will perform
The song that represents the shrimp-chew
that has been sung by the first fan
meeting,
I want to seduce you
Which team will win the competition?
They will make their BLACKPINK formation
into eight.
ATTENTION!
First, a song for the song.
Turn back data's had only one page.
Like the turn back...
Sraz multiplies brain
Thank you for watching!
The new members practiced this song even
during the audition training.
They looked like they were able to dance
without any problems.
the leader time
The choreography was in his head to some
extent, but it's still far from perfect.
In the first half of the show,
the south part of the secretary came out
like this,
but she Innovation undViolation
So it's
We found a lot of new pieces here
M Somehow, daigah Isa
Senior writer tunnel
Senior writers sew packages for the
trainees
Thank you for watching!
And then...
Next, we'll have lunch and then have a
meeting.
Please take a break.
We'll participate on a par withamin &
here is Yuno standing
I'll show you how to do it.
Turn your back.
And then you can do it like this.
5, 6, 7, 8.
By moving them and dancing now, all
three women become confused
The one who carefully follows her new
members
Riina is suspicious
Wonderful
Broad offers the opportunity to show a
stage brand
Their choreography needs to be a good
one
and the mission is very challenging
In thats context, they actively follow
the new members
Yu secret
There are only three people
I'm actually not happy.
NiziU, over their delicious food...
They are teachers and
I want to be loved by you forever
I was
It's totally different from the 8th
Totally different
The location and the movement are
difficult
I can't remember at all
Difficult
The formation is checked over 2 hours
Are you ready?
And the fourth time
I want to dance
Don't be afraid of the future
Just a little more
Your smile is so beautiful
Don't be afraid of the future
Thank you for watching!
I want to be able to see you
I want to find the number of times I can
see you
I can't stop the time
You are the skyline
I'm so happy that I can't stop you
I know that there is a world
That doesn't change even if we don't
meet
I want to embrace the courage of an
unchanging life
I wonder if I'll miss tomorrow
I remember you
I want to see you
Somehow, he managed to dance without
making a mistake in the formation.
You might be a little tired, but you'll
be able to do this kind of thing in the
future.
And I think it's amazing that you're
dancing while looking at the side.
The lines are all together, so I think
it's a good idea.
I hope you'll be able to do it in the
future.
That's all for today. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Can I ask you a question?
I'm a person who can remember the place.
I'll practice a lot. I'll do my best.
It's difficult.
It's a formation.
It's very heartwarming to have three
people.
I still want to seduce them.
I was doing an audition, so I was okay.
I think it will be difficult to do other
things from now on.
The new members will perform one stage
full performance as a private school.
In other words, the songs you have to
remember exceed 20.
The pressure is not only for the new
members.
As the number of members increases, the
choreography becomes more organized.
The moves are also different.
Some parts of the choreography are
broken, but there are parts that are not
in sync with the three members.
I want to work hard to make it more
harmonious.
And the most pressure was...
I have to teach the choreography, not
the teacher.
There are many things that I have to do
as a teacher.
I'm also worried about that.
She is responsible as an educator and
dance director.
70 days until the fan meeting.
Next time, Kashiwagi Sensei's intense
lesson begins.
Next time, I will show you the
choreography of the new member.