The third day of the audition for the
new members
I was so frustrated with what I couldn't
do
I don't know what to do
I don't think I can meet the new members
I can't imagine
Who will take the seat of the new
members?
The second half of the audition will
begin
Good morning.
Today is the third day.
Thank you.
The third day of training starts with a
dance lesson.
We will see the dance moves of each
group.
Each group will show their dance moves.
First, the Muscle Team and the Fire
Team.
Please.
Thank you for watching. Please subscribe
to my channel.
I couldn't go down there.
-"For a short while."
I'm sorry...
Thank you for watching.
The two teams have finished their work.
Next, the Green Salad Team.
Maida struggled with the formation the
day before.
Please.
What will happen?
4HK is prepared for event!
3RD RULE
Thank you for watching!
The 3 of them all show their best
dancing
I think I did better than yesterday.
I think I did well.
I had more things to do than yesterday.
I didn't do well, so I just lived a
little.
-the independent judges.
That's also a possibility.
Each team was practicing on their own,
hoping to get the best result.
But one night, there was an
announcement...
Thank you.
Tomorrow,
I'll be adding another song.
I want to have another song called,
I Want to seduce you.
Suddenly, a new song was added.
This is the reason.
It's tough, but I want to see how it's
done.
Our kids are all tough.
We have to sing a few songs.
But I'm sure we can do it tomorrow if we
get up.
That's why I want to try to put in the
effort.
Then we can understand.
I wanted to try that, so I added one
more song.
Thank you.
The second song is...
I didn't think I'd add another song.
I'm surprised.
That was tough.
This is crazy.
And as the principal said,
everyone is being chased.
The first song is...
Thank you for watching.
As soon as they return from dinner,
they are hit by the added seductive tire
on their heads and bodies.
And so they are back in the dorm for the
third day.
When they put the seductive tires
together...
Blue and yellow.
Good job.
Thank you.
And Nonoka too.
21 hours until the final unit
announcement.
Can they overcome this trial?
I was so focused on the lyrics.
I couldn't concentrate on the dance.
And I had to concentrate on the lyrics.
I couldn't concentrate on any of them.
So I was a bit disappointed.
It's hard.
I think it's harder to dance in the
beginning.
There are some differences in the way I
move.
The clothes... They get messed up.
I'll do my best.
After a break, Nonoka is alone in the
gym.
Nonoka is very motivated. She's always
singing.
I think she remembers the lyrics.
When she heard the results of her
practice, she suddenly...
I think I won't be able to meet my
friend in two days.
I don't know what to do.
I think it's great that you can make a
lot of shrimp balls.
I think shrimp balls don't suit me.
No matter how much practice, they can't
keep up with the huge task.
They feel the passion of other students.
They can't see themselves anymore.
The lesson of singing has begun for the
girls who are in panic just by dancing.
Let's start the lesson.
Let's sing a song.
You remember the lyrics, right?
The lyrics are in a place where you
can't get in the way.
You don't have to look at the lyrics.
First, she sings the lyrics to check the
compatibility of the dance and the song.
But...
Thank you for watching!
I'm not even scared of anything
I'm not afraid of anything
I'm always
I'm always ready to face the sky
I'm not afraid of anything
Thank you for watching!
Yes, this is what it looks like when you
sing and dance.
How much can you do now?
You have to complete one more song.
I want to seduce you.
Let's sing!
Come on, KUMA!
I want to seduce you.
Don't listen to me.
I'm watching you.
I want to seduce you.
I'm in a good mood today
What are you doing now?
I'm going to talk
I wonder if I can help you
Let's do a voice training.
At that time, from behind the students
who are taking lessons,
we will be practicing the dance.
Let's practice the dance to get the
rhythm.
Tom, tom, tom, tom, tom,
Itai, domen.
The new members want to see the dance.
The members of Ebichu rush to the
training camp.
It's hard to meet new members.
We are nervous.
We will do it for each team.
We will pass through all the rooms.
Now, they will show off their skills in
front of the members.
No. I don't want to see it.
First, the muscle team.
孤独で純情 両 Warner humid reopen
人産...
絡оля
zit
... can be tried.
You did well, Rie.
I did.
You almost memorized it.
You're great.
You can memorize it, but you have to.
You did well, Rie.
You can tell by looking at them.
Who stood out the most?
Who did you follow with your eyes?
That's what it means.
Who was the most important?
Next, the Green Salad Team.
I'm not a good singer, I'm a bad singer
lyrics fly berber Ru
I said yesterday that the volume is not
a problem, but if you can't hear the
voice, you can't make a song.
So you have to sing.
Even if you don't remember, you can
sing.
I don't know if you make lyrics on the
spot, but the most bad thing is that you
don't sing.
And finally, Team Anoko.
Nonoka's voice is amazing.
I like singing.
Thank you for watching!
We've learned a lot from default command
dormir,
so we need to analyze,
what should we have gone for more?
and figure out what will happen in the
future
with a дDe Eisler.
Then, we can produce better coffee,
as our ideas.
I also have the habit of getting carried
away easily.
I think I've experienced the same of the
people
I've experienced that.
Once you fall, you have to stand up
again.
You have to listen to the music.
Listen to the music.
Kobayashi remembers her life when she
joined Ebichu.
I've been through a lot.
It's really hard to do three things at
the same time.
I had to do dance, formation and singing
at the same time.
I've been through a lot of things that I
couldn't do at first.
I understand that feeling.
I feel like I can't do it anymore.
But the teachers are still training me.
I'm still doing what I want to do.
I'm doing my best to be good at it.
The teachers are taking care of me.
The students are trying their best to
practice but they don't get any results.
The members of Ebichu feel overwhelmed,
and they're in shock.
I'm sure there are a lot of worries and
worries while I'm doing this.
I want to show everyone that I'm going
to be an Ebichu member.
Today is the third day, and tomorrow is
the last.
I think there are a lot of individuality
in the group.
We're all in groups of three now.
We're rivals, so I want to see more of
myself.
There's a day after this, and it's
really going to end tomorrow.
I think it's really hard, but I hope you
all do your best.
Thank you.
I'm not sure if I can sing well.
But I want to do my best for the rest of
the day.
I don't know what to do.
Me?
But I feel strong.
Good Heart
I'll do my best
I'm actually with the members
I'm nervous and I'm crying
I thought I would do my best to listen
to the words of the person who is only a
day away from this training camp.
I became stronger and I wanted to be a
singer.
And Nonoka, who couldn't see herself.
I was nervous, but I got more nervous.
I was so nervous that I couldn't sing
even though I was looking at the lyrics.
And I was surprised that she was so
cute.
She met the members and regained her
smile.
I want to be able to show my skills and
be a team with the members.
Will their dreams come true on the first
day of the GUST?