Good morning everyone. I'm Fujita Airi
of Crown Pop.
Today I would like to show you my
morning routine.
I'm Yuzuki Ichikawa, a candy flash.
We're close friends.
I'm putting Purikura on my phone.
He still looks sleepy.
Good morning.
I wear glasses at home.
I wear glasses, but I've never shown my
glasses to my fans.
And my eyes get smaller.
My eyes are very sharp.
So I've been trying to avoid showing my
glasses.
Today is a morning routine.
I'm going to show you my glasses.
I've been wearing my glasses for a while
since I woke up.
I usually wear my glasses with the
hashtag FUJITA AIRI or KURAPO KAWAII.
Please tweet me.
This bracelet is from my mother.
I usually wear a watch that my mother
gave me.
I'm going to show you my new glasses.
I'm going to return my glasses.
I think so.
I'm going to the sink with a comb and a
contact.
It's still a little bit of a mess.
First, I'm going to brush my teeth
towards the sink.
I'm so sleepy.
I wonder if it's okay to show this.
I'll show you something special.
I'll change my glasses to contacts.
I think everyone is now like,
I'm like FUJITA AIRI.
I'm combing my hair.
I'm going to do skin care and makeup
from here.
First, I'll wash my face.
Then I'll put on some lotion and lotion.
I always do skin care before makeup.
I'm doing a massage right now.
I'll put on the lotion and take the
swelling off in the morning.
Especially around the eyes.
I'm doing a massage.
And I started makeup.
First of all, I'm doing base makeup.
This is a cheek.
I got this cheek from my member Tanaka
Saho.
I've been using it for a long time.
This is a highlight.
I got this from my school friend.
I'm not good at changing my makeup, so I
use pink brown for a while.
Curl your lashes.
Apply mascara.
I like to apply mascara long.
So I'm more conscious of long than
volume.
Draw a line like a drooping eye.
Apply lipstick.
This is the end.
It's done.
I'm hungry, so I'll have breakfast.
I usually eat bread for breakfast.
Sometimes I eat leftover food.
Today I'm going to put butter on it,
bake it, and eat it with jam.
I wonder what I'm going to put on it.
There are days when cream cheese is
added to honey.
But there are days when you put eggs on
it.
There is.
I'm going to bake bread with a toaster.
I'm waiting for the bread to be baked.
It smells good.
It's good.
The bread was hot.
It's a nice color.
I'm going to apply strawberry jam.
I'm going to shoot a morning routine
video.
I was very happy when I heard that
story.
I saw a lot of YouTubers doing morning
routines.
I wanted to do it.
But I don't have a chance to show it to
everyone.
I was very happy.
It's delicious.
And I can't stop eating while eating.
Basically, I'm moving.
Before going to bed.
I go to college.
I'm taking a break between classes.
I'm always eating.
I'm done eating.
Thank you for the meal.
I often post this pajama.
I think there are many people who have
seen it because I wear this pajama after
taking a bath.
I'm going to change clothes now, so wait
a minute.
Thank you for waiting.
I have a job today.
So I'm going to prepare for it.
I'm going to take my time.
I wear this watch.
I choose accessories.
Which one is better?
I'm going to put the sweets in.
I always carry sweets with me.
It depends on the day.
Put it in.
I'm going.
I arrived at the work place.
I'm going to work with the members.
I played a game at the Tokyo Game Show.
I couldn't go out today because of my
health condition.
I'm a 4 member group.
We are 5 members.
We have a meeting before the show.
Before that, we read the script.
We read it through the members.
And we eat sweets.
I brought some snacks, but I have to put
them in the dressing room.
I always eat these snacks.
And when I go to an event, I sometimes
sign like this.
Basically, Rina and I write our group
name.
I'm eating deliciously.
It was delicious.
700 gueos
This is the illustration of theawa
bridge
filling by hand
And I have a meeting with the staff
while reading the script.
After the meeting, I ate something
salty, so I eat something sweet.
I'm in a meeting with the staff while
reading the script.
And we take pictures for SNS.
And the opening of the third day is the
next generation dance idol unit.
It's the Crown Pop. Thank you.
Good morning, everyone.
I'm the queen of the entertainment
world, Mia Crown Pop.
Thank you.
It's decided. Thank you.
I'm Ai-chan, the queen of the
entertainment world, Fuji-tai.
Please call me Ai-chan.
Thank you.
This is a quiz game that leads the
correct answer while being helped by
fans.
We call the name of the Crown Pop fan,
Mr. Copper.
It was early in the morning, but Mr.
Copper gave us a lot of gifts.
He helped me a lot.
I finished the game safely.
It was fun. I played a game.
It was fun.
How was it?
This is my morning routine.
Report the ganska
Thank you for watching!
What is the reason for the album?
I thought it was the album that my
senior released.
I'm surprised that it's the fourth
album.