K-Kids.
Neo-Media Pro.
Please subscribe to my channel!
The second one is a radio.
Yes, a radio.
Oh, a radio.
I love radio.
Oh, really?
I started listening to radio because I
wanted to spend more time with it after
the pandemic.
I wanted to enjoy various contents, so I
decided to listen to radio.
And I got really into it.
What's your favorite radio show?
I love All Night Nippon.
Oh, here it is.
Whose show is it?
Nobuyuki Sakuma's.
Oh, really?
I love his show.
I listen to his show every week.
What?
I love how he explains his story.
Oh, really?
He talks about the story in order, but I
never get tired of it.
I see.
And at the end, the story ends with a
jingle.
I see.
I love the teamwork with the floor.
Oh, the radio.
I love the freedom of All Night Nippon.
I see.
I listen to the songs of Fuwa-chan, and
I sing along to them.
I listen to the songs of Audrey, and I
talk for 40 to 50 minutes.
I see.
And then I get the title song.
You listen to the songs.
I love how the show changes depending on
my personality.
I buy a radio stick.
A radio stick?
Yes.
It's like a radio set for this fall.
I also buy books written by Japanese
radio writers.
I see.
I read the books that were released
recently.
What kind of radio do you listen to?
I want to be on Tokyo Speak Easy.
Tokyo Speak Easy?
Is that Akimoto-san's radio?
Two people who have something in common
talk on the radio.
I think the radio show is a radio show
where you talk about what you usually
talk about.
I see.
I'm talking about the radio show, and I
fade out and go into the commercial.
I'm talking about the commercial, and
I'm talking about the name of the radio
show.
I really like the radio show where I'm
stealing.
I want to talk to the people I've been
taking care of on Tokyo Speak Easy.
I see.
That's my dream.
There's a radio culture in Osaka, but do
you use it a lot?
I listen to it a lot, but I listen to
All Night Nippon the most.
All Night Nippon?
I listen to the radio show called All
Night Nippon Zero.
I just said Zero!
I first listen to Zero.
Then I listen to Bitter Sweets Samba.
That's amazing.
I'm listening to it.
Let's listen to it.
In front of the Yurukucho.
Let's go to the sacred place.
I'm sorry.
Help me.
It's nice to talk about things you don't
remember.
I don't remember.
This program was brought to you by
Mai Kuwata
Mokobi
Haruna Gyunyu, who brings smiles and
health to the table
Akane
and Kei
Thank you for watching!