Starry Starry
I'll cross time and light up
终于到达了终于
But for the judges speaking, they may
have滞在モマ產生当過 hungry,
or even thinking of
Translated by Releska
It's not a lie, my heart is trembling,
my heart is pounding
Good morning!
Today is our school day with lots of
school
I was doing a E gibt fromubby
Before we go home, we'll go to the lobby
and see the chairs.
Before everyone sees it, I'll show you
the part where I jump.
That's a good one.
I was in the middle.
I was lined up like this.
It's the best.
And I was outside the lobby.
Yeah, it's big.
I was outside the lobby.
I was like this.
I'll take a picture of it.
I want you to make a memory before the
live.
Can you hear me?
Yes, I can.
Did you sleep well?
Yes, I did.
I slept a lot. I woke up at 6.30am.
I was in the meeting at 8.30am.
I looked at the 8 o'clock and I was
like,
Oh my god, it's 8 o'clock!
I screamed.
I said, if you can't see anything, it's
okay.
It was two hours ago.
Two hours ago.
I was like, oh my god, it's 8 o'clock!
My bangs were too short, so I was
embarrassed to show them in front of me.
I'm standing a little longer this time
because I'm going to grow my bangs.
I hope the makeup artist will like it.
So... we only need toahu.
Thank you for watching.
I'll do my best.
I'll go to the office at 3 o'clock.
OK.
With that expression?
It's not yet. It's like 3 o'clock.
Let's sleep. Let's sleep.
If you think like that, you can sleep
anytime.
At 7.45, okay?
Ah, I see.
I was sleeping late.
Yes, you were sleeping late.
I wanted to sleep early.
I always want to have time to relax.
I wake up early.
I have to sleep.
I slept.
Good night.
I forgot to turn on the camera.
What kind of Alrighto videos do you want
for a man rainy daily daily all down to
the sounds of rain morning
I came here last year, so it's a little
nostalgic.
It's a little nostalgic.
This is the costume of Ichan Cafe.
Wow, it's huge!
It's so cool!
Wow!
What is this?
It's below, and not going up..
Now, I want to have a game.
Wow!
Look at this!
So cute!
I feel like I'm growing up.
It's so cute!
Wow, it's so cute!
The stage is huge!
It's so cute!
Hanamichi?
It's like a big festival.
It's like a senior's concert.
Amazing!
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
There are many birds.
Amazing.
That's it!
Wow!
What? So that's our live YouTube...
No....リアルされるなぁ
No......
Thank you for your viewing.
Thank you for watching!
Ah!
This pair is the strongest.
Pretty long.
Thank you for watching!
I'm scared.
It's okay.
The camera is still on.
It's so small.
I'm sorry.
It's cool.
There's a mirror.
I'll take it off.
Thank you.
It's huge!
Amazing.
I don't know if I'm feeling it or not.
I'm starting to feel strange.
It's not like I'm feeling strange.
Wow! I want to go inside.
I want to go inside.
It's like a countdown.
Yeah, I just updated the story.
It's a countdown.
It's 16 o'clock today.
There's a countdown to see how many
hours it takes until 16 o'clock.
It's been 60 hours.
What? No way.
There's only half an hour left.
What?
Isn't it really crazy?
It's really worth listening to.
Thank you for watching!
Really?
I don't know.
I'm not sure if I can do it.
If we do this for another 6 hours, we'll
be under a spell.
I can't do it.
I want you to do your best, so
I think it's fun, but it's only 6 hours.
I think I should do it now.
I'll go to that table.
No way.
Do it.
I'll be scolded.
I can't do it.
Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching.
So thank you
This feeling will never stop!
Please subscribe to my channel!
It just came to me!
phone!
study with me?
Your voice 13其
I'm Suppin
It's Hito-chan
She's tall
Hito-chan, over there
I'm the real Hito-chan
She brought her costume
It's Hito-chan
She's the one who does the encore
I want to be the last one
I'm Su-da-yaki
I forgot! I forgot!
Which one is that?
Su-da-hi-to-ka
Su-da-yaki or Su-da-hi-to-ka? Which one?
Su-da-yaki
I'm Su-da-yaki
Su-da-yaki is still alive.
Su-da-yaki
I know
Today is Makuhari day. I'll do my best.
I'll do my best.
I'm Tsuji no Hangyodon.
Thank you for watching.
I'm so happy.
Kanamin's face is so big.
You're right.
It's so cute.
Kanamin, come here.
Kanamin?
Kanamin!
Your face is smaller.
You should eat more.
You look like Kanamin.
I've been eating a lot lately.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Good day.
I'm sorry.
Please give me a thumbs up.
Thumbs up.
I'm not lying.
This is the real thing.
Angelo.
It's a GVIA.
I'm not lying.
暗크로맨欲しいお仕事につきたいんです。 He is a super
necrotic person.
It's written as Aki.
I don't want to.
It's funny.
Bye bye.
I made it with Y有一半 Y一半
Thank you for watching.
Under this逆ぐ時の
ة
Write
OSS
I'm not sure if I should sing this part.
I don't know.
I'll sing this part.
Today is 22nd of October.
Hello.
We are Makuhari Messe.
We are here on the same day.
Hello.
It's amazing.
Before Makuhari,
we go to the forest and sleep.
That's amazing.
Thank you.
What makes you feel most comfortable?
I'm very comfortable.
The last 30 seconds of the song.
What do you do?
Is it a question of taste?
I'm Julia.
I don't know if I'm going to change the
song.
I don't know how many times I've
changed.
I want to say that and this.
I don't know why, but I think everyone
is really curious.
I was sitting for about 3 hours.
I'm really scared.
I'm sorry.
I should have put on a cushion.
That's right.
I thought I'd never give up my own life.
I'm going to write it on my own.
I don't want to hurt my butt, so please
use the family.
That's why.
That's right.
I know.
It's going to be a long time, but don't
get tired.
Please be careful.
I'm not tired.
I've been doing it for a while, so I'm
not tired.
I want you to do it.
It's fast. It's fast.
It's fast.
It's already 11 o'clock.
11 o'clock.
It's fast. It's fast.
It's really fast.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
And this is the first time I've been
interviewed.
I've been interviewed before.
How many interviews did you do?
How is it?
How do you feel?
I'm happy.
The moment I came in, I could see the
scenery.
If someone starts crying, everyone will
cry.
I'm going to cry.
I'm going to wear a uniform and go.
If you cry like that, it's over.
Don't cry.
If you look at the mirror, you'll cry.
I'm not that nervous yet.
I'm not nervous at all.
I'm nervous.
I'm relieved.
I'm prepared.
I'll do my best.
I'm nervous.
By the way...
I'll be giving out these to the viewers.
These are for 3 people.
And I got this from Kiria-chan.
I got a ticket! Thank you!
I'll go get it!
I'll put the 4 cards somewhere in the
audience and hide them.
I don't know if they'll find them.
I hope they'll take them home as
presents.
It's stuck!
I'll put them on!
Let's go!
I hope they'll take them home.
I'll put them here.
I can't see them.
I've finished preparing.
I hope they won't come home.
I'll be looking forward to it!
They watch us from the front flips.
It's a weird focus that movement does.
Today, therefore, there were stories
behind.
After the performance
They had me interview them.
Ah!
The last challenge.
Wait a minute.
Everything I've done is over.
All you have to do is wait for the real
thing.
That's right.
That's bad.
Good luck.
Bye bye.
How is it?
Is it a legend?
How is it? Is it cute?
Thank you for watching.
How is it?
I got it as a gift
It's cute
There are two語anaíers too
But there was no orange
There are three more
Oh, it's delicious
Because it's cute today
Is it cute?
cute
I will eat the next meal
I willtime
I want to eat
but they are in no mood
I love you.
I'm happy because I can't climb.
Grape
I tried to make it honey lemon.
How about honey lemon?
It's a jelly that I've never tried
before.
I wonder if it's okay.
I'm surprised that I can't do it.
Don't pull me!
I wonder why?
When I smile, it seems like the world is
shining
I can relax by turning the umbrella
Otherwise, I can't walk
Someone is crying somewhere
I wonder if it's cold to wet my body
somewhere again
I'm sure someone is crying somewhere
I want to share my feelings with you
just a little bit
I don't know what's in front of me yet
Look, let's go anywhere
Goodbye Goodbye, Thank you for yesterday
The cityscape after the rain is colored
I'm going to draw the pieces of the
future on my broken heart's canvas
Will you guide me?
Goodbye, goodbye to me from yesterday
The cityscape after the rain is
sparkling
My heart is like a spring
I play the sound of the rain
I play the piano at 2 o'clock
Goodbye, goodbye to me from yesterday
The rain has stopped, the streetlamps
are sparkling
My heart is like a flower, I'm wearing a
rainbow dress with a tear-stained face
La la la la la la la...
La la la la la la la
Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching一直会 surtout