Thank you for watching!
It's time to get in the Zoom into the
Raid CityCamerun!
Do you know why we're going to do this?
Thank you for watching!
Gracefully
Good morning
Yahho
Today
Is the day of the migratory line
Thank you for watching until the end.
See you next time!
Before going back to Thailand, we went
to a place called lobby.
We went to a place where we could jump
before everyone saw us.
It was so cool.
We were like, wow, that's so cool.
We were so excited.
You can see that Brother actually did it
tonight.
I hope you can hear me.
I can hear you.
Did you sleep well?
Yes, I did.
I slept so much. I woke up at 6.30am.
And we were going to meet at 8.30am.
I was like,
I saw 8 people at once.
I was like, wow, 8 people at once!
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's okay if you get sick.
It was two hours ago.
I was sick.
Did you get sick?
Thank you for watching.
My bangs were too short, so I was
embarrassed to show my bangs.
I'm standing a little longer this time
to extend it.
I think it would be better if the makeup
artist did it.
I'm satisfied.
Perfect condition.
That's it.
Thank you for watching.
I woke up at 3.30am.
I woke up.
I woke up suddenly.
I said,
No, it's not.
I woke up.
I was like, let's sleep.
I went to sleep and I turned on the
alarm at 7.45.
You were sleeping until the last minute?
Yes, I was sleeping until the last
minute.
I was sleeping late, so I was like,
let's sleep until the last minute.
I always want to have time to sleep, so
I wake up early, but I have to sleep.
I slept for a while.
I slept until the last minute.
I'm going to get a head massage.
I came here yesterday, so I feel
nostalgic.
This is the costume of Ichan Cafe.
Wow, it's huge!
It's so cool!
This is amazing!
It's so funny!
Please come in.
Look at this.
Wow!
Wait, this is amazing.
So cute.
Was it cute?
I feel like I'm a kid.
So cute.
It's on the ground.
Wow.
It's so cute.
So cute!
The stage is huge!
I'm getting a nosebleed.
It's like a big festival.
I see.
It's like a senior's concert.
It's true.
Amazing.
There it is.
It's a sign.
Good morning.
Thank you very much.
There are many birds.
Wow, amazing.
It's fantastic.
Our concert?
It's a camera!
It's small.
There's a mirror.
I can check my bangs.
It's huge.
It's amazing.
I don't know if it's real or not.
It's like a strange feeling.
Wow, I want to go inside.
It's like a day.
I just updated the story.
It's a countdown.
It's a meeting at 16 o'clock today.
There's a countdown until 16 o'clock.
It's been 60 minutes.
What? Really?
It's only been half an hour.
What?
Isn't it really bad?
It's really bad.
What?
Is it a lie?
I don't know.
It's 4 o'clock.
It's really bad.
If we do it for another 6 hours, we'll
be under a spell.
It's gonna be like this.
I think it's gonna be okay because
you've put it on and we're on stage.
There's only 6 hours left.
I think we should do it now.
I'll go to the audience seat.
No way.
I'm gonna go to the audience seat.
I'm gonna be late.
die
Can you hear me?
I can't stop this feeling
I want to tell you that I want to live
with you forever
I want to live with you forever
And we're dancing, changing the goal
Two of us
We're not laughing
We're the highlight girls
Because we want to Vietnam
We're
2 yet
PEnto
and repo
When we act different
we want to be
alone
Ohhh
I'm a real person.
She brought a costume!
It's Hitachan!
It's Hitachan of the alcohol!
I want to be the sun!
I'm Sudayaki.
I forgot!
Which one is it?
It's Hitachan.
Sudahitoka.
Sakae Aki or Sudahitoka.
Which one?
It's Sakae Aki.
This is pretty good.
Let's do our best today.
I'll do my best.
It's Tsuji's Hangyodon.
It's Kanamin's.
Kanamin's hair is so long.
It's different, isn't it?
Kanamin?
Kanamin's hair is so long.
Kanamin!
It's similar to yours.
You should eat more.
I've been eating a lot lately.
It's similar to yours.
It's like a Han-gyo-dong.
This is Julia's pouch.
Please open it.
It's a Han-gyo-dong.
It's a good one.
This is the real one.
It's a Han-gyo-dong.
It's a Julia's pouch.
It's a cute one.
It's a cute Han-gyo-dong.
It's a Han-gyo-dong.
It's written in the tape that it's
autumn.
Bye bye.
Good morning!
I'm going to do my hair.
I'm going to do my makeup.
A farewell kiss to youaki.
Thank you very much!
Kotoriatyoo
Thank you.
I'm not alone in my tears
Today is October 22nd, the day of the
Bakari message!
It's amazing, right? It's like we're
going to do a burrito or something in
front of the Bakari.
What is it?
I'm so happy!
What are you most worried about?
I'm most worried about the bike.
What?
I'm worried about the last impression of
the girl.
What are you all going to do?
I'm worried about the 30-minute story.
It's all on the screen.
I'm Julia.
Julia, I'm going to show you.
It's getting longer.
I don't know if I'm going to ride it.
I'm more angry than everyone else.
I want to say this. I've said too much.
I'm getting emotional.
I know.
Everyone was surprised when I said that.
I was sitting in the back for about
three hours and it was really...
I got a little sad.
It's time for the puffins to be
cushioned.
Oh, yeah.
That's what the blanket for.
I thought it was over.
I'm going to write it in the story.
My butt might hurt, so please use the
puffins.
That's why you did it.
It's going to be a long time, but don't
get tired.
Please use it.
I'm going to stick it on.
It's been 16 hours since the opening.
It's fast.
It's already been 11 minutes.
It's a Japanese version of the song.
And this is the first time we've been
interviewed.
I think it's a Japanese version.
It's not an interview.
There was a person who was interviewed.
How many people were there when we were
interviewed?
How is it?
It's like a first time.
I wonder how it feels.
It's a little bit of a shock.
The moment I got my hands on it, I could
see the kiss.
If someone starts crying, I'll cry.
I'll just take a look at the reaction.
I'll take a look at the reaction.
I can't believe it.
I'm going to cry.
If you cry for a centimeter, it's over.
Don't cry.
I'm going to cry when I see that.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'll do my best.
I haven't kissed much yet.
I'm not sure if I can kiss you.
I'm a little nervous because it's 5
o'clock.
I'm going to do my best.
I'm going to live with peace of mind.
I'll do my best.
I'm going to do my best.
I'm going to work out now.
I'm not tired at all.
I'm going to do a morning workout.
I'm going to show you my abs.
This is the third time.
구 snooze
I'm going to go now.
I'm going to put these four stickers on
the seats.
I don't know if they'll be found.
I hope they'll be a present for me.
It's stuck.
I'm going to put them on.
I hope they'll be a present for me.
I can't see them.
I'm ready to go home.
I'm looking forward to seeing them.
I'm going to put them on.
I can't reach you
I have a project called a hidden camera
interview.
Before the actual performance,
I'll be asked to do a little bit of a
cover.
Oh, cool.
And then I'll be asked to do a little
bit of a cover.
We've finished everything we've done.
Now we just have to wait for the actual
performance.
That's right.
It's going to be crazy.
Bye bye.
How is it?
Is it pretty?
Is it cute?
How is it?
I got a mark.
It's cute.
Grape and honey lemon.
Two kinds.
I got orange.
But I didn't get orange.
Thank you for watching.
You're cute.
I'm going to the right.
I'm going to the left.
I love you!
I tried to make it with honey lemon.
I wonder what it tastes like.
I've never tried honey lemon before.
It's a jelly.
Is it working?
Is it okay?
I've tried honey lemon.
I'll try it.
It's so funny.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I wonder why? When I smile, it seems
like the world is shining
I can relax by turning the umbrella,
otherwise I can't walk
I'm sure someone is crying somewhere,
I'm sure someone is crying somewhere, I
want to share my feelings with you
I don't know the scenery in front of me
yet, let's go anywhere
Goodbye Goodbye
Thank you for yesterday
The cityscape after the rain is colored
I painted a fragment of the future on
the canvas of my broken heart
It will lead me
I can say it now, the reason for my
tears
When I get lost, I immediately remember
Even if it rains, I'll smile
Look, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye to me from yesterday
The cityscape after the rain is
sparkling
As if my heart is a clear pattern
I play the sound of the rainbow
And play the rainbow piano
Goodbye, goodbye to me from yesterday
The town after the rain is sparkling
As if my heart is a clear pattern
I dry my tears
And wear the rainbow dress
Please subscribe to my channel!