Thank you for watching us today.
Thank you.
I haven't had a chance like this in a
long time, so I have a lot of questions.
I moved to this place again.
I've been waiting for a long time.
I think you like manga very much.
I'm going to teach you the best sign.
It's difficult.
I really want to know.
The more I read, the more difficult it
is to decide the best 3.
It's a genre.
It's really hard to put a course on it.
It's difficult, but it's difficult.
I'll ask you.
I'm trying to make tea.
I was also in charge of One Piece.
That's really amazing.
The reason I read manga first was that I
was reading One Piece at my friend's
house while my friend was playing games.
I read manga at my friend's house
without playing games.
I thought manga was so interesting, so I
started reading manga.
One Piece is still very interesting.
I love One Piece.
I heard that you can know the ending of
One Piece by watching the video.
That's true.
Yes, I think so.
Oh my god!
I know about One Piece!
That's crazy.
I'm a big fan of One Piece, so I wanted
to read it without knowing it.
But yes.
How long did you work on it?
I was in charge of the original work
from the scene where the dress rose's
grandmother appears to the scene where
Sanji appears in the Hall Cake Island.
I think Japanese people should read One
Piece, especially if they are not best
3.
I want you to read it.
I'm doing a lot of free trial reading,
so even if you have a lot of numbers or
don't have much money, I want you to
read it if you have a smartphone.
Can I ask you two more questions?
I'm going to read it without letting you
go.
I'm re-watching the serialized HUNTER X
HUNTER.
I think you can see it if you read
Miyazaki's work.
I made a lot of parodies.
I'm sure you can do it.
I think it's a problem because I put out
too much.
I'm always nervous.
I'm editing it.
HUNTER X HUNTER is a great manga.
I'm a generation, so I love HUNTER X
HUNTER.
It took me about 3 to 5 minutes to read
the first page of HUNTER X HUNTER last
week.
Last week, the exchange of lines was
amazing.
I was surprised.
I was surprised that I could read all
the lines.
It's interesting.
It's amazing to be able to read it.
If you imitate a new writer, it's the
same.
It's all the same.
It's amazing.
It's like a novelist.
HUNTER X HUNTER
I love HUNTER X HUNTER.
I've been to Togashi-tenma.
I love Togashi-sensei's work.
I love HUNTER X HUNTER.
I can't decide the last one.
There are a lot of jump works.
SLAM DUNK, DRAGON BALL, NARUTO, MOHAI
BLEACH, etc.
There are a lot of works that I like.
It's unfair.
I can't decide the last one.
I've been to Togashi-tenma again.
I love HUNTER X HUNTER.
I went to Nodame-tenma.
I love Nodame-tenma.
I read SLAM DUNK again for the movie.
I'm very interested in it.
There was a basketball.
I was interested in it.
There are a lot of balls of some sport.
There are various things.
I love the green MAKIBAO.
I took a video of Miyazaki-sensei's
video.
Tsunomaru-sensei praised Miyazaki-
sensei.
I also read Togashi-tenma.
I read Togashi-tenma.
I love green MAKIBAO.
There are a lot of works that everyone
loves.
I love MAKI-chan.
I want everyone to read it.
MAKIBAO was on TV animation.
It's the best.
It's the best from the opening.
Run! Run! Run!
I love MAKIBAO.
I love a lot of manga.
It was a question that was the best to
ask the manga editor.
Please subscribe to our channel.
I don't want to say it.
I'm the type of person who gets drunk
and tries to say it, but I've never said
it.
I've never said it even once.
I've never said the Japanese character
for One Piece.
You've never said the Japanese
character?
I don't think I want to talk about it.
I want to read it as a reader.
I feel like that.
But even if you know the content, it
changes completely when you make it into
a manga.
Even if you know this is going to
happen, if you read it in the scene,
you'll be able to write it 100 times
more interesting.
I can enjoy reading a completely new
scene.
I'm sure it's a shame if I let you know.
I feel like I don't want everyone to
read it without knowing it.
I don't want to say anything.
If you were to edit this video, what
would you do?
That's crazy.
You mean, to your parents and siblings?
Yes, I've never told them.
I'm in danger.
I shouldn't be important.
I want to tell them about my good
points.
I'm like, look at this.
I should read this part again.
I see.
When I'm in the middle of a scene, I get
nervous.
I see.
I get nervous by myself.
Do you read the world's theories?
I don't read them.
But I meet a lot of people who have
different theories.
I see.
I read a lot of theories.
I finish the video with a smile.
I see.
It's funny.
Please subscribe to my channel.
When I first read Bangman, I had a
strange asseption I had for it.
Like something had changed in the
editors, or when almost anything seemed
like a coffee,
or made me successful.
I wonder if those things still exist?
Backman seems quite close to my 예
But what I wrote in the book is quite an
editorial book.
Of course, there are many places where
the guest's food is dramatized, but I
think the flow is quite similar.
However, there is a saying that if you
admit it as a newbie, you will give out
a drink.
That's not the case.
I didn't have that.
I don't have that much.
I don't have anything like, I'm thirsty,
I'm thirsty, I'll give it out if I'm in
a hurry.
On the contrary, I was conscious of
this.
I wrote it like that in Bakuman, so I
couldn't give it out.
I thought I had talent, so I was shocked
when I first brought it to the writer in
charge of it.
I was told that there was no such rule.
It's different for each person.
That's right.
Of course, I don't have Bakuman
knowledge.
It's not all of it.
But it's like Bakuman.
I'm full of dreams.
The writers are working hard like that.
The editing department may not be so
cool.
I'm a little more.
Do you know what it's like to see the
editing department?
It's a little more messy.
The old men are working hard.
That's right.
Finally, this is related to the main
character.
Is there a manga you are most interested
in and would recommend?
I'm looking forward to it.
What manga do you want to recommend?
Of course, Roboco.
I'm sure it's Roboco.
Except Roboco.
Except Roboco?
I can think of a lot of manga from
various magazines.
But if I were to say Jump,
I like the manga Sakamoto Days,
and I like the manga Aonohako.
It's my personal hobby.
I forget that I'm an editor of Jump
every week,
and I think it's interesting as a
reader.
Of course, there are manga that are
becoming more and more famous.
Those two are probably the works of
teachers who will be active in the
future.
I'm very curious.
Of course, the first one is Roboco.
The first one is Roboco.
In Jump, there are many jokes.
I think it's easy for elementary school
students to read.
What is your target audience?
I think so.
I think it's interesting for elementary
and middle school students to read it.
It's a low target from Jump.
Roboco, which has a high rate of
overwhelming elementary school students'
support.
I think so.
If you say, I'm a fan,
or if you say, my son or daughter is
calling me,
there are many people who are about 10
to 15 years old.
I'm running alone in my teens.
I love Seiki Matsuri Idanen Takeshi.
I love Seiki Matsuri Idanen Takeshi and
One Piece.
The best three are too deep.
I'm sorry.
I heard a lot of valuable stories.
Thank you very much.
I will continue to support you.
Thank you.
Please watch the anime.
What is your dream?
I have been doing idol activities since
I was a child.
I think it's a job that gives people
dreams.
I have a dream of becoming a manga
artist.
I am now because I am working hard with
various characters in the manga.
I will continue to work hard with manga.
Jump is not only a manga, but also a web
novel called Jump Plus.
I am looking for a body, and I am
currently copying.
With Ai-chan
I am looking for a body, and I am
currently copying.
I completed it with the picture of the
monster No. 8 Spy Family left-handed.
There are so many interesting manga in
the world, so I would like to support
the main story and Jump Plus in
parallel.
In the main story, of course, the story
I talked about before is Akane, but the
Ichinoseikei, which started at the New
Year's Festival recently, has started.
The author of the copy I mentioned
earlier is written, but what is this
starting method from the first episode?
I'm drawn in! It's the second episode
and I'm drawn in even more!
It's a manga that I'm really looking
forward to, so I'd like everyone to take
a look.
Oh, I'm looking forward to it! Of
course, Roboco is also!
Roboco's anime, original manga, and
manga are also interesting, so please
take a look!