This week's Ebichutastas is a new year's
edition of Ebichutastas News
The news that was broadcasted on TV
shows
will be
It's a big news
What is the news that will be a big
news?
Ebichutastas Start
Ebichutastas
Add various things to private Ebisu
Middle School
Ebisu Justice
This program is provided by the sponsor
you see
Thank you for watching
We'll be your hosts!
Thank you!
Ta-da!
Today, we're at Odaiba Fuji TV's One Gun
Studio!
Thank you!
Hi, let's introduce ourselves.
I'm Takiuto, the shooting star.
And I'm Chuuya, the shining star.
Chuuya, Chuuya.
I'm the rock star.
And...
Everyone watching on TV, can you hear my
high tension?
I'm the rock star here, Kaiki Ogata.
She's using a new camera.
She's using the second camera.
I'm nervous.
So what are you going to do today?
Today's theme is...
News that makes you feel like you're in
the middle of the night.
What is news?
I want to introduce various news that
have happened in the show so far.
It happened so fast.
Did you have any news recently?
News?
I was walking with my friend.
We were saying goodbye.
Goodbye?
I was walking with my friend.
I said bye bye.
I was walking like this.
I was like this to a big brother.
You were facing the camera.
I went there and went like this.
What is this?
I was happy.
I got along with my friend for the first
time.
I got along with my friend.
What?
That's how you hit me
So today, you're going to introduce this
kind of news?
Yes, in 2015, just a little more
December
So, this is the 10 big news that Ebichu
decides
I'm going to look back on the events
that remained in my memory this year
I see
There were many things
Ebichu Fastas started in April this year
The year has come to an end, so we will
reveal the big news of this year
Ebichu Fastas 10 big news is going to be
announced
What kind of news was nominated?
We will announce the nominated news, so
please decide what it is
So, Ebichu 10 big news
First of all, here it is
First of all, this
It's true
The
Shuku Ebichu Research Unit Sakura Ebichu
is born
The audition was held nationwide and 5
people were selected
Sakura Ebichu audition was held
nationwide for the first time
Out of about 10,000 applicants, 5 people
were selected
In August, the first live performance
was held at the Tokyo Idol Festival
Did everyone get the chance to meet
Sakura Ebichu?
Yes, several times
By the way, have you ever had a lesson
together?
No
I want to
I want to give a presentation
As expected of Mayuma
What kind of presentation do you want to
give to Sakura Ebichu?
First, I want to give a presentation
from a low place
From a low place in terms of price
I will continue to raise it, so it will
be a little harder from the beginning
I will make it a little bit
I said to make it a little bit
It's like a pet
Everyone of Sakura Ebichu, please look
forward to Mayuma's presentation
And here is the middle picture
But after all, the role of the
You can say the names of all the members
of Sakura Ebichu
That's natural
How many times have you raised it?
I'm taking it up
Are you checking it?
I know
Because the other day, when I was in the
middle of the show
We're going to watch the live together
First, we're going to watch the live
together
We're going to watch it
So, when you watch the live together,
you'll know
The name of the members of Sakura Ebis
will be said in order from the left
It's boring, but I know everything
From the left
Momoyo
Momoyo is your sister's name
Why is your sister's name?
I'm not sure
Sorry, I'm sorry
You're not allowed
Kai
I said it
It's natural
Can you say it?
I can say it from the left
Kai is a bit more relaxed
Can Kai really say the name of the
members of Sakura Ebis?
Misato Sakurai
Full name
Mizuhasa
Is Mizuhasa the name of the members?
It's only Mizuhasa's name
I see
From there?
I know
Riju Murahoshi
Ayame Kawase
And finally, Sora Akane
It's not a problem if you say it all
You'll know if you watch it normally
I don't have enough love
I love everyone
Really?
I don't like it
I like everyone
Yamano Miyu san too
Next is Ebichu Tastas 10th News
Next is Ebichu News
Shogi Gini, Kobayashi Kaho and the head
of the boat festival
1st place
This is 1st place?
It's too early
Let's review it
When we were doing the trial
I said something has to do with it
The trial of Ebichutas, which pursued
various suspicions of the members
The suspicion that was put on Kobayashi
It's not clear what you hate
What kind of suspicion is it?
A powerful testimony was obtained from
the
The suspicion that was put on Kobayashi
It was a little bit of a fish party, but
I was a little bit of a bad person at
that time.
What does this mean?
It was like it was useless to do it in
front of you.
I was so embarrassed that I took it to
the ramen shop.
You want me to feel that way?
At this time, the principal felt the
most pitiful.
Then, another testimony from Yasumoto
The principal noticed that I was going
to eat ramen with me.
I don't like the principal.
Did you hear the president?
I see.
I don't like food, but I don't like the
principal.
That's true.
So, this time, we asked the principal
himself.
What was the principal's real situation?
As I explained now, I said I wanted to
eat ramen.
I said, I'm going to eat ramen, but I
don't like that.
By the way, when you were in court, you
were accused of going to eat ramen with
the principal.
Did you go on a trip?
I haven't been there yet.
You haven't been there yet?
You should have done it earlier.
Everyone has a criminal record.
I haven't done it, but I'll do it.
I'm sure you'll be released from prison.
I'll definitely do it if you get a
criminal record.
What's your name?
I don't like it.
That's right.
I see.
If you say that we are just friends with
each other,
Then, first of all, you have to show
your true feelings to each other
If you are really close to each other,
you can show your true feelings
So, first of all, the two-shot talk
between the principal and Hirota
What should we talk about?
The parade was fun last time
It was fun
The principal is behind Aika
I was looking up the clothes of Aika
The principal is behind every Aika photo
It's so exciting
It's exciting
I'm sorry, I didn't get it on the map
I got it on every photo I saw
It's written on every photo
Thank you very much
It's exciting
I was looking at it a lot
It's okay, you two are okay
Thank you very much
The principal is like a regular in this
store
It's like he's here again
Next, Kobayashi
Let's go
After this, the two-shot talk between
Kobayashi and the principal
Then
What should we talk about?
This atmosphere is dangerous
Kobayashi says that the principal is not
bad friends
What will happen if they talk alone on
the hill?
Is it already started?
It's started
What are you talking about?
Why are you crying?
I'm nervous
You're nervous?
I'm always here
What do you want to talk about?
What kind of ramen do you like?
Ramen? Ramen is miso ramen
Ramen?
I'm nervous
When I was young, I was a little bit
thick
Now my husband is good at soup
I'm not good at thick
Do you cook soup with ramen?
I cook soup with ramen
Will there be a new one?
No, there won't be any.
That's not the main dish.
Here, he notices Kobayashi who likes
gyoza.
He asks this question from the
principal.
There are various gyoza, what kind do
you like?
Grilled gyoza.
The staff who saw it, forced to end.
The
Kobayashi's eyes don't match.
The distance was close.
If we go to eat ramen together, the seat
is about this close.
So you can eat while looking at the
eyes.
I ate ramen while looking at the
principal's eyes.
It's not that close.
Why are you in the front and back?
The next news is
Here is the next news.
Here it is.
The principal of the Gekiyoko BBQ
Project, Magisekyo.
This is the one.
BBQ, Bang Bang Gyoza.
The Ebitutas BBQ held at Nakayama's
daily meeting.
It was a plan of the members to eat.
After eating and eating.
Continue to fool around.
The site is in a situation where there
is no collection.
It was so bad.
Later, the principal was seriously
lectured.
By the way, how did you get angry?
It's okay to be free, but it's too much.
That's not true.
That's in front of everyone.
Here again, the principal appears.
Let's hear the truth of Magisekyo.
Did you get angry?
I was angry.
I was too conscious of the camera.
I thought it was not good.
Did everyone call you?
I was talking to everyone.
Everyone seems to be angry now.
The tone is a little low.
How was it to be angry at the principal
and Nakayama?
I was able to use the good part of the
TASTAS edit.
I thought it was better, so I decided to
do my best next time.
He relied on editing.
Why are you relying on editing now?
I was surprised to hear the sound.
You have to do it with the feeling that
you don't have to edit.
That's right.
Ebichu TASTAS 10th News.
The next person to be nominated is...
Next news is
Yes
Ebichu's sports and brain decision
What is this?
Hoshina was active in the sports
By the way, there was a university
incident
The real number one was Kaiki-san
But the number one that Kaiki-san was
absent was Hoshina
Ebichu's sports meeting in October
Hoshina was the only one to clear 110cm
with a running high jump that all
members competed
She won the championship
In addition, in the relay against
Akagumi and Shirogumi
Akagumi leads the big lead from the
point of view of the third runner
Akagumi Kobayashi and Shirogumi
Hoshina's anchor competition
Fast fast fast
Bunch
How is it?
Amazing
Although she lost, she was still going
up to the next step
Hoshina Mirai
She won the MVP
In addition, in the event of Ebichu plus
university
Even in the Shiritu Ebisu University
entrance exam
Hoshina gave the correct answer
Although she gave the seat of the main
seat to the big Kaiki
Among the members, she was the best
It's Ebichu's brain
By the way, the one with the worst score
was Kashiwagi
As a punishment, she showed her strange
face
Here is the legendary scene
Can you do it?
I can't do it
Thank you very much
She did a strange face, and that's why
she was banned from doing it in the
beginning
That's right, she was banned from doing
it
But my mother praised me
She said that it was very interesting
It was good
I was better at words than my face
You weren't praised for your face
Ebichu plus university's big news
The next nominated person is...
Here is the next news
Here it is
It's the first time on air that it's a
birthday
This is
Koba Yashino's birthday, later on
Yasumoto too
We did it together
We did a surprise birthday celebration
At Ebichutas birthday party
Koba Yashino's birthday and broadcast
date coincidentally overlap
And at that time, it was broadcast from
11.55 at night
In the program, countdown the birthday
of Koba Yashino
At this birthday party, to celebrate
Yasumoto and Koba Yashino with a
surprise
Members came up with various ideas
The two of them were also pranked to
fight
How was it? The prank?
I was caught
I was surprised
I thought it was a prank
I was shocked
It was a prank
Koba Yashino and Yasumoto were
completely fooled by the prank
Actually, before they arrived, they had
a secret rehearsal
Here is the video of that time
What is this?
It's long
What are you doing?
It's too long
It's not like that
I saw it
Stop it
It's not like that
It's like a story
It's like my story
The prank was a little long
Next time, let's do it properly
It's long
Stop it
I'm tired
You don't need this
I have this
You don't need it
It's not used
It's used sometimes
Everyone is making faces
Everyone is here
I wanted to say this before
You have to do it properly
You have to distinguish between what is
used and what is not
What are you talking about?
I'm going to press it
I don't know what it is
The tape is not free
I was doing it
What is this?
I heard you laughing
I'm holding it in
Minocchi laughed
I think it's weird
I don't have time
What is that?
I'm desperate
There is no reason to cut it
It's forced
I'm trying to cut it
Mayaman said, I thought you were like
that
I felt like I was being told seriously
I didn't press it
Do you think the tape is useless?
I don't think so
If you don't do it, it's over
What did I say?
I don't know what you said
What are you saying? I'm scared
The 10 major news of Ebichu Tastas
The next nominated person is
The next case is this
This
Ta-da
The high-end product of Futo-para Takiue
Shinichiro
There was
Futo-para
Ebichu Tastas mini-corner
Matsuno and Kashiwagi's
City tour project
Matsuno Kashiwagi walk
In the middle
The incident occurred at the recycle
shop where one person visited
I don't know what to use
Matsuno Kashiwagi likes it so much
Please ask Takiue
Please buy
No
In the end, he paid 20,000 yen
And bought Takiue
After that, he appeared in the show
As an MVP product of Ebichu Tastas
sports
He appears every time
That day he appeared in the studio again
I still think
It was 20,000 yen when it became cheaper
How much was 20,000 yen?
30,000 yen
30,000 yen became 20,000 yen
If I had more
I think it would have been about 10,000
yen
This
Because it's easy
Normally, it's stuck
30,000 yen is 20,000 yen
It's not cheap
Because there is
Yes
It's not cheap
Then it's 20,000 yen
I came right away
Then sell this at 30,000 yen once
And then go to the store again
Then do the same thing again
That's right
Tastas
Shall we go to sell this?
To that store
So
The project to sell this mysterious face
is currently in progress
Please look forward to it
Next episode of Ebichu Tastas
Ebichu Tastas news second edition
Finally, Ebichu Tastas 10 big news are
out
The ranking is decided
I'm a little sleepy
In addition, the biggest 10 major
announcements in the program history
What the hell
And the person who missed Ebichu Tastas
Good news to the person
Ebichu Tastas is on the Star Dust
Channel, a video streaming site for
school videos.
What's going on?
It's not over yet!
If you want to enjoy more like Nakayama,
you can get Ebichu Tastas for 400 yen a
month.
In addition, there are many exclusive
videos that are not released.
For more details, please search on the
Star Dust Channel.
I don't want that.
This program was brought to you by the
sponsor you see.
I don't want that person.
It's a five-person show.
One, two, three.
I don't want that person.
My guitar will ring today.
That was close.
I said I don't want that person.