This week's Ebichu Tastas is a luck
draw.
The member with the strongest luck will
be decided.
This is the room where the members live.
I sleep with my sister.
I sleep in the same room as my sister.
The unexpected private room is revealed.
Who is the luckiest person?
This is so beautiful.
Ebichu Tastas, start.
100 times the annoying emotion
I'm so into you that I can't bear it
What should I do with the heart of the
chubra bin?
Moratorium Moratorium Moratorium Middle
School Student
Add various things to your private Ebisu
middle school
Ebichu Tastas
This is Ebichu Tastas
This program is provided by the sponsor
you are watching.
Wait a minute, there is a mystery
mountain.
There is a mystery mountain.
I'm putting up a poster of my favorite
Kamen Rider.
Ebichu Tastas has started.
Finally, the microphone is gone.
Maybe it's because we didn't have a day
off.
We don't need that either.
Why?
The person who broke it is here.
The video that broke it last time is
here.
It's here.
So, today is Mayama's day off.
Yes.
She doesn't even fix it.
Even so, you're so loose.
Mayama, do you have anything to ask
today?
Yes, I have a question for everyone.
Did something good happen recently?
You're so rough.
It's like an O.L.
For example, in Mayama,
Mayama, the other day,
I forgot my wallet in the bathroom of
the station building.
But...
Only your wallet?
Only my wallet.
What?
You only put your wallet in the bathroom
of the station building?
I put it there so I wouldn't forget it.
You don't forget it.
It's good that you found your wallet.
I heard some good things about you.
What are you going to do today?
Today, I'm going to decide who is the
luckiest among the members.
The first luck eating contest!
This time, it's all about luck.
Anyone can win.
Yasumoto-san, finally.
I'll win.
You might win.
I might.
But you don't look so lucky.
The luckiest among the members.
We will verify everyone's luck in
various ways.
First of all, we will verify everyone's
luck in various ways.
Who is the luckiest person in the room?
Everyone has their own room's window
drawn in advance.
First, we will check the luck of the
room where the members live.
We will announce the ranking based on
the luck of the room.
Who will check the room of the members?
It's Reina Pliadis!
Nice to meet you!
This mask looks familiar.
Yes, Reina Pliadis is the strongest
fortune teller in Getter's Edda.
She is the most popular fortune teller
with her beautiful face.
Check the members' rooms and see who is
the luckiest.
Let's start with Mayama.
First, check the oldest member, Mayama's
room.
Here it is.
Check the youngest member's room.
What does it say?
Blu-ray disc player.
It's in the room.
It's portable.
You can watch TV.
Is there a pillow on top and bottom?
Yes.
What is this?
It's a hand-reverse or a cotton.
When you watch TV with a pillow, it
looks like this.
It's a hand-reverse.
You can watch TV while you are on a
diet.
This is a poster of Yukari Tamura.
I put a poster of Yukari Tamura, my
favorite.
The curtain is pink.
Wall sticker.
It's a wall sticker.
It's a sticker that you can put on the
wall freely.
It's a room for girls.
Next, check Yasumoto's room.
Please check it.
What is this?
The bed is covered with something.
This is a mountain.
There are a lot of mountains.
Why is it a mystery mountain?
This is a mystery mountain.
This is the closest to the room.
This is a room for cleaning.
Mother put this here.
I put my clothes here.
In the mystery, I put my luggage here.
This is a door.
This is a door, right?
It's a door.
What is this?
So I...
I was so into the fan here.
What is this?
I made a mistake.
It's a big fan.
It's a door.
A door.
It's not organized that much.
It's a mountain.
It's not divided into categories.
It's very appealing.
But it was beautiful when I went there.
I went there.
I cleaned it up.
You went there, Matsumoto.
There was a mountain on the table,
right?
There was a mountain.
I couldn't hold it in.
There is a mountain in the room.
I didn't know.
There was no mountain in my room.
Next is Hirota.
Hirota, who usually wears flashy
clothes,
What kind of room does she live in?
Ta-da!
This is the same as my sister.
Same as my sister.
I see.
Same room.
Pink and green.
I'm green.
There is a chair.
On the bed.
It's a desk.
My father made it for us.
Your father made it.
There is a safe.
Yes, there is a safe.
A safe?
It's not a hotel.
It's my safe.
I don't trust my sister because I put a
safe here.
No, no, no.
I don't know my sister.
But it's pretty clean.
There are few things.
It's in another place.
It's not in my room.
I want to make it clean.
I don't really know my room these days.
What do you mean?
I only go in the dark.
What about electricity?
I don't turn on the lights and jump in.
I only go to bed at night.
So I'm not sure if it's okay.
Where is the entrance to the room?
This way.
If you jump in from here, you'll
definitely step on your sister.
It's okay. I'll jump in.
I sometimes step on my sister.
Is this an idol photo?
Yes, I like idols.
I put a lot of idols' albums in a box.
You don't put it in a box.
I see.
Where is the pillow?
There is no pillow.
Which way are you sleeping?
Well...
Are you okay?
Is the sound okay?
I understood.
Next, let's check Hoshina's room, which
has become a girl's room since April.
Take it out.
It's like you're wearing white.
Yes. It was different until the other
day.
I wanted to change the pattern.
I ordered a lot of white clothes.
I see.
I'll take all the clothes you've used so
far.
I'll put them in the mountain of
Yasumoto's house.
I'm glad you said that.
All the clothes are the same.
The same white clothes.
What are you putting in the box?
Clothes and stuffed animals.
I put books, CDs, DVDs in the bottom of
the box.
My mother likes to watch fursui.
I often watch it on TV.
She said the yellow curtain in the south
is good.
The room is white, yellow and pink.
It's not yellow.
It's cream.
Next, let's check Matsuno's room.
How good is Matsuno who won the women's
team championship in the shrimp?
This is a room with high女子力.
Please show me.
It's small.
This is where you can put a house.
What is this?
It's a big thing, so it's small.
I'm sorry to be so hard to see.
There is a bath and toilet around here.
There is a living room here.
There is a room for my mother and
father.
It's big.
It's the same size as the room.
There is no veranda in my room.
It's like a wooden deck.
It's cool.
It's simple.
What is the color of the ceiling?
White and wood.
Matsuno wrote it like it was clean.
I heard that you can't sleep on the bed.
What do you mean you can't sleep on the
bed?
My mother is sad.
I'm scared of it.
I can't sleep in my room.
It's not that dirty that you can't
sleep.
I heard that the room is messy.
I cleaned up the mess.
You cleaned up the mess.
You're not drawing it with a cool look.
You're really beautiful now.
I'm beautiful now.
My mother cleaned up yesterday.
Next, we check out the room of the house
of the housekeeper.
It seems that she made a lot of effort
for this.
Please take care of the housekeeper.
Oh, it's good.
It's good.
The bed is pink.
The carpet is pink.
It's thin.
The shelf is four-story.
This is four-story.
This is a tiger.
It's like a big white tiger.
It's the one taken by the UFO cat.
The one taken by the UFO cat?
How big is it?
It's about this big.
It's quite big.
It's big.
What is this on the third floor?
There are goods.
It's a doll of Yamada.
Is it a triple three?
When I took the triple three, my neck
was like this.
It's a bag.
It's like this.
By the way, how is the inside of the
closet?
Is it neatly organized?
It's a dark world.
It wasn't this beautiful.
I'll tell you.
Please tell us.
To be honest, it's...
It took more than 10 hours to clean
this.
10 hours?
A mountain family?
A mountain family.
A big mountain was here.
Island.
There was an island here.
There were islands except for the bed.
It was all solid.
Now it's like this.
I cleaned it up yesterday.
I couldn't sleep last night because it
wasn't my room.
Next, we check Kobayashi's room.
Is there anything in Kobayashi's room?
Ready, go!
Ta-da!
It's clean.
There are many green things.
I like green.
Yellow, green, and orange.
There are green bed sheets.
The bed sheet is green.
I like green.
Bed sheets?
There is a big bed sheet in the living
room.
Kobayashi-kun has a bed sheet.
I'm not a bed sheet.
When I eat, there is a dining table.
I usually sleep on the bed sheet.
There are two beds.
There is a window.
I sleep on the top and my sister sleeps
on the bottom.
Basically, the older sister sleeps on
the top.
Originally, the room was the same as the
older brother's room.
The older sister sleeps on the top, so I
sleep on the top at night.
Please take her home.
She laughs too much.
It's not a woman.
You are very fast to invite her home.
I'm having a lot of fun today.
It's a little rough.
You don't go to the mountains.
I don't go to the mountains.
There are many Kobayashi.
Kobayashi?
There are many wild animals.
It's not a mountain.
It's a mountain level.
It's a forest level.
In terms of ranking, Kobayashi,
mountain, island.
Kobayashi, mountain, island.
It's a mountain level.
The last is NAKAYAMA.
I can't imagine what kind of room she
usually lives in.
What kind of room does she live in?
She lives in a house like a cardboard.
I imagine it.
Then.
It's fast.
The color of the wall is white and pink
flowers.
The wall paper.
This is a dance.
She wrote a dance.
This is my room half a year ago.
This is the room of the future forecast.
The room of the future forecast.
What is the future forecast?
I used to have my own bed.
There was a TV here.
I gave this to my brother.
I have been using cardboard for half a
year.
This is the room of the future forecast.
This man will come from now on.
This is the room of the shrimp.
Do you have a shrimp poster?
I don't have a poster.
I put this poster on the desk and study
on it.
When did you put this poster on the
desk?
This poster was put on the family's
house in 2013.
I study on everyone's faces.
You study on everyone's faces.
How much do you decorate the stuffed
animal zone?
I decorate it.
I put it in a garbage bag.
Is it a big burning garbage?
I put my favorite things on the floor.
I put it on the floor to protect the
garbage bag.
This is a compact.
By the way, you said that you like
watching the stars.
I like watching the stars in the car.
You don't like stars in the car now.
I like watching the stars in Tokyo.
I like watching the stars in the sky.
I like watching the shooting stars in
the plane on my way home from Taiwan.
The story is a story of shooting stars
seen from the plane.
Please reproduce the story.
Oh, my God! Please change seats.
Nakayama is like a giant.
No, I'm not. He said, please change
seats gently.
Oh, he said that.
It's his arm.
It's not funny if you don't do that.
That's right. It's more interesting than
you.
I thought Nakayama would teach me how to
laugh.
I was raised to be such a monster.
The room check is over.
Based on this information, Mr. Priaris
is the
water purification judge.
Who is the luckiest?
The ranking announcement will be later.
Ebichu, the narrow path to a lyricist.
This project aims to adopt new songs.
The project that Ebichu will challenge
to write.
前回
I want to write lyrics, but the theme
hasn't been decided yet.
To make a song, the theme is first
discussed.
From Hirota.
縫う マトメ 的な いい!
全然知ってても意味ないけど 誰かに言いたくなるような
豆知識をズラーってまとめた曲みたいな
メンバーに指示された 広田の案をもとに 何をまとめるかを決める方に
And tonight, the theme of the poem is
finally decided.
例えば まとめ
For example, let's say that the theme is
to summarize.
For example, there are different
processes.
In this process, everyone is worried.
It seems that it can be summarized by
adding it.
This is good.
It seems that I have entered the world
of the graduation album.
It's good.
It's romantic.
And?
In summary, the theme is the history of
the graduation album.
This is the theme of the poem.
And finally, the theme is decided.
And?
Ready, set...
The theme of the lyrics is the members'
history!
And so, the members' history has been
decided!
It's all been decided!
Amazing!
The history of the Ebichu members.
What kind of history will be created
with this theme?
Please look forward to it!
I'm Yamashita Yama.
After this, we will announce the final
results of the water purification test.
Checking the members' rooms with the
water purification test.
Who is the luckiest one among them?
First, the room with the lowest luck,
not the lowest.
The 7th place.
Sensei, the 7th place.
Please announce the 7th place.
The 7th place is...
Matsuno-san.
That's right.
I heard that my parents are around here
or in other rooms.
The 9th place is the place where the
most important person is in the house.
I become a lady here.
The 9th place is the place where the
most important person is in the house.
Generally, the family's biggest pillar
is the best.
It's good for the entertainment, but
Matsuno is likely to become the family's
boss.
So, the result is the 7th place.
I think I have both the power of a lady
and a boss.
You are strong.
Next, the 6th place is the room with the
lowest luck.
Yasumoto-san.
Please don't say that you're glad it's
not the bottom.
It's the bottom.
It's completely full of mountains.
It's not good to say it in a fountain.
Why didn't it become a villa?
Yasumoto-san will be in a pretty good
state of luck from now on.
You can enjoy your work.
If you clean up.
I'm leaving the mountain.
It's good.
Next is the 5th episode of the lucky
room.
It's Kashiwagi.
Island!
It's higher than the mountain.
It's become that way.
It was a room that was so messy that it
could be an island, but the arrangement
of things was connected to the luck up.
Kashiwagi put goods of people who
respect the position of the north star.
This leads to the luck up of work.
Next, the 4th place is...
Kobayashi.
It's a good place.
Even if it's messy, the window on the
south side is the luck up.
The 3rd place is...
Mayama.
The room is well organized.
Surprisingly, it is said that sleeping
in a futon can relieve fatigue.
The rest are the three lucky people.
The second place goes to the lucky room.
It's Hirota.
I'm sorry.
I was told that I can only use it for
sleeping.
Really?
In the bathroom, it is better to
separate the sleeping room and living
space.
It leads to luck.
Sleeping with his sister is also a good
idea for Hirota.
The remaining players are Ungai, Hea,
Ichi and Saikai.
What are the results of the match
between Hoshina and Nakayama?
Please announce the winner.
The winner is...
I'm right!
According to the official website,
Yellow is Hoshina's lucky color.
The curtains are placed in the south.
The windows in the south are connected
to the luck up.
It has the effect of raising luck.
The white furniture is also unique.
It is a space that gives a total
healing.
And finally, the ireland.
Even lower than the ireland of the
mountain.
Unfortunately, the ireland is considered
to be the bottom of the water level.
There is a tremendous cause that lowers
the ireland.
Why?
I had a lot of things to fix.
A lot of things to fix?
It's a stuffed animal, but basically, it
absorbs good luck.
If you want to put it, you should take
good care of it.
You really shouldn't put it on the
floor.
But it's a monster.
You don't need to put it in a garbage
bag to protect it.
I see.
Furthermore, the poster of the shrimp
that Nakayama is using as a substitute,
and the broken humidifier that is not
needed in the room,
unfortunately, was deemed to be a room
with a lot of good luck.
Finally, the teacher gives some advice.
改善!直すすぐに直せるポイントなので。
俺どうする?中山今日帰って。
今日?今日はとりあえず寝る。
次回は、ウンダメシ選手兼後半戦。
さまざまな試練が待ち受ける。
妖怪みたいだよ。
匂いのまんまの味です。
なぜかゲテゴの料理を堪能を?
さらに、赤ちゃんに翻弄されるエビチュー。
何が?
This program was provided by the sponsor
you see.
I'm Yamase Nao!
I'm a little nervous and my voice is
hoarse.