Ebichu new member audition, second round
of double screening
New members will be decided from here
I was too nervous and my lungs were
about to explode
I wanted to be Ebichu
Ebichu's new member audition, second
round of double screening
50 people who have made it to the second
round of double screening have been
selected for 3 days
This time, they will show us their new
appearance
Please sit down
Thank you
How old are you?
I'm 15 years old
I graduated from a school
You're a dancer?
K-pop?
Yes
Can you show us?
3.0I'm 17 years old
She showed her special K-pop dance.
I forgot to wear my shoes during the
first dance, so I slipped.
I regret that.
I was embarrassed.
But I think I showed my own style.
Special dance.
Please subscribe.
This is called Urban Jazz.
Urban Jazz is a genre.
It's a great impression of the upper
main line.
This is amazing.
Thank you.
The dance level of the participants is
high.
Thank you for watching. Please subscribe
to the channel.
How old are you?
I'm 15 years old.
Especially jazz dance?
I'm still doing jazz dance.
A high school freshman is performing
jazz dance from this pose.
Thank you for watching!
I've been dancing for a long time and I
was confident.
So I think I was able to dance as I
practiced.
Next!
What is your age?
I'm 12 years old.
You're a first grader from spring?
Yes.
Ballet?
Ballet.
Now, professional dancers have started.
Seize your chance, dancers.
A twelve-year-old affairs theprends this
sort of dance.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for watching!
Thank you.
Please go back to your seat.
I'm worried.
I've been doing ballet for a long time,
so I thought it would be nice if I could
use ballet well.
And among the students...
Do you divide the lines into English and
English?
No, it's the production part.
I'll go up.
You've arrived.
Thank you.
The students who wanted to audition from
among the Star Dust promotions owned by
Ebichu
How old are you?
I'm 14 years old.
Are you a dancer?
I am.
What kind of dance do you do?
I do the dance that the teacher made for
me.
I was too nervous earlier that my lungs
were about to break.
Thank you.
How old are you? 今お目通ですか?
I'm 14 years old. 14歳です。
Where do you live? 住まいは?
Akita. 秋田ですよね。
What do you do for a living? 部活は何かやってる?
I'm an actress. 部活は演技部です。
I'm an actor. 感生部長ですよね。
and when I happened to watch anderen
An audition in which sheilaл conference
preparations, while testing her
abilities
Age, affiliation, and birthplace are all
different, but the feelings she has for
Ebichu are all the same.
So, that group has already disappeared?
I graduated.
Oh, you graduated? Why did you graduate?
I knew that there was an audition for
Ebichu, and I've always loved Ebichu
since I was little.
I've always wanted to become an Ebichu
since I was in elementary school, so I
couldn't give up on it, so I graduated
and took this audition.
Oh, that audition. I think it's the best
audition I've ever had.
She wants to achieve her dream.
She's determined to take the audition.
I love Hinata Kashiage.
But since 2013, she's been a great
singer.
I was fascinated by her.
I thought this was my last chance.
Go your own way, no matter what happens
You are you
I'm here because I want to be a shrimp.
I was too nervous to be a shrimp.
How many people will be the final
judges?
The final judges will be decided by the
final live broadcast of the final
audition.
It will be broadcast from Wednesday,
April 21st.
Please look forward to it!