Tell me one thing.
If you can't, you'll be cut.
Just one thing.
You should tell me now.
Yes.
What do you think of the camera?
I think the camera is right.
Are you okay?
I don't know what I'm thinking.
What do you think of the camera?
I'm sorry. I can see it. I pretended to
understand and cried.
Thank you for watching.
Let's interview Chan-Baby!
Clap clap clap
What should I do?
Let's start!
Why did you want to take the audition?
The reason I wanted to take the audition
was because I wanted to be in WAKU.
It's hard. I was vaccinated.
I didn't know anything about WAKU
before.
I'm scared.
I'm scared of pulling my hips.
Really?
It doesn't matter.
I'm Kouro.
I'm Iggy.
I'm Moshi Moshi.
Thank you for your support.
Did you say you wanted to join a group
during the school break?
Yes, I did. I still remember it.
Of course I wanted to join, but I really
thought I could.
I'm not sure if I can join, but I said
it as a hope.
I didn't think it would come true.
Thank you for your support.
I'm Kohei Saito.
Thank you very much.
When I was born...
I didn't know what to do with my right
and left hands.
I was wondering how to climb the stairs.
Everyone in the Go To The Bedz was a
veteran.
So I thought it would be okay to pass
the test alone.
I was told that the moment I got the
test, it was because it was an animal
park.
I thought I might have been in a crazy
place.
At first, I didn't speak.
I only said one word.
I was scared.
I was scared of Yua, but I wasn't scared
at first.
I got along with everyone.
I thought I wouldn't be able to get
along with this person.
I didn't like it.
I was very stressed when I was doing the
GYAMPAL.
I was scared of Dokuson.
I was scared of Yua.
But she was kind.
I thought Yua wasn't scared.
I was scared when I was told to do
GYAMPAL.
Please put this in the middle.
Wait!
Yayyyyyy!
Thank you for watching!
We're going to start the Young Parade
again!
We didn't have time to think and we
started practicing.
We were like, we have to memorize it.
We were like, we're going to go crazy.
But after the live, we realized it.
We became a Young Parade.
I think I became a Young Parade and I
was able to show my skills.
I wasn't able to show my skills when I
was a junior high school student.
I was able to show my skills as a Young
Parade.
There may be people in my age who were
able to show their skills.
But I think I was able to show my skills
because I had more people.
How do you feel about this retirement?
It's difficult.
It's impossible.
How did you feel about the past?
I've never done anything bad. I've
always wanted to be an idol, so I've
lived cleanly.
You've had a boyfriend, haven't you?
No, no, no.
But when I was with the members, I said
that I wouldn't say anything even if I
had something.
That's right. I think I have a secret.
I'm a secretive person.
Translated by Yes dil and gyuu.
So I don't say it.
So you might be there now? No, I'm not
now.
今はってことは
前は行った それはまあ
一人や二人くらいは
一人や二人くらい 今回のインタビューは歴史をたどるとか全く関係なく
どれだけあの何かおばくろできるかっていう
だからあれだから本当はこんな風に思ってた人いるって聞いたのか
なんかなんか流れ的になんか
何かおかしいなって思ってました なるほど
I pretended not to hear you, even though
I could hear you
I pretended to be stupid and gave up
I can't see the full star