Lap 9 is coming!
I'm Koji Nogizaka, the host of this
show.
I'm Nogizaka-chan.
What is it?
I'm the first.
You are very slow.
What is it?
I'm not alone today.
Really?
I'm scared.
If I fall down, you will have to
replenish me.
I smell something dangerous.
What is it?
Protect your seniors!
The second game battle!
Nogizaka's seniors and juniors want to
be stronger.
The juniors of the fourth and fifth
generation will compete in various
games.
However, if you lose the game, you will
be punished by the seniors.
The battle to protect the seniors will
begin.
The punishment is severe.
Did you hear that?
If the seniors receive a punishment, the
seniors will do more than that.
What are you doing?
I'm scared.
You were very excited.
I wasn't laughing.
I was serious.
I'm glad to see that attitude.
What about Akimoto?
I'm the last one.
I want everyone to do their best so that
I don't get a punishment.
That's right.
Akimoto is a living legend.
I'm kind because I'm kind.
Akimoto is the history of Nogizaka.
That's right.
Suzuki is the same.
At first, he was like a doll that didn't
speak.
He is a legend.
Thank you.
I met him yesterday.
I met him at the Yamazaki and Saitochi.
He said, please do Suzuki.
He is a legend.
He is amazing.
He is a generation change.
Himura, let's start the first round.
This is a table cross draw.
I will cross the table.
The junior members will add one more
table every time.
They will challenge a table cross draw.
The difficulty level is increasing.
If they fail, the senior members will be
eliminated.
These four teams will be competing
against each other.
Only one member, Pascal, will be
eliminated.
Who will be the one to take over the
survival pressure challenge?
The atmosphere is getting tense.
It's a little scary when it starts.
Endo.
Yes.
Yamashita is the one who's going to be
eliminated.
Because we are Yamashita.
We are Yamashita.
That's true.
There's no way we can let an Asadora
actress take over the challenge.
Say something to Yamashita.
I've been on the junior team before.
I know how nervous you are.
So, don't be nervous.
You just have to fail.
You just have to succeed.
If you don't give good advice, you'll be
eliminated.
She was a good senior until the middle
of the game.
She said something strange at the end.
Tamura.
I'm a senior who's been getting along
with him.
I'm sure I can't let him take over the
challenge.
I believe in him.
She was under a lot of pressure.
I believe in you.
Tsutsui.
I'm confident.
Tsutsui, you have to be calm and calm.
You have to fail.
This is Yoshida.
Is this your first time to be on the
show?
Yes, it is.
This is bad.
I've heard this from Hazuki.
I heard that the sound of the bell is
like a pentagon.
A pentagon?
That's right.
The people who got hit are doing this.
Two people are doing this.
Only Mukai is doing this.
This is Ogawa.
Ogawa is the youngest.
I promised Kaede that I wouldn't hurt
her butt.
Aya is different from me.
She doesn't spill or drop things.
I'm glad you didn't spill it.
Kaede dropped this when she was setting
up.
I'm glad you didn't spill it.
Rock-paper-scissors.
The important order is decided by the
result of rock-paper-scissors.
I will go first.
Tsutsui is the first to go.
She chooses a plate.
She may fail.
Are you ready?
Please draw a tablecloth.
Please start.
She succeeded.
It's dangerous.
You should not let it go wild.
If it was a cup, you would have been
out.
I'm nervous.
I was scared to put it in.
She also added a plate.
Scary!
Really?
Too scary!
Are you ready?
Yes!
The last table cross-hitting.
Go!
3, 2, 1.
This is good.
You are a professional.
Next, she adds a plate.
This may fall in the first round.
Yamashita.
I just have to drop it.
Let's start.
Please cross the table.
3, 2, 1.
Oh!
You're amazing!
Wow!
She was going wild when she pulled it
out.
It's hard.
That's good.
Ogawa.
What's Ogawa?
I was doing it with a school napkin.
Really?
But I've never succeeded.
Oh, no.
You can set it up yourself.
Wait a minute.
You've never succeeded, have you?
But, I think
you should attack at least here.
It's a hell when you come here for the
second time.
I'll put pressure on Ayame.
I see.
She's putting pressure on Tsutsui.
She's a good writer.
Are you ready?
I think you'll fail.
Please give me a break.
Let's go.
Ogawa's Table Cross.
3, 2, 1
Go!
Wow!
She did it!
She's good.
She's good at sliding.
She's good at it.
The second lap.
Tsutsui is going to attack
with a plate with chicken on it.
Yojida, you were thinking about it
when Ogawa cleared it.
I was afraid of the stability of the
eyebrows
after seeing the rattling of the first
plate.
I see.
But, I believe in you.
Well,
will the first victim appear?
The last table cross.
3, 2, 1
Go!
This is no good!
You didn't get through!
You're out!
So, the senpai, Uchida, is out.
Thank you.
Who's turn is it?
I'll say it.
Uchida, you're out.
My hand is stuck.
It hurts a lot.
My butt is exploding and I'm crying.
Let's go.
Please!
Now, Tsutsui!
You finally did it!
Say something to Yoshida.
I'm sorry.
Did it hurt?
The time when I was being teased was the
scariest.
I see.
You should have teased him more.
No, no, no.
I thought it was a little bit, but it
was a big one.
I see.
Everyone was saying that.
I was so scared.
3 people left. How many more dishes will
Tamura add?
It's not a attack.
2 dishes are added.
Amazing.
If you clear this, it's a big deal.
I believe in Mayu.
Are you okay?
What are you doing?
I'm used to this.
I think it's heavy.
I'm nervous.
It's true.
She changed her mind.
She pulled the tablecloth.
Please.
She was saved.
I feel pressure.
If I succeed, I will be attacked by
Endo.
That's right.
Endo's challenge.
I think Endo is winning this game.
No.
Endo doesn't think so.
I always fail.
I will change from this year.
I haven't been able to do anything.
I will help Yamashita.
I will be successful.
You are excited.
Endo adds a glass.
It's a formation.
He puts the cup in the cup.
It's beautiful.
Yamashita, if you clear this, it's a big
deal.
I think I can do it.
Can you do it?
Will Endo's formation succeed?
You dropped the cup!
You dropped it!
You dropped the entire cup!
You can drop it!
End.
That's a shame.
Good night.
Good night?
Don't sleep yet.
I'm sleepy.
I can't do it.
Please do it quickly.
No, no, no.
What should I do?
Do you want me to do it when you put
your hands down?
When I put my hands down?
What do you mean?
Do I have to put my hands down and do
it?
That's a lie.
When should I start the play?
No, no.
That's how it feels.
How does it feel?
Let's do it when I put my hands down.
I put my hands down.
Then...
I'm sleepy.
What should I do?
Ready or not, here I come.
Thank you for watching!
She was able to win.
She was worried about her.
Don't worry about it.
She couldn't protect her senior.
She couldn't protect her senior again.
I'm sorry.
She has said sorry many times.
I can't help it.
Finally, they will fight.
The last.
3,2,1
The winner is Yuri.
That's amazing!
I'll do two.
And Tamura, who is doing so well,
adds two more glasses and starts the
game again!
One of them has ice in it.
3, 2, 1
Stable!
Amazing!
You're good!
Iwamoto, you're reliable.
You're my friend.
My friend.
That's amazing!
A heated table-cross battle!
Who will be able to protect their
senpai?
I'll do it again.
Ogawa adds another small plate.
There are 11 plates on the table.
What will happen to Ogawa and his
senpai, Sato?
3, 2, 1
AAUGH!!
YAAAAY!!
Out!
That's right.
The plate is also turned over.
What is that?
It's a big one.
It's going to inflate.
Wait.
It's scary.
Is that your first time to use
electricity?
I did it once in the movie, The Beast.
It's different from that.
This is a weapon.
It's a big one.
It's my first time to use electricity.
Wait.
It's really scary.
It's very painful.
Wait a minute.
It's painful.
What kind of signal is it?
Is this it?
Let's do it with your hands down.
Yes.
Wait.
This is the last time.
The last time.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
What are you doing?
You can change the timing of the button.
It was fun.
Iwamoto clears.
I will never let my butt get hurt.
It's the best. Let's go eat.
I'm going.
Let's move on to the next game.
Please, Himura-san.
Surface cooperation
The second round of the competition
In a container filled with water, the
junior members pour water into each
other's cups.
The senior who spills the water first
will be punished by a sharp chair.
This game is a one-on-one confrontation.
Can they protect their seniors while
putting pressure on the other party?
Takaguchi and Mukai are the seniors'
seats.
I had the image of Mukai until recently.
Mukai, you look good in an electric
chair.
Kanagawa, how do you feel?
This is my first time.
I don't want to be punished.
Are you okay? You seem to be shaking
your hands.
I shake my hands a lot.
Because you are an alchemy.
Don't say that.
Yakubo and Kanagawa, you two go to the
store.
I'm not going to do that.
The other party is a bowman.
The bowman seems to be reckless and
scary.
Are you okay? You seem to be in a game.
I'm different today.
I'm taking care of my seniors.
I want to do my best to repay them.
Did you support your seniors recently?
I think I had something.
I don't know.
The other party doesn't know.
I'm okay because I'm close to my
seniors.
I have the image that you are going to
play a game.
I think I will definitely win.
Are you ready?
I want you to do it freely.
The result of the game is decided by
YUMIKI.
Then.
Wait a minute.
I'm afraid I'll do it.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Then let's start.
The game starts.
maybe
I will finish.
You cleared it.
I think you can still do it.
Are you nervous?
I'm shaking.
That's dangerous.
You are shaking.
Please send power.
I will stop shaking.
Don't laugh.
What are you saying?
I will stop shaking.
Please believe me, I will stop shaking.
What are you doing?
Don't make me laugh.
I will stop shaking.
Let's go.
Wow!
Are you still going?
It's OK. You can go further.
A little more.
Yes!
Wow!
It's getting exciting!
She did her best.
Wow! It's getting exciting!
It's getting exciting!
Wow!
The studio is getting excited, too.
Yubuki is going to try the second shot.
Yubuki, Himura, face straight.
Oh, no. They're staring at each other
like monsters.
Let's go. Start!
Wow, that's a lot.
Wow, that's a lot. Is it okay?
Wow!
I'll stop her!
Yumiki, you did it!
If I put pressure on her, she'll lose
her strength.
So I'll do it freely.
I see. Don't say it.
It's getting exciting.
It's getting exciting!
Wow!
Kanata, you're next.
This is dangerous.
Even from here, the surface is getting
exciting.
It's getting exciting.
This is dangerous.
This is a battle.
It's a battle. I didn't expect it to be
this long.
I think you should say what you said
earlier.
I'll stop shaking.
Ganagawa's surface tension is at its
peak.
Start.
Wow, amazing!
This is a one-of-a-kind!
Oh no, what should I do?
It's almost over.
I don't want to!
Thank you!
The party will get even more exciting!
They showed us a high level of
performance, but is it finally reaching
its limit?
OK!
This is scary!
But it's fine to end it with one shot.
Right?
Let's go.
Are you alright?
Yes!
It looks like they don't have much time
left, but can Yumiki make it to the next
stage?
You can do it!
Go for it!
I'm still fine!
I can't do it?
What are you going to do?
I'm going to do it!
You're still going?
Really?
It's coming out!
Yes!
I'm OK.
OK!
That gave pressure to Kanagawa.
Yumiki.
You were very aggressive.
You were very excited.
Are you excited?
Thank you!
Let's go!
The third attempt of Kanagawa, a
breathtaking match!
I'm scared.
She's shaking.
It's okay.
Yes! Okay!
It's a face-to-face match.
It's finally the last chance.
The battle is finally the fourth
attempt.
Who will win?
Seriously?
Are you okay?
It's not going.
I'm going.
It's cold.
I'm scared of heights.
I'm scared of getting stuck.
Wow!
This is amazing!
I'm scared!
I can't do it next time.
The atmosphere has changed.
It's getting more exciting.
Thank you for watching.
A battle that's on the verge of getting
heated up.
Who will be able to save their senpai?
It's already sticking out.
It's sticking out.
I can't see the left side.
Now, let's go.
It's on the verge of surface tension.
Wow!
One?
Yes!
Wow!
What should I do?
It's already shaking.
It's shaking.
In order to bring assurance from the
released soul, a tythi noise source was
retrieved from the room.
Yes, it's OK.
OK.
It's a draw.
The tension is beyond our expectations
due to their excessive concentration.
What kind of result will this battle
bring?
Mukai Sakaguchi is not a child.
It's amazing.
Let's go, Kanata.
Yes, please.
Giri Giri Homen Choryoku Start!
Can you do it?
Can you?
Really?
Yes!
Kanagawa is out!
Thank you for watching!
I thought I wouldn't lose because Yumiki
was going to win.
Sakaguchi, you can win.
My heart is about to explode.
You may be able to win.
I'm sorry.
Yumiki won.
I'm sorry I lost even though I was
stopped.
No.
Is it just no?
I fought well.
I will go.
I will go if I put my hand down.
You should look at it.
What is this?
Here we go.
I was jealous. It hurt.
It hurt.
This is what you were talking about.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
But I'm a little jealous.
You don't have a star.
Ten-year birthday live's Blu-ray and DVD
jacket is complete.
This is it.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I'm going to eat this quickly.
I'm not good at eating this.
I'm really eating this.
Please subscribe to my channel.