The eyes are important too.
I will.
My songs still come out often.
Because my songs are tearful.
Crying over your own songs is the worst.
Oh, Side B.
Thank you for the Side A. It was so much
fun.
Side B. Do you have anything to say?
I'll do a lot.
I hope you'll come and listen to it.
Thank you.
I liked singing, but I liked watching
TV.
I liked the songs of Hideki Saizyo and
Julie.
When I was about 10 years old, my cousin
had a guitar.
When I was playing it, my auntie bought
it for me.
It was a gutter guitar, but I made a
mistake.
When I started playing it,
I think it was around the same time,
he took me to a concert of the downtown
boogie band.
I saw the live for the first time.
Did your auntie do that too?
My cousin did.
So I think the band is cool.
That's how it was when I was about 10
years old.
Then I got to know the Beatles.
Then I saw on TV,
Mr. Cha, Mr. Masanori, Mr. Harada, Mr.
Go Sanke.
I think that's how it was when I saw the
Beatles.
I was interested in bands, and I wanted
to play them.
When I saw them play, I was shocked by
their live performances.
My cousin was older than me, but he was
also playing in a band with his friends.
We went to see them practice.
I was surprised that they were playing
in such a small place.
I was also impressed by that.
You mentioned gut guitars.
Were you playing them for a long time?
I had a guitar with an electric guitar.
I used it all the time.
Of course, I used it until I was in
middle school.
But it breaks.
It was because of the steel wire.
It was broken, so I bought a cheap one.
How did you learn how to play the
guitar?
I learned it from a book.
It had a name and a regular name.
It was written on it.
It also had a button to hold it down.
I learned it from the very first time I
played it.
I took the Cultural Del Duo Danish
Ventures guitar in metronome, Jeong六은.
My cousin learned guitar and saw me play
it, and she bought me a guitar.
I'm not saying I was that good at
playing guitar.
But I remember playing the guitar as a
vocalist, so I wanted to sing and play
the guitar.
I didn't want to be a fast player.
So you played guitar and sang all the
time.
I wasn't a vocalist at first.
Really?
I was a guitarist.
When did you start?
I started playing in middle school.
When I was in high school, I was
studying for exams.
So I became a vocalist.
That's how I became a vocalist.
Was there a moment when you thought you
could be a vocalist?
Well, when I was doing songs like
Beatles,
I had vocals, but I also sang.
I was playing the hammer.
So I was doing it for the sake of
singing.
It wasn't the main vocalist.
It was more natural to become a
vocalist.
But it was embarrassing.
I'm going to talk about this again.
I think the guitar was better.
Even now.
Okuda-san, you have a new song as a
starting point.
This is the feeling of love in a safe
area.
It's a very natural feeling.
This was at the end of high school.
I started listening to it when the
security guard came out.
It's hard to play the guitar when you're
a security guard.
The chord progression and the chords you
don't know come out.
I learned a lot about the chords.
I listened to all the albums, not just
the sound of the voice.
I was surprised to hear the first
version of the song, such as the Major
7.
I thought it was a beautiful song.
I started making songs.
I was using it as a reference.
You started making songs and you started
using chords.
It's amazing that you're so into it.
It's huge.
It's been a great reference. Thank you.
There are many great songs in the safe
zone.
Why did you choose this song?
I like the first chord progression.
My songs still come up a lot.
Please refer to them.
The lyrics are good.
This song was written by Yosei-san.
We were both written by him.
I want to do it with Yosei-san and
listen to how he writes the lyrics.
I want to listen to it.
I can do whatever I want from the
beginning.
I can do this, I can do that.
This is the same thing as before.
I see.
You just do what you see.
But it's not the same as before.
It's like that.
The unique thing of saying.
I do it with that.
So that's not the same thing.
You can change everything into music.
That's right.
So I can do anything I want.
In that sense, I need skills, but I
learned how to make it.
Which one is the first? The marshmallow
dish?
The one before.
Are you connected to the marshmallow
dish?
Am I connected?
But I have that skill.
Even if I can imitate the way of doing
it, it doesn't work that way.
I think I read it in a magazine.
I was told that Mr. Yosui has been
watching NHK education TV all the time.
I have to put an antenna like that every
day.
Why are you suddenly in that mode?
I heard that kind of story.
I don't have any thoughts.
But everyone is writing notes.
Memo.
Memo, right?
I don't do that.
I don't think people who are good at
memo are worried.
When you write songs or write lyrics.
But I don't have any thoughts.
I don't think I'm going to write a memo.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
That's all I'm saying.
That's true.
I don't think I'm going to write all of
them down.
But I wonder if it's different if I do
that.
I'm not sure.
There are times when the melody is also
floating.
And that's when I make a song.
If I can remember it, it's a good song.
I thought it wasn't a good song to
forget.
I didn't even write it down.
But I forgot.
The eyes are important.
I'll do it.
I think it's really good.
I knew what Tamaaki has was great from
the beginning,
and that even now,
he had once a live performance on TV,
and Tamaaki had been bringing
live private shows into the catholic
world marble,
like watching Amore the Turtle's
January 8th or 10th.
Tanaka-san, to?
To in the video,
you showed yourselfuki G posing and
living customers were looking at you and
robots percenting
which was shown before,
cannot keep together
it was good
video
s
I saw them and conductor zas一起 Book said
but at first,
I thought it was great.
Just the first sound?
Yes.
I thought it was great.
I can feel it.
The way you speak is amazing.
The way you play your body.
Yes.
It's like you're playing an instrument.
The quality of your voice is what makes
you a Yosui.
It's like, what's that voice?
It's so far-reaching.
That's right.
It's so destructive, as a weapon.
Ordinary people try to make their voices
reach others.
They do a lot of things.
It's like the voice I usually use.
It's different in frequency.
People like me who are from hard rock
bands
can't hear my vocals in the rehearsal
room.
The surroundings are noisy.
The PA of Yasui Studio is small.
I'm trying to figure out how to make it
sound good.
Of course I'm making a loud voice, but
I'm trying to figure out how to make it
sound good.
That's how it's going to be.
It's going to be a bit of a metal style.
That's how it is.
I'm like this.
If you're not like that, you're like
this.
Yosui-san is a talkative person.
He's going to look at the girl at the
back of the bar.
I'm sorry.
I said sorry in the bar, and the girl at
the bar said,
Yes!
I think she was the most effective part-
time job.
She didn't say sorry when she was so
excited.
No, she said sorry.
That's good.
That's great.
I would be surprised if I said that in
the voice of a snake meter.
I think the potential is different.
I'd like to ask you a few more
questions.
What do you think is the difference
between working in a unit and solo?
The biggest difference is that there's a
lot of work in solo.
Yes, solo is more important.
You have to make a lot of songs, and you
have to sing and play.
Unicorn is a five-part song, so there is
the biggest difference.
But it doesn't really matter how good
the music is.
In the old days, I was a soloist because
I disbanded.
But in Unicorn, there are many things I
wanted to do without doing.
I thought about doing it.
But in the final, it's a mess.
It's like, either way is fine.
So it's not that different.
It's easy to do it live.
You have to take responsibility.
That's also a big thing.
The power is five times, maybe not five
times,
but the band has that kind of energy for
the number of people.
But the solo is also...
It's a little different, but it's a
band.
Oh, that's right.
So it's not much different.
It's just that people are different.
So personally, the story of the song is
the most...
There's no reason to do it.
What?
Because...
Without being stimulated by anyone,
you have to do it yourself.
It's a self-release.
I used to be a shy guy.
You did it well.
I always thought,
I'm going to sing this much by myself.
I was embarrassed when I first thought
of it.
But you often sing alone in the stadium.
That's right.
In the stadium,
I don't know if the audience is far
away.
I don't know if there are people.
離れてる。 恥ずかしくない。 今一恥ずかしくなかった。
ライブハウスの方が恥ずかしいですよ。 近いから。
めちゃめちゃいるけど、よくわからないんですよ。 表情なんか見えないじゃん。
だからなんかこう、失敗したの、今みたいな顔は見えないじゃん。
なんか、ほんまに緊張しなかったんですよね。 心配してる状況じゃないっていうか。
,すごいすぎて。でもやっぱり人、
引き語りが一番だからこう、嫌だなってことはないけど。 純粋なソロっていうのは、本
当全部自分でこう、空間を作り上げなきゃいけないってことはありますもんね。 いや、
俺はやってよくや、今日がよくやったぞとかっていうのもね、なんか。一緒にやる人がい
るといないよって、だいぶ違うよね。 ま、ただね。
I'm playing both guitar and singing.
Both are me, but...
I play the guitar like this, and the
timing of the song is not the same.
Of course.
That's true.
I don't say that it's a band, but I have
that feeling.
I see.
There's a part like a duo, playing
together.
That's right.
That's interesting.
There are many things to do.
Thank you for watching.
Extend your
Rel 뻔
Get up
Come on
Do
The sun that doesn't look at me is
watching
Where are you running away?
This song is not a mashup, but it's very
simple.
The sound is very simple.
When I heard the song, I forgot if I had
talked to Tamiya before.
But she told me that she sings it very
simply.
I think so.
I don't think it's good to put too much
emotion into it.
The part where the sun is looking at me,
I don't know what to say.
I had a part that was singing in a calm
way,
and it was something that came to my
mind.
How do you feel about the way you sing?
I like songs that are simple.
Basically.
I stopped using vibrato for singing.
I used to use it as a standard.
When I started using Unicorn, I used to
use vibrato.
Oh, I see.
I wanted to be like an instrument.
There are some instruments that have
vibrato, but...
I wanted to play it like this.
I wanted to get used to it without
floating away from it.
I think this is because I'm playing
Hamoru.
In my life.
I said it earlier.
So, the so-called singer people have a
pond.
It's floating away from the pond.
With a great presence.
Not like that, but this way.
I wanted to live in a well.
That's why it happened.
You mean you can put your emotions into
it?
If you put too much emotion into it,
you'll cry.
You'll cry, so you can't put that much
emotion into it.
I think that's what he was saying.
Because tears are fragile.
It's the worst thing to cry over your
own song.
You'll cry over your own song, and
you'll be like,
You're stupid.
You have to calm down a little.
He sang really well.
I was like, ah.
I was a little surprised.
Thank you.
It's a solo work.
So recently,
I haven't done it until the offer came.
The offer?
Yes.
I do it when I do live performances.
So the previous work, the previous work,
was called Faction Daimaou.
Before that, Chico-chan did it.
I won't do it until the offer comes, so
please.
I won't do it until the offer comes.
Solo is a bit of a late-bite.
You don't have to make a song when
you're alone.
For example, when you start making an
album,
you don't have to make three more songs.
If you have someone to ask for help,
it's a big help.
Thank you very much.