Night time and Idol
And the second element
Nakamoto
Nakamoto, this is also my favorite food,
but I really like Mouko Tannmen.
Mouko Tannmen, right?
Yes
It's spicy, isn't it?
Nakamoto's spiciness is delicious, so I
can eat it.
I see
The usual custom is to change to the
Japanese-style ladies' set konjac
noodles.
There is a custom of 3 or 4 spicy and
less oily.
Oh, how to order yourself
First of all, Mouko Tannmen, right?
It's a North Pole, isn't it?
It's spicy even if it's just a North
Pole.
It's spicy, but...
It's 3 or 4 times as spicy.
I'll take out the oil.
The noodles are healthy for konjac
noodles.
Nakamoto's konjac noodles are a little
konjac-smelling.
Yes
I don't feel that at all in Nakamoto.
It's healthy and originally a little too
much.
Even if it's a ladies' set, it's about
half the normal noodles and half the
rice.
Half rice? Is the ladies' set half rice?
Yes
It's quite a lot.
That's great.
It's really good, isn't it?
That's 620 yen.
Oh, great!
And change to konjac noodles and it's 70
yen plus, so it's 690 yen.
It's a young era.
You're going to be a good wife.
I'm going to eat after this.
Are you going after this?
How many times a month do you eat?
I eat about 2 or 3 times a week.
2 or 3 times a week?
Yes
You're eating 7 times a week.
That's great.
I'm friends with my sister.
Oh, really?
Is the spicy one okay?
The other spicy one?
Well, that's...
What was it?
It's like the spicy one of Peyoung.
There was.
I thought I could eat it in the video of
the birthday party, so I took it.
It was so painful that I couldn't speak
just by touching the air.
I understand.
I'm not sure if I should say I like
spicy food.
But that spiciness is a little...
It's abnormal, isn't it?
It's abnormal.
Takagi likes spicy food, too.
I like spicy food, too.
That was spicy.
I can't eat raw eggs or butter.
I can't.
I can't eat anything with milk.
I understand.
I want to go eat spicy food with RENI.
Really?
Yes.
Tell me about it and I'll shoot it.
Really?
But she can eat spicy food, too.
She can eat spicy food.
I can eat spicy food, too.
I'll shoot it.
I want to try it.
I'll think about it.
Yay!
Yakan and idol
What else do you eat?
I eat a lot of things.
The most happy thing about eating this
is that
There was a collaboration between
Ametalk and Nakamoto.
I played Nakamoto's favorite comedian in
Ametalk.
From the next day,
I ate the noodle with coriander in it.
I went to the restaurant to eat it.
really?
Yes
I saw it on the show.
I saw it on the show and thought I would
definitely eat it.
There were a lot of people like that.
really?
I went to the restaurant about 10
o'clock in the morning.
I ate it in front of the restaurant.
Did you go?
Yes, I ate it.
What did you do?
It was very delicious.
It wasn't spicy.
I ordered a spicy soup.
I see.
I changed the taste.
Yes
I changed the taste after I enjoyed the
taste.
You changed the sourness and spiciness.
Yes, it was very delicious, so I want
you to come back.
Is the rice only white rice?
Yes, but the rice bowl is also
delicious.
Is the rice bowl delicious?
The rice bowl is delicious, but the
spiciness is not enough.
It's not spicy enough.
That's great.
I really like it.
I couldn't eat it, but I liked it before
I knew it.
Is the spicy soup famous among fans?
I think it's famous.
I often go to NAKAMOTO and shoot a
story.
I write the menu for today and make a
highlight that is very spicy.
I'm not good at cooking.
반
but it would be great if we can serve it
to fans who are accidents-minded.
This program was provided by MameMabo,
Ikkun, Yutaro, Iete Neizo, and Kei.
Thank you all!