Idol vs. Superstar
That star is you.
The star next to you is me.
Two Idols on this stage in a day.
Minami identity
It was small back then.
The Adult Juri
What's your gender?
I'm a real adult.
I don't know what gender I am.
Please tell me.
It's a mess.
Let me explain.
A fake garden
The ship suddenly swam in the ocean
and it floated up
Wow
I found this outfit in the warehouse
It's really cute
This year too?
It's the school year
It's like space
Is it Mayuma again?
Why is it red?
This year too?
Sumagama TV
Yo
Great
I got it
Charisma
What is this?
Is this a sword?
Look, it's coming out
It's moving
What?
I like it
Who is it this time?
It's Chuu
Chuumi
What is Chibaruboshi?
I wonder what it is
But, I'm sure it's OK
Great
Akabayama, as expected
OK, then, the most interesting
AHHHHHHHH
Not so fluffy
Hong Kong
When can I experience transformation?
I'm already all devoid of secret
After all, I can't say one word
Creamy
By the way, we have kind of loose skin
I'll stop here for now.
Where's the battery?
I don't know.
What's that?
Let's all be fluffy.
Please subscribe to my channel.
It's so heavy and fluffy.
It's so fluffy.
No, I mean this boat is not fluffy.
This boat is not enough.
It's not enough.
I'm sorry for the CG god.
I'm sorry.
Let's do it again.
No light.
Again?
Let's think about the space ship's mark.
Really?
I got it.
What is this?
A kit.
I want to do something like that.
I don't want to do it.
Let's get along well.
I'm sorry.
We are going to be gone.
What?
Real junior high school students.
We are all in the fourth grade.
We are going to be gone.
You are in the fourth grade.
We are all in the same age group.
I like being alone in the same age
group.
What is this?
First, from Mayama
Present
Start!
Ta-da!
You're not pulling out your hand
I'm not
I'm not pulling out my hand
You were like, I'm going to write a
letter, so it's okay
Eri-chan!
Present
Start!
Ta-da!
The theme is space.
The earth is coming out.
The earth is surrounded by the shrimp.
The point is the shrimp-shaped tube.
Oh, really?
It's easy to understand and has a casual
design.
I didn't know it was too casual.
I thought it was messed up.
I'm wondering how the infinite love that
spreads in space will be.
I agree.
I was surprised when I saw it.
It's casual and fashionable.
It's a word from a senior.
It's a word that you can't say.
That's right.
I'm sure they'll choose me.
I think so, too.
destroys each immediately
ok thank you
What's cute about that Hello Guys were
youSTEEL?
I'm Nasa.
This is my Nasa.
Nasa is a bit dizzy.
Apologize to Nasa.
This is my mark.
The theme is anyone can imitate.
Mark, shrimp, and shoe.
This is a space suit.
Oh, I see.
What are the two things in it?
This is a shrimp.
Oh, I see.
Is the person inside a viking?
This is an alien.
This is cute.
This is like a character.
I want to make it a pin badge.
I want to imitate Kid.
I want to imitate this person.
Because it looks kind.
How about Kid?
I'm getting used to it.
Let's get along.
The third person is a presenter.
It's like an esthetician.
This is the mark I thought of.
The theme is to travel the universe with
everyone.
Everyone is connected and draw a star.
This is a presenter.
I'm glad. I'm a gyro-pon jump.
Mayama is a gyro-pon jump.
Riko has a three-way net.
Yes, I have a three-way net.
Hina has a twin tape.
It's connected.
This is a presenter.
This is cute.
I thought this was good.
I was convinced.
I want a T-shirt with that pattern.
I want to make it a mobile phone
cleaner.
I'm looking forward to the goods.
Next is the star confession.
This is the mark I thought of.
This is cute.
This is better than the usual picture.
This is a mark I thought of.
This is a theme that I want to shine
with everyone.
This is a sparkling theme.
I give this to KITTO.
I want to give KITTO this position.
I want to keep this mark for a year.
Thank you very much.
I'm also looking forward to buying these
goods.
Please give me a towel and so on.
I want a towel.
Emi-chan.
Well, Ms. Matsuno.
I'm like this.
I don't know.
This is E.
B is C.
I can't do it.
E is here.
E is C.
Red is E.
Ebi.
The theme is this program and Ebi.
It's the fourth time for Shiro to do it
in the frame.
So I want to go back to the beginning
and do it with a pure feeling.
So I made this place white.
I think that word will come out from now
on.
I'm definitely thinking about it now.
When I'm in line, I'm thinking about
what to say.
This time, Ebi team will do our best.
Let's do our best with this emblem.
I'm sure.
Thank you for watching! Please subscribe
to our channel!
Here is what I came up with!
The theme is EBC
It's like a sweet shrimp
Oh, it's true!
The key point is this connection!
That was difficult!
You did your best!
The key point is the number!
It has a shrimp's sense of taste!
Oh, it's cute!
I don't have a sense of taste anymore.
Oh, yes, yes, yes!
It's rare!
It's very simple!
It's a little bit of a weird place.
The connection is the first thing that
comes out of your mouth.
It was difficult!
You like sweet shrimp, don't you?
Yes!
Ebichu!
I'm Kit Nakayama!
Yes!
The theme is
Ebichu with shrimp.
It's the opposite!
Ebichu with shrimp!
Shrimp!
I'll leave it to your imagination!
The key point is
I looked up the shrimp and drew it
seriously!
I drew it properly!
It's the best quality shrimp I've ever
seen!
Kit decided to do this!
I'll give you this as an exchange!
Thank you!
Applause!
Now, everyone's marks are out!
What will it be?
I don't know.
There's no shrimp, so...
I have a feeling of Ebichu!
I have a feeling of Ebichu, so...
I don't have shrimp!
Oh, really!
Matsuno's is very similar!
That's right!
I'm sure it's the final one!
Best actor!
Please rest assured!
I can't read the kanji!
Please look forward to the next episode!
The most beautiful
What's that
Because you were sleeping
Because I was sleeping
I opened it but it's still there
It's a mess
What's that
Everyone's Enbunomaru is
just put it on
Just put it on
It's good
It's a good place
H-M-R-J-U