Please!
Long time no see!
How long has it been?
It's been a while since we did this in
August.
So it's been 3 or 4 months.
This time...
We can only talk for 5 minutes.
So let's talk about what we did.
Please.
Our outfits are similar.
It's like a unit outfit.
White and black.
We didn't plan this.
Let's get started.
Let's go.
Start!
Bye bye.
I'm the same age as you.
Yes, but we are seniors.
So, we always speak in honorifics.
You always speak in honorifics.
Yes, I do.
I'm nervous.
Then, let's talk in honorifics.
What?
Let's talk in honorifics for 5 minutes.
Can we do it?
I'll do my best.
Let's do it.
You're nervous.
Yes, I am.
I'm nervous.
You should have used honorifics.
I've been getting along with the
members.
I haven't talked to them much.
I don't think we've had much contact.
We've had some group activities, but
we've rarely had a chance to be together
because of distance issues.
I agree.
I have an image of you that you're
modest, but you're always determined.
I've always thought that was cool.
I'm glad to hear that.
I'm always nervous when I'm in the
dressing room.
But when I'm on stage, I'm like, leave
it to me.
I've always thought you were cool as an
idol.
I'm glad to hear that.
I used to have a short impression before
I became an idol.
How many years ago was it?
I think it was when I was a junior in
junior high school.
I had a short impression.
But when I met you, I was tall and
stylish.
You were like an older sister to me.
I didn't feel like you were my sister.
I felt like you were taller than me.
I was very humble.
I think it was the year before last.
We were in the same age group at the
Starpla Festival last year.
We were born in 2000.
We sang a song together as a unit.
I was surprised to see so many people of
the same age.
I thought there were a lot of people of
I was surprised to see Riko Ueda and
other people of the same age.
I was able to meet people of the same
age for the first time.
I have a lot of memories.
It was a lot of fun.
It was a moment of glory.
I'm talking now, but I really like your
choice of words.
When I worked with you when you were a
radio drama,
Your choice of words was beautiful.
You purified my mind.
I'm not good at talking at my pace.
I'm not good at talking to people.
I can't say this and that.
I can't tell you when I'm like that.
I have a lot of things I think.
It takes days to write a blog.
I write a blog for two hours on social
media.
I write a blog for two hours and write a
blog for one day.
I think it's the same.
I found it.
I'm going to do it after I've done it.
I like the beauty of it.
I've been doing it.
Thank you.
You do a lot of things.
I've done a lot.
I'm a little bit.
When I was on a show with you,
It's more like my own thing than a play.
I'm the one who wants to talk the most.
I forgot it was five minutes.
I was here a little while ago.
It's short.
It's over.
I'm sure you'll hear the rest somewhere.
I wanted to praise you, but I couldn't.
I've been praised a lot.
Can I say this?
I'm practicing my speech in the dressing
room.
I'm reading a lot of scripts.
I'm just doing one thing.
I'm thinking about it as a job.
I respect you for being able to do that.
Thank you.
It's hot.
It's too short.
Let's talk slowly.
Thank you very much.