This week's Ebichu Tastas is the Ebichu
Tastas BBQ that continued last week
Kashiwagi-san, don't look at the pizza!
The personality of Kashiwagi is
destroyed!
Furthermore, the personal relationship
of Kobayashi Yasumoto is revealed!
Here it is!
Jin Kaito is the next!
It's a stomach bag!
It's a drinking bag!
So, Ebichu Tastasu Start!
From Ebitz
Thank you for watching!
Let's eat!
Let's eat when it's ready!
You have to eat it with chopsticks!
Let's eat!
Last week, the members were waiting for
the barbecue
The tension was at its max
Delicious!
Thank you!
Suddenly, Kobayashi starts running.
Matsuno is sitting down during the show.
The scene is very messy.
It's not a proper show.
The second half of the show is about how
the shooting stars go down and observe
everyone.
Please watch the shrimp stew that enjoys
the barbecue freely
Shrimp stew is endless when you start a
barbecue
I can't hear anyone
It's just that it's decided that you're
going to grill it
Mayama is
Hirota also cooks
That's right
Hirota goes to both
Eat while grilling
Hirota is probably doing what he wants
to eat
That's right
Everyone is trying hard to show that
they are grilling
Then I noticed that there is a master
Nakayama is full
There was no one who wanted to eat
It was a pattern that I got sleepy after
eating
Kobayashi who is out of concentration
That's right
It's easy to do it with tongs
I'm full
Actually, the members who ate miso ramen
before the barbecue
I'm full
Basically, I ate a lot
The first explosion is gone
Open and you can see
Kobayashi is here
What is this?
Did you eat the beef tongue?
Finally, the original beef tongue
This barbecue is
The original ingredients that members
put in when they barbecue
Kobayashi prepared
What is the chives that you don't see in
barbecue?
Did you eat chives?
It seems that chives fell into the
barbecue
That's right
It's flat
The bean sprouts also fell
Bean sprouts
It's not good
You don't have to be sad
Mayama is doing it as a good girl
Kobayashi left it
Mayama is taking care of it
That's true
Kobayashi
Only wait for the meat to be finished
You forgot to put bean sprouts
Then
Please look at the chives and bean
sprouts
It's wrapped in silver paper
It's put on aluminum
It's not falling
Of course, Kobayashi didn't do that
That's not right
Does someone with such a wisdom exist in
the shrimp?
Who is it?
Who put chives and bean sprouts on
aluminum?
The answer is
Everyone
I brought pizza
Pizza from here
How is it?
I found a pizza with a chive
Are you kidding me?
Are you still eating?
I will cut it
Aya-chan is tired of it
I want to eat it
This
Matsuno is tired of it
He is going at his own pace
I think so
He is looking for a four-leaf clover
He found it
The problem is that Matsuno wanted to
have a barbecue
That's right
I want to have a barbecue
I'm listening to the story of Kaichi
Two people in eight people
Iro and Yaki
Please eat
The first thing I do is waiting
It's amazing
The taste changes, so you can still eat
it
Seriously
Delicious
I spilled it
I hate this
Hey, Riko-chan
What's wrong with Riko-chan?
Look over there
Riko-chan, the pizza is covered in sauce
No way
Wipe it properly
They are doing it forever
BBQ free time is over
we watched it
Hirota and Mayama
are doing their best to grill it
Mayama is a big sister
Kobayashi
put in chives
and went to play
Mayama was taking care of it
chives and bean sprouts
I thought it was a waste to burn the
ingredients
I thought it was a waste
It was great
It was like a silver paper
Who was that?
It's a good thing
Mayama did her best
to grill the chives
Kobayashi, did you eat chives?
No
And Kashiwagi
was grilled well
Kashiwagi
was staring at the pizza
What was that?
I thought the pizza was coming
Were you surprised?
Why did you stare?
I was staring
Kashiwagi is usually staring
I'm not staring
You are
I'm just looking
You were staring at the waterfall
I'm scared
I've been wondering
The bandana
is like a belt
Kashiwagi only
It's a transformation belt
Can you transform?
I can't
What?
Mr. Takigue, Mr. Kashiwagi doesn't look
at pizza
I want to change my personality
What is your name?
Ogata Kaiki
I see
You have transformed into Mr. Ogata
I'm really into it
My feelings are
I'm very happy
Thank you
You speak slowly and make people pay
attention
It's like a place where there is nothing
Kobayashi Yasumoto Jiji team
After this, Kobayashi Yasumoto will make
a big impact on society
Here it is
Ta-da
The storm of Jinkaito
Furthermore, it's a talk time at the BBQ
place
I always put your picture in the enemy's
ticket
The waiting is the public
Kobayashi Yasumoto Jiji team
Last time, it ended in great success
Yasumoto Kobayashi's birthday prank
The program has prepared two special
guests to surprise them
But the two guests are more than
expected
So let's see their appearance tonight
Kobayashi Yasumoto's Gigi Taidan
White board is a high tension board
suitable for new corners
I was surprised
I'm not good at it
I can't stand it anymore
Everyone, this program is for the
socialists of Ebisu Junior High School
Yasumoto Ayaka and Kobayashi Kaho will
talk about the social issues
That's great!
Before we start talking about the topic,
there is a rule
You can't say things you don't know
But you can't say things without saying
It's a rule for variety
It's not variety, it's social
Yasumoto Kobayashi's talk show
The first topic is compliance
Compliance is to protect the company
from the law and social norms
What kind of opinions will come out from
the two of them?
First, Yasumoto
What do you think about compliance?
Compliance
Compliance is complex in the world
Compressed
Compliance is complex
Compressed  Compliance is complex
Yasumoto, who has no complex, is anxious
about the future
I think compliance is about the complex
Do you think compliance and complex are
the same?
Yes, it's the island of the complex
What? Island?
Compliance
We live in the complex
The island of that country is called
compliance
The island where the people with complex
live
Where is the island full of complex?
It's up there
This world is the bottom
It's a parallel, so we'll raise the
level
We'll make the technology to go to that
island
And then we'll go to that island
You're very conscious
Yasumoto, who is very conscious, says
that compliance is the island where
people with complex gather
Of course it's different
Next
Kobayashi, compliance again
The island of the complex
In that sense, we have to complete it
Complete
That's right
You're being pulled by the complex
Kobayashi says that compliance is about
the people who are trying to gather
something
Compliance is about the people who have
completed too much
After all, it's the first time to be
compliant after gathering something
We're still in the complex
Compliance
There's a new word
There's a new word, it's compliance
Compliance
We're still in the first class, so we're
still in the complex
We'll go up to the level and then we'll
go to compliance
In other words, compliance will grow and
compliance will be completed when the
level rises
Of course it's different
Next is the Tokyo Olympics, which is
scheduled to be held in 2020.
About the main venue, Shin Kokuritsu
Stadium
What do you think about Shin Kokuritsu
Stadium?
It seems that it will cost more than 1.6
billion yen to build it.
Thank you for watching.
I can't show this.
Can't you show it?
Can you stop talking about this?
For some reason, the two people are in a
hurry because they can't afford the
construction cost.
The story doesn't go on as it is.
There are various problems with shape
and area.
What kind of building would be a
national stadium that everyone would be
convinced of?
Let's draw it.
There is a white mode.
First, let's announce the new national
stadium that Yasumoto is thinking of.
This is it.
This is the world's national stadium.
The world?
It's not limited to one.
It's not limited to the country called
Japan.
The picture is also drawn.
It's a grand story.
Let's ask the person who is listening to
the story.
There is a person on the stage.
What is the point?
The point is the height of this stage.
This is also going to space.
To space?
Yes.
The name is space.
There is no oxygen because it is space.
I don't need oxygen.
You don't need oxygen in 2020.
It's a country of space.
I don't need oxygen because I live in
space.
The new national stadium that Yasumoto
suggests is characterized by the fact
that the stage has reached space.
Next, what is the new national stadium
that Kobayashi thinks of?
This is it!
Ta-da!
What is this?
Shrimp?
Yes.
Actually, this shrimp is a real shrimp.
Kobayashi's suggestion is...
What is a real shrimp?
This is a rare shrimp and a 100-line
shrimp.
There were many kinds of shrimp in it.
Is this a half?
Is this a shrimp half?
This is a shrimp half.
I can only sigh.
Just look at that luxury!
Century Spring Shrimp
A
53-year-old
Thank you for watching!
How was the first meal, Yasumoto-san?
I've used up all my energy
We're not stomachs, but brain cells
I said it clearly
There's a bag in the brain, right?
Brain cells
Actually, they've been filming for over
an hour and a half
Yasumoto Kobayashi's Jiji Talk
To be continued
Next is a talk time at the BBQ place
The members will talk about things they
are interested in
Today, Nakayama was the first MC. How
was it?
The crow answered
I see
She said she didn't do anything
So, everyone has a clip
Actually, everyone wrote what they think
about the members
I will announce them in order
First, Nakayama will ask Yasumoto a
question
The idol that you are most into right
now is?
By Oniichan
From Nakayama Oniichan?
I couldn't decide so I asked Oniichan
Ayo-chan is now
So Nakayama Oniichan is Yasumoto fan?
No, he is a fan of Mirei
Ah, he is a fan of you
He is a fan of Nakayama Oniichan?
Is there a member who is a fan of you?
Yes, there is
My Oniichan is Mayama Oniichan
Is that so?
Then, who is the idol that you are most
into right now?
The idol that I am most into right now
is
Gem
She is the younger sister of Supergirl
We have a lot of dance moves
I like cool idols
I see
So I am learning a lot from them
Then, who are the other cool idols?
Morning Musume's One Five
She is standing up
I thought she would fall down like this
She is like a shrimp
I like her a lot
Then, you should properly greet her
Aya-chan, please dance
So, a message from Yasumoto to Morning
Musume's One Five
My name is Ayaka Yasumoto
I would like to meet you
I would like to go to your live show
Thank you
Who is your favorite idol?
I like Yumi Ishida
That's amazing
I am also an idol
By the way, who is your favorite idol?
Who is it?
It's not an idol, but a girl group is
E-Girls
I was told to wait a long time
I love you
You two like E-Girls? Then, you two
Next, Hoshina and Matsuno's message to
E-Girls
Do you see me, Reina?
I don't see you
I'm watching you
I'm watching you too
I always put your picture in my diary
It's close
I'm encouraged when I'm not feeling well
I also put your picture in my diary
What is this?
What is this corner?
I love your singing voice
I want to be able to sing like Washiho
Thank you
Get out of the way
I respect Ryuhei Ueshiba
Who are you talking to?
We just ate sushi together
He was drunk in the airport
He looks cool when he's drunk
Let's move on
This is interesting, so let's do it in
another corner
Let's do it
Let's do it next time
Next, Mayama's question to Hirota
When did you start?
I wore flashy clothes
The first time I met Aika
There were days when it was flashy, but
there were many days when it was black
and white
I like black and white pandas
The first time I met Hirota was when I
was in the movie directed by Sekine
At that time, I was very cool
I wore a monster hand
A glove like this
Do you walk around with that glove on?
Can you bend your fingers?
I can't bend it
What do you do with the train skin?
I remove the skin
When did you start?
I don't know which is the level of
everyone's flashy
I don't think it's flashy
You don't think this kind of glove is
flashy?
Someone said that you wear fluorescent
colored clothes
I feel sick if I don't wear fluorescent
What do you mean?
When I wear the trendy clothes that are
popular now
I feel sick
I don't feel well without color
If you wear fluorescent
It's easy to find from a car driver
I don't get lost and I can be a
gathering place
Gathering place is good
It's important to go to the gathering
place when you go to the last minute
It stands out in the city
It's a gathering place
Mayama, you can go to the gathering
place
Mayama asked a question
The last question is from Hirota to
Kobayashi
Why do you stick out your nose when you
wear a mask?
When I wear a mask, I stick out my nose
I sharpen it and stick out my nose
I sharpen the wire of the mask and stick
it under my nose
What are you doing?
At first, I make a mountain according to
the position of my nose
This is what everyone does
I think it's going to be hard
It's hard
I may be breathing through my mouth
You're breathing through your mouth but
sticking out your nose?
If you're breathing through your mouth,
you should hide your nose and breathe
through your mouth
That's strange
Please do it when you do a mask
So, what is the shrimp barbecue?
Did you go to Kobayashi?
Yes, I went to Kobayashi's original
restaurant
Mayama finished Kobayashi's chives
Mayama did her best to grill chives
Kobayashi, did you eat chives?
Yes
Next time on the shrimp game project
Here is the character I thought
Shrimp chive game character design
More details on the next episode
Next episode of Ebichu Tastas is...
The entrance exam of Ebisu University
The test of Ebichu's ability to do it
There are many shocking answers
Who are the excellent members?
Furthermore, the first interview test is
a big problem
Are you sleepy?
I'm awake, I'm fine
I don't want to do it anymore
What is this?
This program was brought to you by the
sponsors you see.
Ready, set...
Pon, pon, pon, pon, Iwappa
That's all?
I'm not going to film this, am I?