I'm Itoha Mukai, a 16-year-old high
school freshman from Hiroshima
Prefecture.
I'm here at the zoo.
It's cold, but I'm excited to see the
animals I want to see.
I'm at Saruyama.
Can you see?
I've been coming to the zoo since the
opening ceremony.
I came here every year on a trip.
I took a group photo in front of
Saruyama.
It's a rhino.
It's big.
It's walking.
I found a giraffe, so I'm going to meet
it.
Come here.
There are three.
Giraffe.
It looks good on you.
Look at this.
Cute.
Thank you for watching.
It looks like a stuffed animal.
Animals are all cute.
I like all kinds of animals.
Many people say, I like this animal.
Animals are so comforting.
I've liked animals since I was a kid.
Chihuahua!
So cool!
There are so many.
Elephants are eating snow.
So cute.
They are eating snow.
They are coming.
They are coming down.
So scary.
They are so big.
They are so powerful.
I've liked this group for the first
time.
I've watched a commercial of Silent
Majority at Keyakizaka46.
I've never felt that I was chosen as a
third-generation student.
I'm worried about what will happen.
I'm sure the fans are warm-hearted.
I'm relieved.
I'm not worried about my dream.
I'm more excited about it.
I went to the zoo the other day.
I'm going to draw a picture of an animal
that I remember.
I'm going to draw elephants, monkeys,
hippos, and owls.
I was impressed by the big crying
elephants.
I've already made an elephant.
I've been drawing for three years in a
club.
I'm not good at drawing.
I was drawing because I wasn't good at
drawing.
I was drawing because I was good at
I like to concentrate on small things.
I've been doing it for a long time.
It's the second day of the Kirie.
I've finished drawing the rhinoceros and
the owl.
I'm going to put the picture on a big
piece of paper and finish it.
I've finished drawing the Kirie.
It was my first time to draw Kirie.
It was a lot of fun.
I'm going to draw a picture of an
elephant.