Thank you for watching!
I'm a liar. But I'm a cool liar.
You're amazing.
I'm a cute liar.
I like peanuts.
You look like a peanut.
I'm a liar. But I'm a cool liar.
I'm a cute liar.
I don't have many friends, so I can't
talk about anime.
I'm glad I could talk about anime even a
little bit.
It was fun.
I like the anime, Tenkai no Animesou.
If I have to choose one, I would choose
Family.
I love family, but I also like dark
stuff.
I really like the characters that make
me think,
Oh, so this is the person who did the
black mask!
I really like that.
What kind of character do you want to
play?
I want to play a character that is not
human.
I want to play a character that is like
a character.
Do you want to play a character that is
not human?
Yes, I want to play a character that is
not human.
It's very difficult to act with just a
voice.
I want to play a character that can do
anything.
Asuka is the most similar to me.
I will play Evangelion's Asuka.
I will play the role of Asuka Soryu.
Are you stupid?
How is it?
You are similar to me.
Am I similar to you?
I'm glad.
I've only been told that I'm similar to
you.
I've never been told that I'm similar to
I'm glad.
I'm...
kind of...
I'm going to cry.
Recently, Rikoriko has become a hot
topic.
The 14th, 15th, and 16th episodes of
Maboroshi are trending.
Everyone is like,
Oh, Rikoriko, today is the 14th.
Is it still? Is it still?
I saw a lot of tweets like that.
Oh, we're done.
I thought.
Yes, I do. I touch my computer.
What do you do?
I don't do anything in particular.
Well, I guess I do.
I watch anime, read manga, and play
games.
I touch my computer and social media.
I guess I do.
Everyone is so cute that I can't look at
them.
Seriously.
You know, there was a big event at
Stapler.
I was sitting at the end of the stage.
Everyone was so cute and dazzling that I
couldn't look at them.
So if there's anyone who wants to do a
collaboration with me, I'd like to talk
about anime.
I do a lot of things, including games.
I mentioned the manga, Suisei no Majou.
I have another favorite manga, Bocchi
the Rock.
It's a Kirara manga.
Please watch it.
I've been talking about my feelings
since the beginning of the first
episode.
I love it.
I felt something close.
It's Bocchi the Rock.
When I saw the anime of the next Kirara
manga, I thought I had to watch it.
I've been looking forward to it.
It's interesting from the first episode.
The opening and ending are also good.
I hope you'll watch it.
Please subscribe to my channel.
________________________________________
______________________________
Bye!
You seem to be doing well,
and I've heard that the theaters you
appeared in became a really popular one
even just this year.
errr?
ahaha, that's right got it.
It's hard for me to think...
I still hate to hear that I'm secretly
popular,
so...
Its ok, just ignore it didn't get byeced
about it yet...
Starters as well!
I see.
So, you practice with other actors and
staffs, right?
Is it fun?
Yes, it is.
You don't practice in parallel?
No, I practice one by one.
I see.
I heard that actors often say that their
roles are not good when they watch our
show.
I watch your show thinking, ''Oh,
really?''
I think that when I play a strong
character, I can speak a lot.
At that time?
You are a strong character.
I get drunk.
I see.
I don't think that you can understand
it.
But I can understand how much effort you
put in which shows.
You can sense my heartbeat.
I want to tell to my viewers that actors
usually have natural freedom in
practicing their roles.
At first, I was focusing on my musical
activity.
It was necessary for him to adjust his
Slow Vocalization on stage.
Well. His ability was critical to him.
To tell you the truth I haven't been
good at singing since I starred in the
musical.
Y programmers criticized that I barely
had vocal volumes which caused me a lot
of problems.
At first, I was really shocked.
My voice gets louder.
I see.
So, um...
How should I put it?
For example, I used to live in Kansai,
so I used to take the Shinkansen to
Tokyo.
My voice was louder then.
I think I can relate to that.
I used to work at a company,
and I was told to speak to the wind
because it was too loud.
I was like, oh, really?
We have a lot of voices.
Yeah!
It's great, right?
Yes.
You used to say, your voice is loud.
Yeah, I used to say, isn't the volume
too loud?
You did?
Yes.
It's great that you can say that now.
I'm glad I did.
Right?
Yes!
What's the role that left the biggest
impression on you?
The role?
Out of all the roles you've played, is
there a particular role that you
remember?
Well, after I stopped being an idol, I
was invited to a stage for the first
time.
That's right.
I was invited to a stage and the role
was a ghost fox.
A ghost fox?
Yes.
I don't know if everyone is familiar
with it.
A ghost fox?
That's right.
A fox that haunts people?
Yes.
A fox that has been raising a boy who
has been friends with a tanuki for a
long time.
The stage is called KENGA KIMI.
Originally, it was a game.
I see.
The world of games is also bright.
I have a deep image of anime.
I like it very much.
That's right.
When you heard the role, did you feel
like this was the right role?
I was very happy.
I see.
What was the name of the character?
The ghost fox.
So I put on the ears and the tail.
You put on the ears and the tail.
That's a cute thing.