Please wait for our next video!
It's fine You can leave
Yay!
I pushed her for no reason
It's started
So, it's sudden but
Do you know who I am?
Yes
Which one?
What about you, Kaaya?
You know me the best
I know you the best too
Really?
I see
Today's topic is
Story survey
Yay!
So, we have to understand ourselves
Yes, we have to tell our stories
So, we asked you 10 questions in advance
Thank you
The member who you think is the most
likely to be the tomato is
You can choose the 10th place
We have to guess where we are in the
10th place
The difference between the member who
you think is the most likely to be the
tomato is
Then, you might be the tomato
It's embarrassing
We are going to imagine that we are not
the tomato
I'm sorry
Thank you
ーThe first questionー
ーYou look energetic todayー
ーThat's trueー
ーThe first questionー
ーWho looks the most athletic?ー
ーThat's not itー
ーWait, this is embarrassingー
ーThe first questionー
ーOne, twoー
What?
1.5th place
1.5th place?
I'm not very athletic
but I want to be athletic
I'm doing my best to be the best
I'm in the 1st place
I see
Let's leave it for now
I'll do it again when I don't get a good
result
I'll leave it for now
I'm in the 1st place
I want to be the best
Cool
I'm in the 2nd place
Well...
I'm a little...
Are you embarrassed?
I'm a good person
I'm saying something very embarrassing
Please announce the result
I'll announce the result in order from
the 1st place
Suddenly?
1st place
Yasumori
I'm so sad
Thank you
I'm in the 1st place
Next, 1.5th place
1.5th place or 2nd place is
Date-san
What?
I'm embarrassed
Really?
I'm surprised
What made me in the 2nd place?
What?
3rd place
Why?
I'm wrong
I'm just a prediction
I'm embarrassed
4th place is
Kazuki
5th place is
Sakura
6th place is
Fujisaki
7th place is
Tachibana
8th place is
Yuna
I think I know more about her
I see
2nd question
Who is the smartest?
This is...
ウッズ? ウッズ?
It's my turn.
I know.
Ready, go!
I'll start from you.
3rd place is...
4th place is...
2nd place is...
Oh no, it's the highest!
But there's a reason.
I saw a test on YouTube.
I was 2nd place.
Shinjyu was 1st place.
So I think everyone watching this is
thinking about me.
3rd place is the smartest.
3rd place is...
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
Science is a good thing, isn't it?
Science is a good thing.
I think you're smart.
It's like a nuance.
It's a feeling.
This is...
It's a joke.
What's the reason for the second place?
I prepared this because...
Well, it's just...
Let's make this four.
You forgot to erase it.
Let's make it three.
Don't try to guess.
Calm down.
This is...
I think it's just normal.
So, I'm in the 9th place.
I thought it would be nice if it was the
middle class.
Please announce the results.
The first place is...
Kichizuka.
The second place is...
I'm embarrassed.
3rd place is Hazuki.
I think I should die again.
I'm wrong.
4th place is Ritsuki.
I thought it was that stupid.
I'm going to leave the distance.
5th place is Yasumori.
I'm half right.
I'm embarrassed.
I want to be in the top 10.
Please.
6th place is Tachibana.
I lost to Tachibana.
I'm embarrassed.
7th place is Sakurasu.
you closed it
Why?
That was cute
This is...
You guys are the weird ones.
But as a result...
Let's have a study contest with Iginari-
chan.
Question 3.
Who has the biggest voice?
This is...
Isn't it overwhelming?
But...
Wait, wait, wait.
But it's surprisingly out.
When we were in the army...
There's a scene where we go, bam!
Ready, go!
Ta-da!
1st place!
7th place!
What is this?
I wonder.
What is it?
I think I'm going to be able to sing.
1st place.
Date-san.
You're happy, aren't you?
I'm happy I got it.
2nd place.
5th place.
It's surprising.
3rd place.
Fujitani-san.
4th place.
Sakura-san.
5th place.
Hazuki-san.
6th place.
Yasamori-san.
7th place.
Ritsuki-san.
8th place.
Kichise-san.
9th place.
What?
Seriously?
I didn't expect this.
I thought the number 1 or 2 would be the
number 10.
I thought so too.
But I think I'm the one who's thought of
being the cutest girl in the world.
Oh no, I'm the loudest one.
Question 4.
Who's the loudest?
Wow.
I think I'm the loudest.
I've never shown my true self in a meal.
Ready, go!
Ta-da!
2nd place.
4th place.
3rd place.
I love meat rice.
I want to be the 2nd place.
I see.
I'm the 4th place.
I don't know myself well.
So I'll try to be in the middle.
I'm not sure.
I think it's because you're saying that
you like sweets.
I think you're the top.
You said you love rice.
Please tell us the result.
1st place.
I'm the first place.
2nd place.
3rd place.
I've been guessing for a long time.
You're good.
You know yourself well.
3rd place.
Sakura.
4th place.
Tachibana.
Tachibana is the first place.
I'm the first place.
I'm the last place.
5th place.
Yasunori.
I see.
I'm the first place.
6th place.
Fujii Kanna.
7th place.
Ritsuki.
8th place.
Kitano.
9th place.
7th place.
Tachibana is not that good.
I agree.
I'm glad I got it right.
Wow.
Ta-da.
You don't know who you are.
Question 5.
Who is the member who hates food the
most?
Have you ever said that in front of
people?
That you hate it.
I've been told not to say that in front
of people.
Come here.
What's this?
5th place! 7th place!
8th place!
The reason is that you hate natto.
But as you get older, you get to eat
more.
I think that's why you're 5th place.
I don't know.
But you don't seem to have a problem
with it.
I don't hate it, but I don't eat it
because I like it.
It's different from what you think.
So I want to make it a number that I
don't know.
I see.
You don't hate natto.
And you don't hate it because you don't
eat it.
So I'm confident that you'll eat it
again.
1st place!
Ritsuki!
Ritsuki?
I don't think so.
What is this?
It's not a matter of time.
It's an image that I think.
2nd place! Sakura!
3rd place! Fujitani!
4th place! Kichisue!
5th place! Date!
I'm so happy.
Why?
I'm scared.
6th place! Hazuki!
7th place! Yasumori!
It's the opposite.
If you exchange it, it's a panel.
Maybe.
7th place! Yasumori!
I got it.
You don't know yourself.
You know yourself best.
If you exchange it, it's a panel.
8th place! Kitano!
I know.
You're right.
9th place! Tachibana!
It's hard to decide the order, but it's
different from the real thing.
It's still hard to decide.
Question 6. Who seems to have the most
out-of-work?
I'm not good at guessing the first
place.
I can tell the first place right away.
If I had to guess the first place,
But the results so far are different
from the facts.
That's right.
But I want to believe the facts.
Because it's the truth.
One, two, three!
Chaka-chan!
Yua-chan and Kodaya-chan are in sixth
place!
I'm in third place.
I'm in third place too.
Question 7. What is your favorite
member?
I like her.
I thought someone would notice.
I knew it.
She's cute.
I didn't think she'd be like this.
I don't think I'm very out-of-work.
I'm good at guessing.
I think you're right.
I think I'm older than her.
I think I spend most of my time at home.
I'm in third place.
I'm in third place because I'm in a
famous show.
I'm in the middle of a cafe.
I think I'm in a lot of cafes.
I'm in the middle of a restaurant.
I think I'm in third place because I'm
in the middle of a restaurant.
I'm serious.
Please.
The first place is...
Kazuki-san!
Everyone knows me.
I'm in second place.
Ritsuki-san!
I'm in third place.
Yasumori-san!
It's a start!
I got two in a row.
I was surprised by the previous one.
Of course.
I'm in fourth place.
Date-san!
You're still in high school.
I'm in fifth place.
Kitami-san!
Yay!
I'm in fifth place!
It's like an athening game.
I'm in fifth place.
I'm in the middle of a cafe.
Fujitani-san is in sixth place.
Sakura-san is in seventh place.
Kichisa-san is in eighth place.
Tachibana-san is in ninth place.
Thank you for watching.
I see. This is the image.
But I don't know the real thing.
Everyone is like that.
I know that there are many unexpected
things, but I don't know.
I'm going to grab it.
I'm going to grab something. I'm going
to grab it.
Yasumori Waka, please tell me the
answer.
I'm going to grab something with a
spark.
Yasumori Waka, I'm going to grab
something.
Question 7. Who looks the strongest in
the morning?
This is a quick answer.
I'm going to answer.
2, 3, 1.
1, 2, 3 people in the top three.
I think so.
These three are really strong.
I think Yasumori Waka is in first place,
so I chose 2.
I'm in second place.
I'm going to sleep.
No.
You're going to sleep.
I don't sleep deeply when I'm on a trip.
I always wake up early.
I think I'm going to lose to these two.
I chose 3.
I'm very honest.
I'm not sleeping.
I sometimes pack my luggage and leave
when I wake up.
I don't think this is the image of the
person.
I'm not hurt.
I'm very honest.
Please tell me the answer.
1, Yasumori Waka.
Thank you.
2, Kitami.
This is the opposite.
Next is Kurewa.
3, Yasumori Waka.
I think it's Soda Asayoshi.
It's not Sada Ichi.
4th place.
Datesu no Nen.
Did you notice that I've been sleeping
recently?
But it's not the top.
If it's the top.
I'm looking forward to the bottom.
5th place.
Kichisetsu.
Oh, no.
6th place.
Hazuki.
7th place.
Fujikawa Natsuki.
Hachi.
Ritsuki.
9th place, Sakurazawa.
It's not good to put it in the top 10.
It's not good.
It's different for each person.
Weakness and strength.
The image...
I can't follow it.
Who is it?
Question 8.
The person with the most luggage.
This is the first person, right?
Yes.
I'm sure it's me.
Ta-da!
9th place!
5th place!
7th place!
You guys are pretty behind.
I thought I was the least one.
I was surprised.
I thought you were the least one.
You were like, is that all you have?
Yeah, I was told that.
Even if everyone's suitcases are big,
I always use the small ones.
I see.
I'm not good at having a lot of luggage.
I have a lot of luggage during the live
show,
but I don't have much privacy.
That's why I think I'm in the middle.
You're really good at making decisions.
You're the 7th place with a woman's gut
feeling.
What's the correct answer?
1st place!
Tachibana!
This is...
I think it's a good one.
You have a lot of shoulders.
2nd place!
Mitsuki!
Oh!
3rd place!
Fujitani!
I think it's the first place.
4th place!
Sakurasu!
Hmm...
5th place!
Hazuki!
Oh!
6th place!
Kitami!
Oh!
It's not much different.
6th place!
Yay!
I got it!
You got it!
That's great.
7th place!
Kichisei!
Oh!
8th place!
Yasumori!
Oh!
Okay!
You can do it!
Look!
Oh!
I can't believe it.
It's a twisted 8.
Okay!
But only one is different.
9th place!
Date-san!
I got it!
Why?
It's exactly as I imagined.
It was exactly as I imagined.
Question 9.
Who is the member who seems to be most
impulsive?
Wow!
I'm worried about this.
Ready, go!
5th place!
9th place!
6th place!
Wow!
Why?
I have an image that I used to buy a lot
of things.
I have an image.
I have an image that I used to buy a lot
of things.
But I think I'll just buy it.
I'll buy it if I want it.
It's been a month since I bought it
online.
I'll buy it.
I'm in 9th place.
I'm not impulsive.
Basically.
So I'm in 9th place.
I'm in 4th place.
You said you liked old clothes.
I have an image of clothes, so I think
I'm impulsive.
And if it's an old clothes, I think I'll
buy it.
That's true.
I'll announce the result.
1st place!
Paz!
I'm in the same place.
I have an image.
2nd place!
Pachimano-san!
Wow!
I don't think I'm impulsive.
3rd place!
Fujitani-san!
4th place!
Sakurazan!
What?
5th place!
Yasumori-san!
Wow!
I'm in the same place!
6th place!
Ritsuki-san!
What?
You're serious.
7th place!
Datesan!
Can you make this 7th place?
I think I can.
I'm in the same place.
Wow.
It's a cave.
8th place.
Kichisenshu.
I'm here.
Q. What is the most messy room?
Hmm...
What?
Are you saying the most messy room?
Ready, go!
3rd place!
Mine is 9th place.
9th place?
Wow...
It's a bit like that.
But you know,
you guys are saying that you like messy
rooms.
I'm saying it to you guys.
I'm saying it so it's overwhelming.
1st place...
Fujita.
I'm sorry.
My ranking is Fujita.
2nd place...
Date.
What?
At least 3rd place.
3rd place...
Sakura.
I knew it.
4th place...
Tatsuki.
5th place...
Tachibana.
6th place...
Ritsuki.
7th place...
Kichisei.
8th place...
Katsuki.
Yasunori. 役割りさん.
9th place, Kitami
I'm glad I didn't get it right.
So, I got all the answers right.
The number of correct answers.
Yasumori got 3 points.
Kitami got 1 point.
Date got 4.5 points.
4.5 points?
So, Kay was the most understanding.
Yasumori got 3 points.
I understand what you're thinking.
I agree with your image.
I can't hide my image.
I agree.
I think I was honest.
I have a serious question.
Is it an image?
Yes, it is.
Thank you for watching.
See you next week.
Please subscribe to the channel.
Thank you.