I made the bento from scratch.
I made the one with the side dishes.
I think you'll want to eat it right
away.
I'll eat one by one.
If I hadn't done the chair dance, I
wouldn't be here.
If I hadn't done the chair dance, it
would have been difficult.
I'm impressed by your skills.
I want you to eat it.
Yakan and Idol
One day, Yakan, who was sleeping in the
living room of the Star Dust
headquarters, showed up.
His name is Yakan.
Yakan, who is interested in idols, will
make delicious tea for the people of
Star Dust.
Please let me talk to the idols.
The people of Star Dust who are kind and
tea-loving are okay.
Yakan, who was born in the dormitory,
was born as an idol.
Today, we have Yakan, who grew up in the
dormitory of Viva Home.
Let's get started.
Let's call today's guest.
This is an idol.
I'm Chihho Takaichi from BOLT.
Nice to meet you.
I got a call from BOLT.
Yakan, please.
Thank you.
I feel like talking to Yakan today.
This is my first experience.
Thank you.
I got my first experience.
Mr. Takaichi, I think you have your
favorite autumn.
I love it.
I heard that you are familiar with
drawing artistic illustrations.
Really?
I made my art debut in this autumn.
What is your art debut?
I sell my original digital art.
Did you have a picture book?
Yes.
Really?
I'm sorry.
Have you finished drawing?
Yes.
Please put me in the inn.
Yakan, can I come in?
I don't think so.
I think so.
Can I draw Yakan?
You can draw Yakan.
Can I draw now?
Now.
You are doing NFT here.
Everyone was taking a cute picture.
Do you like Yakan?
I like Yakan.
Are you happy?
Please draw Yakan while talking.
Will you go away?
I'm the type to finish drawing quickly.
Please go away.
What do you care about when you draw me?
It's important not to think.
I'm worried.
I don't care about drafts.
Yakan and IDOL.
I finished drawing Yakan.
Please introduce yourself.
This is Yakan.
I can imagine the atmosphere of Yakan.
I don't know.
Is this a 30-piece work?
Yes.
I don't know.
Each artist has his own way of drawing.
Thank you for drawing me.
I will give you a present.
I was glad that I was doing a cheer
after receiving a present.
I was told that it would have been
difficult if I hadn't done it.
I was told.
I was told that it was because of the
cheer.
Thank you for watching.