Ready, come on!
This week's Ebichu-TasTas is Kobayashi
Kaho's Ebichu-Tas! Kobayashi Project!
The members are having a fun time with
the project that Kobayashi came up with.
And also...
Kobayashi's dream since he was a child,
to fly a giant paper airplane to the
sky!
Demigod you.
Emityu Fastasu, Start!
Modokashii kanjou kakete hyaku
This frustrating feeling, I'll multiply
it by 100
Jyaa! Jyaa!
Mitou na
I'm so into you that I can't stop
What should I do with my heart that's so
full of you?
Moratorium, moratorium, moratorium,
middle school students
Add all kinds of things to private Ebisu
Middle School!
Ebisu Middle School
This program is brought to you by the
following sponsors.
It's started. Ebichu Tastasu.
It's just the two of us today.
It's started calmly.
What's going on?
Trick or Treat!
I heard a voice. What?
She's laughing so much.
What? What? What?
Trick or Treat!
What is Trick or Treat?
I don't know anything.
You're going to prank me!
She's just going ahead without asking.
Is it Halloween?
Halloween's cosplay?
I'm wearing a costume today.
The cheerleaders are already in a big
mess.
It's been a month since Halloween.
What's this costume?
It's a zashiki-warashi.
You can't draw this.
She probably drew this because she
doesn't know.
You can't tell without this.
What's going on?
Today, I'm going to do what I want to
do.
I'm going to prank Ebisu-san and
Kobayashi.
I see.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Do you remember?
Last year, Mariko Nakayama broadcasted a
show where she did what she wanted to
do.
Too free, it so felt like the vivid
flight time was lost.
In the previous episode of Nakayama
World, the members and staffs kept on
being shaken.
It's a legendary project.
The second episode of such member
project.
Tonight, the project of Kobayashi Kouan
is going to be a big one.
What kind of development will it be?
You wanted to do this Halloween cosplay,
right?
That means, the members are doing the
same cosplay.
I chose it.
Then, let's call them.
Everyone, come on!
Come here.
One of them doesn't know who it is.
Everyone, say something.
It's a TV.
Halloween that Kobayashi imagines is a
big gathering of Japanese youkai.
What a strange world view.
Kobayashi schneezes shrimp.
their forbidden romance was finally set
in motion.
This is all cooked by Kobayashi.
Yes, it's exactly as I imagined.
It's exactly as Kobayashi imagined.
This is exactly as I imagined.
I understand this.
This is cucumber and cup.
Yes.
I understand.
Next.
This is Konagi-jiji.
But...
The quality of this is not good.
The feeling of the tape.
You shouldn't show such a tape.
Who is this?
Who is Matsuno?
This is Nurali-hyo.
Nurali-hyo?
How do you feel?
It's hard to say.
It's cold.
Next.
This is a waterfall.
This is a party people.
This is good.
What is this?
This is a cat girl.
This is cute.
This looks like Hiroto's hairstyle.
It looks like it's coming from the back.
This is just right.
This is closed.
What is this?
This is a cat.
You shouldn't hold this.
This is cute.
I will do it with the members above.
The members above.
What?
Kasa said something.
Who?
I thought it was Kasa.
What is this?
This is Kasa.
That's right.
This is Mayama.
This is Mayama?
This suits her.
This is a high quality.
This is amazing.
This was fun.
This is not just Halloween.
This is scary.
What is this?
What did you do?
I laugh easily.
I want to do a project that doesn't make
me laugh.
A project that doesn't make you laugh.
Are you okay?
What is Kobayashi?
We are very noisy.
She laughs easily.
Please watch again.
In the meeting with the staff in
advance,
I laugh, so if you can do something that
I won't laugh at,
I'm happy. Congratulations.
I think it's interesting.
What kind of project will Emi do,
imagining a project that doesn't make
her laugh?
Kobayashi presents, a project that
doesn't make her laugh.
Let's do it.
It's a K-1 Grand Prix that you can't
laugh at.
K-1 Grand Prix.
So, K-1 Grand Prix means fighting?
No, no.
What does it mean?
It's a festival.
Kobayashi's K.
Oh, Kobayashi's K.
That's what it means.
Not this one.
Not this one?
K-1 Grand Prix is not a laughing match.
It's a laughing battle between two
teams.
The rules of this battle are to endure
laughter and to be eliminated if you
laugh.
The team that laughs the most wins.
The winning team will get a gift from
Kobayashi Kōan.
What is it?
Can I open it?
I'll eat my favorite dumplings with
yakitoshi.
Kobayashi Kōan will divide the team.
I'll eat the dried fish.
Yasumoto Kōan will eat the dried fish.
Shime Matsuno will eat the dried fish.
Kobayashi Kōan's team is a team that
can't hold back laughter.
Is this a strategy to make them laugh
quickly?
The Mayama team is a team that can't
hold back laughter.
All the members are tough.
The first half is the side where the
Tobayashi team makes people laugh.
The Mayama team is the defense.
How long can they not laugh?
The K-1 Grand Prix that you can't laugh
at, starts now!
It's already started?
Good luck!
Yes!
What? What?
What should I do?
Earth extinction, one day before
Wait, this is the one that Chuu-nee-san
did
One hour before
Hoshina, out!
I'm going to go again
What are you doing?
Nura-ri-hyo
What?
Chuu-ara-ya!
I got it!
Let's fix your makeup!
Let's eat!
I'm happy!
Amayama Out! Hirota Out!
Time's up!
It's over?
Okinawa Out!
Nakayama, you should clap at Matsuno.
That was funny.
I was thinking of doing that.
I'm a little disappointed.
The record is 1 minute 9 seconds.
At the end, the face of Kashiwagi became
a deadly blow and blew out at once.
Next, the Mayama team is doing a funny
attack.
Will Kobayashi's team be able to hold
back their laughter?
K-1 Grand Prix, second half, start!
Ready, go!
She's a poor girl who has no parents.
Please let her be happy.
She's doing this on the street.
She's really a poor girl.
Poor girl.
5 points out!
You're a fool!
You're a fool who only knows bad things!
You're in danger!
Come back!
She's coming back.
You're in danger.
You're a poor girl.
You're doing your best.
You're a poor girl who has no parents.
Please let her be happy.
She's doing this on the street.
5 points out!
Poor girl.
Please let her be happy.
deliberating
She heard both screams
Thank you for watching!
What's going on?
You're good at this game
You're good
Good luck
What?
Oh no
Cute
Rina-san
Oh no
The record is 1 minute 35 seconds.
The K-1 Grand Prix is won by Team
Kobayashi.
Let's see the prize.
Open.
1 minute 35 seconds.
If you have a lot, you can't eat it all.
I can't eat it all.
Thank you for the meal.
Kobayashi is very satisfied with the
dumplings she loves.
She thinks it's over.
Are you satisfied?
No.
I'm not satisfied with this alone.
No way!
I want to fly a giant paper airplane!
At the meeting, Kobayashi said this.
I made a big one by attaching several
small origami.
I want to fly a big one with everyone by
folding origami.
You'll be very happy if you fly.
I'll be very happy.
I think I'll never fly a big one.
If you are determined to make the
biggest paper airplane in your life,
Can you do it? Can you do it?
Sweeeeetây auуr!...
It's Mr. Ahojirô's Giant Paper Airplane
Special!
Yaaay!
You're Mr. Ahojirô, right?
I'm Ahojirô.
I'm glad your dream came true.
I'm so glad.
Thank you.
Please say something to your mom.
Mom, I can fly an airplane with this!
Thank you.
I'm watching.
I'm sure your mom has heard it.
Kobayashi, challenging to make his dream
giant paper airplane.
But, he's worried about his dream just
because it's his first time.
So...
This time, we asked a paper airplane
specialist for help.
Mr. Jun Tanba, who has been a champion
of paper airplanes in Japan, will
support him in making a giant paper
airplane.
I think it's going to be difficult to
balance left and right.
So you want to do it more carefully?
Yes.
The teacher says that the bigger the
paper, the more difficult it is to fly a
paper airplane.
However, the origami that Kobayashi
prepared this time is...
Here it is!
It's huge!
It's so big!
It's huge, isn't it?
It's amazing.
It's coming in front of everyone.
It's 2m x 3m origami.
2m x 3m?
It's huge!
Origami that is bigger than you can
imagine.
Can he fly this?
This time, two giant paper airplanes
will be made in two parts.
All the members will challenge to make
Kobayashi's dream come true.
Let's start the giant paper airplane
experiment!
Yes!
Thank you!
It's the first time I've heard the word,
yes.
Please subscribe to the channel!
Fold it like this.
Kobayashi is actively giving
instructions for the realization of her
dream.
It's important to be straight.
Let's spread it out.
Please subscribe to the channel!
It's a paper airplane!
And...
It's done!
Let's look at it from this side.
Ready, set, go!
Everyone, flap your wings!
To the whole world,
with courage, dreams, and excitement!
Go!
Is that the name?
Yes, that's the name.
What is the name of this?
1, 2, 3, Kobayashi-dan!
Go!
I did it seriously, so I don't think I'm
joking.
You're joking a lot.
I'm not joking.
After this, Kobayashi's dream will go to
the sky.
Where did it go?
Kobayashi's dream, the giant paper
airplane, is complete!
The experiment is finally complete!
First, let's take off from the giant
paper airplane of Kahojirou's team!
We are now on the roof
How high can you fly this airplane?
The roof is 13 meters high
If you can fly 20 meters, it's good
enough
If you can fly well, you can fly 40
meters
How high do you want to fly?
I have to aim for 20 meters
If you can fly well, you can fly 20
meters
Giant paper airplane that they have been
longing for since they were young
Let's go to the sky
Let's go
Kobayashi No.3, launch
How was it?
Where did it go?
Ah!
After the flight, was he blown away by
the wind?
Or did Komayashi-san fall down with
regret?
How was it?
Where did he go?
He disappeared!
Unfortunately, the huge paper airplane
that Komayashi-san wished for...
...was blown away.
But the huge paper airplane of Hirota-
han shows a miracle
How far do you want to go?
I want to go to the blank
So if you hit the blank, it's about 60m?
Let's go!
Everyone, fly!
Courage, dreams and inspiration are all
over the world!
Here we go!
Ready, go!
Wow!
What's going on?
Ready, go!
Wow!
After the flight, she was flying well,
but she was hit by the wind and the
shape of the plane collapsed.
Chie-san, how many meters is the result?
The record is...
16.9 meters.
10m 55cm
10m?
But it's better than I thought
I don't know
Even though he was blown by the wind, he
managed to fly over 10m
Did Kobayashi's dream come true?
So Kobayashi, did you have fun?
I had a lot of fun
I'm glad to see the plane flying at the
end
Yes, it was like a real plane at the end
It was flying
The view was...
I was a bit disappointed that I was
blown away by the wind
Yes, you are blown away by the wind
The power of nature
The power of nature is amazing
That's true
Giant paper airplane experiment
It didn't fly much, but Kobayashi seems
to be satisfied, so the experiment was
successful
Please subscribe to this channel
Studies Unit in the production group of
movie with I-Trunc
Snake Ebi três
Here, really right in halloween,
The 4th one-man live
Sakurai Bees have stepped up step by
step after experiencing many stages.
This time, they will make a big
announcement.
Next, we will show you our new song!
The new song is completed.
Let's see the first performance.
I want to know more and more about you
Good Good Chicago
A shining breakfast
Time flies by so quickly
If we're together forever and ever
We'll draw our first love pattern
I want you to tell me what you like
Let's dance together
No matter what we do, we're always
together
We're a perfect team
Let's dance together
And lastly, the youngest member Serizawa
Moa Moa
The six of them perform together
The fragments of our memories are
connected
To the future we saw that day
And so, the 5th One-Man Live will be
held on Christmas.
The program will continue to follow
Sakurai Bees.
Kobayashi's second half of the project
He talks with his mentor Yasumoto
And then...
Wait, wait!
A sudden twist and the scene freezes
And then, a new project of the Christmas
University Games begins
Good job!
The next day
This program was brought to you by these
sponsors.