Ebichu no Douga Toka!
I'm Marika, 30,000 yen before my birth
date.
I was told to go to Ichiran when I was
in high school.
I didn't think Ichiran was so famous.
Everyone said, let's go to Ichiran.
I was surprised that there was such a
famous ramen shop.
That's why I decided to go to Ichiran.
When I was a kid, I wanted to eat ramen
every day.
I like Kuromaya ramen the most.
I love the miso of Kuromaya ramen.
I eat a lot of cup ramen.
My family has a time to eat cup ramen
after meals.
My favorite ramen is a sesame ramen.
It says sesame on the package.
It's so delicious that I can't think of
it as a cup ramen.
I want to eat it after meals.
I eat a little expensive cup ramen on
the day I work hard for a reward.
I want to eat it in the morning.
I want to eat sesame ramen in the
morning.
I want to eat it today.
I eat it after the live.
There are people who eat it before the
live.
I want to eat a light meal.
I want to eat something salty.
My mom exercises before she cooks.
It's a long time and I get hungry in the
meantime.
I'm going to eat snacks.
Don't you eat?
I did.
I did it when I was in middle school.
I ate instant noodles at home.
I'm going to the supermarket to buy it.
I'm going to the supermarket.
There are a lot of vegetables and
fruits.
The fruits look delicious.
This is a side dish section.
There is also meat.
I boil it and put it on ramen.
This is a noodle section.
I will choose.
I will choose the ramen I want to eat
before the live.
I don't care about what I eat before the
live.
I choose the ramen that doesn't smell on
the microphone.
I will talk to myself before the live.
I want a ramen that is as oily as
possible before the live.
I want to enjoy the noodles and drink
the soup.
I don't want to be over-eaten.
I don't want to eat a lot of food.
I want a ramen that is light and easy to
eat.
I want a ramen that is stable and has a
gentle taste of eggs.
I want a ramen that is oily.
I choose chicken ramen before the live.
I choose the ramen I want to eat in the
morning.
I want to eat a lot in the morning.
I'm worried about which ramen to choose.
I like UFO ramen.
I feel UFO ramen is night.
I want to eat UFO ramen after drinking
alcohol.
I want to eat UFO ramen with a lot of
pickled ginger.
I choose the ramen I want to eat in the
morning.
I want to eat UFO ramen with mayonnaise.
I choose ramen for snack time.
I choose seafood noodles.
I can arrange it.
I can add kimchi.
I can make it with milk.
It's more creamy and delicious.
I can also add ice cream.
I can add anything.
I want to enjoy various flavors when I
eat it for snack time.
I choose seafood noodles.
I choose ramen for entrance exam study.
I studied for the entrance exam while
listening to the radio.
I was a cultural broadcaster.
I recommend ramen.
I recommend ACE COOK.
I saw a lot of commercials for the Super
Cup.
I think this is a Super Cup.
The amount of ramen is large.
It's for students.
I recommend ramen for entrance exam
study.
I choose ramen for entrance exam study.
I choose ramen for snack time.
I think you don't have such a culture.
I have a snack time at home.
I eat ramen alone before and after
eating.
I eat ramen with my family after eating.
I have such a culture.
I choose ramen before eating.
I usually eat ramen for snack time.
I eat new products and food that I have
never eaten.
I don't care about eating before eating.
I choose food that increases my
appetite.
I choose spicy food.
I choose ramen.
I like ramen.
I like ramen very much.
I eat ramen before and after eating.
I put soup stock in ramen.
I eat ramen with a mild taste.
I eat ramen before eating.
This looks delicious.
Recently, I eat mixed noodles.
I eat ramen because it is a popular
dish.
I eat this.
I eat this because it is a popular dish.
I don't put noodles in ramen.
I eat this because it is delicious.
This soup is light.
This soup is light and easy to drink.
I like this ramen very much.
I eat this often.
This ramen contains soy sauce and dried
seaweed.
I like this simple taste.
I'm curious about mixed noodles.
I have never eaten this.
I like this.
I buy this.
I bought this.
I want a little extra.
I like to put kelp in ramen.
I like kelp very much.
I eat ramen with only kelp.
I think this is delicious.
I put this in ramen.
I put kimchi in ramen.
Kimchi and ramen go well together.
I have chosen this.
I pay.
I chose this, but it doesn't taste like
soy sauce.
I feel like I want to eat this.
I look like a junky.
I have never bought this much.
I got a receipt.
I think I can just eat it as usual.
It's amazing.
It's easy to know what I like.
I can choose the amount of food I want.
I often choose a big ramen.
I want to eat a lot of delicious food.
Because I'm a human.
I bought it.
It's raining as soon as I bought it.
I'm back.
Let's review.
Chicken ramen is for before live.
Shin ramen is for before meal.
I'm going to open it.
Super cup MAX is for studying for
entrance exam.
Seafood noodle is for snack.
I want to eat this ramen for breakfast.
This is the salt mixed noodles sold by
Maruchan Seimen.
I was curious about this, so I wanted to
eat this.
This is the sesame ramen.
This is my favorite ramen.
I eat this with salt.
What should I eat for breakfast?
There was nothing.
What was there?
I found this.
I eat a lot in the morning.
It says YOMISE YAKISOBA.
I don't care.
I put hot water in it.
3 minutes.
It's about 3 minutes.
I throw away hot water.
Then I put mayonnaise.
This is the sauce.
Sprinkle it.
Mayo beam.
I can't do it at all.
I'll eat it.
I ate it with mustard. It's delicious.
I'm getting sleepy.
I ate it with mustard.
It was delicious.
I'm going to the office.
I'm going.
I'm not in a good voice condition today.
I'll make my throat smooth with this
chicken ramen.
3 minutes?
3 minutes have passed.
This is it.
Let's eat.
Mmm.
It's good.
I feel safe eating this chicken soup.
My throat is getting hot.
It's good.
I'll do my best at the live show.
It's hot.
I'm going to eat this.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Is the food ready yet?
Are you going to cook it now?
I'm hungry.
It's 8 o'clock.
Can I eat ramen first?
I'll eat it.
I'm irritated when I'm hungry.
I eat Shin Ramen at this time.
I'll make it refreshing.
It's spicy.
I'll add hot water.
It smells good.
I want to eat it.
Finally, 3 minutes have passed.
I'll eat it.
It smells like Zoshin Ramen.
This is Zoshin Ramen.
It's spicy.
I'm getting tired of it.
I'll put in a little bit of kelp.
I'll eat it.
It's good.
It's a little mild.
Did you make dinner?
Okay.
I'll eat.
I'll eat. I'll eat ramen too.
Oh.
It's 3 o'clock.
I'm kind of...
I'm kind of hungry.
I should eat some seafood.
Seafood is the best snack.
I'll eat.
All right.
I put kimchi in the refrigerator. I'll
eat it.
Kimchi goes well with this seafood soup.
It looks delicious.
I always eat the seasoning because it's
delicious.
Octopus is delicious.
I will put the sauce in the soup.
I put a little less sauce.
I wait 3 minutes.
3 minutes have passed.
It's been 2 minutes, but I feel it's
been 3 minutes.
The noodles look good.
I eat this.
This taste is delicious.
This is the taste.
It's good.
The best point of this is that it
doesn't taste like seafood at all.
It's a little mild.
I'll put kimchi in it because it's too
mild.
It's good.
It's absolutely delicious.
I want to take a picture of this.
It looks delicious.
I don't mix the ingredients that I have.
I eat this.
The sourness of kimchi and the soup of
seafood go well together.
Tastes good.
I'm quite sure
this is what it is called
proper cup noodles
Have an atmosphere
you know
something you can arrange
and
eat as well
And it doesn'tardo more to the stomach
This is the good thing about seafood
noodles.
I've eaten a lot of cup noodles, but I'm
a little full today.
I'll introduce you to the 5 crappy
things I've used.
I'd like you to eat it.
I'd like you to eat it and tell me how
delicious it is.
I'd like to call you.
Thank you.
Is this your favorite?
Yes, this is my favorite.
Let's eat.
I'm eating yakisoba.
This cup ramen has a delicious soup.
It's very sesame.
How long did you boil it? 3 minutes?
Yes, 3 minutes.
Please warm the oil on the lid.
Are you a noodle person?
Yes, I am.
People who are a noodle person want to
eat it quickly.
I said it earlier.
I think so.
Do you usually eat cup ramen?
I don't eat it.
I used to buy it.
I bought it because it was fun to buy
it.
My wife usually eats it.
I'm not a wife.
I'm a wife.
It's been 3 minutes.
I will eat it.
Please look at this.
It's like a YouTuber.
I put this in this.
This is sesame.
Yes, this is sesame paste.
If it's really good.
This is delicious.
Please mix it well.
It's important to mix it well.
It's going to be there.
Let's eat.
It smells like sesame.
It's sesame.
Yeah.
It's good.
You can smell it, right?
The aroma is good.
It's like a rich peanut butter.
It's like peanut butter.
It's like a sesame that exceeds sesame.
It's good.
It's high quality.
It's like a tonkotsu ramen with sesame.
But it has a lot of sesame and paste.
It's good.
As expected of Chef Lepe.
Please try it.
It was a bonus video.