This week's Ebichu Tastas will continue
last week and head to the Daikyo
amusement park!
The last game battle will be a hit!
Furthermore...
I want to go to the amusement park!
Ebichu Tastas Star Phone
urban Ebisu middle school
Add many things to the city's urban
Ebisu high school.
outta Ebisu
Family
This program is sponsored by the sponsor
学ば系
The members who came to the popular spot
in Ichikawa City, Daikeen in Chiba
Prefecture
The game battle between the two teams
has started
Who will be the one to get the original
jumper of Daikeen?
In the first battle, the representative
Matsuno and Yasumoto will battle
The two teams will compete for the first
place and win the game
The second battle is the body-eye game
The oldest, Mayama and the youngest,
Nakayama, are competing seriously
Even though they are fighting in a low
level, they are still tied at the same
point
The third battle, the goldfish speed, is
a team competition
Ah, I'm already wet
Nakayama, open it!
Matsuno's unexpected talent has been
evolved
Matsuno's team has won!
Currently, Matsuno's team is in the lead
with 100 vs 50
The match is finally...
Climax!
This is really wide
And now, before going to the final
battle, let's refresh with a break time
It's break time now, and actually, there
is a hidden camera at Ebichu-chan's
place
You can hear what Ebichu-chan is talking
about
Let's listen to what he is talking about
This is absolutely almost food
Let's listen
Wow, amazing!
It's a break room!
This time, they set up a hidden camera
in a break room for the members
What kind of story will they tell?
I thought they would talk about food,
but...
I didn't think they would come again.
Really?
It was cold when we first went.
It was cold, it was really cold.
Because it was November.
We will go to the event.
It's a memory from last year.
The four members of Matsuno team filmed
the opening movie of Saitama Super Arena
Park here in the park.
The members are excited about the story
of the time.
It's a great idea.
It's going to be used in a set.
And then, the next single song.
Johnny, where's the piano? I haven't
heard it yet.
Johnny is in Hawaii.
It's like a sea.
Is it going to be in the sea?
After all, if you go to Hawaii, you
probably don't have time to play.
I'm going to go and come back soon.
It's like going to school.
Who? Mayama?
It's a realistic opinion.
It's like I know the water and sweet of
the entertainment world.
I'm hungry for now.
I'm hungry.
I've never heard a voice like that
before.
What's for lunch today?
What is it?
That's what the topic is.
I'm hungry.
I like udon.
I like the wheat.
I want to eat the weather udon.
What's the basic?
Is it a noodle?
Ayaka, do the voice challenge.
Let's do the voice challenge.
You can do the voice challenge.
I'm eating what I want to eat.
The voice challenge to say what you want
to eat in a loud voice.
Say it in a loud voice.
A very loud voice.
I ate rice porridge.
This angle is amazing!
I want to eat it!
No! No!
I want to eat the front!
Front! Front!
Ah, front!
Try it again!
No! No! No!
Front!
Front! Front!
Give me that!
We can fake healthcare withoutooo
I want to eat BBQ.
I want to eat bean sprouts.
I want to eat ramen.
I want to eat meat.
You can eat anything.
I want to eat ton-tanshi.
I want to bring gyoza.
I want to bring yui.
Bring the freezer!
So, the Ebitune members are talking
about food during the break time.
That's right.
And they are more excited than the
actual performance.
That's right.
So, Ebitune-chan, you have to eat lunch
quickly.
That's right.
If you don't do this, you won't be
excited for the actual performance.
That's right.
But, they have to endure a little longer
for lunch.
To the last battle!
After this, the final battle!
The hot-blooded slick kart battle!
Everyone beefmed up and went Iron Man!
And the Sakura Ladies' big announcement!
What is the last battle, Matsuno-san?
The famous Go Kart!
It's Go Kart!
The final battle is the Slick Kart!
Each team will compete in 2 races.
The broadcast will be 5 rounds. The
first place will get 150 points, the
second place will get 100 points, and
the third place will get 50 points.
Let's start the race.
Look at the screen.
The screen is over 155 cm.
There is a small child.
If you are under 155 cm, it's dangerous.
How tall are you?
154 cm.
154 cm!
What is it?
mail aussi
But he says he is growing, so he checks
it.
No, no, no, no.
Now, I thought it was about 160, but
it's extending.
It's extending!
Thank you!
No, no, no!
Why?
Takai san will judge this
No, no, no!
It's still floating
Still?
I can't ride it
Why? What's the speed?
Now
It's like it didn't go 154km per hour
Mayama's visit is decided
By the way, even children under 16 years
old can't ride it
So, children under 16 years old, raise
your hand
Kobayashi and Nakayama can't ride it,
but if you can ride it, it's OK
So, Chue san will ride it with you
Please try it!
Unfortunately, Mayama is going to watch
the race because there is only one car
for two people
Kobayashi and Nakayama will challenge
with Chue's female seat
So, let's start the first race!
The first race is between Matsuno and
Ogata
The one who runs first is Hirota
The one who runs first is the one who is
going to run first
The one who runs first is Hirota
And Matsuno chases after him
But at the second curve
Hirota is at an unexpected loss
Matsuno is in a big trouble
Kobayashi's center field is in the lead
Ogata is in the lead
He is not good at curves
But Matsuno is not good at curves
He is going to run first
The last curve
Hirota is in a big trouble
But at that time
He is going to run first
The last curve
It's so cool
The winner of the reverse battle is
Kobayashi and Chuei
2nd place is Ogata, 3rd place is Matsuno
and Hirota is Bili
The winner is...
Kobayashi
How was it?
I didn't have to drive
I was sitting next to him and it was so
fun
Everytime I turned, Kobayashi was
like...
And Chuei-san also got the switch and
you were able to drive well
I was able to drive well but I hit
Hirota once
Hirota was in the 1st place until the
end
I was able to drive fast
I got drunk at the end and I couldn't
drive
The winner of the 1st round is the
Yasumoto team
The 2nd race
The 2nd race is the battle between the
Matsuno team, Kashiwagi and Hoshina,
Yasumoto team, Yasumoto and Nakayama
Chuei team
3,2,1, start!
Hoshina's rocket start!
It's so scary!
Hoshino doesn't know how to brake and is
struggling with the curve.
Hoshino is struggling with the curve.
Hoshina is accelerating even more.
Chuu is trying to cut off the front of
the Nakayama Piano.
From theWoman who became Hinata Saito
And finally, the last lap
While Hoshina was fighting, Yasumoto
showed a stable driving and was in the
lead
And as he did, the goal is doing great
Hoshino is 2nd, Chuei is 3rd, and
Kashiwagi is 4th
Kashiwagi is 4th, Chuei is 5th, and
The second match, the one who is the
best is Yasumoto
Thank you
And the second place is Hoshina
And the third place is Nakayama Shurepei
And the last place is Kashiyaki
Safety driving is the most important
She is a real runaway
She is really a runaway
Safety driving
I can't turn, I have to hit the car
Hoshina-san always hit the car at that
corner
Every time
I can only hear the sound
Safety driving
Hoshina is also a runaway
Hoshina, please don't take a picture
with the license closed
I'll take a picture after a year
It's dangerous
Nakayama
She was on the car
How was it?
It was fun
You raised your hand a lot
What kind of face is that?
It was amazing
I was doing that
I was so excited that I was here
I did it like this
What are you doing?
I was so excited
My heart
Please do it
Thank you
Go
What are you doing?
What is that?
I'm excited
I don't know why
The winner is the Yasumoto team
Yay
I won
Has anyone forgotten?
Mayama-san, are you alive?
Mayama
Mayama, come
I have
Mayama-san
Mayama
Mayama, come
I won't go
Mayama, you're mean
I have
Mayama, come
I don't want to
So, they added a big show during the
trip
I have
Mayama, come
I don't want to
Mayama is angry
So, they played all day
Which team won?
First, I will announce the points of the
Matsuno team
Matsuno team has 350 points
I did my best
You did your best
And the team of Yasumoto
400 points for the team of Yasumoto
So the winner will receive a special
jumper
The winner will receive a special jumper
from the owner of Daikeien, Takahashi
You can work as a staff for 10 years
You can be like Kobayashi and Amagappa
The winner will receive a special jumper
from the owner of Daikeien, Takahashi
What will be added to the next task?
Everyone, look forward to it!
Thank you for watching!
Sakuraibisu Zensen!
This January, a research group was
announced to recruit students.
The name is Sakuraibisu!
Auditions are held nationwide.
Finally, tonight, the members are
decided!
The announcement will be broadcast on
TV!
Who will be the winner?
There are 4 winners
Sakura Ebisu is decided by 4 people
Until the announcement of Sakura Ebisu
Sakura Ebisu
The real B
This is the Ebichu Research Unit, Sakura
Ebis!
Now, let's introduce the members one by
one.
By the way, this is the first time we've
filmed it, so please watch it with a
warm heart.
So, the first one is...
I'm Misato Hakurayo. I'm 12 years old,
and I'm in the 6th grade of elementary
school.
From now on, I want to challenge myself
in various things and improve myself.
Thank you.
And the second one.
I'm Mizuha, 15 years old, and a first-
year high school student.
I joined Sakura Yubiz and I'm going to
experience a lot of things.
I hope I can grow as a group and as an
individual.
I look forward to working with you.
The third one is...
I'm Muraho Kirizu, 12 years old, 1st
year of middle school.
I want to enter Sakura Ebiz and
challenge various things.
I want to dance like Momoiro Clover's
Momoda Kanako-chan and Ebichu's Ayaka-
chan.
I want to challenge many things like
acrobatics.
I want to do my best from now on. Thank
you.
And the last one is...
I'm Ayame Kawashiro, 13 years old, 2nd
year of middle school.
I'm worried and anxious about joining
Sakura Ebis, but I'll do my best.
Thank you.
With the four members, Sakura Ebis has
finally started.
So, let's start the program with the
four members of Sakura Ebis.
Please show us your special skill in 30
seconds.
By the way, this is really the first
time to shoot, so please watch with warm
eyes.
First, what is the special skill of
Misato Sakurai?
I will imitate a gorilla
It started from the imitation of a
gorilla
Next is Mizuha
I'm a friend of a boy who puts his butt
out
Mizuha imitates a character
I, Fu-chan, play
I can't do it! Stop it!
Thank you.
And the third one, Murahoshi's specialty
is?
I will imitate Koma-san from Yokai
Watch.
Thank you for watching.
It's a night view.
Thank you.
Murakoshi managed to get on the stage.
And the last one is Kawase's special
skill.
And Takagi Neri-chan's turn.
As if you can go to the future as much
as possible with the courage to start
running on asphalt.
Thank you very much.
Well, then, is that all?
The Fujii Kocho that was watching it.
I think I have more courage than I
thought.
I'm still a complete amateur.
I think I did well at first.
Sakura Ebis was started like this.
In the future, we will surprise you with
the appearance of Sakura Ebis.
Please look forward to it.
Next time is the special edition of
shrimp chutas.
To celebrate the birthday of Kobayashi
Yasumoto born in June,
It should be the shrimp chutas birthday
party.
The first handmade birthday party is a
big mess.
And the members' thoughts and miracles.
Thank you for coming when I was
depressed.
Please look forward to it.
Today's theme is...
This program was provided by the
sponsors you see.
3, 2, 1,
Thank you!
No one is going to say it, right?
Why?
I'm the only one who has to say it.
Thank you for watching!