This week, we have the big news for the
new year, Ebichu Tastasu!
And so...
Mayama-chan!
Mayama's new catchphrase has been born!
Ebichu Tastasu, start!
Ikemo Nante Mo Irarenai Modokashii
Kanjou Kakeru Hyaku
I'm so into you that I can't stop
What should I do with my heart?
Monotrium, Monotrium, Monotrium
Middle school, Monotrium
Try adding various things to private
Ebisu Middle School
Why?
I'm so into you that I can't stop
This program is brought to you by the
following sponsors.
It's cold.
Today, we are at the Wangan Studio
Mirei-chan, since when have you been
absent from university?
I'm Mirei
You have a smaller face than usual today
You don't have legs
I have a little
Is it because Hoshina is absent today?
I'm absent from university today
It's been a long time since I saw a
mannequin
You have a smaller face than usual
It's very small
What are you going to do today?
I'm going to announce
It's the year-end event, Ebitu Tastasu,
the big news of 2016
I'd like to look back on the memorable
events of this year
You did it last year, didn't you?
Yes, I did it last year
Ebitu Tastasu, which had a lot of events
this year, is just a little bit away
from 2016
So, we are going to announce the
memorable events as the big news of
Ebitu Tastasu
The Grand Prix will be decided from the
event
By the way, do you have any personal
news?
Yes, we do
Matsuno-san, what is it?
I bought a dog
What is it?
It's a poodle
Toy-toy poodle
Why did you buy it at this timing?
Because it's a Kameido, and you didn't
see a toy poodle?
I saw it, but I think it has nothing to
do with it
It has nothing to do with it?
Hoshina has a big arm
It's a big arm
It's broken into pieces
Let's get started
Ebitu Tastasu, the big news of 2016
The first big news is here
What is it?
Jyan!
Hoshina is a college student and Mayama
is 20 years old!
I'm really surprised
Hoshina is also a college student
Is there anything that changed about
Hoshina?
Like what changed?
Sometimes when I'm on vacation I do my
nails
I'm like a girl's boy
I don't know
You were like a feather
I was like a fluffy feather
You were like a fluffy feather
Where is she going?
And Mayama's birthday is 2 days after
this show
That's when you turned 20
Mayama is 20 years old, so there is a
big problem
What is the Mayama 20th problem?
What is the catchphrase of Mayama?
It's a high tension girl
It's a girl at 20
20 is a girl
It's up to teens
So let's make a new catchphrase
Because you are 20
So we will think of a catchphrase for
Mayama at 20
Mayama will pick the catchphrase she
likes the most
If it's quick, it will be used at the
end of the year at the university
If you think about it properly
Everyone, Yasumoto is not joking right?
I'm not joking
Ah, she's not joking
Yasumoto's face is not joking
I'm joking
I'm not joking
This is not joking
What is the catchphrase that Yasumoto
thought seriously?
Gari Gari Ramen Junior High School
Leave this Gari Gari Ramen to me, and I
want junior high school students to do
this
Yasumoto, you're not joking right?
I'm joking
I'm joking!
Why are you so angry?
I'm not joking, I'm serious
You're serious right?
I'm serious
Next is Hirota's catchphrase
Muscle, muscular, angel, doll
That's good
It's perfect for Ayama
Girl is impossible but doll is
I see, you're stepping on the line
Girl is possible
Girl is impossible but doll is
Give up on girl
Why?
Next is Kobayashi Kouan's catchphrase
Teenager middle school student, Mayama T
What is Mayama T?
20 is 20, right?
That's why I wrote Mayama
I see
I think this is good too
Thank you
That's good
T is T
Mayama T is 5
You are tied up to that
What is Nakayama Kouan's catchphrase?
Ebichu's Hosomatcho 3
What is 3?
It's number 3
I see. Is there any movement?
Hosomatcho is slow and 3 is loud
It's like a technique
It's like listening to the movement
There is no movement
There is no movement?
Let's try it
Ebichu's Hosomatcho 3
Like this
Ebichu's Hosomatcho 3 2 1
Gari Gari Ramen Chugaku
Thank you for watching!
Now, everyone has their catchphrases
Who will Mayama choose?
Muscle, muscular, thin, and muscular
3,2,1
Mayama
It's so cool
I'm so happy
So you're going to do this next time
Yes
Do we have to do this on such a big
stage?
Yes, it's a big stage
Why did you choose this place?
Ebichu Tastasu's big news
Next is
Next news is
Nakayama's big news
There is a Nakayama project
Is there a Kobayashi project in a year?
Yes, there is
Following the Nakayama project, the
second member project in November
Ebituutasu Kobayashi will be held
He challenged to make a giant paper
airplane
By the way, we've seen Nakayama and
Kobayashi so far.
Is there anyone who wants to try next?
I've never thought about it.
Yasumoto, you?
Me?
Origami?
I've done it.
But Origami is really good.
Yasumoto, you're good at Origami?
Sometimes, you can make a dinosaur with
Origami.
3D?
What about you, Ayano?
I can make a Pakupaku.
Pakupaku?
So, you want to make a Pakupaku?
A giant Pakupaku.
A giant series?
It won't fly.
You mean, you drop it from the roof?
But it looks like it will fly.
It won't fly.
What's this?
Ebichu Tastasu, the big news.
Next.
Shandong!
Fashion competition, 3 consecutive wins.
Ebichu's fashion leader, Yasumoto.
The first winner of the popular project,
Ebichu Fashion Coordinate Battle is the
Yasumoto-Kashiwagi pair.
The second time, Yasumoto won.
They headed to Kameido in Hiroshima to
visit で honestly, Yasumoto still won.
And they ended theiracknowledged fashion
competition.
I'm sure they'll talk to me about the
clothes I'm wearing.
Like, it's nice.
Are you sure?
Who?
I don't know.
Who said that?
You can say anything.
Yasumoto-chan, who told you that?
Today, I thought the fluffy muffler
looked warm.
No, it looked warm.
It looked cool.
It wasn't fashionable.
The fashion leader's feelings are not
well conveyed, so we'll show you
Yasumoto's latest fashion.
After this, we'll show you the fashion
leader's unique fashion.
Black is not good.
The fashion leader Yasumoto will show
you the latest fashion.
First, this.
Chidori-bo!
I like matching the patterns.
I like matching the patterns, so I made
it as a theme.
You have a high sense.
My student said, you have a high sense.
A student without sense said that.
I see.
Let's continue.
Here.
Who is this?
I took this after taking a bath, so I
thought I'd hide my face with a hat.
No, no, no.
It's a coordination that started with a
hat.
It started with a hat.
It's udon.
It's true. It's udon.
It's a pattern of udon.
My favorite is the fluffy one.
It's like deep-fried tofu.
It's like Kitsune.
This is a wall, right?
It's a pattern of a wall.
It's a sticker.
It's almost the same as udon.
It's integrated with the wall.
It's great that you can match the
fashion with the wall.
Where are you praising?
Thank you.
You're praising the wall and the
pattern.
Thank you.
As expected of a disciple.
Let's go to the last one.
Here.
It's scary.
Is this Yasumoto?
It's Yasumoto.
Is this a straight bangs?
Yes, I'm wearing straight bangs.
I see.
This is a trendy black outfit.
Is it a trend?
Yes, black.
Matsuno is bitter.
It's amazing.
Matsuno, is that so?
Is it a trendy black outfit?
You're involved in this.
I want to get out of here.
It's a black outfit.
I can't finish it with just a trendy
style.
I like patterns.
You often say that.
I chose a muffler pattern around my
neck.
By the way, how do you feel?
How do you feel?
Mayama, how do you feel?
It's a strange atmosphere.
Did you notice?
What should I do?
I'm upset.
Are you upset?
Chijiwa was here.
Chijiwa gave me these three evaluations.
Thank you.
Let's go.
The evaluation of the members was not
good.
Yasumoto's fashion.
How did the professional see it?
Let's look at the comments one by one
First, the fashion is unique with the
different patterns
The trend color terracotta is a fashion
trend
The retro glasses are cute
This fashion is amazing
What is terracotta?
I don't know
You don't know?
That's amazing!
What is this udon-style clothing?
I collaborated with the wall paper
pattern and the T-shirt pattern and got
200,000 yen!
Wow!
That's amazing!
Really?
You're praising me too much, aren't you?
Are you a disciple of Chijiwa-san?
That's strange, isn't it?
So far, it's been a high-rated video
without any complaints.
Next time, the black outfit of Nigawarai
in Matsu.
This year's trend is the color of the
clothes.
On the other hand, the one-color outfit
is the trend.
The outfit is a combination of a coat
and a cardigan.
The size is a little big.
It's a big outfit for an adult.
It's a scary outfit.
Yasumoto-san, what do you think?
I heard that it's a scary outfit.
I don't know how to say it, but
Yasumoto's fashion is praised in a
strange way.
I see. You're not used to being praised.
Ebichu Tastasu's big news.
Next.
What is it?
Hinata's Hiding the Secret of the Snow-
Covered Oogiri
Oogiri, a popular segment in the Mini
Corner Festival
Here, Kashiwagi showed her hidden talent
Both of them have love, right?
The topic is, is it a person in a photo?
The answer that Kashiwagi gave to Oogiri
is...
Yes!
I think I'm the only gorilla in this
village.
Kashiwagi, you got 2 points!
You noticed after I got this big?
Special project!
Special project! Kashiwagi vs. Ebichu
Tastasu vs. Oogiri Challenge!
This is not the top!
Let's take a look at this photo
What is this?
It's raining. I thought I'd bring an
umbrella but it's just a green onion
I'm not going to quit
I'm not going to quit. I'm going to do
Kashiwagi
Hi baby, I'm not scared.
Are you scared?
I'm definitely scared.
That's good.
Let's stop.
I noticed something.
In this program, there is no one who is
good at playing the game.
Let's take a break from the important
news and move on to the next segment.
I asked the people who watch TASTASU
often to tell me their favorite scenes.
Who are the people who watch this
program?
Kobayashi Grandpa and Yasumoto Papa's
Pick! Ebichu Tatsusatsu!
Kobayashi Grandpa is watching this
program?
He is always watching this program
He called me and said he was glad
Kobayashi Grandpa and Yasumoto Papa are
watching this program every time
They chose the best scene of this year
Kobayashi Grandpa's Pick! Ebichu
Tatsutatsu!
Kobayashi's Birthday Special!
What's with this grandpa?
In the end, it's just a grandchild.
That's the result of all the things
we've done.
It just happened.
It's not like it's a special because we
have a grandchild.
Kobayashi's Grandpa's Pick!
The family members sang the song,
and the audience was excited.
I think it was a very harmonious
performance.
I'm so embarrassed.
That's what it is.
Grandpa said,
Absolute Anarchy!
Grandpa doesn't say that.
He doesn't say Absolute or Anarchy.
Next,
Yasumoto Papa's Pick! Tastasu's Famous
Scene
The chosen one is...
Tastasu's Pick! Tastasu's Pick!
Tastasu's Pick!
According to Yasumoto Papa,
It was natural for TV to see Aya-chan
asking the clerk,
What do you recommend about this shop?
But from Aya-chan's perspective,
It was a surprising action.
Actually, Aya-chan is not the type of
person who can ask the clerk anything.
That's what it means.
This is the scene where Yasumoto asked
the clerk for a recommendation.
Did you choose?
I chose!
Excuse me, but do you have any
recommendations for this shop?
Like, what do you recommend?
I'm sure the clerk was like,
Eh? Aya-chan?
I don't know!
I don't know Aya-chan usually.
But usually, you definitely ask your
parents, right?
I usually ask them to whisper in my ear.
You're a princess!
What's the name of the person?
University of Arts and Letters News
The first draft meeting in the history
of Ebichu.
The first unit in history has been born.
So, tonight,
We're finally going to show you the
recording.
And we're going to announce the title of
the song.
You might only be able to hear one
phrase.
Let's go straight to the studio and
shoot the producer Ogata.
The theme of the song was Isoginchaku.
Usually, when Isoginchaku and other fish
are in contact with each other,
It's said that it's poisoned.
But I'm fine with just bear meat.
I'm going to pay a little attention to
that.
I'm going to make a love song between
bear meat and Isoginchaku.
I don't think you've ever imagined what
it's like.
I think it's enough if you keep in mind
that Isoginchaku and fun are in your
head.
Even if it's the first time you hear it,
you'll get really excited.
I'm getting excited.
Let's get Isoginchaku naturally and
dance in the venue.
I hope you can enjoy it with your
family.
There's a rumor that there's a high-
pitched response.
Please look forward to it.
Let's sing together.
The title of the song is...
Tamageta Koi no El Niño
Next, the unit produced by Tenkomori
Satsuki.
The theme of the song was bear meat.
I'm going to show you a song that will
make the whole venue a bear meat crowd.
Please look forward to it.
It's a new song in many ways.
I think it's fun.
Please play the bad bear meat part.
It's a story.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's a bad bear meat.
The title of the song is...
Shintairiku
Next, the unit produced by Takuta.
The theme of the song was crab.
Why do you have a crab on a holy night?
I hope you don't get fooled by the crab.
I hope you enjoy it.
I think the truth of why it's a crab
will be revealed.
I hope you enjoy it.
Takuta, Tokyo 03, who mixed crab and
Christmas.
Crab and Christmas.
What's in the way?
The title of the song is...
Dinner Christmas
Only one phrase.
The unit name has been decided.
First, the unit that Ogata Kaiki went to
is...
Heisei Isokin Trio.
This is a gathering of geniuses.
Their talent is exploding.
Please look forward to it.
The unit that Satsuki and Tenkomori went
to is...
Puku Puku.
The unit that I, Satsuki, and Tenkomori
went to is...
Puku Puku.
It's a song that makes you feel like
you're being attacked by a bear.
I hope you enjoy it.
And the unit that Kakuta, the Tokyo 03,
chose is...
Sankaku Kanita-san.
Please enjoy the live!
The next week is coming soon.
Private Ebisu Middle School Christmas
University Games 2016.
Ebichu's Ocean's Guide.
There are only a few tickets left.
For more information, please go to
Ebichu's website.
Next episode.
The Ebichu Tastas News Grand Prix is
finally decided.
That's no good. No good. No good.
What kind of news is it?
This program was brought to you by the
following sponsors.
I can't do it!
Why are you sitting there?