Yakan and Idol!
Yakan and Idol's main corner is here.
We're asking you to give us your title
call.
Can I ask you to do it?
Yes.
My three-dimensional appearance!
Can I show this?
Yes, you can.
Can you show us three of them?
Yes.
Idol's three-dimensional appearance!
It's pretty general.
No, no, it's good.
First, music, then rice, then sleep.
I see. Music, rice, sleep.
Now, the first one.
Please subscribe to our channel.
I love HIDE from X JAPAN when I was in
high school.
I didn't have any fans until then.
I didn't have any favorite artists or
celebrities.
But HIDE was the first artist I became a
fan of.
I started listening to rock music and
western music.
I've been a fan of music since then.
I see.
You became a fan of music because of
HIDE.
What made you like HIDE?
HIDE is a coincidence on YouTube.
What a coincidence!
I watched a video of X JAPAN's live
video on YouTube when I was 16.
I see.
I knew the band name at that time, but I
hadn't seen their performance.
But the number of views was amazing.
I think so.
I thought I had to know the band name as
a common sense.
That's great.
I didn't know the band name at that
time.
I was attracted to the guitarist when I
clicked the button.
That's how I became a fan of HIDE.
I see.
You've been looking for a lot of
artists.
You've been active as a solo artist.
I've been looking for a lot of artists.
I see.
But you can't express your performance
well.
But I have a lot of rock taste.
I see.
So, I have a rock image.
I can express my image easily.
You're not a rocker.
You're a rocker.
But I want to be a rocker.
I'm influenced by rock.
I've heard that you've been to a
festival.
I often go to festivals.
I want to perform soon.
You want to perform soon.
But I haven't been able to perform
recently.
I want to perform soon.
You're a new director.
I'm looking forward to your performance.
The first thing I make is music.
I always finish my lunch.
Not a side dish.
I'm fine with rice.
Today's wonderful child has come out.
This program is
Atsu
Miyaku
Satoma-san
Kani-san
I sent this to you with Nao-chan's
favorite Eri Eri-san
Thank you very much! Bye-bye!