I'm sleepy.
I'm sleepy too.
Hey, everyone!
Can you hear me?
Hey, everyone! I'm here!
Kanamin, Juri-chan, Hito-chan, Hiyorin,
over here!
I think I've heard of them before.
Oh, Tamarin?
Yes?
What are you doing here?
Kanamin and Juri-chan said they were
sleepy, so we came here.
We came?
What do you mean you came here because
you said you were sleepy?
Why did you become a bubbling cushion?
Actually, bubbling is not just a
cushion.
Hey, Juri-chan!
Don't say it like you're a soldier.
Can you try spreading the cushion?
Juri?
It's not just a cushion.
Wow! It's a blanket!
Actually, it's not just a cushion, it's
a blanket too.
Wow, it's cute.
It's really convenient.
I'm getting sleepy.
Juri?
Juri is sleeping.
This blanket is really cute.
It's convenient because you can put it
under your chair during a concert.
That's true.
I'm going to borrow it.
I'm suddenly sleepy.
Kanamin?
They both fell asleep.
This is magic.
I made a mistake.
Maybe bubbling became a cushion blanket
and protected us.
Piyo was talking in bubbling's voice.
What?
I'll protect you all anytime.
Bubbling's cushion blanket.