Ebitune's videos
I'm the second child of the Ebitune
family, Mariko Nakayama.
Mariko Nakayama's story of one person
Yes, that's right.
I bought another camera around summer.
I bought an iPad because I wanted to
edit and retouch.
But I haven't made any progress since
then.
It's over.
I bought a camera because I thought it
would be easier to take pictures.
But this time I bought a difficult one.
I take pictures every time I go to
various places.
I don't know the settings, so I want you
to teach me.
How many minutes have passed?
It's been a minute.
It's difficult.
I bought an iPad and a camera together.
I used the iPad to edit the 23rd summer
night.
I wanted to take a picture of a person.
I want to take pictures of people who I
took with.
I want to be able to use it.
I want to take pictures of people who I
took with.
I still have two minutes left.
I'll do my best.
Please subscribe to the channel.
Yuck😅
I don't know what is a iron plate talk.
I searched for iron plate talk.
It's like a story with confidence.
It's like a story without a doubt.
What is an iron plate talk?
It's not iron plate.
It's a popular thing now.
Peyoung's...
There's a 4000-something calorie thing.
I was so curious about it.
I tried it alone.
I tried it yesterday.
How many?
4?
I think there are more than 4.
It says, don't eat alone.
Everyone is eating alone.
I thought I could do it.
I was full in the first 10 minutes.
I ate noodles, so I was full.
I didn't lose weight at all.
I ate breakfast and came here.
Everyone, please try it.
I thought it was not sold.
I found it at the supermarket and tried
it.
There is a powder in yakisoba.
I thought I should put it under the
noodles.
I thought it was common sense.
I saw it, so please try it.
But what is it?
Recently, Hinata-chan has a musical, and
there is no gathering at all.
Not at all.
Recently,
I wonder when it will be.
It hasn't changed at all.
It's not at all, it's not at all.
So, the memories of the six of us are...
About two months ago, after the shoot,
we all took a purikura.
After that, at the cafe, what was it?
The latest version of the Werewolf game.
It's like a set of werewolves and
werewolves.
At the birthday party of Mirei, we were
playing a video during the live.
We were going to play a werewolf, so we
decided to try it out.
We all did it in a small voice at the
cafe.
The shoot ended early.
Everyone had plans after that, and we
were wondering what to do during that
time.
Harajuku was close, so we all walked
together.
We went to the cafe while having a party
like JK on Takeshita Street.
It's something that you don't notice
unexpectedly.
The last cafe staff asked us if we were
shooting.
It's interesting. It's interesting.
It's a story that we found very
interesting.
Bye bye!
2 more seconds!
What about the live concert?
I'm not sure if I can have a birthday
party this year.
I think I have a birthday party before
October.
I think about it every year for about a
year.
I don't know if I can do it this year.
I think I've been working hard on it.
I'm going to do a cover song of an
artist every year.
I'm going to be able to sing a lot of
songs.
I've been working hard on it.
I'm not sure if I can do it.
But I finished it safely.
What did I do?
I'm doing a piano and trumpet
performance every year.
I couldn't think of anything.
I'm going to make a video of myself this
time.
I took a picture of the summer night
version of the 23rd song.
I edited it myself.
What else did I do?
It was my 20th birthday.
I didn't actually turn 20.
I was drinking alcohol at the age of 20.
I couldn't do anything.
I made a video of myself and willedl do
it.
I think the most important thing is the
sake of the Ebi-cho.
I didn't think I would drink sake for a
week when I turned 20.
And I drank a lot of sake for the first
time there.
What? I finished in 30 seconds.
What was it?
What I realized when I turned 20.
What I realized is...
That's it.
Oh, yeah.
I dyed my hair.
I've been telling my fans a long time
ago that I'll dye my hair when I turn
20.
I told them that I would definitely dye
my hair.
I turned 20 on my birthday.
I went to dye my hair the next day.
Can you see it?
I think it's getting pretty old.
I haven't had a pudding for a month.
I'm going to dye my hair every time I
have a concert.
I don't think I'll change my hair color
much.
I'm looking forward to changing the
atmosphere.
What color is the university arts
festival?
There's a stage before that.
I don't know if I'll be able to play the
role of the stage.
I might turn black.
I don't know. I might be blonde.
Please look forward to the university
arts festival.
What else?
It's half-hearted time.
It's been about 10 seconds.
I don't think I'll change my hair color
much.
I think it's about to happen.
Please look forward to it.
What is the highlight of the stage?
Shibuya Shoryo Railway
I will be on Tsuchiya's stage this year.
I did it for the first time the other
day.
I don't know what to do.
There are many things that can happen on
Tsuchiya's stage.
It's hard to explain what kind of stage
it is.
There are so many things that can
happen.
Well...
I can't think of anything.
So, I think that people who watch my
videos can enjoy it many times.
Wait, can I talk for 2 minutes?
Why do I talk?
I really don't know.
To be honest, I only did it once
yesterday.
I hope I can do it with you guys.
I don't know.
It's difficult, but I want to do it with
you guys.
Please do it with me.
This is a message for Tsuchiya.
There's more.
Tsuchiya, how are you?
Thank you.
I Together
Dr. Nakayama is focusing on Dr. Move
over and over again.
So, we'll expose something that didn't
look good.
Thank you for watching!
What?
I said something.
18 or 19 years old, after graduating
high school,
I want to be an adult.
I'm not going to say it anymore.
I want to be an adult and grow in
performance and singing.
I want to be 20 years old.
On the contrary...
I want to be the same as I was.
I hope you can support me as I am.
Thank you!
I often...
I don't know...
I didn't know that JK wanted to wear a
uniform.
Even after I graduated high school, I
didn't know...
I don't know...
I didn't want to go back to high school.
But when I turned 20, I thought I should
have enjoyed my school days more.
So, students, please enjoy now.
I think it's good to take a polaroid
picture wearing a uniform.
I had a lot of fun taking polaroids with
the members.
Please enjoy studying and club
activities.