This week's Ebichu Tastas is a full-on
brain-sauce quiz battle
Mr. Wada
As expected, it's a series of questions
How did you pass the first one?
I passed it in 10 hours
From questions about members
What did you eat?
I ate a chicken
To exciting reasoning quiz
Please eat
starting from Peri-chuu現代大綱
What should I do with the hearts of 10
million people?
Moratorium, moratorium, moratorium,
middle school students
Add various things to your private Ebisu
middle school
Middle school students
Ebichu Justice
I don't know at all
This program is brought to you by these
sponsors
I don't know
Why is this only one?
This program is brought to you by these
sponsors
Ebichu Tastas has started!
Recently, the one who carries hand cream
The one with high女子力, Ayaka Yasumoto
will be the MC for today
That's right
But her skin is dry
But she smells good
She's the one who loses to everyone
Hand cream
She smells like wood
The smell of wood?
Is it still on?
It's not on
It's not on?
It's not on right now
So what we're going to do today is
Please read the diary
Ebichu Quiz!
The final point is Magical Shrimp Tiger
Quiz!
Shrimp Tiger Quiz!
We said Shrimp and Tiger together.
Let's do the first ever quiz show with
shrimp.
What are the members' enthusiasm?
By the way, who wants to appear in the
quiz?
Yes
It's surprisingly few
What?
Do you watch the quiz program?
I watch it when I'm doing it
What is your own correct answer?
Not so many
Probably
If it's a daily program, it's still easy
to understand
It's like common sense
Common sense?
Really?
No, no
Some members are not so reliable
This time, they will battle in a team
battle
There are 5 stages
They will compete in various quiz
The team with more points will get a
prize
The team's captain is the youngest,
Mayama
And the smartest, Hoshina
They will scout the members they think
they want
Hoshina, please be the first one
Hoshina, are you happy?
I don't know, I'm just lucky
Who is Mayama?
Me? I'm Nakayama
No way!
Why?
I want to be the funny one
It doesn't matter if you get the correct
answer
They chose the answer like this
What's left?
Oh no, what's left?
1-1!
She's playing 1-1
Wait, wait, I'll loosen my shoulders
She's a newbie
I'll do anything
She said she'll do anything
I'll bring water
I'll do something bad if I do a steak
combo with her
I see
I'm sorry
So Kobayashi is going to be in the
Mayama team
Who will win the quiz battle?
The first stage is...
Answer and of course the general
knowledge quiz!
Wow!
It's the general knowledge quiz!
First, let's see the members' skills in
the general knowledge quiz
If you write the answer on the flip and
get it right, you get 1 point
If all members get it right, you get 10
points
Let's go
Question!
The bread that was born in France,
croissant
It's cute
It's named after that shape
What does croissant mean in French?
What is that?
It's the shape of croissant
That's right
Can't we have two?
I like this the most among croissant
bread
Try to remember the shape
I got it
Let's start with Mayama team
Go!
Mayama is mountain
Hirota is crescent
Wada is croissant
What is this?
Croissant
Wada is croissant
The name is croissant
It's a competition
Nakayama is cloud
Croissant
I see
Let's see Hoshina team
Go!
It's not
It's a roll
Yasumoto is butter
It tastes like butter
She said shape
The next is moon
Is it the shape of moon?
What is the answer?
Moon
It's crescent
You said moon but you said crescent
It's the shape
It's not a circle
The answer is crescent
That's right
Mayama team got it right
Hoshina team got it right
Hoshina team got 2 points
You are satisfied with what you got,
right?
Let's move on
I see
Let's go
Question
What is the biggest planet in the solar
system?
Planet?
It's a planet
It's a solar system
I don't know
It's the same as elementary school
You said it's strong
It's strong
You are right
Let's see
Hoshina team
Wait, which one?
Hoshina team, open
It's not
It's a star
Mayama team, open
It's not
Mayama team, sun
Hirota got a star
Kobayashi got a sun
It's a planet
The answer is
It's a sun
Nakayama is doing well
You like hips
I like the main part
I don't know much about it
Nakayama became an adult
Suddenly
Let's continue
Next question
Human's five senses
Visual, hearing, taste, smell
What is the other one?
There are five senses
I'm sorry
There is one more
Let's start with Mayama team
Mayama team, open
First, senses
I know, I know
The same, senses
This one too
Sense
The sense is so real
And
Nakayama is amazing
Hoshina team, open
Shokkaku, shokkaku, shokkaku, no
I don't know
It's a sudden question
It's fine, it's fine, but why did you
say you are good at general knowledge?
The correct answer is shokkaku
So, Mayama team got 1 point
Hoshina team got 3 points
What? That's interesting
You are wrong
It's a close match
This is a good match
Hoshina team is leading by a small
margin
The next stage is...
If you don't know, you're disqualified
Members' episode, quick press quiz!
Oh, another Shinkansen!
Well, if you know the members, you can
easily understand
Unlike before, it has nothing to do with
knowledge
That's right
Episode quiz that is given by member's
questionnaire and manager's testimony
If you get it right, you get 5 points
If you get it wrong, you get 1 break
Let's start
Question
Hoshina was surprised
What does Yasumoto always do in the
dressing room?
Nakayama was fast
What is it?
She wipes her face with a tissue
Wrong
Mayama was correct
She eats in front of the trash can
Please look forward to next week's
episode!
No!
Hoshino-san, let's go!
My face is rolling around
The roller is getting scratched
No way!
My face is getting scratched!
The secret of Yasumoto is being revealed
one after another
It seems that she was about to go home
Hoshina-san seems to be surprised
Nakayama!
I'm going home with the food in the
school
Correct!
It's the first time that Nata Yada has
been useful
It's here!
The time has come!
Hoshina-san was surprised, what's the
meaning of this?
For example, when you receive sweets
If you bring a lot of it home, you can
praise your dad
You can praise him?
You can say that you were popular
You can go home like a
You can go home like a toban
Let's continue
Question
Celery and Chinese cabbage cannot be
eaten
Already?
I got it
Really?
Let's continue, Matsuno-san
Matsuno Rina
It's completely wrong
Listen to the question
I'll ask it again
Celery and Chinese cabbage cannot be
eaten
Matsuno-san
What was the most delicious food you ate
during the last tour?
Please answer it properly
Teba gyoza
Wrong
Kashiwagi
Hakumai?
Matsuno, what did you eat?
The hint is meat
Thank you
Jingu-sukan
Jingu-sukan?
I got it
Grilled meat
Hirota-san
Jingu-sukan, hot pot
Wrong
Matsuno-san
Salt Jingu-sukan
Correct
It's about yourself
Let's continue
Question
Recently, Kashiwagi-san is thinking
about food right away
What's with the information you just
said?
What did you say?
Recently, Kashiwagi-san is thinking
about food right away
I'll enjoy it while listening to the
information
That's right
Kashiwagi-san was surprised by Hirota-
san who was getting his hair done
What did you use to get your bangs done?
Yasumoto-san
Claw clippers
Correct
This is famous
This is famous?
You actually did it?
I didn't want to be seen with my bangs
I was in the hotel and my bangs were
long
I didn't want to get my bangs clipped
I only had my bangs clipped
I had my bangs clipped for the whole day
Let's continue
Question
When you sang Oh My Ghost live
You said you saw a white dog's ghost
Wait a minute
You saw a white dog's ghost
That's right
When she was singing Oh My Ghost during
the live show, Kobayashi saw a white dog
ghost
I'm more curious than the quiz so let's
listen to it in detail
When I was singing Oh My Ghost at Nagoya
Park in Osaka
There was a time when I was crouching
and moving to the left
When I was singing Jujikkan, a white dog
came running towards me
I was surprised and thought I saw it
How did you pass the door?
I was singing Jujikkan
The timing is amazing
Can you show us again?
Jujikkan
Didn't the other members see it?
I was standing behind her
I was singing Jujikkan too
Stand up, stand up
It was a formation
I was about to cross the line
Jujikkan
That was amazing
That was dangerous
If I didn't cross the line, I would have
been dragged away
That's right
Why did you avoid it?
Show us the formation again
I love it
Jujikkan
I think she was aiming for Yasumoto
Maybe
Let's go back to the quiz
We are in the middle of the quiz
Please listen to the last part
When I sang Oh My Ghost at the concert
I saw a white dog
Recently, I have been thinking about
something
What is it?
Matsuno
I dreamt that a lot of dogs came out
That's scary
That's a lie
Kodai is here
She is here
I can't make dumplings at home
Correct
I don't know
I can't make dumplings at home
But I can sing white songs
I can't think of anything
The quiz is over
The score is the same
Hoshina team is slightly ahead
The next stage is
The captain wants to eat now
A favorite food quiz
This quiz is
Team challenge
The 3 questions that will be given to
the captain will be the most popular
ones.
If you can guess what the captain wants
to eat, you will get 10 points.
First, Mayama, please tell us what you
want to eat.
What is it?
It looks delicious.
I want to eat it.
Please wait.
I'll give you three.
What is Captain Mayama's favorite food?
1. Soy sauce ramen
2. Fish bone soup noodles
3. Abura soba
What is the most thing that Mayama wants
to eat now?
All three kinds of noodles.
It seems difficult to guess.
By the way, they wrote down which one
they want to eat the most.
These three, there are three things you
want to eat right now. Mayama-san, how
do you feel?
It's the best.
The best? Thank you very much.
Wait a minute.
I don't know what this is.
Noodle, noodle, noodle.
It's really hard to understand.
What are you talking about?
The noodles of ramen, noodles of
tsukemen, noodles of oil soba are all
different.
The noodles are all different.
I want to eat it.
Mayama has a strong attachment to
noodles.
What is Mayama's current favorite food?
Will the Hoshina team be able to find
out?
3D Start!
The questions are free to ask.
Do you have any questions?
What did you eat yesterday?
I ate cup noodles yesterday.
How is your life going?
It's like a master.
That's a good question.
I'm not doing so well, but I'm still
eating.
Please smell each one.
Sounds good.
Mayama's favorite food?
Please look forward to the next episode!
You are always late. You are always
eating something that is not fully
grown.
How many hours have you been eating?
I'm fine.
Mayama Rika loves noodles so much.
Which one of the three do you want to
eat the most?
Hoshina team's answer is...
Mayama's favorite food is...
Soy sauce ramen!
Why is that?
I don't think there is any soy sauce
ramen.
I can't express my opinion about the
noodles.
I think it's good from the beginning.
The noodles are a bit...
To be honest, it's just the noodles.
The Hoshina team is expecting soy sauce
ramen.
Will it be the correct answer?
So, Captain Mayama, please eat what you
want to eat.
Mayama's favorite noodles are...
Scary!
She got it!
Congratulations!
Ah, meat!
Unfortunately, Hoshina team is incorrect
They don't get a lot of points
Next, please choose what Hoshina wants
to eat
What is Hoshina's favorite food?
1. White strawberry 2. Mini tomato 3.
Beef tongue
Can Hoshina guess what she wants to eat?
Let's start the reasoning!
Hoshina-san, how do you feel?
Happy, happy, happy!
Mayama team, please ask questions
I'm the one who cares about my character
Nice, nice
The type who is full of energy
I'm the one who is seen by 360 degrees
I'm an idol no matter what I eat
I don't care about my character
What's the difference between the white
strawberry and the normal one?
It's different from the normal one
But I was told that I can eat anything
Stop it with your hands
I'm a bit bad at drawing
I see, you're a bit bad at drawing
It's very sweet
So I often eat the ones that are not
good looking
Which one is the most common?
This one is the most common
Why?
It's this one when you think about the
types
Let's say the middle one
White strawberry
Why?
It's overwhelmingly expensive
The price is...
You can't eat it unless you want to
It's expensive
It's not a Michelin
The shape is beautiful
I see
You can buy the Aiku
You can buy it
It's important to eat the beef tongue
Hiro, you look like a famous detective
A famous detective
I see, you look at it well
What does Hoshina want to eat the most?
What is the answer of the Mayama team?
What do you think Hoshina wants to eat
the most?
Ready, set, white strawberry
White strawberry
Based on the reasoning of the famous
detective Hirota
They bet on the white strawberry, not
the Michelin
Will it be the correct answer?
The correct answer is
Hoshina's reverse
Let's eat
I don't like it. Why is this only one?
It's that kind of game
Ah, but I'll take the tomato and
chopsticks
I want to eat it
What's going on?
Please eat quickly
The correct answer is Gyutan
It's beef tongue
By the way, why did you choose beef
tongue?
I'll tell you later
I knew it
We said beef tongue
Unfortunately, Mayama team is also
incorrect
The result is still the same
The next episode of Ebichu Tastas is
They are searching for the quiz in the
house
It's hot
Grandpa
Why did the old man go missing?
And
Question
Where did Ebichu do the super
consciousness of their major debut?
The members are challenging the Ebichu
history quiz
What will happen?
However
Our game, Ebichu Junior High School's
coming-of-age party post stole from绿 정도
Rock A
Yes
Thank you for watching!
Please try playing it
Let's go!
Super macho
This program was provided by the sponsor
you are watching
Among the 8 members of the Ebichu
members
A little more!
Do your best!
I'm hungry
The sound was terrible