I'm a woman type.
You are a woman type?
Yes.
I'm a woman type.
The next is a woman type.
Thank you.
I'm going to have an interview today.
I'm going to have an interview with a
company that is in Ishinobaki,
which is a subsidiary of Fuse Shopping.
I'm nervous.
A while ago, you and Sakura-san were
accepted by Kinoya-san.
You failed.
We were thinking of trying something
else.
We're going to add Ritsuki-san and
Hazuki-san to the company.
Nice to meet you.
I'm fine.
Thank you.
I fell.
Last time, it was like a joke.
I asked you to write a history book
seriously this time as well.
I wrote it properly.
Is it okay?
I don't look at it properly.
Today, you can do it alone, so you
should be accepted.
Let's do our best.
I'm going to be accepted alone.
I'll do my best.
Please come in.
Thank you for coming.
Nice to meet you.
Today is the interview.
I'm Taichi, a student of the Fusei
Shoten.
Nice to meet you.
First of all, can I see your resume?
Yes.
Thank you.
Well...
What is your name?
My name is Gunde Ariyama.
I'm 82 years old.
I was born in 2002.
I'm a little old.
Can you do math?
I can do it.
You graduated from a famous university
abroad in 2002.
Yes.
Harvard University.
Thank you.
You are dismissed from college.
Dismissed?
Your salary is 60,000 yen per month.
Really?
But you are late.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
This is a photo sticker.
It's cute.
Thank you.
Ms. Hikaru Hitsuki.
It was an שלusion event run by V Bangkok
pretty soon.
Gradually we were forced to decide on
where to place the newalkae's
Q4. asta point of order
What part of the spider are you
preparing?
The softest part.
You're saying that you're healing from
the softest part.
Oh!
You're a second-grade English test
student?
Yes.
That's amazing.
I passed the test when I was in the
third grade of junior high school.
I thought your death motive was amazing.
I was very impressed by your attitude to
treasure the earth.
I thought you wanted to use the magic of
your mother's hand and your wife's idol
activities to heal and experience death.
Yes.
That's amazing.
I think you have to treasure the earth.
I'd like to move on to the next person.
Thank you.
The picture is a pre-credit scene.
It's probably a pre-credit scene from
when I was in elementary school.
The picture is a pre-credit scene from
What is your address?
My address is in the upper reaches of
the Tokyo and Minato district.
I work in the Ijinomaki area.
I see.
I think it's better to have a male
voice.
I see.
You are thinking about a hair color.
Yes, I am.
I'm thinking about whether to have black
hair or blond hair.
I want to get some inspiration.
Which one is better?
I think black is better.
I see.
I'll consider black.
Sorry.
I'm thinking about black hair because
it's a food factory.
You don't like the morning.
Yes, I don't like it.
I start work at 5 a.m.
I want you to start work at 14 a.m.
I'm glad to start work at 14 a.m.
I don't have time to work at 14 a.m.
I see.
I think you should start cleaning at 14
a.m.
What?
I'm not a cleaning lady.
Do you work late at night?
Yes, I don't work late at night.
I see.
I'll check your answer.
You are a very smart kindergarten
teacher.
You are a cute kindergarten teacher.
You are a very popular kindergarten
teacher.
I'm not a kindergarten teacher.
I don't want to make you feel bad at the
time.
Because you are cute.
That's amazing.
Thank you.
As a self-promotion, I will sell the
image character of the fish with the
same name as the cherry blossoms.
I think it will be cute and more
popular.
I think it will be the best result if
you put out goods.
I'm not kidding.
Everyone is hungry.
I have a question.
Yes.
I'm a YouTube photographer.
I introduce fish.
What kind of YouTube video do you want
to shoot?
Yes.
What kind of video do you want to shoot?
I want to shoot a video of my parents
and my butt.
I'm talking to Sakura Madara.
I have to talk to the fish after I talk
to the fish.
What kind of video do you want to make?
I want to make a video of my family.
I see.
What kind of YouTube video do you want
to make?
I want to make an ASMR video of Sakura
Madara.
Oh, really?
You want to make an ASMR video of
Madara.
Yes.
I want to make an ASMR video of Sakura
Madara.
I'm confident thatAlexander will come to
torpedo.
Please introduce the gag using your
image.
Well...
That's Sakura Madara and a swimming
sucked.
Well, I can't swim well.
but my girlfriend...
I will take someone with me to swim.
I am also boatman.
Combined with a water tank and...
I'm a big girl
What about you, Sakura?
I'm breathing in my stomach to be with
my feelings from the past
Breathing in your stomach?
I see
Have you ever done this before?
No
I see
Thank you
I have a question for you
You are very particular about your
relationships with people
But you are not good at it
Yes
Are there any people you are not good
at?
If there are, who are they?
I'm not good at it
But I'm good at it in my own way
I see
I'm not good at it
But I'm not good at it
I see
What about you, Yuzuki?
I'm good at making people happy
I see
What kind of relationship do you have
with people like that?
Well...
Passion
Passion?
Yes
What is it?
Hazuki?
She is a womanizer
A womanizer?
She is a man and a woman
I often hear that women are a little
bit...
She looks like this
She is a womanizer
Sakura, please do your best
I will do my best
Is it a child type?
Yes, I'm a water type
I came in a water type today
I'm weak to this type
I've heard a lot, so I'd like to change
it
Thank you
We will give you a secret
How about each of you write a secret?
Yes
For you,
I'm sorry
I got it
Your salary was 60,000yen
I spent 500,000yen per day
It's difficult for me
It's 30,000yen per day
It's not bad
Please write a secret
Yes
Ritsuki
You value the earth
That's what we think
Yes
I'm sorry
Thank you
I'm sorry that I can't communicate with
you from the clouds.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I can't communicate with
you from the clouds.
I'm sorry.
Sakura Madara is the same as Sakura
Madara.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Sakura has a driver's license.
Our employees are not good at driving.
They are not good at work.
They are not good at working.
I can't help it.
You failed this time.
I'm sorry.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
Let's go.
Please.
Thank you.
Please introduce yourself and promote
yourself.
I'm 18 years old.
My appeal point is my cute side.
Thank you.
I'm YUNA HAZUKI.
I'm 19 years old.
I'm not bad at expressing my opinion, so
I think I can express my opinion
clearly.
I like talking to people, so I think I
can talk to anyone.
Thank you.
I'm RITSUKI KAL.
My appeal point is minus 4.
Thank you.
I'm MIYU FUJITANI.
I'm 17 years old.
My appeal point is funny.
Thank you.
Please introduce your
company's website.
It's a challenge for each person.
I'm good at building dominoes.
I think I can make the same feeling by
creating each one.
I think you are more like a leader.
I think I use mackerel, but there are
many people who are not good at it.
I thought I could convey the charm of
mackerel from a young person's point of
view.
I want to be a force in this company.
HIKAKIN, please.
I saw the doctor's website.
It says that it is easy to take a break
without any work.
I thought it was very attractive.
Are you okay with the work at the site?
Yes.
I will do my best.
Please.
I was able to eat delicious mackerel
ramen because I was in the game.
Next, I will interview you in person.
We have an exhibition at our company.
We have a company called Twisten.
Please introduce this product to the
buyer.
Yabai.
I look for good products at the
supermarket.
I want to make products that are related
to our company.
I'm excited.
I want you to try the coin-licking at
the exhibition.
Normally, I would like to do it one by
one.
This product is a package that imagines
the pattern of mackerel.
I think that many boys are interested in
fish.
Please come to the snack section.
I think it's very good because it has a
strong impact.
If you come to the snack section, you
will be able to see the products better.
I recommend it because the tempo is also
bright.
This is an exhibition, isn't it?
Basically, there are other companies,
such as the next door or the front door.
So, how many times do you want to stand
out?
Yes, there are many people around here.
So, I'm going to look at it if I'm
interested in it.
Yes.
I understand. Please leave it to me.
Thank you.
Hello everyone!
I'm going to sing a movie.
Please listen to it.
Saba.
What?
SUBF
Saba, Saba, Saba-chan.
This is ramen, this is oden.
This is miso, this is miso.
This is pasta, this is curry.
This is tea.
There are many things.
SUBF
Let's eat together, Saba-chan.
Please buy a lot of Saba-chan.
If everyone buys it, the world will be
peaceful.
SUB-A, SUB-A, SUB-A, SUB-A, Saba-chan.
Wow, thank you.
How was it?
It was quite delicious.
It was a standing still pose.
Yes, it was.
The point is that you can create a sense
of unity by using your hands.
It's like a sense of friendship.
That's the point.
Thank you very much.
It was delicious.
The winner is...
I cooked this mackerel.
I did it!
Thank you for watching!
I want to bite it.
I'm going to bite it.
I'm going to start.
What is this?
No! No! I don't know what's going on!
I'm waiting for you!
Everyone, I'm waiting for you!
What is the question that I ask?
It's a question about the moon.
The moon?
I've never been on a plane.
It's a rare question.
It's a question about the Harvard.
Oh!
Thank you for watching!
exemple
today payments
so,
for this time,
Thank you for watching!
It was zero people.
Zero people?
You are so bright.
It was zero people.
I've been here three times.
I'm going to do my best again.
If you have any advice, please let me
know.
You should study the history of the
company.
And you should study the industry.
I see.
I'm so grateful.
Next, I'll go to the meat restaurant.
I'm going to eat meat.
I'll do my best.
Thank you very much.
We failed to get two cars.
We failed.
I don't think we can do it.
It's not true.
Really?
Let's do our best again.
This is the fourth car.
Yes.
We have to be careful.
I got some advice.
I think we can do it next time.
Let's do our best.
If you have a job interview, you can
come here.
That's right.
Please.
If you are good at interviews, you can
come here.
Thank you for watching our video.
See you next week.
Bye bye.