vol.94 Yuno Kokubo in Aichi
We caught up with Yuno Kokubo, who made a triumphant return to her hometown Aichi Prefecture for her first spring tour!
Aichi Prefecture is her hometown.
It's my hometown.
She was very nervous.
It's not because it's her hometown.
It's not because it's my hometown.
I'm going to do my best to make the live better than last time in Ibaraki or Hokkaido.
I will do my best to make the show better than the previous ones in Ibaraki and Hokkaido.
Self introduction
Aichi Prefecture residents!
Are there any Aichi residents here?
I think there are? Why don't you ask them?
Aichi Residents
Expedition group
There are a lot of people here, so I'll do my best!
You're going at your own pace.
I'll do my best at my own pace!
I'm looking forward to working with you!
Next Mirei!
Yes...!
I'm still not sure what to say...
It's just that the pitches are too varied.
Don't worry. I'm with Po-chan.
You're used to this.
I'm used to it.
I get it.
Aichi Prefecture has the fourth largest population in Japan.
I'm from Kariya.
There's a Jimotte here.
One more time, Aichi Prefecture residents.
I didn't know there were so many Aichi Prefecture residents.
Quite a lot...
There are a lot of people here.
I didn't know there were that many people in Aichi Prefecture.
Of course there are!
Aichi is a big city...
I think it's big!
Hmmm...
What kind of a bitter smile is that!
I got a really bitter smile.
Recommended Aichi Gourmet
Today is Yuno's hometown.
Yuno brought a lot of pictures of Aichi
Yuno brought me some pictures of Aichi.
I've got them! She brought us pictures of Aichi
Seino
D'oh!
You have three pictures.
These are dumplings.
You've eaten them before.
The middle one is a meat sushi.
It's sushi with Hida beef on it.
What does it taste like?
Mild.
Mom took these pictures, all of them.
Yuno didn't eat the whole thing.
She kept saying it's delicious, delicious.
She's sure of it.
And the last one?
Okoge skewers. And the last one?
The last one? It has pickles on it.
And pickles. And this one, too.
Yuno ate this too!
Who took the picture?
All mom!
Thank you, Mom!
The waiting room after the performance
Hinata Kashiwagi, Rika Mayama, Yuno Kokubo of Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku
After the triumphant return
Triumphant return...
Well, it was a triumphant return.
My friends and juniors from school came.
From the school I was at before?
They called me and said it was really fun and cool.
Yuno's junior.
A junior came?
A junior came. A junior came?
You mean they love you as a senior?
I've never spoken to him in honorifics.
Oh, I see.
Yuno's junior is great.
In terms of age, Rika is her junior.
Yuno is!
Too much of a baby, huh? Yuno is!
But I'm glad you came.
Didn't you tell your friends I'm a baby?
No, they didn't.
Just us?
Just us? We thought it was a baby.
Continue to Recommended Aichi Gourmet Foods
Onimanju and Sugakiya... Onimanju and Sugakiya...
TEAM SHACHI is doing a commercial.
I want to eat at the store.
I've only had cup noodles.
If you eat it in a restaurant! The soup is even better!
Yuno's favorite is
After eating the noodles, she puts in the bean sprouts.
There's usually a store in a nearby shopping mall or something.
It's a little different in Tokyo.
Most of the shops in the shopping malls serve Yokohama-style ramen.
If you ask me what I recommend to see, I don't really have any.
I don't have any.
There aren't? Surprisingly.
I said Inuyama castle town.
You don't go to Nagoya Castle?
No, I don't.
I painted Nagoya Castle for a school event.
Higashiyama Zoo!
Wait! I think I've been there!
It's full of animals. Wait! I think I've been there!
Yes!
It's a zoo. It's full of animals. There they are!
Why are you in the same pose?
It's a zoo, it's full of animals!
Shabani the gorilla is famous.
What line is that?
The Higashiyama line! What line?
I think I took...
When you were filming the TV drama "Villeurban"? When they were filming the drama "Villeurban"? I think I took it.
Villeurban! No, I mean...
Aichi Prefecture, the 4th most populated prefecture in Japan
I have an image that there are a lot of people in Aichi.
There are so many people in front of Meieki station.
Nagoya is probably the most crowded place in Japan
Nagoya station has a lot of people.
Is it the area of the Golden Clock?
Shibuya is crowded compared to Tokyo...
Is there any similar place?
No. Maybe there's a place like that?
Maybe it's Yuno's hometown.
Rice fields all around the house.
Nice place.
It's nice.
It's relaxing, isn't it? It's nice.
To Yuno, who loves her hometown.
You recited what I always say backstage.
I felt Nekono's likes and values.
I haven't settled in Tokyo yet.
I wondered if she'd come back to Tokyo.
She has so much love for her hometown.
I'm looking forward to seeing her in person.
I wanted to know more about the charms of Aichi.
Aichi Prefecture for Yuno
There are a lot of places around Nagoya station.
There's a lot of fun things to do, like going to Sakae.
but when you go out a little bit, there are rice paddies, forests, mountains
Rivers...
There are also animals, birds, foxes, and so on.
It's fun to go for a walk in the countryside.
Please come!
Aichi is the best!