Ebichu's videos
I'm from Aichi prefecture
I'm very nervous
I'm not saying this is because I'm from
Aichi prefecture
I'll do my best to have a better live
performance than Ibaraki and Hokkaido
I'm from Aichi prefecture
1,2,3,4
Thank you for watching!
Great!
Let's play the game
It's the cutest
What is it?
Where are we now?
Our career
One song!
I'm listening
Good
Thank you!
I'm not nervous.
Do your best.
Do it sometimes.
I'm a career.
Where are we?
Career!
We are
EBITU!
IZONE!
Thank you.
Join me!
We are the EBITU of STARREST!
The champion present in that class is
the base of atorint Arsenal.
By the way, there was an
announcementoudo in that video.
After the video, Everyone uses kicks of
Notosahope.
So, the video Kim Momo opponents.
There is a long selfаSL A takes video,
so it is
the video of Subscribe me.
Sub habrchan potato potatoes in the 【''
Does
Next, Yuno!
Hello! I'm a junior high school student!
You know? I know!
I like my pace.
I'm a 14th grade student, Fuku.
I'm from Aichi.
What's your name?
Wow!
I'm from the ESEE class.
I have a lot of students.
I'll do my best!
Thank you!
Recently, I've been watching you.
Yes.
You always have a ball that flies.
It's okay. It's the same as the
poachers.
I'm not used to this.
I understand.
Thank you.
The next day.
Today, Aichi Prefecture.
Aichi prefecture
Kariashi
It's a very Kariashi area
Oh, there is
There is a local
Just now, in Aichi prefecture
About half of them are from Aichi
prefecture
Oh, once again, Aichi prefecture
Aichi prefecture
Thank you
It's amazing, there were so many people
in Aichi prefecture
You know
There were quite a few
I'm grateful
There were so many people in Aichi
prefecture
That's right
Aichi prefecture is a pretty big city
A big place
What is this bitter taste
It's not half, it's bitter
Aichi prefecture
Today, you know
Well, it's a local
So
Today, Yuno is
A picture of Aichi
I brought a picture
Oh, what is it?
One, two, three
Three pieces
This is a dumpling
Everyone, look to the left
This is cute
This is
I'll post it
That's true
Can you see it?
Certainly, this dumpling is something
You may see it on Instagram
Have you ever eaten it?
Oh, there are quite a few
There are many girls
It looks delicious
There are also boys
That's true
It's fast
This and
It's cute to line up the orchestra you
are playing on the board now
That's right
In the middle is meat sushi
I want to eat
It's sushi with beef
What does it taste like?
What kind of taste
Something delicious
Oh, this is a picture of my mother
I haven't eaten anything
I only ate in the middle
Yuno, talk
I heard you didn't eat
My mother said it was delicious
Then, not much
Yuno has a lot of delicious food
There is no doubt
Because my mother is
And the last
This is a small mouth
It's cute
There are various things
Mom
I ordered a small mouth
But who took this picture?
All my mother
Mother
Thank you
Thank you mother
I'm not a good student, but I'm a good
student.
You're a good student?
I have friends and classmates from
school.
You went to school before?
Yes, I went to middle school.
I thought it was fun and cool.
Really?
What is your favorite character?
My junior.
Your junior?
Yunho.
Yunho?
Yunho is my senior.
What do you mean by senior?
I've never talked about it in school.
I see.
I'm a junior.
Junior sounds great.
Yunho.
When you talk about age, Yunho is a
junior.
That's right.
Yunho is too young.
Yunho is also young.
I'm glad you came.
Did you tell your friend that you were a
baby?
No, I didn't.
You're a baby because you're at home.
What is your favorite food?
Onigiri and suga-kiya ramen.
Suga-kiya ramen?
The one that Shachi is doing.
I want to eat tempura, so I only eat cup
ramen.
I like soup more than cup ramen.
I like to put bean sprouts in noodles.
I want to eat it.
I often go to shopping malls nearby.
I see.
You like shopping malls.
Tokyo is different.
Tokyo is a shopping mall, so it's a
ramen shop.
That's right.
What is your favorite tourist spot?
I don't have a favorite tourist spot.
I didn't have a favorite tourist spot.
I went to the Inayama Tojo-ka town
during the live show.
You don't go to Nagoya Castle?
I don't go there.
I painted at the school's
I went to the zoo.
I've been there.
There are many animals.
I went to the zoo.
What is your favorite animal park?
I think I've been there.
When you were in that movie?
When I was in the movie,
I went there.
I want to go there.
I'm looking forward to it.
There are many people in Aichi.
In Nagoya,
There are many people in front of the
station.
There are many people.
When I'm on tour,
I feel like there are many people.
Nagoya station is also very popular.
I went to Kizuken.
Compared to Tokyo,
Shibuya is also very popular.
I think there are many people like that.
I think so.
I think it's Yuno's hometown.
Yuno's hometown is Iwami.
It's a good place.
I'm crying now.
I'm sorry.
Yuno always says that he is a good
student.
I think I felt Yuno's value.
I'm not used to Tokyo yet.
I'm wondering if Yuno will come back to
Tokyo.
There is a lot of local love.
I'm looking forward to it.
I want to know more about Aichi.
There are many places around Aichi.
There are many fun places.
There are many places.
It's fun to go to a place that is a
little far away.
Aichi is the best.