Ebichu's video
Good morning
I'm so nervous that I'm buying a lot of
things
It's amazing
I'm like a person who went to the
supermarket
Today is the birthday party
It was the first time for a long time
yesterday
It was also in the weather forecast
For example, today is a clear sky
If you say it, it will really be a clear
sky
I thought I was a clear woman
I will do my best for a day
Good morning
I finished my makeup
My nails are cute
This is Rihana
I will drink sweet sake and go
What was the high note?
I will do part 1
Part 1 is yellow
I made two patterns
Actually, I'm doing it
I will do my best
I will do part 1
I will sing for those who are really
gathering
I put a song that Mayama doesn't put in
the set list
So I'm looking forward to it
I will do my best
I'm nervous
I finished
I finished part 1
The set list is also for those who like
Mayama more
I chose a song that I haven't heard
Thank you
I was looking for a set that was
suitable for the set
But it's not in the set list
I didn't see it
Did you see it?
I was really happy.
The
roshi breaker was really
good.
I was able to get a lot of points
with the new function and the
diamond mask.
It was fun.
It's the second year of Mayama Setsun.
I was dancing with
you.
It was fun.
Mayama Setsun.
The second part is
almost over.
I was relieved
after the first part.
The members
came to see
me and Kaho.
Kaho didn't meet me directly,
but he gave me a
big thank you.
I feel relieved
when I see the members.
I always feel that when I'm
on a solo concert.
The second part is
Rikuo Nakayama.
Rikuo said
I'm going to die
after I die.
I will do my best
to make it reach
Nakayama.
I will do my best
to make it reach Nakayama.
It's over.
The second part
is over.
Yes.
I
I was
very happy, but I was very tired.
It was a very
fun time.
Thank you for watching.
I
want to share
my songs,
people's songs,
and the power I get from Ebichu.
That's the big theme of this time.
See you again
at the Christmas party.
Please meet
Ebichu.
Thank you very much.
Yes.
Today
I was
very happy.
I was like
Why am I dressed like this?
I have my own live broadcast.
I will go with this costume.
It was fun.
I'm so excited that I can't sleep.
But it's just right to have a live
broadcast.
Thank you for having fun.
See you again.
I'm going.
This time, Mayamania Level 5 started
with a thud.
It was a live performance with the light
of a firefly.
I feel like I'm watching a movie.
The songs I've been listening to are
dark.
Like the song of the new generation of
the Lion Mask.
And the song of the new generation of
Passion Night.
It's not a bright pop DA.
It's dark.
This time, it's my style.
I was able to have a live performance.
I still have a lot of tasks to do.
But I'm glad I was able to finish it for
the time being.
And I'm glad I was able to see your
faces.
There was an online conversation the
next day.
Your faces were smiling and I was very
relieved.
I'm going to think about something
interesting from now on.
I hope you enjoy it together.
I've become very mature.
I'm going to make the costumes very
soft.
I'm going to make a lot of frills and
pajamas.
I was able to add cuteness to the
costumes.
But when I look back, my back is open.
I'm going to paint my back and skin.
I sometimes add skin color to my
clothes.
I made it a see-through costume.
I can see the IAMORI line.
I'm a little mature.
The front is cute, but the back is
mature.
Thanks to the power of the costume, I
was able to stand on stage as an idol.
I was thinking of the powder and
ARIAMALTOMI.
I was thinking of cocoa and Niji.
I wanted to sing a little mature and
hopeful song.
The reason I wanted to do that was that
the beginning of MAYAMANIA LEVEL 5 was a
breakthrough.
I wanted to cover songs with a mature
image, and I wanted to share the songs
that I received a lot of support during
my self-restraint.
The music inside the song has changed a
lot.
At first, I was thinking about making an
acoustic block twice in January, but it
was only once.
I decided to make it a second part in
April, and I thought about it again. I
made a new one about a week ago.
I didn't think about it, but I made it.
I like easy-to-understand setlist.
I think it would be interesting if the
story of the next song was a bit more
interesting because it was a bit of a
two-day rental.
I'm a little worried that everyone is
satisfied, but it was one of the things
I wanted to do, so I'm satisfied.
I was thinking about the contents of
Mayamanya Level 5 earlier, and I decided
to do it.
I was thinking about it in August, and I
decided to cancel it before the
rehearsal in January.
I was waiting for the food to be served.
I couldn't speak. I went home and...
I didn't eat much, so I thought I had to
eat something, but I went straight to
bed.
Then my father said he brought a
separate delivery for me.
I had a strawberry daifuku for everyone.
I had four strawberry daifuku, but I ate
it.
I said, I didn't eat it.
I thought it was a little bad, but I ate
a strawberry daifuku on the bed.
I slept with my teeth out.
I was tired, so I thought it would be
hard to do a part two concert.
I want to do it again if I have a
chance.
I'm the youngest among shrimp
I can approach it as the youngest.
It's a little far from the image of a
shrimp in the ordinary shrimp.
It's not a big deal for an adult woman,
but it's like an adult woman.
I always think that I can approach it
differently from other members.
Especially this time, I was able to
approach it with a soft approach.
In the Mayamania I had before, I left my
preferences aside.
I was thinking about what everyone
wanted to see in Mayama.
This time, I'm really a citizen.
I'm 24 years old.
I wanted to grow up a little and try to
do an adult stage.
I'm wondering if I should do it at level
6 or 7.
I think it would be fun to go back to
the starting point and do an idol-like
live performance.
I think it would be fun to deepen my
thoughts on what I want to do.
I think it's either way.
I think about what to do at the
Christmas festival every year.
I spend the year thinking about what to
do at the Christmas festival.
I think I've been able to express myself
this time.
I have two plans, but I haven't thought
about what song to do.
So I'm waiting for a new member to
change.
I don't have much opportunity to sit
down and sing, so I'm going to do a solo
concert.
I'm going to sing a song with a sofa, a
table, a lamp, and a carpet.
I'm going to use the sofa as much as
possible, so I'm going to sit down.
It's not hard to sing, but it's similar
to singing at home.
But I'm on stage, so I'm going to be a
cat's nest.
I'm thinking of a live performance
that's not just a live performance.
The first thing I want to do is to enjoy
the people who come to the concert.
But there are also live performances, so
I want to make sure that the people who
come to the concert are not lonely.
I want to do a dinner show.
There are people who say that if they do
a dinner show, they will get tens of
thousands of yen.
I'm a set list that's conscious of being
told that someday.