Yakan and idol!
So, the main project is...
Can you please give a cute title to the
camera?
Okay, here I go!
My three elements!
Today we will introduce three elements
that make up Shinahama.
Let's get to know more about the guest
idol.
Please tell us about the three elements.
My three elements are...
Ta-da!
It looks like this.
Oh!
Shinahama is a video editor.
Yes.
Game.
Fashionable.
She also wrote a cute
That's right.
It looks like Shin-chan.
Number 1 is video editing!
It's Piko Piko!
I made a mistake.
I made the first and second ones the
opposite of Piko Piko and Kachi Kachi.
The game is Piko Piko, but I made it the
opposite.
No, no, no.
I'm just worried about you in the world.
I'm glad.
Are you okay?
Yes, thank you.
By the way, it's video editing.
The first video I made was the birthday
video of Chihon Takai.
I edit videos on my smartphone.
I've always admired video editing.
I've always been interested in video
editing because I've been filmed and
edited.
I wanted to make a video editing video.
I was in the sixth grade of elementary
school.
I made a video editing video for
Chihon's birthday.
I was very happy.
I made a lot of birthday videos for the
members.
I put a lot of pictures and lyrics on
it.
I want to send the first video on my
birthday.
I send it exactly at noon.
Do you make birthday videos?
Yes, I make birthday videos.
I started making birthday videos.
I'm doing TikTok these days.
I want to show you my video editing.
I put a serious video editing.
Your video editing is going up.
Yes, it's going up.
I'm happy to be praised by everyone for
editing the memories of Osaka.
I'm also making a video editing video.
I'm making a video editing video in
Osaka.
I'm making a video editing video.
I haven't made a video editing video
yet.
I didn't know how to make a video
editing video.
I'm making a video editing video.
I'm happy.
What is your favorite part of your video
editing?
I haven't changed it yet.
You're brave.
I'm making a video editing video.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I sent it to Saki-san, Tappi-san, and
Mamo at Mark-san.
I love you all! Thank you!