Please like and subscribe to my channel!
Please follow my Instagram too!
Yakan and Aida-Ru!
Please like and subscribe!
Thank you very much!
Thank you!
Could you tell us about the event?
Yes!
There is a VOLT One-One Live!
On December 23, the LUNA Festival will
be held at Yokohama Bay Hall!
That's right!
It's a one-one live for Luna's birthday.
We always do the LUNA Festival every
year.
Luna is planning the event.
She always thinks about us even though
it's her birthday.
Really?
Luna thinks about us. Chi-chan, think
about us.
Chi-chan is thinking about us.
Don't talk about that!
Sorry, I'm sorry.
Chi-chan is thinking about us.
Chi-chan was already doing it last year,
but she was playing drums.
She was playing a new song.
Chi-chan is not saying that she is bad.
There are many things to do together.
You can't follow everything.
I'm sorry.
We are happy to have you here.
I was saved by a junior high school
student.
There is one more thing.
VOLT's 4th single will be released on
December 14.
The first limited edition Blu-ray will
record the 3rd anniversary live and the
tour final.
I hope you are looking forward to it.
The release event is also in progress.
Please come to the event.
Please check the official site of VOLT.
I pray for you next year.
I want you to drink tea from me.
Thank you.
Today is Shizuoka tea.
I drink Shizuoka tea for the first time.
Really?
Yes.
Wow!
The tea smells good.
Thank you for your watching.
It's delicious.
I feel relaxed when drinking tea.
I want to have a tea time with Yakan-kun
at VOLT.
Thank you.
I feel warm.
Please say goodbye to the camera.
Thank you for watching until the end.
I'm advertising.
I'm also doing Instagram.
Please follow me.
Thank you, Yakan-kun.
That's all from VOLT.
Bye bye.
Looking great!
lol
Thank you for watching!
Thank you very much!
This is Ayano Shirohama.