Thank you for watching!
Calometer Jyoshou TV!
Yay!
It's over!
Good evening!
Is everyone awake at night?
I was awake.
It's been a while since I've been on a
show like this.
Certainly, the making of the show has
been going well recently.
Thank you very much.
TokiBeki Shinken Suijaku!
Suijaku!
I'll use this card.
Oh, cool!
Thank you for watching!
Take this!
I can tell from your weird face!
How was Candle beam instead of a includ?
It was fun!
Thank you for watching!
I think everyone knows about the new
game, but if you play the same card, you
can win.
The person who gets the most cards will
be the winner.
This time it's not Trump, but it's like
a private game.
I'm glad to win.
Please enjoy it.
I'm done.
3 points for me.
3 points.
I go shot.
The timing is different.
Yay!
Which one is the clock?
This one.
I'll go.
I'm the last one.
That's right.
I'll start from the first one.
I'll choose...
It's a summer picture.
Is this a summer picture?
How old is this?
It's a summer picture.
It's cute.
Thank you for watching!
I'll take another one of Aki-chan.
That's right.
This is Aki-chan.
Look.
What?
Who?
Stop it.
No, no.
I'll show you.
This is the same photo, right?
That's right.
No, no.
It's the same photo as if there was a
person.
It's exactly the same.
I see.
Here's a can of beer.
What's this?
Is this a strawberry?
It's definitely a strawberry.
It's blue.
I was surprised.
It's decided from the members.
I don't remember.
It's a picture of a Japanese girl.
Cute.
I'm sorry.
I was scolded.
The picture is long.
Yes.
Thank you for watching.
I'm a girl group member.
I remember this.
I think this is it.
It's Kimo Damishi.
I don't like it.
She's crying.
Everyone, please turn up the screen.
Tokimeki Kimo Damishi.
I've been watching her recently.
Who is it?
Don't tell anyone.
I've already forgotten.
I don't know.
I'll go.
I'll change it.
What is it?
It's cute.
It's upside down.
Look at her face.
What is it?
She's crying.
I don't like it.
I'll go.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Oh my god!
What is this?
Where did you get this?
Whose phone is this?
Tell me!
Who brought this?
This is an old phone.
It's a pretty new phone.
It's not a new phone.
Is this what happened recently?
I made it right!
Right here!
This is difficult.
So the game ready within 20 Lift
I can't do it anymore.
You did it!
Amazing!
I can't do it anymore.
You did it!
Thank you for watching.
Who is the cutest?
Cute!
Hair, hair.
Yes, it was all growing up.
Super power.
Cute!
It was on the top.
This is a hit.
It's a little small.
Who is the cutest?
Same.
Thank you for watching.
It's Aki again!
Really?
I'm scared.
I'm scared too.
So cute.
I'm scared when a girl is at a festival.
Amazing.
It takes about an hour.
I'm going to go now.
Oh, it's Aki-chan!
It's Aki-chan!
This is the first time I've seen this.
It's a picture of a child.
Aki-chan, let's go!
I don't know.
No!
No, no!
Kaname, you have to do it.
You have to pull it.
I forgot.
I forgot too.
Kaname, you go.
Wait.
It's not the same.
I forgot.
This and my turn.
I did it.
I said it just now.
I forgot.
It's the first round.
It's the second round.
Wait.
Where was it?
I don't remember.
What was it?
This is...
How was it?
It's difficult.
Was it this?
How was it?
Ah, I can't do it.
I can't do it.
This?
I don't remember.
Why are you...
I forgot.
I don't remember.
I got it again.
I see some.
It's new.
Is this a flower?
It's me.
It's a flower.
Which one?
This one.
You are too good.
This one is easy.
You got 2 right.
Do you remember?
I don't remember.
I'm scared.
I'm going to try.
Where is this?
You are too good.
It's here.
I remember the one with the flower.
Which one is the flower?
This one?
This one.
This is the one.
Where is it?
It's not here.
No way.
It's here.
It's there.
No.
It's here.
You are all wrong.
There are only 2.
What is this?
This is your festival.
This is fun.
You are all wrong.
Look at this.
Is this the one?
No.
This is Victory.
It's not! It's a water tank!
It's not a water tank.
It's a tank.
That's right.
It's nostalgic.
It's cute.
Eh?
I forgot.
It's very bitter.
It's bitter.
I haven't taken a picture yet.
I haven't taken a picture of this side
yet.
This is the latest one.
It's the latest one.
I'm sorry.
You can't remember it.
No.
Oh no.
I did it.
But I don't remember.
What is it?
This?
This is the second one.
I'm sorry.
Who is it?
Hey!
What kind of face is that?
This is bad.
This is weird.
I'm crying.
This is not a good thing.
The person who chose this picture is a
genius.
I chose a picture of a cute girl.
This picture was here.
I chose a picture of a genius.
Where is the picture?
Who is it?
This is a picture of a girl.
Where is this picture?
Is this a picture of a girl?
Please subscribe to my channel.
Oh!
That's all?
No, no!
Next to her.
I don't want to push it.
Who is it?
I did it.
Let's see what Junia got.
I don't know what it is.
Thank you for watching.
I can't remember.
Wait.
This is the first time.
I can't remember.
Et ooo
, ooooo,
ru
This is the
next stop
I'm very
round
office
What? What is this?
This is different.
This is a Gimia.
This is a...
Ah!
You pulled the wrong one.
Aki-chan, go!
Which one should I pick?
Ah!
You got it!
Thank you!
One more time.
Interesting.
I forgot!
You pulled it.
I pulled it.
You still have one more.
I'm sorry, I'm not good at this.
Ayase's junior is watching.
I'm not good at this.
I'll try.
It's very close.
You did it!
We did it!
We can do it!
No!
That's not good!
Hurry up!
No!
What should we do?
Hurry up!
No!
Listen.
We can do it!
Here we go.
Thank you!
I did it!
Where was it?
Please subscribe to our channel!
It's Kito-chan!
Where was it?
What is this?
What?
I'm glad I got it earlier.
I'll take it off.
So cute!
What is this?
Mini tomato.
No!
Stop it!
It's a moon.
It's cute!
I don't like this.
This is too old.
I don't like it.
I want to try this.
What?
Oh!
I didn't get it.
Eri.
Chiruria.
What is this?
Ah!
That's right.
It's noisy.
What is this?
What?
It's cute.
What is this?
It's a person.
It's cute.
It's a person, isn't it?
What?
You are smart.
What is this?
What's this?
It's not on my hand?
Hahaha!
It's not what I thought.
Someone, please explain.
Seriously?
It's the one I saw earlier.
I got it.
Where was it?
I got it!
Thank you for watching!
Aki-chan is strong!
We're probably weak because Aki-chan is
strong.
I forgot!
Don't forget, Aki-chan.
Don't make that face.
Sorry.
Don't hide it.
Don't hide it from each other.
Your speech is too funny.
Aki-chan is not good at speaking.
She разрd YEAH!
This is...
...the dream of OHARE.
What was I doing?
Thank you for your viewing.
Aw Reporter
You did it Ititu
You are great
Haha
And this time
Please subscribe to our channel!
I miss it!
This is so weird!
This is crazy!
Please collect it!
Help me!
Poor thing.
It's not out yet.
What's wrong?
Did I say this?
Wait a minute.
This one!
It came out from somewhere.
I didn't want you to say it.
She did it!
She's good at this.
This is a good match.
It's coming out.
That means...
Please listen to it.
What?
Thank you!
Thank you for saving me!
I like this.
Thank you for watching!
I don't know what I drew.
What did you draw?
This?
There is still a new one.
I'm scared.
I'm scared to see it in the middle.
I will never forget this.
I'm scared to show everyone.
I drew Aki.
Thank you for watching.
I'm not good at this.
I can't do it.
This is the last one.
I'm scared.
Oh, the one from before.
The one from before.
It's here.
This one?
What is this?
Julia.
So cute.
What is this?
A wig?
The one that you dyed.
I asked for a snack.
And I got it.
Julia's face.
I got it.
I agree.
I'm not sure about this.
You're not sure about this.
Oh, I got it.
I got it.
I'm not sure about this.
Oh!
I see!
It was on the ground!
Oh!
I can do it!
She's doing it!
So close!
I thought I was going to eat it.
I want to eat it.
Thank you for watching!
I'll go with this one.
You're already going with this one?
Wait, which one should I go with?
I'm not sure.
I wonder which one it is.
It's a very difficult question.
I don't know.
Really?
I'll go.
I got it.
Thank you.
Kanamin can do it, too.
Do you want to mix it?
I'll go.
Thank you for watching!
The winner is Yui!
Nice way to close the game!
I'm done!
She's always so close!
So, that means...
I know the answer!
What?
Aki wins!
primeira הי after last five games
I'm still young, so I don't know.
I think there are a lot of amazing
things in the world.
I'm sorry.
Special prize!
I got it.
So, this time,
I used the photos of the members from a
young age.
I made a new collection.
I've never seen it before.
How was it?
It was fun.
I was embarrassed.
I had a lot of fun using the photos.
I want to see the members' photos.
Please try it.
That's all for today.
Thank you for watching.
Bye bye.
Thank you for watching!
Please subscribe to my channel!