Ebichu's video!
Wow! Look!
Wow!
It's a
My mom made my favorite yaki-onigiri
this morning.
Doing it like an old woman.
It seems like a big problem has
occurred.
The final!
What did you say?
I was asked if I would quit.
I said I would quit.
N is the opposite.
But Yenomayana often writes the
opposite.
It's like a horror movie, but it's not.
The final!
Thank you for watching. We are CJ MC.
Thank you for watching.
The next day
You're so cute, Chimmy!
I'm sorry.
Oh, no.
Ready, set, go!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5!
I'm Harinabe.
I'm Hana.
I'm honored to accept your invitations.
We appreciate you all the way to the
end!
We'd appreciate a lot of people from
there coming by.
We're the team we want!
Great job!
Kacchan!
I'm scared.
Okay, go inside and listen to it.
Okay.
I want to talk.
Riku will be caught.
I'm scared.
Final.
Practice after the break.
Please.
Finally, I came.
Final.
Let's enjoy until the end.
Let's go.
I forgot.
I came but I forgot.
Nice to meet you.
I speak like a gyaru.
I'm sorry.
Did you finish?
Yes.
I can speak like a gyaru.
I'm sorry.
Let's go to the live.
Let's go.
Everything is spinning
Spinning round and round
Bye-bye!
Don't be so kind
Hey, please
The electric signal that connects us
You and me, always at a distance
While looking at each other's eyes
Let's talk about things that don't exist
Connecting feeling, accelerating feeling
Heat up burning, it's still not enough
Oh, please send me to my place
classification
Thank you for watching!
Even now, I'm getting old
I can't talk anymore
Where did that person go?
Was there a good person?
That's enough
I can talk about the past
I don't know where I am, if I can forget
the past and the future
I'll give you a hug once again, the one
you're holding in my heart
If the power of this star is buried in
the sand
I'll turn everything upside down and
start over again
I don't want to be a burden to you
I still have a lot of things to do
Beyond the sea
We can go anywhere in the distant future
Let's look at the hourglass called the
universe
Almost
Visitor Registration
God of Rice
In the Anything Consultation Room
Ok approve
Sendblast
Come on
Man P
I remember the day I bought the moon
Those days, the days
Time that I can't see
The memories I want to tell
With an unbreakable heart
I aim for you, who is lacking
I can't say the blood, but
There is no legend of the movie
I'll rub me nose with this feel
Pipion
Yup
According to the umbrellas
Wanya
This is
No matter what
Meat
Anywhere
I can draw it by myself
I love Uji Ujou
Thank you for your hard work!