Thank you for watching.
Hello?
Haruka?
Haruka, it's been a while.
Eh?
Mio-tan?
Wait, wait.
Oh my goodness!
Haruka, how are you?
Wait, wait, wait!
Hello?
Hey, your voice is changing, right?
Haruka?
Who is it?
It's Fukuharu Haruka, right?
Eh? Didn't you see it?
You saw it, didn't you?
You saw it!
I tried hard to not notice it, but it
was completely useless.
You saw it, didn't you?
I saw it.
Yaho Harupyon.
Yaho, I always call you Harupyon.
Harupyon? Yeah.
When I say Harupyon, you'll definitely
understand.
I've never called you Haruka before, but
I didn't call you Haruka at all.
I didn't call you at all. I knew it by
your voice.
I didn't call you at all. I thought you
sounded like Miyata from the beginning.
It's kind of... It's kind of...
It's kind of mysterious.
Really? Thank you.
I'm so happy.
Recently, because of the coronavirus,
until then, if I had time,
I would meet her three times a week.
I couldn't meet her directly.
I did contact her, but...
We didn't have much time to talk about
our time together, so...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I thought it would be nice if we could
talk about it today.
Hahaha!
I'm so happy! Let's talk!
Thank you!
kissed...
I have a lot of friends, and it's a very
welcoming house.
Harupyo came to visit me a few times.
I really look back at the photos of
yesterday and the time when he came.
It's a birthday cake, isn't it?
I look back at the photos of that time.
I thought it was nostalgic.
I miss you.
Yeah. Yeah.
Because...
How old are you? 17?
Yeah, Harupyon is 17 years old.
I'm 16.
You're 16?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
How many years?
Yeah.
Six years?
But when you say six years,
it feels like it's only been six years.
Yeah.
But it's been about seven and a half
years since I made my debut.
When I think about it, I think I met
Harupyon as soon as I made my debut.
Harupyon has been doing it since I was
little.
So it was so umm…
I was watching it on Harupyon TV.
So when we first met,
it was like…
It was like…
I didn't think I'd be friends with you.
I met him.
Really?
But we got along really well.
Right?
It's strange.
Yeah.
I feel like we can continue to be
connected in the future.
Right?
何か変な感じするよね。 私さ、多分さ、
一番ミュータンが友達で電話っていう、 電話する?
ミュータンが一番多い気がして。
あ、本当?
そうだね。
私も一番多い気がするんだけど、 私も一番多い気がするんだけど、
I don't even know how to ask you out.
How long have you been out?
Well, the other day, I met you at the
dance show.
I really thought it would be the first
time in a year if I was really bad at
it.
You didn't get along with me?
Yeah.
So sorry, it's almost the 3rd episode.
I think so.
Oh.
Right?
It's not quite right.
That's right.
It's like...
Oh, but that's right.
Haruto came to my location in the
afternoon.
Yes, yes, yes.
He came to work and traveled with me to
Tokyo.
At that time,
I was...
I was really...
Harupyon is the best friend I want to
make a girlfriend.
What do you mean?
Harupyon is really considerate.
No, no, it's my line.
No, no, no.
He's really good at cooking.
I feel relieved just by talking to him.
Really?
But when I say that,
Haru-chan says,
I want to be your boyfriend.
Do you remember what you said?
You said it.
I don't know if I remember.
년
, I wonder if I really have Harupyon in
me. I wonder if I'm relying on you. I
thought so. Because when we were in the
basement, we were a little bit together.
Do you remember crying at the hotel?
I remember.
We were next to each other in the room.
We were talking and talking.
That's right.
You cried together, didn't you?
I did.
I was crying in the bathroom.
I was like, Harupyon, are you okay? Come
out.
Wait a minute.
Really.
I was really supported at that time.
そうだよね。なんか、私たち結構さ、なんかこう、人との関わりをさ、
うんうんうん。
すごくさ、大事にしたいって、こう、強く思いがちというかさ、
そうだね。
すごいそういう気持ちが強いじゃない?
確かに、そうかも。
だから、こう、なんだろうな。
People want to believe more than their
own capes.
That's right.
I'm sure that's the case.
I couldn't organize it, but I really
believed in people and liked them.
I was probably 16, 17 years old at that
time.
So, I don't even know how to worry.
That's right.
But you know, I'm worried about
something similar. That's right. That
might be the case.
That's why I get a lot of encouragement
from my parents.
I get a lot of advice from my parents. I
get a lot of advice from my parents.
Really? But I really like people.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. It's been like that
for a long time.
I was with Miu-tan and I was watching
her live.
I thought, there's a song that makes me
think,
there's a song that makes me think,
Something for the invited concert and a
tea.
You gave me an album after the concert.
Do you remember?
I still read that black file.
I don't remember until you say it's
nostalgic.
Really?
You made it so well.
You made it.
Something for the songs
I cut the photos into hearts and made
it.
I was so moved by that.
Really?
I thought you were a really warm person.
But I also like Harupyon's...
I'm not asking for advice, but I've
heard some of your concerns.
Like...
I want to be of some help to you.
Thinking about it...
It's connected to my own sanity.
So...
When I think about people, I wonder what
would happen if I changed that.
When I talk to Harupyon, I feel like I'm
being purified.
Yeah.
But Harupyon, even now...
Is there anything you want to cry about?
Something I want to cry about?
It doesn't matter if you're sad or
happy.
Is there anything?
Harupyon and I used to cry a lot back
then.
You used to cry.
Yeah, I guess so.
Even now...
I guess so.
I think I've gotten stronger than I was
before.
But I wonder...
I wonder if I have any worries.
I wonder if this is right.
What is my...
Actions and stuff.
That's why, really...
When I'm with Miyu-tan, I really feel...
It's really, you know, a kick-off.
Something around me...
It really makes the environment one.
Miyu-tan, you know.
I talked a lot during the interview the
other day.
So I think it's great to see that.
When I was in the lead role, I was
wondering if I could do it.
I think I'm thinking about it.
I see.
There was a time when I was worried that
I might not be suitable for an actress.
At that time, I couldn't say good words
to you.
Why?
I'm sorry.
I really want to be like this, not a
worry about Harupyon.
I was worried about Harupyon.
I want to teach Harupyon now.
I think it's shining.
It's the same as when I watch it on TV.
It's the same as when I was working.
I don't know if I'm going to the good or
not, but I feel like I'm starting to
climb the stairs from Harupyon at that
time.
I think I have to do my best.
Why are you happy?
I'm so happy.
You're so understanding.
Oh, wait.
I...
I listened to Harupyo's new song the
other day.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Thank you.
I collaborated with Okamotozu.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I like bands and I listen to them a lot.
Oh, really?
I thought it was a mysterious
combination.
I was really excited to hear that.
I like that.
I feel like I can see a different side
of Harupyon, the artist I've seen
before.
Really?
Yeah.
I'm so happy.
I wanted to tell you a lot today.
Really?
Yeah.
I wanted to tell you a lot.
I'm so happy. Thank you.
You know, Harupyon is...
What is it?
Probably days before we went to a live
performance?
Long time ago...
I have a job, so I was asked if I could
go to karaoke.
I was asked if I could go to karaoke.
Do you remember?
I don't remember.
You went with Haru-kun.
Before the singing job, you said you
couldn't swallow your throat.
How much did you sing the day before?
I was wondering about karaoke, and Haru-
kun kept saying...
I put my own song in it, and...
I've been practicing for the next day's
work.
But at that time, I was doing an
actress, and I was also doing a variety
show MC.
Ah, Hoshitsu?
Yes, I was also doing voice actors and
singers.
I was doing various genres.
Harupyon, who is working hard and is
moving people, is very important to each
and every one of them.
I feel like I like singers, artists, and
jobs.
Do you have any dreams as an artist?
A dream as an artist?
Hmm...
But...
I want to make a song that people listen
to can be a good idea,
or a song that can be shared with
others.
I want to make a healing space.
And I want to make a live performance
for many people.
I want to perform on the stage.
Sounds good.
I want to go.
I want you to come.
I don't plan to go.
Please call me at that time.
I want to give you something.
What?
I think the drawer is on the desk. Can
you open it?
What?
What is this?
What's in it?
What is this? Like a book?
Yes, a little...
What?
Hey, it's nostalgic.
Wait, what?
Oh, what?
I thought I'd write a letter for a long
time.
Simple.
Something like this.
I think it's a genre that we talk about
when we're working.
There are private things.
We have a lot of relationships.
We have a lot of things to do.
But...
I simply want to say thank you for being
my friend.
That's what I wanted to say.
I'm so happy.
The photo...
I remember it.
It's the first time I took a photo with
Harupyon.
I was thinking it was a bit cheesy.
But I've been doing it since then.
About 6 years.
We've been sharing a lot of joys and
sorrows.
I'm grateful that we've become friends.
I just want to say this.
Me too.
I'm so happy.
Yes.
Thank you.
I'm sure there are a lot of hard things
ahead of you, but please consult me
anytime.
Um...
Thank you for being my friend.
There aren't many people I can consult
with.
I've been talking about a lot of private
things rather than work.
I've been working hard together.
I'm a very special person.
I'm going to cry.
Don't cry.
Thank you.
I'll put this picture in my house.
I'll go play at home again.
Come and see me.
Please take care of my mother.
Thank you.
I'll give my mother a croquette.
I want to eat avocado croquette.
I'll give you. Thank you.
Let's meet again. See you.
Bye bye. See you.