This week's Ebichutastas is the last
episode of Ebichutastas, which continued
last week.
I'm not going to eat it.
Who will be judged by what kind of crime
tonight?
Ebichutastas, start!
cosmos
username
Please add various things to the private
Ebisu Middle School!
I don't want to hear that.
This program is provided by the sponsor
you see.
I feel like you.
Please subscribe to the channel.
The trial of the members is held in the
trial room.
In this trial, the prosecutor is the
prosecutor and the defendant is the
defendant.
The member's multiple votes determine
whether he is guilty or not.
The judge's attention is on the verdict.
The next basic case is this.
The defendant is the defendant.
This is terrible.
According to the information of the
program staff, the defendant is the
defendant.
The defendant is the defendant.
This is a clear testimony and there is
no doubt.
The defendant is the defendant.
There are many types of laughter.
I don't laugh like a comedian.
I laugh like a cute dog.
It is a skill to make a dog a specialty.
It is a skill to write a skill.
This is a proof.
Please look at this website.
This is a skill.
This is a skill to make people laugh.
Hoshino said this is a marathon.
Hoshino is the defendant.
Please stand up.
I don't want to hear a marathon.
Did you make more mistakes?
The defendant is on the profile.
For example, if you make us laugh now
and the defendant is angry, you can keep
the profile.
I see.
It's a pity that you suddenly do it in
front of everyone.
According to rumors, it is normal for
Kenji to laugh.
I've heard that too.
Kenji is quick to blink.
This is a gag battle between Kenji and
Hikoku Mayama.
First, Mayama will imitate the shop
clerk and aim for a jackpot.
Welcome.
Please come in.
The green bag is very nice.
Let me try to match it.
I'll open the mirror.
It looks great on you.
You have a clear face.
It's a little flashy.
No, it's not.
I'll put blue camisole on it.
Camisole?
I'll put it on the other side.
I'm talking about happiness
It's funny
Next, Kenji Takiue will play a joke to
catch up with the defendant
What are you doing?
I'm using my stuff
What's going to happen?
Can I?
Now it's time for the defendant of
Takiue High School
Kenji
Interesting
You're slipping
Wait a minute
This is...
It's different from what I thought
Kenji, are you Kenji?
I wanted to help you but I couldn't see
anything
You did it?
I understand
Please return it
Please return it quickly
What's going on?
It's not written
Why did you get hurt?
Don't act like a big boss
No
Seriously
It's not written
The person who thought the previous one
was interesting is innocent
The person who thought Takiue High
School was interesting is innocent
Now it's time for the judgment
Was Takiue High School interesting or
Mayama High School?
Ready, go
I was wrong
It's wrong
It's innocent
The defendant is innocent
The second trial today is...
The next
The next is...
Ignoring the idol's promise
What is it?
The defendant, Aika Hirota, is in the
front
What does that mean?
Aika Hirota
Ignoring the idol's promise
According to the damage report by the
Dastas staff
The defendant, Aika Hirota, even though
she is an idol
She is not afraid of insects at all
Come on!
After the idols were daar confirming
whether their l........
I see
ujoe company
i sa
What purpose do you have in making this
show?
Mrs.Hirota
has been convinced by her
that it has to be a good and니다
I'm afraid that I can't say it's cute.
I'm worried about the staff.
Here is the evidence that it doesn't
move.
When I put out the blue dye, which is
the bait for shrimp fishing, in the
shrimp-chewing shrimp shell,
I pay attention to Hirota's speech.
It's cute! It's cute when I touch it!
Can you touch it?
It's cute when I tickle it!
Is this correct?
Why do you hate bugs?
Kenji, what's wrong?
I see, it's a basic thing
Do you want to go to the basic thing?
Bugs are alive, right?
Why do you hate bugs?
Be honest, you can't lose
If you are a bug, you are more
uncomfortable
Wow
Be honest
Kenji, I see
You want to see the reaction of the
right idol
I want to see it as a representative of
the audience
First, can I show you a sample?
Hoshina Kashiwagi, please come forward
I can't
I know
Hoshina Kashiwagi, please come forward
It's not like that
It's a good reaction from now
That's a good reaction
Kenji prepared a strong dish in Nagano
prefecture
Zazamushi Tsukudani
First, please see the reaction of the
right idol by Hoshina Kashiwagi
What is the reaction of the right idol?
I thought it was a toy for cockroach
I thought it was hungry
Wow
It's good
No
Zazamushi
What?
It's a bug
Hiroota-san, this reaction
This reaction
Thank you very much
Please go home
Looking at this
Isn't it cute?
Looking at this, the viewers will be
scared
But Hiroota-san won't think anything
even if he looks at this
Please show us
What is this?
This is a bug
Can you eat it with a bug?
I can eat it because it's a bug
There are many friends
Matsuno-san, don't eat it
It will be dirty
It's poisonous, so it's easy to eat
For some reason, Matsuno, who is
interested in the bug, moves to the
defendant's seat
I will eat
Please eat
It looks delicious
How is it?
Well
Why is this?
It's a little bit sour
Sour?
Why is it sour?
Matsuno, you ate the second one
Can I eat a little more?
I've been eating since I was a child
It's delicious
The defendant's truth is that it will be
delicious
Matsuno first
It's not good to decide by appearance
I think it's the same as like or dislike
I see
I understand
I think it's wrong to say that you know
everything even though you can't
understand it by the surface
I can see a new discovery
I will kill that chance
I understand
If you think Hirota's reaction is right,
you are innocent
If you think it's wrong, please raise
the criminal card
The verdict
Is Hirota's reaction true or not as an
idol?
Ready?
I'm innocent
All are innocent
So, the defendant is innocent
Thank you
Thank you for watching
After this, the TASTAS trial continues
And the new development of the TV drama
TASTAS trial to pursue the
Today, we are doing the trial
Isn't this set amazing?
It's amazing
I saw it for the first time
It seems to appear in TV dramas
It seems to be used in TV dramas
Really?
What does that mean?
Who is it?
I don't like this rumor!
Yup. That is...
The first episode, rule of conduct drama
Curtsys
Last time, Hiroto escaped from the
prison and took a hostage in a house in
Rikken.
He continued to resist without listening
to the police's persuasion.
The owner of the 100-House God's Misa!
Then there, the God of the 100-House
God...
I won't forgive anyone who robs this
village!
It's mine!
The God of the 100-House God...
However, HAN AO was probably her Mother.
Why?
Because...
...I didn't wants to brainchild a child
like her?
God of chaos!
Even the operations of small buttons are
the hunter.
And...
Thank you for watching!
A few days after arresting Hirota
The police were investigating whether
Hirota had stolen money
that he was hiding
Hey, Hirota
Shut up
I know you did it
Where did you get the stolen money?
I don't know
Are you listening?
No
Listen!
Let's go home, Chiyo.
This is Rika Warai.
Rika Warai is a legendary detective who
makes any criminal laugh and make him
confess.
You're done, too.
Please.
Hello.
Why did you come here?
I don't know
You don't know?
Why did you come here?
Please do your best
Why? Why?
Please laugh
She's scratching
She's holding it in her hand
Shall I touch it?
This is a mode-mode
You're done
You should tell us
We should change
Let's change
You are a crybaby
Mr. Shiroda
Can you give us a hand?
I have a family
I have to make this easy
I can't buy goldfish food
You are crying
Let's change
Mr. Otoshi
I'm the legendary one
What is your favorite food?
My favorite food is ice cream
No
That is the steamed bread
I know that
Steamed bread
Yes
It's a cheese
It's delicious
I ate chicken
I don't know
What is your favorite food?
I like fish
I eat fish with fish
Where did you get the money?
I don't know
What should I do?
The negotiation period ends without
knowing the amount of money
And the day of the trial came
Officially
I will change
First, please enter the court
Where did you get the money?
I don't know
Where are you?
I'm the goddess of Sattoko!
Oh no!
The goddess of Sattoko
What is that?
I am the god of the man.
Hey, you guys! Get out of the room and
get out of here!
Hey!
I can't move.
What's this?
Run away from here.
Thank you, everyone.
Wait, Hiroto. Let's shoot Samurai.
Mom.
I...
I can't remember raising such a child.
Mother!
Son!
5 o'clock, 45 minutes. Prepare the
hospital.
Son!
Father!
This was fun!
It was fun!
But Kaiki-san, this is your first time
in this drama.
I'm glad you were able to play the role
for the first time.
What did you say?
I said, what?
I'm glad.
I didn't think this god would be in the
drama at all.
I'm glad you used this.
I didn't think you'd use it.
I used it.
It's heavy, isn't it?
I think you need a lot of acting skills
to be able to do this.
It's a hard job.
I'll practice.
Next, the next act.
The next act is this.
A strange face, persistent temptation.
Who is it?
I don't know.
I can't believe I'm the one who said it.
The defendant, Riko Nakayama, forward.
Yes.
What is persistent temptation?
According to the members' testimony, the
defendant Riko Nakayama is a persistent
person who makes strange faces.
Therefore, he is accused of making
strange faces with persistent material.
I see.
What on earth is it?
Hiro-taka has such a testimony.
Riko Nakayama's testimony.
There are too many strange faces in my
phone that I can open a photo shop.
You can open a photo shop?
There are so many kinds of strange
faces?
That's why I can make funny faces.
I want to wear a lot of funny faces.
As a result, I can only make funny
faces.
There are so many strange faces.
I have prepared a testimony for you.
Here is the testimony.
Are you checking?
What is this?
You are taking photos from the bottom.
This is amazing.
I'm sorry.
Please be quiet.
Is this a strange face?
I think it's not.
I think it's a very cute photo.
Thank you.
You have a strange face.
What is a strange face?
Really?
Kenji Takiue, what is a strange face?
I understand.
Kenji Takiue, please tell us the strange
face.
Is it a strange face?
Please.
It's always like this.
Don't you have many photos like this
today?
Kenji Takiue is quick to blink.
Kenji Takiue will show us a strange
face.
For example, if I have a strange face,
Please tell us.
What is it?
What is it, Matsu?
It's like a brick.
Really?
It's really like that.
I think I'm aware of my face.
That's why I think so.
Break your shell.
Break your limit.
Don't use your hands.
I understand.
I'm scared.
Is it okay to be a defendant?
I'm nervous.
It's not a position to be in.
So let's participate.
What?
It's not a position to be in.
We do it together?
We do it together
What?
Then, stand next to each other
The person who says the name will do the
face change
I'm going to do the face change
What do you mean?
I'm going to do it
Cute
You can't do it so realistically
It's okay
Next, the face change test by the three
people
I'm going to do it
First is
Takiyue
Next is Kaiki
Next is Naka Yama
What is this?
The final decision
Is Naka Yama's face change guilty or
innocent?
What?
Innocent
I did it
Innocent or innocent?
Naka Yama
Next part will continue
The next episode of Ebichu Tastas will
be the final episode of Ebichu Tastas
trial!
You'll be charged!
That was a waste!
A court battle that has never happened
before is now on the rise!
The shocking verdict will be given!
This program was brought to you by these
sponsors.
I'm crying!