I went to Bakuhari Station.
Where is it?
It's here.
Let's go to Bakuhari Station.
Did you see it?
Everyone, please sit down.
You will definitely get lost.
Thank you for watching.
This is the costume for the first day of
school.
Wow!
What is this?
Oh my god!
Are we going to climb the bridge?
Yes, we are going to climb the bridge.
Wow!
Look at this!
Amazing!
So cute!
I feel like I'm growing up.
The ground is so big.
The stage is so big.
So cute!
It's like a flower road.
It's like a big festival.
I see.
It's like a senior's concert.
Amazing.
Two people.
The stage is so big.
Thank you!
There are so many seats!
Amazing!
Center?
Our concert?
I'm scared.
It's okay.
The camera is still on.
It's cool.
There's a mirror.
I can check my bangs.
You can check it.
I can check it.
It's big.
It's amazing.
I don't know.
I don't know if I can feel it or not.
I feel like it's a strange feeling.
It's not like Anna Live.
Wow.
I want to go inside the hole.
I'm scared.
It's huge.
Thank you for your hard work.
Let's check the location.
The bicycle is under the car, so please
get off the stairs.
Julia, please come here.
The wind is blowing.
I'm coming.
I'm scared.
Not that way sometimes
Please press and hold here
Please subscribe to the channel and give
it a high rating.
I'm rehearsing each and every move
carefully.
I have to be careful not to get caught
in the middle.
Bicycle, bicycle.
I have to be careful not to get caught
in the middle.
I might get caught in the middle.
I'll do my best.
They're adjusting the fish.
Isn't it big?
All of these are in the
I'm surprised that all of these are in
the
I'm riding a bicycle.
I feel different.
I'm going at a different speed.
Center stage.
In front of me.
I'm going to go inside first.
Wow, look at the ceiling.
Is this it?
Oh, it's a stand.
I think so.
Oh, I just saw this.
There's this.
Let's go.
It's amazing.
It's amazing to see it from below.
I want to see it from the outside.
It's amazing.
It's flying away.
It's the same size as the circle, isn't
it?
It's smaller than the circle.
Are you okay?
It's amazing.
It's flying away.
It's flying away from the engine.
It's a little sudden.
I'll turn the engine on.
If you go down, go over there.
Everyone, let's go forward.
Let's go.
It's amazing here.
It's already there.
I'll turn the engine off.
Tanami Julia Toka Aruto
Aki Yori Super Tokimeki Sengenbun
Please subscribe to the channel.
Thank you for watching!
So I'm reallyavorite the father and
mother.
I can't move.
I know.
I knew it.
I can't move.
I didn't feel it.
We can move.
It's like watching the illusion.
I can't move.
It's amazing.
Jumping endurance
Riki has a talking ability
So cute
Smells likeiation
Brushing your teeth
This school has the strategy of mental
fitness
Thank you for watching!
MZ Style
Newborn
57 appreciated
Thank you for watching.
May we take photos?
When was it taken by Green Light?
Scary
I'm scared.
Calm down.
Please take a picture of the sound.
I'll turn it off.
I want to be in the dark, dark, dark
scent with you
Let's go!
Don't get in the way of our own world
I can't stop, I can't stop, I can't stop
I'm so into you, I can't stop
Let's go!
Go! Go! Tomorrow!
Let's go! Tomorrow!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Amazing!
The first time I've seen a big fish!
Hello!
Please come in!
Can I get on?
I'll get on!
I got on!
Amazing!
The first time I've seen a big fish!
I'm a little nervous.
Wow!
I got up a little.
I'm not nervous at all.
I feel safe.
It's fast.
It's surprisingly fast.
And it's very low.
It's a little low.
The truck is like this.
It's so nice.
It's like a two-seater.
It's cute.
It's like my sister's sister.
It's like a two-seater.
It's very nice.
I'm going to take a break now.
I'm going to climb slowly.
It's amazing.
It's not steep at all.
Wow!
Isn't it great?
The person who rides this is absolutely
fun.
This is the first time I've been to an
amusement park.
Wow.
I can really ride while eating.
It's a Yuka.
I want to do it with Rubi.
Thank you.
You can talk to both of them.
Then I will turn around.
Oh, it's working!
Wow!
It's spinning!
The wheel is too hard!
Wow!
It's working!
It's amazing!
It's perfect!
It's so stable!
I can't feel the vibration.
It's amazing!
It's like a real ride!
It's so smooth!
It's amazing!
It's moving backward!
It's so smooth!
It's amazing!
It's our power!
We did it too!
We did the same thing!
Isn't it amazing?
It's like a real ride!
It's amazing!
It's fun!
I want to use it again!
It's amazing!
It's like a real ride!
Oh!
We did it!
It's amazing!
Thank you!
It's fun!
It's amazing!
I want to eat ramen!
Ramen?
Thank you for watching!
It's so cute!
Thank you!
I didn't expect to experience this
before the actual performance.
I hope you enjoyed it!
That's all for today.
Thank you for today!
Let's have fun tomorrow!
Let's have fun!
Thank you!
That was great!
Good job!
We finished the rehearsal!
It's been a long day.
I'm wearing sneakers because the heels
are so high.
I'm so sad that it's over.
I'm so happy.
We'll do our best tomorrow.
We'll do our best.
We finished the rehearsal.
I'm so sad.
I'm so sad that we have to go back to
the rehearsal tomorrow.
We're going to have a great time today.
I'll do my best tomorrow.
I'll do my best!
Bye bye!
The rehearsal is over.
It's over!
We'll do our best tomorrow.
Bye bye!
I wonder why
When I smile, it's like the world is
shining
I can relax by turning the umbrella
Otherwise, I can't walk
Someone is crying somewhere
I'm getting wet again
Isn't it cold?
Someone is crying somewhere
I want to share my feelings with you
I don't know the scenery in front of me
Let's go anywhere
Goodbye, Goodbye, Thank you for
yesterday
The cityscape after the rain is colored
I painted a fragment of the future on
the canvas of my broken heart
Will you guide me?
I can say it now, even the reason for my
tears
When I'm lost, I immediately remember
Even if it rains, I'll smile
Look, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye to me from yesterday
The cityscape after the rain is
sparkling
It's like my heart is a spring
Playing the sound of the rain shower
Playing the rainbow piano
Goodbye, goodbye to me from yesterday
The cityscape after the rain is
sparkling
It's like my heart is a spring
Drying the tears
I'll wear a rainbow dress
LaLaLa...