Do you have any encounters?
No.
You seem to be doing it.
I'm going to take it to the mountain and
go to the lake.
You have to pull out something from the
lake.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to ask Yua from Yume no Yua
today.
I think I'll ask you from the beginning
of POP.
The first POP was at the opening
ceremony, right?
That's right. In May.
June?
I did it in May.
I didn't feel any joy or sadness there.
It's impossible?
But I haven't felt it yet.
I haven't felt the feeling of going to
work from now on.
We didn't dance much.
It was terrible.
I was told that I was dancing a lot now.
I was really living a life that I
couldn't touch dancing.
The unit before Saki-chan stopped
working?
To be continued.
I cried a lot and I remember falling
down.
I only remember that. It was a sauna
suit.
But when the live ended, I was in a
sauna suit and it was too hot.
I fell down as soon as I entered the
dressing room and told the event
producer...
I thought, is it okay? I thought I was
going to die.
I remember that I was just trying to
lose consciousness.
You said you wanted to do your best as a
band, but what did you think when you
were told you would quit?
I was really sad. It was my first
experience, and I had been working with
them for about a year.
신ל grading
Well, I think people who can stop it
will stop.
Well, that's right.
I don't think people who can stop it are
timing.
I don't know.
I think it's because we're doing this
for a long time in the same group as
idols.
I think it's weird, but I think it's
because we're blessed by the
environment.
That's right.
There's power around us, and I think we
have weird things.
Is it weird?
Everyone...
I think we should stop being idols.
We should be doing something for a
certain period of time, and we should be
doing something that we can easily do.
I think we have that image.
I think we have that image in Japan.
We have that image.
We have a lot of choices, but we're not
satisfied with anything yet.
I think I've changed.
It's amazing that people continue to
support me.
I'm grateful for the power and power of
the people around me.
I think it's a miracle that I met the
person I like.
Is there anything you haven't said yet?
I want to say something about the MV of
Pretty Pretty Good.
I was told that I was a great creator.
I'm not good at negotiating.
I'm not saying it's impossible now, but
I'm afraid it's impossible.
There was an incident while I was
moving.
I lost contact.
I was too high up, so I didn't tell
anyone.
I was alone, shaking, and I was scared.
Is it okay to say something like this?
What do you think?
It's impossible.
The story of the surprise is basically
about money or men.
That's why I don't have that story.
Actually, I borrowed 300,000 yen from
Akon.
But we had a hard time with money.
Thank you for watching.
I'll say it if I can say it, but I was
running around three jobs at night.
I had a lot of pay and clothes, so I
couldn't sell yellow T-shirts.
I couldn't sell a single T-shirt a day.
I had a lot of customers.
I worked at night and in the morning.
I was careful from then on.
I worked in the kitchen.
I worked at a clothing store when I was
a student.
Beef and PE class.
I asked them to hire me.
You did it behind the scenes.
I did the hangers.
I asked the staff to arrange the
hangers.
I worked at 6am.
I worked at Komeda too.
What did you do when you were working at
Komeda?
I only talked about NG, but I did
everything in P.E.D.
When I heard this...
I worked at Komeda too.
でもバクロにはなってない。
このインタビューが、今まで世に出てなかった、何かしらバクロとかを出さしてほしいん
だって。
自分のことで言ったら、返答戦取ったとか、入院してた。1週間実は裏で入院してたこと
があったとかはあるね。
毎回。毎回でも何かありそうだから。
私も無理だ。 落としたっていうぐらいだと、がっかりだよね。
落ちたら、おしっこ漏らしたとかだったら、大いずられない。
俺もおしっこ漏らしたんだよね。 わっわっくんだから。
漏らしはしないんだよなぁ。
それカメラの前で絶対毎回やんないっすよ。プロだもん。
カメラ回ってない時の楽屋とかで撮ってる分だったら、P入れていくらでも多分言ってる
ことあると思うけど。
カメラ回ってますって。
When I was a kid, I thought that he had
a long history of speaking, so I thought
about it a lot.
I can't hear you, I pretend to be dumb
and give up
I can't see the future, I can see it, I
pretend to understand