Ebichu's video
Good morning
Today is the birthday
I want to enjoy my day
Good morning
Thank you.
Just a little.
It's a bit.
Yeah.
We practiced yesterday,
because we were singing the song
of OK NO BEMX X.
We practiced.
Soba-san practiced
for about 3 hours in advance.
So it was almost perfect.
We practiced
and we were dancing
together.
We're going to rehearse now.
We're going to do our hair
and the costumes for the first part
and the blusher.
We're going to do our best today.
I'm getting nervous.
We're going to the stage.
Good morning.
I'm Hoshino Mirei, a junior high school
student.
Nice to meet you.
Thank you.
Hello everyone, I'm a woman.
Today is the birthday of Mirei.
I came to the Miripen talk show as a
guest.
I appeared in a video about 2 years ago.
I was invited by a guest.
My relationship with Mirei has deepened
in the past two years.
I will tell you about that in the talk
show.
I would be happy if I could talk about
things that only I know about Mirei.
I'm looking forward to it.
Congratulations Mirei.
After that, we will invite the guest to
the talk show.
This is a card.
I was invited.
I'm a woman.
Thank you for watching.
She seems satisfied.
She was the last one to leave the room
doing shackles.
Alone
Thank you~~
I'm going to sleep.
I'm going to sleep when I'm out.
I finally got a gift.
This is a candy.
I got this ring from SANA yesterday.
I said I'd wear it with you today.
I forgot the person who gave it to me.
Don't tell anyone.
It's a secret.
I have a strong friend.
I'm going to enjoy it.
I'm eating candy because I'm fat.
The costume is cute.
I finally forgot my shoes.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm Mirei.
So, what's today's costume?
Cute!
It's a matching costume.
Mirei is pink, so she wears a pink
dress.
One piece is easy to move.
I'm dancing today.
It's a secret, but I'm dancing.
It's easy to move, but it's cute.
It's like a costume.
We chose it together.
It's cute.
It's a matching hairstyle.
The color of the ribbon is different.
Cute!
I'm happy.
I was relieved.
I'm nervous.
I'm nervous because it's the night
before yesterday.
I'm not sweating.
I'm sweating because it's my birthday.
I'm nervous.
I'm not sweating.
I'm happy.
They have been one of the unique among
shoots
They come to play meeting!
I heard that working together has made
the atmosphere interesting.
Hey Majima!
Thank you.
The pink part is a little...
It's about 1 in 10 of the whole.
It's a long boot.
It's okay if Mayu-san comes.
It looks fun.
Are you going out together?
No, I'm not.
I'm watching it on the top.
Please come again today.
When you're on live, I go to the sauna.
You want to go to the sauna?
I'm going to the sauna.
Thank you.
Please come again.
Okay.
Hello, everyone.
Hello.
I would like to call the audience
Ms.Sora
Hello
I'm the current revolution of the
YouTube world, Soran-man!
Happy Birthday to you, Mirai-chan!
Happy Birthday to you, Jun!
I'm really grateful that everyone who
follows me is here.
Thank you very much for always
supporting me.
I hope to spend more fun year with
everyone.
Please continue to support me.
That's all. Thank you for watching.
I finished the talk show.
I was able to talk with everyone.
Soa-chan also talked a lot of fun.
I'm grateful.
I finished the talk show.
I will do my best in the second part.
I finished the first part of the talk
show.
I changed my clothes in a second.
I changed my clothes.
The guest came.
Soa came to the guest.
It was really fun.
I was glad.
Thank you.
I made a good memory.
It's the best memory.
I was relieved that everyone laughed a
lot.
I was able to laugh a lot.
Thank you.
Please continue to support us.
I will do my best.
Hello, I'm a famous person in the
Christmas festival.
Good evening. Good morning.
I'm here at Miele's Christmas festival.
I wore a hat called a ghost and a
T-shirt for this live show.
I'm the most famous person in Miele.
I came here.
Please wait for me.
Thank you for watching!
I'm the most fan of Miren.
Miren is always by your side.
Where are we?
We are Miren.
The first song is Miren.
Miren fight!
Let's go.
Everyone!
Please bow.
Where are we?
Pink Dora House.
We are Miren.
The first song is Miren.
Miren fight!
Thank you.
I'm so nervous.
Help me.
The other bed is big.
Let's do something wrong with the
prediction of the future disappearing
Paradox Paradox Come Come Come Paradox
Paradox Paradox Come Come Come
I have a lot of opportunities to receive
the words that the fans who love me are
really passionate about me.
That's really connected to me now.
Thank you for always supporting me.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you to you
I'm done with the birthday party!
I'm done with everything, so I'm going
home now.
I'm so excited and my hair is still
shiny.
I was in the showroom, but I didn't get
a good video.
I'm a little sad.
I'm really happy today.
Thank you, everyone.
I'll keep doing the birthday party until
I get home.
Thank you, everyone.
I'm 24-year-old Hoshino Mirai.