Someone is copying down on my bad
personality?
Thank you for watching!
I have zero.
Oh my god!
Next, Yuu?
I want to hear information that I've
never told you before.
Money or love.
It's hard.
I'm almost the same age as you.
You're annoying.
The story of the Aya Gyampare era is the
main story.
It was the story of Yuu's visit to
Wakode.
It was announced in Akarenger.
What happened?
Let's go home!
There is no one in the gang parade.
But, Miss Aya 8 PRINCE,
Aya 8 PRINCE, Kamiya Saki,
They will do a rental trade.
Aya 8 PRINCE will go to the gang parade.
Kamiya Saki will go to the gang parade.
It was the first time we did it at WAKO.
We were on the way, and then the trade
was announced.
I was worried, wondering what I had
done.
We panicked for the first time.
What does trade mean?
There was no precedent.
It's a motive.
I'm a bit disappointed because I'm a bit
out of business.
When we weren't active,
we were about to release our album.
I was so upset that I could cry while I
was changing.
I don't know how to deal with people who
are active with groups.
It's been about a year.
I thought it was about half a year,
but it's been about a year since the
trade began.
I have memories of that time.
I have a lot of memories of the night.
I can say it now.
I was tall, so I was tall until Aya came
in.
When Aya came in, it was like a twin
tower.
I was often disturbed.
I remember receiving customers from Aya.
Everyone pulls a group.
It feels like we're all making it
together.
That's where the group came from.
We had a lot of fights.
We had a fight.
What did you fight about?
What kind of fight?
We had a fight at the angle of the
chorus of the song.
How many degrees?
We have different heights and different
arms.
So how many degrees is different?
We had a fight a lot.
We were so particular about it.
We were.
We received it from Saki-chan.
We had a strong desire to show the
colors of the gang parade.
We had to make every detail of the
choreography.
We had a lot of things to say to each
other.
At that time, we were doing a lot of
things, but we were thinking that we
would do it again in the future.
Do you really go back to the business?
Which one are you?
Are you okay with that?
What is the answer?
I tried a little bit.
Actually, this interview was just right.
I was wondering if I could tell you the
secrets and the back-ups that I had
never told you before.
Just a little bit.
Really? I didn't know. So we're going to
do it again?
I'm scared!
I interviewed a really good girl
earlier.
You did.
You did a back-up.
So you lost.
Yes, I lost. So I was told that I had
zero hands.
Earlier.
Is it okay to have a camera?
So, based on that.
Based on that.
Can I ask you one thing?
I can't laugh.
I can't laugh?
Actually, the hamster died.
I can't laugh.
When?
At the end of August.
I only did it to Canon.
Junior.
I can't laugh.