Thank you for watching.
Good morning.
I arrived Yokohama, Tokyo.
I was supposed to leave after the show,
but I'm going to leave after I shout out
loud.
So I'll do my best to shout out loud.
I'll do my best.
I'm at the FITO Pro Fest.
I'll be on stage soon, so I'll hurry up.
Please subscribe to my channel!
I'll do my best to get the most points.
I'm going to do my best.
I'm at Yokohama Arena in Staplefest.
This time, the group of Cinderella will
be decided.
We will compete in a group.
Until last year, we fought individually.
I feel like I can hope for a new
feeling.
Staplefest is a cute idol group.
I'm doing my best with a lot of people.
I will do my best to be cute and fun.
I'm about to start.
I'm done with my make-up.
I can't draw well.
My make-up is broken.
I hid the under of my eyes with a
concealer.
I'll add eye shadow from now on.
My tear bags will change.
I'll do my best to make up.
I'll do my best for today's performance.
Thank you.
I got my make-up fixed.
I'll be on the stage in a few minutes.
I'll get ready for it.
I'm glad that everyone said,
thank you for your hard work.
I'll do my best for the performance.
See you later.
I'm in a hurry to go to the Stapler
Festival. I came back from Shizuoka.
I arrived and changed my clothes. I'm
ready to go on the stage anytime.
It's an original dance. You don't know
what I'm going to do, do you?
I'm shooting a video for the time when I
didn't make it in time. I want you to
play it.
I have to perform in front of you
because I'm already on the scene.
I'll do my best. First of all, I'll do
my best. I'll do my best to do a special
stage.
I'll do my best to be a Cinderella. I'll
do my best to be a star.
I think it's going to be good today.
I'll do my best because I still have two
more stages.
I'm going to watch the live show.
I can't go to the live show of the same
staff idol.
Today is a chance.
I'm enjoying it as an idol and as a
guest.
I'm going to do my best.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'll do my best!
I'm going to sing a little more, but
I've been singing live before.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay!
It's a perfect match.
We made it.
It's like a perfect match.
It smells good.
Really?
She said it smells good.
My goal this year is to be a good girl.
I want to be a good girl.
I'm going to do my best.
Thank you for watching. Please subscribe
to my channel.
I'm nervous.
My goal is 107.
107?
Wow.
Bye-bye.
I was close to the bell.
Asahi, right?
How many times have we been here?
This is the fourth?
No, it's the fifth.
We are back!
It's cute.
The letters are cute.
I like it.
I'm into this these days.
I'm into the season.
Let's go.
Kisa-chan.
Kisa-chan, your voice is loud.
My voice is loud.
It's OK.
There is art.
I don't know what Kanamin drew.
Kanamin drew one picture before spring.
Oh, really?
Then, it's here.
Yes.
I drew this.
What is this?
BLREAKING OUT
There's a huge stage!
Okay!
Coming up next
Next year
Thinking of next year
It's hard to imagine
But what is developed
Subaru All-Stars!
From here, the super special team has
returned in time.
Thank you for waiting.
Sakurai, are you confident in your
voice?
I think it's the biggest of the special
teams, but I'll do my best.
Please shout your wish.
Ah!
How was it?
Let's see.
I think it's too different.
Let's check the points.
Did you eat something?
Shoes.
Ah!
But it was 109 decibels.
Thank you.
I think there was no sound of the floor.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
You can ride a bicycle, right?
I'm sorry.
Good luck! Harina!
It's so difficult!
I thought I would have a louder voice.
But when we rehearsed, everyone was so
quiet.
Yeah, everyone was like that.
We weren't serious.
You were nervous?
Yeah, definitely.
That's frustrating.
Definitely.
Where's the dressing room?
We're here.
I was sad.
I'm so sad.
I was so sad.
The penlight was so red. Did you see it?
It was so red.
We were so happy.
This is the camera.
You all look so cool.
You look so cute.
I used Kanamin's costume as a reference
for my birthday costume.
I love your birthday costume.
I'm so happy.
Next, Fujino, you are wearing a
beautiful leather jacket.
It's beautiful.
I used the Earth symbol of the planet,
Star.
The letters on the outside are also
designed.
It's amazing.
I finished it.
Everyone's drawings have various
characteristics.
I lost a little, but I did my best.
Please take a look at it.
I'll do my best for my live performance.
Please subscribe to my channel!
Thank you for watching!
Moon, fight me!
Please tap my back.
Thank you.
Go for it!
I got a hint.
Hiori's strategy this time.
I can't win even if I do it normally.
I came to see Piyo's.
It's embarrassing.
The manager thought that I should
combine the idols I have with the idols
I have.
I want to use various things in the
future.
I have quite a lot.
Just luck
Well this is a pillar of good luck...
Actually, the first time I took a photo
with Hiorin was in 2019.
I think it was the time when we just
started.
It was 100 years ago.
Let's take a photo today.
Let's take a photo later.
From now on, we will do our best with
our originality.
We are serious about it.
I feel like I'm having fun.
Getters is the judge.
No, it's not.
Wait, Getters is the leader.
Lucky, lucky.
I'm a pro.
I'm sorry, Lucky.
Can I use that?
Stop it.
Getters is the judge.
Getters is the leader.
I've been doing it for 7 years.
Lucky is the judge.
I see.
I have different personalities.
I'm cool, cute, funny, and sexy.
You are sexy.
I'm not going to be sexy today.
Don't wear it.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Super exciting promotional event
Yoshikawa Himi-san!
Go for it.
3, 2, 1
Please subscribe to the channel.
Amazing!
Her face!
That was fantastic. It felt like you had
a lot of information in 20 seconds.
GYAAAHHHHHHHHHH
I'm not done yet!
She's moving so much!
She's not done yet!
She's a genius!
She's like...
This is unacceptable!
Very intense ends
Wimpering
The last scene was really interesting
for us.
It was best because The last part was
sparkling!
How was it?
I don't remember much.
For now, for now.
Really?
I did ad-lib just now.
I did it like a DOS voice.
I got a request from everyone.
I hope I can make the venue more
exciting with all my might.
I have no regrets.
Everyone was amazing.
Everyone did their best, but Hiyori did
it like a DOS voice.
Everyone is amazing. Everyone has a high
level.
Everyone has their own cool and sexy
side.
It was great.
Momokuro's live is just starting.
After that, it's our turn.
This is the first time I'm on stage.
It was my first time.
Well, well, well.
I wonder if I can win the special round.
I don't feel like I can ride the
Cinderella.
I'm not giving up yet.
Everyone, help me.
I'm going to ask the members for help.
I'm going.
Thank you for watching!
I can do it!
I can prove it!
Thank you for watching!
Sexy habtum
You haven't broken Kamoã¨Louie's spider
webs yet!
Three of them fast forward until she
reaches them.
Yamagami convincing her of what she has
to do and managing the behind the
scenes...
4 minutes ago
We might not get there
But it was really close
This was very closeanta Kana has the
points
It was so close
I'm doing well this week.
This is my fault.
I'm not allowed to say 10 seconds.
It's my turn to do my best.
I'll do my best with all my heart.
I'm the last one.
I'll do my best to make the rest of the
members happy.
I'm the last one.
You're cute.
Everyone is excited.
I'm the last one.
I'll do my best.
Please come out next week.
First, Angelia.
I'll give you a challenge.
I'll give you a voice.
Please continue after that.
Please look forward to the next video.
Hi-yaaa!!
Unfortunately, we have to move on.
Please sit down and gather in the
center.
Please go to the center.
Now, let's continue.
Oh, it's Chie-chan.
Give me a candy.
Oh, Chie-chan is the first one.
Oh, it's An-chan.
Go!
Oh!
Chiria-chan! Chiria-chan!
Chiria-chan!
I've been practicing a lot!
I've been practicing a lot! Chiria-chan!
Really?
I shouldn't laugh, but it's funny.
I guess she is nervous.
She was nervous in the rehearsal, but
she is relaxed now.
Chiria-chan!
Are you nervous?
Is it because of the monitor?
Chiria-chan!
Wow!
She is really good!
Hana-chan!
Wow!
Is it cool?
Toki-san has no points now.
Toki-san has no points. She has two
points left.
I'll do my best!
I've been injured a lot.
There's only one left.
But there are some left.
How about that?
Now, everyone, please open the boxes at
once.
If you find something, please raise your
hand.
Now, please open the boxes.
Oh, my!
I love you, Oniichan!
Thank you!
I'm not going to be Cinderella yet, so
I'll show you something good at the
live.
Rock on!
Let's have fun!
Rock, paper, scissors!
It's a luck.
But, you can win in the short-distance
race.
What will happen?
Let's give a big hand to the winner,
Mako Akimoto!
Thank you!
That was the 16th day of the 16th
challenge.
Now, there are two more places to leave
the live.
The next live is this group!
Rock, paper, scissors!
I'll start the VTR.
I'm not nervous at all!
I'm nervous!
Hello, everyone!
We are HITO!
Thank you for watching!
tell me!
You'll be killed.
NANJYANUNA
Fantedusing, blossoming
I won't stop, cry cry, I even nod my
head
Let's go higher!
Each and everyone is desperate!
Growing bitter bitter bitter bitter!
I'm strong!
Tell the truth
Echi Wo F Koreanu
I want to be by your side
Look at me, I'm super cute
Don't take your eyes off me
Who's the cutest?
Of course it's me, I'm the boss
From today, I'll be more honest
Tell me your love
I'll get your heart
Don't leave me alone
I love you, I'm super cute
I might be a little bit nervous
But I love you, I'm so proud of you
I'm the strongest among all the girls
So I say hello to myself
I don't care what people say
I'll be the best in the world
I'm the strongest among all the girls
So I say hello to the infinite
possibilities
I'll challenge myself to do what I want
to do
And prove my future to you
I'll be a new generation
Thank you very much.
This was Panamin!
This was Julia!
This was Hitoka!
This was Iharu!
This was Aiki!
This was Kiyomin!
We will be performing at Yokohama Arena
next year.
If you are interested, please come and
see us!
Let's go! Tokisei Yokoi!
Bye!
Rock on to your heart!
This has been Super Doki Doki
Advertisement!
Thank you very much!
It was fun!
Thank you!
It was so hot!
It's so big here.
Thank you!
It was fun!
I'm exhausted.
It was hot.
It was fun.
Do your best, Gash!
I'll do my best!
I was too excited.
I can't look back at today's live.
I thought I would be the only one next
year.
But I was surprised.
It's been two days.
I can see the view for two days.
I want to see it in full screen.
Let's go!
I'm exhausted.
It was fun.
I like this big venue.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Thank you for your viewing.
I'm going to make a video.
I was going to die until I freeze.
I told you.
I'm going to die.
Who is going to run?
Hitochan is going to run.
You can wait here.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for watching my video.
I'm nervous. I'm not good at this. I'm
not good at this kind of competition.
I'm good at relay. I do it with
everyone.
I'm not good at the sound of the bell.
I'm running, but I'm running at 0
points. I can't get 3 points.
How many points do you have now?
I'm running at 0 points.
Did you practice running?
I didn't practice running.
I think I'm the fastest among the
members.
I'm not fast.
Why are you here?
I'm in trouble.
I'm hungry.
I want to take a picture.
I feel like I'm going to get a skirt.
It's heavy.
It's in the way.
I'm in trouble.
I have the last event left.
I'm running at 0 points.
I'll cheer for you!
It's OK.
You are cute.
I'm going to do my best.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you very much.
I want to go there.
Thank you for watching. Please subscribe
to my channel.
Start!
I hurt my hand.
Go home!
I'm nervous.
3 points.
We have 0 points now.
We have 0 points too.
We have the same points.
We just had a live performance.
I'm tired.
If we can't do it, we'll appeal.
It's okay. Let's do our best.
What? What?
We'll do our best.
It was so funny.
We had a tripod.
We were all like this.
We were laughing so hard.
It was so funny.
We were so happy, but we couldn't get
the first place.
I'm nervous.
This is the best.
Please subscribe to my channel.
My heart rate is already going up.
I'm going to go.
Thank you very much.
Kino-Kan, good luck!
I'm the first one.
You are the first one.
Oh, you are not the first one.
I'm going to go.
So fast!
Oh my god!
Why!?
MMD-san is escaping
15.02 seconds
It was so good.
But it's not enough.
I think we should give up.
We should do our best.
46.5 points.
If we keep doing this,
if we keep doing this,
we'll get 3 points.
So we'll get 0 points.
Oh, no.
I'm dead.
It's so exciting.
I want to see it.
Rock-paper-scissors.
We couldn't do it.
We ran for a long time.
We should have practiced.
I will do my best for the last!
Please subscribe to our channel and
follow us on Twitter!
So, rock on to your heart!
This has been Super Exciting Seneb!
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much.
They're not over yet!?
I got it.
I don't like it.
Why do they all like it?
It's a small place.
It's amazing.
It's over.
It's fast.
The day is over.
But there are many here.
I got on the train.
I did it.
Don't forget to subscribe
Please subscribe to my channel!
I can hear you.
I didn't do anything.
We had Paschin and Paschin!
I did it!
I told you!
I have muscle pain.
I have muscle pain on my hips and here.
I'm young.
Riko smells good.
There are two people who like sweet
potatoes.
Sweet potatoes?
I'm not interested in sweet potatoes.
Thank you for watching this video.
Please subscribe to this channel.
What do you recommend?
Cute!
There are many sweet potatoes in Tokyo.
I'm jealous.
I go to the sweet potato festival 4
times.
I want to see the drawing.
It was cute.
Did you draw it by hand?
Yes.
It was cute.
I want you to make shoes for me.
I want to make shoes for you.
It's cute when we meet.
Really?
I want to eat it.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
I didn't know that I like such a cute
girl.
Cute.
I was next to her when she was dancing.
But I didn't know she was like this.
It's strange.
I didn't know she was like this.
It was cute.
She was like a cheerleader.
I was embarrassed.
I was blushing.
Thank you for watching this video.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Good job!
Can I take a picture with you?
I'm so happy!
I was so surprised.
I was surprised, too.
I was surprised.
Thank you for watching this video.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
You're the best.
Thank you.
Take a lot of rest.
It was early in the morning.
I'm sorry.
I heard that.
It was around 8 in the morning.
Everyone was good.
Thank you for your hard work.
Weki Meki was cute.
You were cute.
Did you see it?
I saw it.
I saw the triangle.
I like it.
Cute.
It's fashionable.
Everyone looks like a princess.
Everyone is fashionable.
I was pushed.
It's good.
In the middle.
Let's go.
Thank you!
Please take a picture of us!
I want to be surrounded by you!
Thank you!
I see.
Cheese!
Cute!
Let's have everyone do this.
This is a popular heart this year.
Let's change it to a super cute one.
Please.
Super cute!
It's so cute!
If Momokuro-san is here, I'll do it.
We added a new heart to our song.
Oh, this is it.
I see.
You're our rival.
It's cute.
I think it's going to be popular.
I'll take your advice.
I'm glad you said yes.
Thank you.
Thank you for singing for us.
I won't change.
No!
Thank you.
So, we've finished the Stappler
Festival.
Was it fun?
It was fun.
It was different from usual.
It was different.
It was like a group battle.
We had individual corners.
We did our best.
It was fun.
But, unfortunately,
the point was...
It was a tie.
But, we won. It was good.
There were many young actresses in the
audience.
I was so happy.
When we were on stage,
the fans drew us in red.
I think the young actresses drew us.
I was happy.
Thank you.
We will be back here again next year in
January.
We will be back as a solo artist.
It's not big.
It's too big.
I thought we were only doing a
commercial.
I thought we were doing a live show.
I thought we were doing a one-man show.
I thought it would be fun if we could do
it.
I think this time was a very motivated
live show.
There are still a lot of things to do
until next year.
I will do my best for a year.
It's the last year.
I will do my best.
Thank you.
Congratulations on your third year
anniversary.
Please subscribe to my channel!
Translated by Vortex
Thank you for watching!
I don't know if it's because I'm a
little bit of a pervert, but I feel like
I'm getting into the mood of the song.
I don't know if it's because I'm a
little bit of a pervert, but I feel like
I'm getting into the mood of the song.
I don't know if it's because I'm a
little bit of a pervert, but I feel like
I'm getting into the mood of the song.
Please subscribe to my channel!
Translated by Releska