Ebichu's video
Yasumoto Yaka's first photo book
The reason I made this photo book is
I made it myself
I told my sister and my principal
It's a great opportunity, so please let
me make a photo book
I asked my sister for a photo book
And I made it
I've always wanted to leave a form of
gratitude to my fans
I've always had a voice saying that I'm
waiting for a photo book or a photo book
I've always wanted to make something
like that
I wanted to make it to thank my fans
That's what I talked about
When I actually made it
I told my sister that I could do
everything I wanted
And I became a voice producer
It was my first time
I've thought about it in my childhood
But it was my first time to make a big
form
I was wondering what to make
When I thought about what I thought was
the simplest
I thought it was fun
And I was confident that I was able to
come back to the stage
I was able to love myself
I thought it would be nice to convey
that through photos
I thought about various concepts and
made it
This black dress photo
The most I wanted to do in this photo
book was this black dress
When I lost my hair during the time I
was sick
The person who gave me courage was the
person who shaved her hair and became a
boy.
The person who wore a red carpet and
walked in a dress was a foreign actress
or model.
I got a lot of courage.
Hair is very important for girls.
Even if I didn't have that, the person
who shined from the bottom of my heart
was a person who lost her hair and lost
her confidence.
I was able to be cool and connect with
myself.
I think that even small things are
complex and there are many things that
make you feel anxious.
I wanted to make a photo that could give
me a little courage at such a time.
I said that I definitely wanted to do
this dress.
This is the most important photo I took.
When I was fitting the dress, I was
already ready.
Everyone thought that I could take a
good photo.
The moment I entered the shooting site,
I was able to take a good picture.
There may not be many photos with a lot
of cuts, but I was able to take a lot of
photos.
I was very worried about choosing.
This is a room cut.
I'm a very natural figure. I'm happy to
say that it's fun.
This time, I'm taking a picture, so I've
never done it before. I've seen my legs
and I've been a little nervous.
It's a challenging costume for me.
But I'm still a natural figure.
I was able to capture my own expressions
in this scene, so please look forward to
it.
The other cut is also very cute, so
please look forward to it.
The location was taken in the
Yatsugatake Resort in Hoshinoya, and it
was taken in the room there.
It was a very cute room.
There are many cuts in the photo book,
so please look forward to it.
Next is this photo.
There was a photo of me smiling because
I was bored, but it was taken in my own
room at my parents' house.
It was my first time taking a photo at
my parents' house, but I was able to
remember myself when I was in the
hospital.
I wanted to express how I became a
bright person from that time.
I was able to capture a lot of photos in
the long interview, such as the past and
the future, and I was able to capture a
lot of photos that connected to that.
This is also a special cut, so please
pay attention to it.
This is a photo of my room.
I don't know what kind of house this
photo is yet, but I have a lot of
memories in the photo book.
I'm taking a picture of the background
in the back, so please look forward to
it.
This is a photo of me in the pool in the
photo book. I'm wearing a dress and
going to the pool.
I don't think there are any cuts like
this. I think it's a cut that I can see
a little more mature.
I'm really a bright person.
I think that I'm a person who looks good
in white clothes.
I think that my pure feelings are
contained in this white dress.
I think that I can express myself as an
adult who is heading for the future.
I used a lot of water.
I was in a state where I couldn't tell
who was throwing water into my ears.
This part is also really cute.
I've never seen it before.
When I was selecting the page, I said
that this is a good place to be with the
staff.
I want you to see it soon.
The title of this photo book is AYA.
I'll take my name and be AYA.
The theme of this photo book is that I
am who I am.
I wanted to express my real, straight
figure.
I also want to take a lot of pictures
that I can imagine.
I think that's the meaning of this
title.
I took a picture of what I was actually
drawing in my head.
I'm not sure if I'm doing it right now,
but I was very happy when I was
selecting the photo.
Anyway, it was a lot of fun when I was
shooting.
I was very excited when I thought that I
could deliver this to my fans.
I'm really excited to see what kind of
reaction you guys will make.
I'm surprised that I was able to make a
work that I was satisfied with.
I'm so happy.
I'm so glad that I said I wanted to
release a photo album.
It's not over yet, but I'm so glad I
said it.
I think it's a good thing to think at
this stage.
My first photo album, AYA, will be
released on October 29th.
I'm really, really confident about it.
I hope you all can get it.
Please look forward to it.