This week's Ebichu Tastas is a temporary
meeting of Ebichu Tastas, which
continued last week
The members who came in uniform wanted
to do it in a temporary meeting
The big fuss at Takopade
Ebichu makes takoyaki
Inago-san came out
Furthermore, if you are looking forward
to the day off
Girls' talk in pajamas
The theme is
I'm going to make love flowers
That's good
Finally forbidden love flowers are in
full bloom
Ebichu Tastas start
In the next video
React
I will give 4-stick ebisu kid's class a
lot of stuff
when it mattered
nousnold.
Yeah!
Let's start the takoyaki party!
The takoyaki party starts with the two
teams!
The ingredients are what everyone wants
to put in the takoyaki party.
This is the team that took the leader's
name.
Takoyaki-like kimchi and cheese.
And the luxury ingredients like caviar
and other ingredients.
On the other hand, the team that has too
many members.
Team Ai Hikari.
The Inago, who likes Hirota, is the
next.
The line-up is full of anxiety.
Let's start the takoyaki party!
Team Ai Hikari starts cooking with the
enemy.
Team Ririaho.
Let's eat strawberries.
It sounds good.
First, Hoshino is out.
I'm eating strawberries.
I like to eat strawberries.
Make sure to make takoyaki.
I'm eating strawberries.
You can do whatever you want.
I want to eat caviar.
You can put more caviar.
It's the first time for Yasumoto to eat
caviar.
Riria-chan is eating first.
It's spicy.
It's delicious.
If you eat it now, it will be gone.
Yasumoto, put the egg on top.
You are a fool.
Finally, Ririaho team started cooking.
And then...
Is it calm over there?
It's a very spicy sauce.
What is the spicy sauce mixed with?
Mayonnaise.
Try it.
It's okay.
I'm cheating with mayonnaise.
It's Chinese sauce.
It's not the meaning of Chinese sauce.
It's spicy.
Here, Hirota is acting.
I'm eating caviar.
She is eating like a snack.
It's delicious.
Please watch again.
Both teams have completed their original
takoyaki
Then, 10 dishes from the Aihikari team
Let's eat
Spicy sauce takoyaki
They started eating
They are fast
We were playing at first
How is it, Hiroto?
This is more delicious
How is the baking process?
It's the best
The best?
Kobayashi
How is Kobayashi?
It's hot
You have a great face
It's delicious
It looks delicious
This is also beautiful
Nakayama
Inago-san came out
How is the taste?
It's hard
It doesn't match
Then, the Giriyaho team has 10 dishes
I'm going to eat
Thank you for the food
It's delicious
What is the ingredient?
It's not out yet
And, Mayama?
Strawberry chocolate
How is the strawberry chocolate?
It's delicious
Do it with your finger
Oh, sandwich
I can't say which one
Then, Hoshina ate takoyaki with caviar
I think I'll put caviar on this
It's luxurious
Caviar on caviar
The super high-class takoyaki is
completed
How is the taste?
This is gyoza
Caviar
Put caviar on takoyaki
It's delicious
How is it?
Do you want to eat?
It's the same
I don't know the taste
Do you want to eat?
I don't know
You should eat caviar
Wait, Yasumoto
You turned it too much
I put my head on it
You're a fool
As expected of the fool team
We've had takoyaki party
How was it?
There were strawberries and chocolate
It was a new discovery
The strawberry and chocolate takoyaki
were delicious
Kobayashi?
I turned it over for the first time
So I want to turn it over again
Please do your best
Next is...
This one!
So we're staying here tonight?
Yes, that's right.
It's rare to sleep in a room with 8
people, right?
Yes!
Don't you want to play with toys?
Come on in!
Then...
Let's start with the pillow game!
Let's go!
After this, they'll be in pajamas before
going to bed.
Of course, they'll be in Taiwan.
I'm going to do a love story.
That's great!
The talk is going to explode!
And...
Sakuranin 5!
The first live performance of Sakuranin
5 is finally happening!
Will it be...
The members in the shrimp suit are in
pajamas, and the girls talk on the
futon.
What will happen?
Meanwhile, these three are just adults.
Or rather, they're really drinking
during the recording.
So, the girls talk begins!
Should we talk seriously or talk in a
cute way?
There are two ways to talk.
The first is to talk seriously.
There are many parties when we're alone.
The second is to talk in a cute way.
Then, shall we talk seriously?
Let's talk in a cute way.
In a cute way?
Not that way.
Let's talk in a cute way.
I'll do it in a cute way.
The girls are talking seriously.
Yasumoto is getting angry.
Meanwhile...
Kaiki, please make me a miso soup.
Kaiki, how old were you?
I was 35.
We moved to the same place.
You moved to the same place in 1957?
I was born in 1980.
Can I make you two sake?
Of course, I'll make it.
I want to live in this industry.
How long have you been working here?
It's been about 6 years.
So, you still have a band.
I have a band.
I disbanded the band and became a
singer.
Can I make it?
I'll make it with tea.
Thank you.
Meanwhile, what kind of topic are the
members talking about?
Let's talk after the fun is over
That's the most exciting thing recently
I'm in front of you, so I'll do this
If you can see it in front of you, laugh
Isn't it too early to laugh?
I'm the happiest person in the world
Explain the handsome Shiritori
The original game in which the members
become handsome and do Shiritori with
the lines that the handsome man will say
Then, Mayama Rika's Rikaara Shiritori
Start
I'm ready
I think I should request
What is it?
I won't say it
From you
Kiss me
Mayama says
What is it?
What?
Where do you want to go on your next
date?
I love this
There is a mouse next to you
Here comes the mouse
The lips of the rooster
I feel like I'm going to get a little
bit of a break
I'm going to get a break
It's cool
It's really beautiful
Is it open at 4 o'clock?
What is it? Is it exciting?
It's exciting from the beginning
Is this a girl's talk?
I think this is the tone of the girl's
talk
This is the talk of the girl when she
was in the room of a boy during her
middle school trip
Back then, people asked who you think is
the cutest in your class
Yeah, that's true
Who is your favorite?
I wonder if they are talking about that
now
I wonder if they are playing with the
pillow
Or maybe they are talking about girls
They are so shy
What will the members do?
Don't just look at the side, look at me
I was chosen as the bride
I will stay by your side until then
I'm your fan
I'm your rival
I like you, but I like me
Riko-chan is making a really bad face
It's not luck
It's Hinata-chan
Who?
I will always be in the alley
You are like a ghost
I'm not going to stop talking about
ghosts
Let's just talk
Now it's time for the girls talk
What is the theme?
I'm going to talk about love
That's nice
Who do you think will get married?
I'm decided
I'm Mirei-chan
It looks like a hassle
Why?
I'm going to open it with my hands
There are so many things in the house
It's not a girl's symbol
It's different from me
The other person is a girl
If I get married as a boy
Which one?
Both
If I get married as a boy, it's Aika
If I get married as a boy
No, Aika is a boy
I see
Who do you want to marry?
If I were a man...
Rina?
That's a big deal.
Bigger!
I like eating.
You like eating.
I always eat good food.
I think we can go to a fancy cafe.
I'm nervous because I'm a smart-skater.
Oh, no!
Next, Hirota.
If I were a man...
I'm worried.
Why?
Rina?
Rina is a good woman?
I like the appearance of a woman wearing
a big thing.
I like eating a big melon bread and a
cup of coffee.
I like eating.
I want to see that kind of situation.
I want to take her to a good place.
That's cute.
Who do you want to marry?
This is amazing.
If I were a woman, who would I be with?
I'm with Aiai.
Let's get married.
Yay!
Why?
Because we have the same taste.
I think taste is important.
If I were a woman and I were a man, I
would be with Aiai.
I think I'm with Riko if I were a woman.
I need time alone.
If I were a man, I would be with Aiai.
You're good at this.
I like women.
I'm good at this.
If I were a woman, I would be with Aiai.
I like a refreshing and kind person.
You're funny.
What about you, Kou?
I don't care about the atmosphere.
If I were a woman, I would be with Aiai.
I'm safe.
Safe.
I'm sorry.
I'm sure someone is alone.
If I were a man, I would be with Aiai.
I want to marry her.
Cool.
I don't think I can do it.
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know.
What if it's a girl?
If it's a girl, it's a married person.
That's Aika.
No, I can't do it anymore.
I don't know.
Please put it in the middle.
If it's Aika, it's a girl.
We have to do our best.
Girls talk that seems to continue until
the morning.
But it's about time.
So the three of them go to the shrimp.
If you think about marriage, it will be
this way.
Safety first.
I want to be a good friend.
That's good.
I want to be friends with everyone.
Friends.
How long are you going to stay up?
Good night. Bye.
It's time to sleep.
Light up the light.
I'll turn off the light.
I'll turn it off.
I'm really going to sleep.
I'm really happy.
I smell alcohol.
Turn off the light.
Good night.
It's noisy.
It's a good night for everyone.
It's cute.
So, what if you add a room change to the
shrimp?
If you were a woman, who would you be?
I'm Aiai.
Let's get married here.
Yay.
A couple who recognized the members was
born.
Sakurai Bees first live special.
Sakurai Bees, who finally started, will
appear at the world's largest idol
festival, Tokyo Idol Festival.
Sakurai Bees, who visited the last
senior's live show and got excited.
And finally, the day of the live show.
This year, 154 groups and 1140 famous
idols will appear in two days.
Over 50,000 people will come.
Sakurai Bees, who are in good shape, are
excited.
First of all, I want to enjoy it.
I want to do my best to practice until
now.
A lot of fans are watching the live
show.
And finally, they are standing by
The members are desperately trying to
overcome the tension
And the youngest member, Sakura, is not
able to stand it
Furthermore
The members are trying to overcome the
tension
It's scary to fail
The moment of their debut, everyone is
going through
They will blow away all the worries with
the help of the five members
Sakura, Sakura, MNT, fighting!
We are going to be the first stage today
Please watch over us, and listen to us
The members are trying to overcome the
tension
And the youngest member, Sakura, MNT,
fighting!
The moment of their debut, everyone is
going through
They will blow away all the worries with
the help of the five members
Sakura, Sakura, MNT, fighting!
The first stage is completed
Members who are not excited after the
first stage
However
What happened?
I made a mistake?
She couldn't stop crying because she was
frustrated that she made a mistake in
the starting position
Was it fun?
I want to do my best and make sure I
don't make any mistakes
The second live performance will be held
on the roof stage.
They want to show a better performance
than before.
The second live performance will be held
on the roof stage.
On this stage, they will perform a song
that no one expected!
And they will perform a song that no one
expected!
5 people who ran with all their might
It's like a dream
Today, it's like...
Murahoshi was also crying with this
expression.
It was fun!
A message from Sakura Ebi's.
We will continue to grow.
Please support us!
In the program, we will continue to
watch their activities.
Next time, we will show you the special
episode, the family end special!
So let's go to the family end today!
OK!
Another family end with three men!
Please look forward to it!
This program was provided by the sponsor
you see.