We are the new cast of the morning show,
Ebi-Chu!
We are the new show, Ebi-Chu!
Ebi-Chu, help us!
Today, I, Ayaka Yasumoto, will be the MC
as the host.
This is the first time.
Yasumoto-san, what kind of program is
this?
Ebi-Chu plus something equals something.
You're being very rough.
This program is an experiment variety
show where idols collaborate with
various things to create a variety of
science reactions.
The first time to add the shrimp paste
is to add the switch
When you add the switch, the chemical
reaction is like this
Add shrimp paste, start
It's warm
Please be quiet
After all, a man will never be choose by
an adult.
Y przek 서러울 수 Brother
In addition, let's look Who is waiting
your hint
answer
The game is called Ebitu Tastas, which
is a game where you add something to the
members of your private Ebisu junior
high school.
The idols will collaborate with various
things, and as a result, they will have
a variety of experiments that will enjoy
the reaction of science.
You add something every time, right?
Yes, you add something and something.
After that, you have to watch it until
the end.
I don't understand.
Anyway, I want to do my best with all
eight of us.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
It's still not a good start.
It's been a while.
Hello, we are the shooting star,
Takiguchi and...
Chuu Ames!
Pagan, Pagan, Pagan, Pagan!
Chuu Aiden!
As a support member, Chuu Aiden will add
a shooting star to his debut.
I was wondering, what's up with the
Kashiwagi?
There's one.
There is.
That's strange.
It's stable.
There's a face.
How are you doing today?
I'm fine.
Who's that?
Long time no see.
Was the guest earlier interesting?
It was really interesting.
It was really fun.
It's like we're going back to Kobayashi.
This day is a day off for Kashiwagi
Hinata because of the shooting.
The End
What will you add to today's Ebitu?
I want to add a jacket
What about Kobayashi?
What do you want to do?
It's not a game to play now
Let's do it
Let's start with rock-paper-scissors
Rock-paper-scissors
Wait a minute
Come back
So, it's time to announce the theme
What are you going to add?
I'm going to add a switch
A switch?
You're going to add a switch to your
finger?
I don't know what it means
This is the first time, so I'm going to
turn on everyone's motivation switch
I see
I'm going to add a switch
Nakayama, you can't run away
Nakayama, please press this switch and
turn on everyone's motivation
If you press this, everyone will turn
on, right?
Really?
Yes
Please press this switch and turn on
everyone's motivation switch
It's a 30 minute program so we'll be
doing our best
Let's switch talk
Switch talk?
That famous switch talk
What kind of switch do you like?
What's your favorite switch?
The remote control switch
It's small and it's in the middle
I touch it all the time
What about you?
The button for the PS Vita
The button for the switch
It's a common switch
What kind of switch do you like?
It's getting smaller
I like the switch for the traffic light
I want to press it
Ignore Yasumoto's switch
What about you?
The button for the water machine
What's that?
The one that the shop makes
What kind of switch do you like?
It's like this
I can't understand
It's the whole switch
Shrimp chew plus switch experience
Kobayashi becomes a switch
The first one to come is NK switches
that make various switches from domestic
to foreign
Excuse me
I'm scared
Please take a picture of me
It's really amazing
Amazing
It's amazing
Please take a picture of me
There are 800 types of NKK switches,
mainly for industrial use.
Feel free to touch it.
There are so many types.
I love this kind of switch.
This is fun.
This is a butter-sugar switch.
Kobayashi, this is a butter-sugar
switch.
It has a button.
Isn't it easy to understand?
The explanation is easy to understand.
If you do this,
If you turn it to the back,
You were doing this.
It's amazing.
This is fun.
Everyone, please pay attention.
Listen.
This is a member.
This is Aoyama.
Nice to meet you.
Let's ask Kobayashi about his favorite
switch.
Kobayashi Kaho's switch is...
This is called toggle switch.
It has a lever like this.
You can turn it to the front or the
back.
Listen to me, everyone.
I'm talking to you.
I'm sorry.
It's an old-fashioned switch.
You can turn it to the front or the
back.
It's a switch like this.
Aoyama-san.
Where can I use this switch?
You suddenly changed your voice.
I'm sorry.
It's not a bad thing.
The switch is...
Let's read what's on the box.
I got it.
This is for connections.
Of course, it's for airplanes.
Our switches are used for industrial
devices.
And Kobayashi's switch is...
This is for NKK.
I see.
So it's toggle NKK?
Yes.
Is it NKK?
No, it's not.
It's toggle TGR.
That's right.
That's interesting.
Kobayashi Kaho's switch is...
TGR switch that makes NKK proud.
After this, the most advanced technology
is added.
It's a surprising switch.
Thank you for watching.
Add the latest switch to the Ebitune.
What is the name of this machine?
This is called Intelligent Switch.
It is actually a switch with a screen
added.
Intelligent Switch is the most advanced
switch beyond the common sense of the
switch world.
What is amazing?
Ebitune plus Intelligent Switch is
This is a big long and thin screen
Each of these is a switch
It's a normal switch
Oh my god!
It's a piano!
You can play it like a piano
Can someone play the piano?
Who can play the piano?
Kaho!
I can't play
Try to play
I saw a cat
It's not a cat
It's a cat!
Is there anything else besides the
piano?
Yes
There is a menu here
There is a hole
There is a bed
Please subscribe to the channel
If you switch the button, you can make
various sounds such as the flag and the
trumpet.
Thank you for your viewing.
What was that sound?
Nothing is written here.
Interesting.
What was that?
A gun and a miracle.
Can someone shoot Chiu with a gun?
Someone who plays the role of a gun and
someone who plays the role of a gunner.
What role am I playing?
I don't know.
I'm going to lose.
Emi Chutas Intelligent Switch is
I went to wait by myself.
Yes, we have seen various things, but
here is the switch quiz.
After this, switch quiz. But before
that.
Ebichu Game Quest
Hello, we are Yuji said Sluice
Jamaica's, invited by Noveitan.
There's a box
Welcome
I thought there was something more
It's so sad
What should we do?
Every time, the members of Ebichu will
go on a great adventure in the world of
games
First, let's open this treasure chest
Let's open it
What should we do?
If there's smoke, we'll fall down
Let's do rock-paper-scissors
Rock-paper-scissors
I'll be a grandpa.
You'll be a grandpa?
There are two papers in it.
What is this?
It's a blue tongue.
You became an old man.
I didn't become an old man.
It's a treasure hunt.
Oh, that's not it.
But it's still in Japan.
There's nothing to hide.
I have an important announcement to
make.
I'll do it first.
I have an important announcement to
make.
The 2015 shrimp making project is in
progress.
It's a secret.
I know you're waiting for it.
The shocking announcement was hidden.
What will it be?
Let's open it.
What is this?
I want to open it.
They are not very confident.
Is this a shaving machine?
I want to shave.
It's already out.
Shaving machine.
It's good.
I will throw it.
Wait a minute.
Game.
I forgot.
I'll say it again.
I have a big announcement.
I don't understand.
Say it.
I have a big announcement.
The project to make a game in 2015 is in
progress.
Game?
What kind of game?
Are you making an FM game?
This?
Let's open the other one.
Let's open it.
Matsuno, you're taking it so well.
I want to take it.
What is it?
What kind of game do you want to make?
What?
You mean making a girl with shrimp
paste, right?
Yes
If you make a girl appear in the game,
the game of girls is card game
Yes
The main one
The dungeon
Clear the quest
and collect cards
Such games are becoming popular
Tonight, the shrimp paste game project
will start
Next week, shrimp paste members will
explore the world of games
We will keep you updated on the next
episode
This week's theme is adding switches to
the shrimp paste
What is the answer?
We have seen a lot of things, but now
it's time for the switch quiz
What is the switch quiz?
Let's go!
Because it's warm
Please be quiet
Let's start, Yasumoto
Ready, set, switch, go!
It's not strong at all
First question
The first question is
This one
I can't see
This switch
Can't you change it?
The first question
What is this small blue switch?
If you know, please answer with a hint
I don't press the switch
I think you pressed the back
It's a little hard
You have to wait for the switch to be
hard or loose
How is it? I touched it a little
It's a TV switch
The first one
TV switch
TV remote control
Hirota
Please answer before you get it right
TV remote control switch
It's wrong
Nakaima
Air conditioner switch
It's wrong
The hint is inside the house
It's me?
If you press it, the earth will break
It's not A
It's close
Don't lie
You can't lie to the MC
Matsuno
The switch that the space beast can call
Wrong
Nice
The space beast can call
It's not close
Yasumoto-san, you can't say it's close
Is it space?
It's not space
The thing that makes the rocket sound
Rocket?
It's space
Not power
Close?
Not close
Give us a hint
Train, car, commuting
Something like that
I got it
Aika
Bus switch
The button to get off the bus
is correct!
Congratulations!
Ready, set, go!
Nice switch!
When I said ready, set, go,
Yasumoto was like, huh? What was that?
We were just having a meeting.
So the correct answer is the bus's turn
signal.
This is the final question.
So far, the closest to the switch queen
is Hirota.
This is the final question, so you will
get 1 million points.
If I get a point, will I get a switch?
That's what you'll have to ask Aoyama
later.
Let's go on.
Switch Q
Is it a small one?
Yes, this is it.
It's a small one again.
What is this?
This is cute.
It's cute.
It's small.
Riko likes it.
Really?
Next, this switch is said to be used by
someone who likes Nakayama.
Where is this switch used?
It's small but it works well
I've seen this before
It's a bit soft
Thank you
I've seen this before
Kobayashi, what's this?
What's this?
It's a keyboard
What is it?
It's a keyboard that changes the sound
It's like a laptop
It's a keyboard
It's a button that changes the sound
It's small
It's not
Chie, please play a game
OK, I'll do it
It's small so it's used to do something
small
If you push it, ants fly
It will fly away
So cute
It's not
You got minus 500 points
Please don't say that I'm going to make
you laugh
Hint! Hint!
Hint!
Hint is something that everyone used a
while ago
A while ago
Future phone button
What is future phone?
Garake
Correct!
Amazing!
Well done!
The correct answer is the mobile phone
switch
It is used in the button
You understood it well
You understood it when you heard it,
right?
I used it a little while ago
Did you understand?
Hoshida also understood
I understood
Really?
I understood such a hint
I think you have pressed it
Then, shall we give 1 million points to
the mountain?
That's right
If you give 1 million points, it will be
strange
So, with 1 million points, Mayana will
switch it on
So, they added a switch to the shrimp.
This is...
Oh, it's open.
Kobayashi became the switch.
Emergency Report
This January, the research student
recruitment of shrimp was announced.
The name is Sakura Ebi!
She will be auditioning in all over
Japan!
The camera will be entering the audition
venue!
We asked the principal of Ebisu Junior
High School, Fujii, what Sakura Ebiz is.
As a student of Ebichu, I want to be
able to improve my skills and try out
various things as a talent.
In the future, Ebichu Tastas will
continue to share information about
Sakura Ebiz.
Next time on Ebichu Tastas...
Wait a minute!
A mysterious new member has appeared!
The second episode of the switch!
The shocking science reaction is about
to begin!
Is the world's first switch idol born?
This program was provided by the
following sponsors.
We did it! We did it!