Ebichu's videos
Hello, I'm Kobayashi-san, number 11.
Today is a walk!
Su Su Su
Yes, so today I'm here.
It is Nakano Station.
I'm going to walk around Nakano
Station.
Let's go to Nakano Station with me.
The weather is so nice.
The weather is so nice, but I made a
mistake in my clothes.
It's hot now.
I don't know why I wore tights.
And I don't know why I wore thick
trainers.
The weather is so nice, but I made a
mistake in my clothes.
Today, I'm going to Nakano Broadway.
I'm going to Nakano Broadway.
I'm sorry if I can't think of anything.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for the interview.
I'm sorry I can't go to Nakano
Broadway.
I'm going to go to the main gate.
There is a person.
Are you stupid?
I'm stupid.
and
oh!
That restaurantash
I would like to go there
Oh, she's tying a knot
H-Hi-
We're at the K Amazingeness Hall!
Make sure to enjoy it if you haven't!
It's easy to enjoy by going up!
Did you enjoy the exit?
There are many people from the elderly
to the non-elderly.
I'm curious about this.
There are many shoes shops.
I can see the middle of the road!
It says Nakano Broadway!
I arrived at Nakano Broadway!
I was surprised when I saw the sign at
the end of the shopping street.
It was a terrible impression.
I'd like to go inside now.
Let's go!
Let's go inside.
I want to stay in New York.
There are so many things.
Where is it?
How many floors are there?
One floor?
Wow!
Is it going down?
I imagined it.
It wasn't Broadway.
It's like this.
It's pretty deep.
I went deep.
I want to go next.
I'm often told that I absolutely love
Nakano Broadway.
But it's my first time.
I want to go to the cinema.
I don't want to go back.
What?
Wait a minute.
Nakano Broadway.
Wow!
There are so many things.
Thank you for watching.
I can see a lot of pro-wrestling masks
and shoes.
There are a lot of figures.
I've seen them before.
I guess this is a place for anime and
characters.
There are a lot of figures.
I'm not shy to show my teeth recently.
I'm surprised to see a secret blade.
I'll go to the next one.
Oh, there is something.
I wonder what it is.
I'm going to do it.
It hurts a little because there is a
panel on the face.
It's not the face, but only the eyes.
It's a feature.
I'm going to do it.
It's over.
I'd like to go.
I have a lot of unnecessary feelings
and will not watch.
Lovely!
I'm so excited!
Cute!
Today's special is honey lemon.
It's a honey lemon.
It's here!
I'm so excited!
It's getting cold.
Honey lemon.
I'm so excited!
I didn't order this before.
Why is there so much foam?
It's not foam.
How should I eat this?
Should I eat it while drinking ice
cream?
I'm not good at eating ice cream.
My dad puts indispensable effort into
it.
Itadakimasu.
It's so good!
It tastes like honey lemon.
It's so good! It's refreshing.
It's a refreshing taste of lemon and a
little sweet taste of honey and vanilla
ice cream.
It's so good!
Why didn't I order this before?
I didn't buy it.
Thank you for watching until the end.
I walked around the middle of the
Broadway.
I enjoyed the dopes of the coffee shop.
There was a bar near here.
I will walk around there.
Let's go.
It's quite deep.
wow!
a ferris wheel is projected to a
billboard!
St alone and make it as a02
Cl War OfRIGHT?
Let me stop being bore
it turned into like rice and curry.
Wow, it's amazing.
The restaurant is preparing for the
opening.
I wonder if they will come to this kind
of place.
I don't know.
But it looks fun.
I don't drink much outside.
I want to come here again when I can
drink more.
I will come here again when I can drink
more.
Wow, it's dangerous.
I can't come here alone.
Wow, I wonder if there are any saurie-
man.
They are preparing.
I want to go to snack shop someday.
I want to drink various things in
various places and go to snacks.
I came to the end of this drink.
I'm hungry, so I want to eat yakisoba.
I'm going to eat yakisoba.
I'm not sure which sauce to choose.
I can't choose the sauce.
I'll choose salt.
I don't choose salt.
I've never eaten Shio Yakisoba.
So I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you for your viewing.
It's delicious.
It's very fresh to put it in a silver
plate.
The dog still won't let go of the
leash.
The last spurt before the tail goes
into the water.
Well done, dad.
It's hot.
It's good.
It's really good.
The noodles are flat.
It's not the usual noodles.
It's saltier and lighter.
It's good.
I'll eat it slightly.
Because you don't eat the meat.
A міliecă da turkă presesă
Thank you for watching.
It's like an Internet où on ne décolle
pas sur des tra Je fais une course.
By the way
Speaking of Nakano,
Nakano Sun Plaza
You know....
It is expensive
Well, we can't really go home yet.
I'm going to write it down.
I'm not going to write it down.
Ebitune is a fan club event.
I was in charge of the live performance
of Ebi Mani and Ebi Hai, which was held
at the 2018 FANTASY event.
Thank you very much.
I have a dream.
I've only been to San Prato once, so
I've never done a live performance.
I think everyone has a better memory.
What do you think?
I'm very interested in the diagonal.
It's a nice building.
I want to do a live performance here
again.
I'm not a Pori-Pori.
I'm glad to see Nakano because I came
here.
I'm tired because I saw Nakano Sun
Plaza.
I found a bench.
I'm going to sit on the bench.
Yes!
This is what Nakano's bench looks like.
It's not a tree.
Is it a tree?
It's a beautiful bench.
There are many people in the building.
They are all sitting on the bench.
I'm going to sit on the bench, too.
I thought it was a tree.
I'm going to take a boat.
I hope you can take a boat there.
I was wondering where to go for a walk.
But I decided to go to Nakano because
the weather was nice.
I'm sleepy.
I just wanted to come back to Nakano.
It was fun.
I want to take someone who likes anime
to Broadway.
I want to find someone.
I want to go to the next place.
This time, I went to a place that is
representative of subculture.
I went to a fashionable downtown area.
I went to Shimokitazawa.
I went to a park.
I think that is also a subculture.
I want to go to a place with a lot of
fashionable places.