Can I?
Ta-da!
Thank you for coming.
Welcome.
I'm Konishi Nanami.
I'm Oda. Nice to meet you.
I read a fashion magazine.
A fashion magazine?
I read it when I was in elementary
school.
It was written on the back cover as if I
was looking for a model for a grave.
I really wanted to come here so much
that I thought I'd ask for it.
I'm so happy today.
There are so many things.
I don't know.
Wow.
I usually buy it from the place I go.
Yes.
I wear dresses at restaurants.
I wear denim at the neighborhood.
I usually wear clothes that are easy to
move.
But I like clothes.
What do you think is good?
I think it's good.
I've always admired Kobe.
I feel happy and happy.
I love Kobe.
I love my hometown.
I can go anywhere in the mountains and
the sea.
I like the city center.
I went to the Ijin-kan in the north,
and went to the San-no-miya to shop,
and bought clothes.
I played with my friends and took a
picture.
I went to the Uroko house and Platon
Museum.
If I could be a member of Hinatazaka46,
I would like to be a warm idol who can
make people who are in contact with me
happy.
I first saw Hinatazaka46 a year or two
ago.
Until then, I was a member of
Hinatazaka46.
I watched the idol on the street.
I only knew Nagizaka-san.
At that time, I saw Hinatazaka46's cute.
I knew that there was such a cute,
bright and sparkling idol.
I was worried about the path.
I liked makeup, but it was almost a
hobby.
I didn't really want to do it.
So I just answered whatever the teacher
asked me to do.
Then, the new member audition for
Hinatazuka 46 started.
I applied immediately.
I'm Nanami Konishi, a third-year high
school student from Hyogo Prefecture.
Nice to meet you.
My feelings when I went to the final
screening were like,
I didn't believe it at all.
I was really nervous from 2 o'clock.
I was really nervous.
I was really nervous until 4 o'clock.
My face was stiff and I was always in a
straight face.
So I didn't want to be thought as a
straight face person.
In the final screening, I will move my
nervous and stiff face.
I will move it forcibly and express my
excitement.
Ki
Do
Ai
I'm easy-going.
Yay.
That's all. Thank you.
My personality is...
I'm too shy.
How can I say?
And my face is cold.
So people think I'm cold.
But inside,
I'm bright.
I'm noisy.
But...
I'm a good person.
But I'm a good person.
When I was a kid, I played a lot at the
athletics in the World Flower Park.
I played with my friends in the
mountains.
I'm not a talkative person, but I'm not
the type to talk or laugh.
I'm a very talkative person, but I'm not
I used to like ids.
I watched the DVDs over and over again,
and I learned the choreography and sang.
I think I've liked ids since I was
little.
When I was in elementary school,
there was a free pass called Nobi Nobi
Passport.
It had a sense of identity.
私の近所にも異人感があるんですけど、
小学生の時は、それがどこかも知らずに、
何かのびのびパスポートを見せて、
その人の家、異人感に入って、
ただ歩いて遊んで、出てくるみたいな、
よくわからない遊びをしていたり、
高校生になってからも、
ここの北野の異人感を友達ともあって、
I used to play with them.
Nice to meet you.
I like the sense of belonging here,
and I was looking up about it when I was
planning to come here.
I know that feeling.
It's a secret. I don't tell anyone what
I want to say.
What do you miss the most about your
family?
I miss being separated from my family.
My mom says she misses me the most.
I don't feel that way yet.
I think I'll be away for about a week.
I was in Tokyo for a lesson for the
music video shoot.
I didn't feel like I wanted to go home.
I think I'll be able to go home.
I'm relaxed now.
I like my hometown, Kobe.
I like quiet places.
I can't come back to Kobe.
I wanted to go to...
I want to go now.
I'm happy to be here today.
Exactly what i call a
back
It was cool
It's so true.
It's so beautiful.
The sound and the atmosphere are so
good.
As a new member, I can't imagine what
I'm going to be like.
What kind of person I'm going to be,
what kind of person I'm going to be in
charge of,
what kind of position I'm in, what I'm
doing.
I don't know anything.
My goal isn't just that.
I don't just cry.
As my existence...
No, my existence...
My goal?
My personal goal isn't that clear.
What I'll be in a year...
I have no idea.
I'm sure that Kobe is such a wonderful
city.
I'll do my best to be an idol who can be
proud of Kobe.
I'll do my best with all the 4th
generation.
I'll do my best to come back here at the
HINATAZAKA46 concert.
No. 23, Nanami Konishi.
Str publish me né
Nordschulse
Ad
White
Get
It
You
Beach
cock
El
cement
R
W
What
admitted
Che
injections
Se
Abigail
minute
By
warehouse
dr
France
What
Why
I'm 18 years old from Hyogo, Konishi
Nanami.