MIZUKI
Thank you for watching.
The Greatest Martial Arts Games in the
History of Japan
It feels so fresh when I listen to it.
I wonder if we can sing.
We'll rehearse a little.
It's the first time we're doing it with
an orchestra.
What's going to happen?
I'm going to listen to the beginning.
Thank you.
I'm so nervous.
It's so difficult.
It's amazing.
I don't think I've ever heard a sound
like this before.
There are some sounds that are not
always there.
The sound is increasing.
I wonder if it's okay.
It's hard to get the pitch right.
It's okay.
I'm nervous.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for watching!
We may join up the powerful force next
time.
Street Dance of China YUKICHI
I'm nervous.
Thank you for watching.
It's a bit of a stretch to say that, but
I'm sure you'll enjoy it.
The orchestra is totally different from
usual.
It's totally different.
I'm so excited.
It's amazing.
I can't do it.
What should I do?
I'm going to cry.
I'm so excited.
She is alive.
She will be normal soon.
Oh, my God.
I felt so.
Let me introduce the members of Super-
Tokimeki Sensei.
Let's do it together.
1,2,3,4,5,6
We are Super-Tokimeki Sensei.
Rock on!
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Everything you see is a picture of love
to be a star
don't worry baby i'll be fine
i'm strong you can count on me
I want to hold you tight in my arms
Thank you very much.
The 16th anniversary concert was her
Don't call it a love that can't be
stopped
I'm sure I'm just a standard
I'm a normal girl
I'm your heroine
I'm always a dream
I can't be a fool
I'm a dream that can't be fooled
I'm a sensational boy
I want you
If I can protect you, I'll do anything
I'm a normal girl
I'm not that bad
I'm in love, I'm in love, yeah yeah
yeah, woo woo woo woo
I'm in love, I'm in love
Love Love Love...
Do you have a new feel?
Something until the end
I love you
I hope we can be together someday
Thank you for watching!
You gave me a lot of feelings,
everything
We're about to cross the sea, let's go
together
I like the place where we connect
Thank you.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Grandpad dies
You two are told to put down the cards
Tag- is Azusa
Agu- is Hasesa
так annotation
Grandpa dies
The toeyour who came to visit
Thank you!
Nevertheless, it is needed in exercise
this time.
You are doing very good!
It was difficult for me to lower this
ball in the first half, but I
d …
Oh no!
Look!
Yes.
Thank you for watching.
FCSp4 3.20 (-0.77 StSq2 2.60 (-0.00)]
StSq2 2.60 (-0.00')
FCSp4 3.20 (-0.00')
She is crying.
It's amazing.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
We'll record it now.
nice
At first, I thought the song was
different from the one I like.
I thought I was too bad at it.
I thought I didn't know where to start.
Then, I saw the song and I thought,
Wait, this is not right.
I thought it was not right.
It was too fast.
I was nervous.
My legs and jaw were shaking.
My hands were cold.
But it was so powerful.
It was a different kind of music.
I never had a chance like this.
I was enjoying it.
From the rehearsal.
It was a different kind of music.
It was like a concert.
It was beautiful.
It was like this.
I hope we can enjoy the performance.
I was nervous.
I hope we can enjoy it more.
It was like a birthday party.
I was surprised.
You were the conductor.
Happy birthday.
At first, our conductors were not in
sync.
I thought I couldn't keep up.
I thought I was doing something wrong.
But it was a different kind of music.
I thought it was not right.
It was a precious opportunity to have a
birthday party for us.
I wanted to get a video as soon as
possible.
I wanted to show my mom.
It was a wonderful memory.
I'm glad.
I was so nervous when I was on stage.
My heart was beating so fast.
I checked everyone's heart.
I was excited.
The sound of the orchestra was gorgeous.
I was captivated.
It was like going to another world.
I was so grateful that everyone cared
about us.
I was so grateful that everyone gave us
a sign when we entered the stage.
We performed our song today.
We will perform the next song.
It's amazing.
It's too obvious.
When we were singing, everyone was like
this.
We were all looking at the same
direction.
We will do our best.
We will sing while looking at the
audience.
We will do our best.
It's our first time.
I was surprised.
At first, we didn't match at all.
I was sorry and messed up.
I was surprised at the happy birthday
song.
January? These two?
It's my birthday.
I was surprised and happy.
I thought Juliano noticed it before
Oharu.
Who noticed it first?
Oharu noticed it first.
Really?
She stopped the performance.
She stopped.
Juliano was like this.
Juliano was off.
I see.
I thought I messed up.
That's what you thought.
I was happy.
I didn't know.
I don't care if I make a mistake.
You should sing powerfully.
More than usual.
There are many people in the orchestra.
So, you are under a lot of pressure.
You can't sing while feeling it.
I see.
Don't hesitate to sing.
Don't worry about missing the sound.
Thank you for watching this video.
Please subscribe to this channel.
3, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6
To your heart, knock on!
We are CHO!
We are the TAKIMIKI Girls' Team!
Nice to meet you!
The stars are aiming for the sky
While drawing the future in the night
sky
The days when tears flow
I'll run with my dream that you'll come
Now, it's time for the rehearsal!
Please look forward to it!
The rehearsal is over!
It's a cat.
How do you feel?
It was easy to raise because the bangs
were just stretched.
Pio, your bangs and hair are in good
condition today.
It's so cute.
I especially like this side.
I like the length of the bangs.
This side is cuter.
It's cuter when you look outside.
I'm a heroine of the day.
It's the first day of the 2013 VIRTUAL
FESTIVAL.
I'm moving today.
It's the first day.
I'm in charge of the first day.
Let's go!
I'm going.
We're going to start the show soon.
We're going to sing in the orchestra for
the first time.
It's exciting, but it feels different
when we sing live.
It's different from the orchestra, so I
hope you'll enjoy it.
I'm really excited to sing with the
orchestra for the first live show of the
year.
It's a rare opportunity.
All the songs are completely different
from the existing songs.
It's a song that's familiar to you.
It's a great arrangement.
It's a song that you can only see today.
I love that arrangement.
I think some people have seen it.
I think it's a precious opportunity.
I'm looking forward to it.
We'll do our best.
When I rehearsed with the orchestra for
the first time, I was very nervous.
I'm looking forward to the actual
performance.
I had a rehearsal before the show today.
I had a lot of adjustments.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's a rare experience.
Angela and Shoko Nakagawa's
collaboration is amazing.
The control is amazing.
The vibrato is amazing.
Everything is amazing.
I thought it was cool.
We'll do our best.
Today is the first live concert in 2023.
It's been a luxury from the beginning.
I like orchestras.
I was going to go see the concert with a
ticket.
But I couldn't go.
I have less work.
It's a very precious and important
experience to sing with an orchestra.
I want to enjoy it to the fullest.
It's fun to sing with a comfortable ear.
We're looking forward to it.
I wonder what the promoter is looking
at.
I'm curious.
What kind of clothes will the promoter
wear?
It's a concert.
It's always colorful.
I'm looking forward to hearing what you
think.
Let's do our best.
We'll do our best.
It was time to prospects.
I envy them right now.
You became a star.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for watching!
See you next time!
Bye!
Ready, set, go!
Thank you!
What was that?
That's all.
This is the end of the ceremony.
Please give a round of applause.
Thank you very much.
I'm in love with you
I knew it, I knew you were the only one
My heart is beating fast
I can't stop my heart beating
Keep on loving me
I have a favor to ask you
Hey, give me a hug!
Just a little more, just a little more
I want to be with you tonight
I hope we can be together someday
What should I do to make you look back?
I wonder if I have to change myself more
I thought so
I just want to be myself and be with you
I hope we can be together someday
Ah...
Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss Kiss
Kiss Kiss
I wish I could give you all of my
feelings
If I'm about to melt, I want to hold you
tight
I want to hold you tight
Thank you very much.
I'm nervous.
I can't help it.
I've been watching you.
I saw you.
We're on standby.
Let's go when you're ready.
The first live show of the new year is
over.
Thank you for your hard work.
We performed at the UNISON New Year
Special Gala Concert 2023.
It was a precious experience.
I was very nervous because I sang in the
orchestra's performance.
But it was fun.
I enjoyed it.
The sound was beautiful and I couldn't
stand the feeling of the sound coming
into my ears.
It was the first time for the orchestra.
Everyone was so kind.
They sang freely without thinking.
It was fun.
They were smiling all the time when they
were playing.
I like it.
I like orchestra and music.
It was the best experience.
Thank you.
This is the best live show of the year.
Thank you, everyone.
I'll do my best.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Thank you for watching!
Translated by Releska