Shiraishi and Ume's collaboration camp
Hello
We came to camp
Yes, we came
Long time no see
I'm happy
Thank you
We are shooting a collaboration camp
with Shiraishi and Nogizaka
I think so
We are camping in the
campground
The sound of the river
It's a nice weather
It's relaxing
I can see the stars
It's a nice weather
We started from the evening
We have a lot to do
Please say hello
I feel like I'm with Ume
It's a little difficult
Thank you
Shall we start?
Let's go
They are matching
I'm happy
It's amazing
It looks delicious
Amazing
It's butter
It's a lot of small things
I borrowed this from Robosh
Thank you
There are a lot of cute blankets and
tents here
It's cute
It's compact
There are some mosquitoes
There are mosquitoes
This is a camp
There are
There are mosquitoes
Let's go down together
I can't help it
I'll carry it
Be careful
Will mosquitoes fly?
I think so
Hold it
There are three mosquitoes
Amazing
There is a step
I'll stop once
Let's go
I'm sorry
Ok
Kamemushi-san is safe now
I'm safe
I'm here
This is amazing
What should we do?
Let's build a tent
Can we build a tent?
It seems like we can build a tent
Since we are inside here
Kamemushi-san
I'm waiting for Kamemushi
I'm thinking of making a meal here
That's right
Cool
Kamemushi is playing
Thank you
Have a nice day
Amazing
It's good
We are here
Amazing
Can we build a tent here?
Let's build a tent
I'm going to sleep
It's good
We have a camera
Thank you
It's good, it's good, it's fashionable
It's funny
It's a very natural place
It's amazing
Thank you for your viewing. Please
subscribe to the channel.
Shall we go?
Let's go.
It's not so steep.
No, no.
4 places to fix with pegs on the ground.
I'm sure we can do it with a stick.
Yes, we can.
Do we use all of these?
I think we can use them all.
I think so.
I'll put them out.
Thank you.
What is this on the ground?
I'll spread them out.
Okay.
What is this?
It's very big.
It looks very big.
Can I put them on the ground?
But...
But there are check marks.
Right.
Is it above?
Does it mean that it will be like this?
Oh, batte!
There was batte, right?
Wind?
Frying sheet
For the time being, we use this.
This?
This is it.
That means batte.
First, we should put the bottom of
batte.
It looks like this.
Where to put it?
Let's put it a little more.
OK
It looks good.
Please put it.
I'll try this side.
If we don't stab it, it's over.
I think so.
It sounds good.
It's ringing.
Go, go.
Is it a stone?
There is a stone.
I entered.
This one is better.
Is there a problem with the location?
What?
Umezawa san?
I might be bad at this
Oh, it's coming
It's coming
I can do it
I did it
Nice
OK
Good, good
Spread it
But
But it's right
It's right, isn't it?
Was the back side the opposite?
Yes
Should I take it off?
And the location of the stopper was
wrong
It's true, 45 degrees
I'll take it off
I took it off
Be careful
Please subscribe to our channel!
Are you ready?
I'm sorry
Thank you
I want to cook rice, but I can't spend
time in the tent
Shirai-san is going to build a chair for
us
You can make a chair in a second
Wow, a chair in a second
There are many things
I got it, I got it
Connect it, it's easy
This is good
It looks like a pet
This is a chair
A chair is important
If you sit down and sit down, it's a
chair
This is very important
It's amazing, with such a thin stick
It supports me
I'll try it too
Try it
What is this?
The other side
It's good
Surprisingly...
Here we go
Wow, it's fast
Wait, wait, wait
This is crazy
Here we go!
Here we go! Amazing!
Amazing!
As expected
Here we go!
It's good, it's good!
Is it right?
It's right, isn't it?
Here we go!
It's good, isn't it?
It's good!
It's good
The house is complete
It's a tent
With this
Here it is.
Okay.
Here we go.
Can I adjust the angle?
It's getting better.
Thank you.
Is it the one on the side?
This one too?
Yes, I think so.
Is it done?
Yes, it's done.
Ahahaha, got it.
Here we go.
Wow, it looks scary.
Sorry.
Ah, I did it.
OK.
Oh no.
It's a fire.
Here we go.
This is autumn.
Let's go this way.
Can we reach it?
Yes.
We made it.
It's down there.
Wow.
Wow, it's amazing.
This is this way.
Is it right?
This way?
The top of the mountain is a mountain.
Wow! We did it!
We did it!
Let's take a picture.
I found something cool
This is Ume's
This is Shirai's
The color is different from mine
It's Nogizaka color
I see
Please use two of Shirai's
Really? Thank you
You are...
Nogizaka color
Thank you for watching!
I'll do it.
Sorry, I forgot to do it.
This is really difficult.
I think it was really difficult.
Oh, great!
It's amazing!
Here it is!
Amazing!
You're a genius!
You're amazing!
The first one is a success!
Here it is!
Amazing!
I was surprised!
We've already collected about 5 bags.
5 bags?
That's good.
Now...
Oh, the wood!
The wood is the key to the
capre that wasarin Manari has been
using.
Go! Go, go, go!
Go, go, go!
Go, go!
Oh, it's coming!
It's coming!
Finally!
It's really hard!
It's really hard.
Please, turn it.
But it's stable.
It looks good.
I'm sure it will be more and more.
Wow!
We made it!
We finally made it!
Let's make dinner!
What are we going to make?
I prepared something I want to use
This is a multi griddle
This looks great!
It's really cool
It's this thin
It's true!
So, I hope we can use this
I hope so
I want to eat one yakisoba
Please make yakisoba with this
Please!
It looks really good
It looks like a plate
I think we can use this
I want to make
Takikomi rice
Takikomi rice and
pumpkin
I like pumpkin
Let's make yakisoba
We have aluminum foil
Let's do it
Let's put it in a bowl
Let's do our best
I hope it tastes good
Let's try it
Let's start making
Let's put it in the bowl
I'll cut the ingredients for takikomi
rice
What do you need?
What do you want to put in?
Mushroom
I want to put in sake
Fried chicken
I want to put in chicken
I'll put in the vegetables too
And maitake mushrooms.
Wow, it's absolutely delicious.
I think it's okay to use half of the
rice.
Okay, please.
Three kinds of mushrooms.
There are also shiitake mushrooms.
Then, I'll go get them.
One or two.
Please add them little by little.
It must be delicious.
Should I put it up?
I'll turn it around.
It's done.
Is it big?
Not at all.
Is it that big?
It is.
Is it big?
How big is the strawberry?
This is enough.
It's strawberry, so it looks a little
good.
All of it.
Do you put it in?
I'll put it in.
I wonder if it will be hard if I put a
lot of ingredients.
I'll put in shimeji.
I'll put it in.
It's going to be small.
It looks really good.
I'll put in shiitake mushrooms.
Thank you for your viewing.
I think one shiitake mushroom is enough.
I think so.
There are many ingredients.
Then,
seasonings?
Yes.
How much do I need?
A little bit.
Sake.
A little bit more?
Hey!
Should I try?
Nice!
Turn the lid on
Should I try?
Mix it up
It's really nice
It's nice, isn't it?
Nice!
OK!
OK, with this
Yes
I'm scared!
Have a nice day!
Thank you very much.
It looks good.
What should I do?
And three hours has passed!
It's be TOP of the Top 8 of 2021!
Wishing for goodwill bros!
Thank you for watching.
Ume, do you have any work after this?
Yes.
Can I have a beer?
Yay!
This is great!
I'll make some yakitori.
Can I make yakitori?
Go ahead.
Can I grill it here? Let's eat it with a
snack.
Let's eat.
Here comes Umezawa.
Yay!
Thank you for the food!
Asahi, your turn
I'm looking forward to this river
I'm watching you
Thank you so much
Thank you for the food!
It's so good!
It's the best!
There's milk, so I think stew is better
There's milk
There's also fresh cream
I'll put in the pumpkin
It looks good with the mushrooms too
I'll put in the hard ones
The carrot was so small
It's okay
Thank you very much
I'll fry them in the gas stove.
I'll use the fire.
I want some snacks.
I'll have some sausages.
Ouch.
It's going to take a while.
glutinous rice
please, I'll village
everyone really
cases
want box
Thank you for your viewing.
I'm sorry, I'm not filming at all.
My hand can't turn that way.
I'm making a lot of snacks.
I'm so embarrassed.
My manager is making snacks.
It's the best while drinking.
Thank you.
Let's go from the front.
This way.
Yay.
Let's go in.
Let's make yakisoba.
Great.
It's definitely delicious even if you
bake it without the sake.
Certainly, it's grilled foil.
Grilled foil.
Do you want to put mushrooms on it?
I wonder if I can put it on.
Let's use the chopsticks we used
earlier.
Let's go.
These remaining mushrooms.
Do you need some sake?
Let's add some.
Done.
Thank you.
What's this?
Thank you for watching.
The
Get up.
We have a lot of them.
We have two.
We have a lot.
Enjoy the ride.
One, two, three, four, five.
Is there anything else?
Nine, ten.
Ten.
We can't get in.
It's getting dark.
Oh, no.
Ten.
Eleven.
Twenty-four.
Twenty-one.
Twenty-two.
Twenty-three.
Twenty-four.
Twenty-five.
Twenty-six.
Twenty-seven.
Consomme.
Yaki-soba
Let's try it.
See you later.
Okay.
Can you do it?
I'll try it.
But I don't think so.
How is it?
It's pretty soft.
Really?
Let's cut it.
It must be hot.
Here we go.
It looks so good.
It's done.
It's alive.
Let's do it while eating
While eating
It's hot, so put it here
Thank you
It looks delicious
Let's try
Is it good?
Please subscribe to my channel
It's great
It's really good
It's sweet
It's great
Amazing
Yaki soba from my hometown
Yaki soba
It's hot
The soup is coming down
Yaki soba
Everyone, I'll give you now
I'll give you now
I didn't do anything with the vegetables
It's sweet
Oh no
Please subscribe to my channel
Wanna live happily for a few months
It's not cold at all
It is
I thought lived the fire
Because of the debate
Can you eat yakisoba?
I love it
Let's make yakisoba
I want to make yakisoba
Can I make yakisoba with this?
Please, please
Please use it
I'm happy
I'll make it with this
Cool
Meat looks delicious
Delicious
It's going to turn red
But it's okay
I'll make yakisoba
Should I leave the oyster butter?
I'll try it
I want to taste the stew first
It's good.
Done!
Wow!
Is it done?
Soup?
Yes!
What?
But the pumpkin may be hard.
If it's delicious, anything is fine.
The oysters look delicious.
They look very delicious.
The color is very beautiful.
It looks delicious.
Yakisoba too.
It looks delicious. I want to eat it.
I'm happy.
Only one is not put in.
This pot is very good.
Is it okay?
It doesn't stick?
Thank you for your viewing.
It's cute.
The oyster butter is cute.
Ta-da, oyster butter.
Oyster butter.
It looks good.
How about the rice?
I didn't see the time.
I didn't see it.
I forgot it.
Oh, no.
The stew was terrible.
I forgot it.
It looks delicious.
Welcome.
There are many dishes.
How is it?
It's the best.
Is it okay?
Of course.
Let's eat.
I made so many dishes.
It's the best.
Put the tatami.
I'm surprised.
Let's eat together.
Let's eat.
Wow, look at this squid.
Cut the squid into small pieces.
Of course.
Do you want to make it with butter and
soy sauce?
Look at this.
It's so big.
It's so good.
I thought you were saying something.
I want to eat oyster butter.
Is this squid okay to eat here?
I think it's okay to eat it like this.
I want to eat squid with butter and soy
sauce.
This is...
Hot!
It looks good!
It's hot!
How is it?
It looks like a camping.
It looks so delicious!
It's like a camping.
Is everyone here?
Let's try.
Let's try to eat something we can eat.
Delicious!
Awesome!
It looks so delicious!
Wow!
Butter! It's so good!
Mmm!
There was a school festival for the
graduates
and we were so proud to hear the sound
of tea
I think I can see it!
Already!
I can see it!
You're drinking coffee while looking at
the stars
Ah!
I'm so excited!