Thank you.
Please come again.
Yes.
Thank you.
The sound of a bell is heard in the
background.
The bell is ringing.
cute
I'm going
I'll do my best
If you get the first place, please sit
down together
I'm going
Can you do it?
I don't know
I'm so happy.
I don't know the rules yet.
How many can I show?
I've been thinking a lot.
Thank you.
Hiyari's name is Mamuten.
It seems difficult.
The items.
What's there?
Something like an egg.
I'll do my best.
Dental.
It seems difficult.
But I'm excited.
Do your best.
Momo's chair.
It's not big.
It's not possible.
It's interesting that Momo's chair
appears in the video.
It's the best.
Good morning.
I'll check the items.
What did you do?
I played a game with songs.
I see.
You were good at it.
I listened to many songs.
I was good at it.
I'm not confident.
I'm not sure what kind of person I am.
It's
Yana loves cabbage Engineering style
I've been thinking a lot about it, but
I'd like to release something that I
think is the most interesting.
I think that's the most interesting.
Three, two, and five.
Cut!
How was it?
It was a little funny, so I'll give it a
high score.
Shiho took four Katies.
I thought about 6 of them.
You decided to do that?
I want to see the others.
I thought a lot about it, but I wanted
to do it more.
Next is Julia
Julia is a senior
It's like a 10-second quiz
I should get close to the time
I'm the worst at this
What should I advertise?
Now, we are going to shoot for Julia.
Oh, I see.
We are going to shoot for Julia.
Oharu-san came.
What is your role?
I'm a game that has a song.
Let's think about it.
It seems difficult.
I don't have confidence at all.
How do you fight with everyone in the
VTR?
I don't know who can answer the question
the fastest.
Or the number of songs.
If the number of songs is large, it will
be a game.
I can't answer one by one.
But you are good at practicing.
I'm good at practicing.
Is it over?
Oh, I see.
I see.
Twin combi.
Twin.
It's difficult. I can't do it by myself.
You can't do it by yourself.
I'm tired.
I'm tired. I can't do it by myself.
Thank you.
When was the last time you saw me?
I remember the time when we were at Get.
I only come here when I'm at work.
You're always by my side.
January 14th.
It's a good day.
You're being selfish.
What should I say?
Thank you for watching.
Oh, there it is.
Is she always running?
Marine Goh Hinata
I'm going to do my makeup today.
Your face is your makeup.
That's right.
What's the point of your makeup today?
I've put on a lot of makeup.
A lot of glitter.
I didn't know.
Is the color of the glitter different
from the glitter below?
Yes, it's different.
The color is different.
It's been a long time since I've done my
own makeup.
You've been doing makeup lately.
Yes.
What's the point of your makeup?
The point of my makeup is orange.
I'm hungry.
Let's go to the restaurant.
Hello, everyone. I'm Angelia from Chota
Muscle Advertising Club.
Let's get started.
I'm going to shoot.
I'll introduce the Tokisei Family.
Kanamin, Julia, Hito-chan, Aki-chan,
Haru-chan, Hiyori,
Suta-chan, Sende-kun, Burano, Apina!
Please.
Don!
That was great.
7.74 seconds.
Thank you for watching.
Cut!
What's with this husband?
I'm sorry.
You were so fast.
I was 8.6 seconds in rehearsal.
I was so fast that I forgot to say
something.
I was 7 seconds.
I'm glad I didn't exceed 10 seconds.
It's my fault.
We have a dog face.
I'm making a microphone.
Good morning.
I'm done.
I'm not sure if I have anything to do.
I'm getting closer to the stage.
Really?
I'm looking forward to it.
I just came here, so I haven't seen
everyone.
Everyone was amazing.
I just came here, too.
Is Tio finished?
Tio was doing her best.
I was watching you.
Is it on?
You're amazing.
Why are you screaming?
It's a great match.
What?
Good luck.
I feel it!
Omg omg
Kabukichou
What?
What's this?
What, eh?
Hey, that's the Society Standing
Committee's best student dad.
It's too small.
Thank you!
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
I'm not sure if I can do it.
What's next?
When is my turn?
Next?
I'm nervous.
Whoever is certain about the result will
do it for the first time.
Whoever takes the unusual action will do
it for the first time.
I'm excited.
With a nervous heart
It's so difficult.
The first one is open.
It's difficult.
I could hear the voice of the vocalist.
But I didn't know what song it was.
I didn't know anything.
I didn't know any song.
Let's jump.
I'm sorry.
I got stuck.
How much is the average?
I'm sorry.
300, 500, 400.
It's cute, isn't it?
It's amazing if it reaches 100.
It's like a guitar.
But it's 82.
It's stocking up.
Shut up.
What?
Do you want to make a gap?
Number one!
Number one?
Which do you think is better?
Number one!
My name?
Da?
I'm the best!
Is my voice too loud?
You were like that just now.
I'll just say I'm the best.
I'm the best!
I love you!
Don't laugh!
OK!
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Number 1!
Now, the Choto Kimiki Advertisement
Club, Hitoka Sakai's loud challenge!
Go ahead!
I'll do my best!
Ichida!
1, 2, 3
104!
Are you ready?
Let's go!
You interrupting the forth one
Is written
T정
You cunning
I have jadi
Dropped
Music
Good
That's good.
It's embarrassing.
I'm in.
You're in.
It's my first time.
First time?
Oh, is it your first time?
Oh, I've never seen it.
It's so beautiful.
I'm going to do it.
It's high.
I can't do it.
How is it?
Rica got nervous.
Is she a bit nervous?
Well, my body is...
But what's with running around?
See you!
another one
Worst
person
While
under
it
Round 1.
The person who fails to get off the
chair will be eliminated.
What?
Round 1.
The person who fails to get off the
chair will be eliminated.
Oh, I see.
The person who gets off the chair in all
4 rounds will be eliminated.
Can I get off the chair?
What should I do?
Thank you for watching.
I'm sorry.
Ta-da!
Dis asks, which Kubota is the most
memorable movie and alsolers.
If I were to recommend a movie to folks
watching, I'd go for an entire series.
I'll put a star on my face and put the
planet logo on my body.
This is the logo of the store.
It's written in the letters MEGA, S and
D.
I drew it.
What?
Isn't it amazing?
Isn't it?
Isn't it great?
It's like an official event.
I did my best.
You did your best?
Isn't it great?
It's good for the environment.
It's SDD.
I love the earth.
It's good for recycling.
It's true.
It's good for the environment.
It's good for protecting the earth.
I wrote it.
I made a two-headed Yuru character.
We came here and saw something amazing.
I can rely on my seniors.
Oh, it's over.
I think it's my third year.
Me?
I heard the sound once.
Oh, it's on.
Did you take it?
I took it.
I'm Hiorin Yoshikawa, a member of the
group, DOKUON, and I'm a member of the
group, CHOTOKIMIKI SENRENMU, CHOTOKIMIKI
GRIN.
We will do our best with free dance and
improvisation!
Three! Two! One! Go!
No!
OK, OK.
...
essment
he is the best
Cut!
I got there.
Let's run away, let's run away.
It was fun!
We are Chou! Takemiki Channel! Thank
you!
Thank you so much!
We look forward to working with you!
So, we have finished the pre-recording!
It was fun!
It's sad that we can't go to the actual
performance.
It's sad, but...
We'll show you the video.
Your voice is...
It's like a big venue in a street
corner.
Is it OK?
It's like a big venue in a street
corner.
Hiroki Kubo's DAD
It was fun.
If we make it in time, we'll do it.
Which part?
They said, welcome.
If we make it in time, we'll do it.
Let's make everyone laugh.
I want to see that video.
We'll be in the video this time.
We'll do our best at the venue.
Please watch it.
I'm looking forward to it.
If you enjoy it, it's a live broadcast.
I'll do my best.
It's a meteor!
It's a huge meteor!
It's a huge one!
Please subscribe to our channel and
follow us on Twitter!
Please subscribe to my channel!
It's a very good seat.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm watching you in a very good seat.
I've been watching the rehearsal of
Tomokuro.
What kind of rehearsal?
It's rare.
And it's a pretty good seat.
It was a pretty good seat.
I had an eye.
I got a lesson.
Please take care of me.
Like a fan.
It's fun.
You're wearing earphones.
I'll do my best in the rehearsal.
Thank you.
I'm Hiyorin Hiyorin, a member of the
group, and I'm also a member of the
group, Yoshikawa Hiyorin.
Thank you.
thank you!!
I'm Kanon.
I'm Julia.
I'm Hitoka.
I'm Kana.
I'm Naoki.
I'm Kyurin.
So,
Like for real!
We were CHOICE!
We just finished our rehearsal for STAFF
LA FES!
Tokay, everyone, so sa-
It was so much fun.
It was big, wasn't it?
Yeah, it was.
It was so different from our usual
rehearsal.
We can't rehearse tomorrow morning.
We'll do our best for the next
performance.
Let's do our best!
We'll do our best!
The rehearsal for STAFF LA FES is over!
We'll do our best for the next
performance!
See you next time!
Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching.
Please subscribe to my channel!
Translated by Releska