Ebichu Tastasu Broadcast 100 times!
This week's Ebichu Tastasu is a special
program of 100 times!
Super high tension Karaoke battle!
100 times Karaoke
Ebichu Tastasu, start!
Modokashii kanjou kakeru hyaku
This frustrating feeling, I'll multiply
it by 100
Zoro!
Mitou mo nai
I'm so into you that I can't even
breathe
What should I do with my heart that's so
full of you?
Monotrium, Monotrium, Monotrium, Middle
School
Add all kinds of things to private Ebisu
Middle School!
Ebisu Dattaku!
This program is brought to you by the
following sponsors.
Ebichu Tastasu, which started in 2015,
has finally reached 100 episodes.
So, this time as well, we have a special
edition of the 100th episode of the
luxury goods battle.
The winner of the bowling competition
last time was...
Kawashima!
And the winner of the second round
was...
Tomoto Kawashima!
They couldn't get the chance to get the
luxury goods.
Will they get the luxury goods this
time?
The third round starts.
We came to Karaoke Box.
We will have a Karaoke battle for 100
seconds.
This Karaoke battle is a relay.
They sing while turning the microphone.
The person who sings the song first
measures the time.
The member who sings the song in 100
seconds will be eliminated.
The member who sings the song during the
show will be selected.
The person who sings the song and
remains in the end will be eliminated.
Let's choose a song.
Let's look at the ranking.
That's good.
The ranking of the songs during the
show.
Will it be there?
Which song?
I will contribute.
Let's run more.
Let's contribute to the person who sings
the song at the end.
That's good.
I didn't expect that the person would
sing.
The order is the same.
The first person is advantageous.
Let's decide by lottery.
I will start.
This is it.
Stop.
Kashiwagi.
That's good.
The first round is 100 seconds and 200
seconds.
One person will be eliminated.
The battle starts in 100 seconds.
The first person is advantageous.
As expected, even in a place where there
is nothing
It's because it's Hong Jin-young
You sing for a long time
I don't know
Thank you for watching. Please subscribe
to our channel.
I don't want to lose. I can't lose.
I can't lose. I can't lose.
I'm not good at this.
I've sacrificed my day off and my day
off.
I'm going to cry.
Thank you for watching! Please subscribe
to our channel!
We are having a secret sports day!
Even if you have to bow down to us
Let's work together!
We are having a secret sports day!
Please come!
Please sing with us!
We don't want to lose!
La la la la la!
Yes!
Good!
The white-haired host is faster.
No, I'm not.
I'm faster.
White-haired!
Yes!
Keep going!
Just 100 seconds before the line,
Maya is the first one to fall.
And after 100 seconds, another one
falls.
Run more! Run more!
The end!
I'm going to pull the mic.
It's cool if this is out.
I agree.
Because the dream is right there.
I can't finish my dream.
I'm going to run.
I've been crying all this time.
I've noticed.
Friendship Sports Day
Even if you lose now
Believe in the reversal and go forward
Even if you are timid, you will melt in
the autumn sky
I'm not afraid
N Transforming into a Pokeball
Turn off the music
Bye bye!
It's a little creepy.
I'll do it well.
I wanted to sing.
If you let me sing, I'll be Hirota.
By the way, who sang the part now?
No one sang.
Mayama and Yasumoto are eliminated, and
6 people remain.
The two who were eliminated have nothing
to do.
I'm just standing behind you, so I'm not
good at this world.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Please cheer up Ebichu-nee-san.
The rule of the second round is...
4 people will be eliminated every 60
seconds.
And the time for the new member to be
eliminated is...
But if Chuu-ei is eliminated in 60
seconds, she will be eliminated.
Please go with me.
This time, all four of them will be
eliminated at once.
The second round of karaoke battle
starts.
It's pretty good.
Hiroto!
Hiroto, you're doing pretty good.
Thank you.
Turn it around.
The show is starting.
Hiroto, wait.
Thank you for watching!
I love you Kyo-tan!
You guys are the best!
Yeah!
The situation, the situation
I want to call it a school game
But I arrived here
I want to go to the next step
I'll leave it to the adults
If you don't have your own value
Why put it over the issue
If you don't like it, you can't do it
I can't do it
I can't go home until I finish my
homework.
I'm sorry!
I didn't mean to do that!
I want to be a hero!
I have about 8 million eggs
in my stomach every day!
Boom! Boom! Boom! Boom!
Gi-O-P-P-O!
I'm a hero!
I'm going to show you the most exciting
dance.
Kiroppo! Kiroppo!
Don't forget your head!
S.M.X!
M.X.!
Oh yeah!
Power!
B!
What a surprise! 60 seconds!
Unexpectedly, the middle-A out!
With this, one more person will be
eliminated.
Who will be the winner?
I'm so excited!
I'm going to win!
I'm so happy!
Thank you for the food!
This is my...
I'm the boy, Ebichu Terikura!
Thank you for the food!
So...
Hoshina Kobayashi from Makino is out!
No!
I'm out!
Chuuei-san, it's not even related to the
song.
I was shocked when the whistle sounded.
I was shocked too.
And the people who are singing are more
excited than the people who are singing.
They are really standing out.
The second round has ended, and the
remaining members are these three.
The next battle was supposed to be the
final, but Chuuei's unexpected
elimination changed the plan.
Who will advance to the final?
One person will be eliminated in 60
seconds.
The semi-final starts now.
Start!
Thank you for watching!
Only threeogan Kanako
The first round gogogo
Not a well-bared
In the second round rock to rock
You can do nothing
But going further and further
but effort and effort and effort and
Effort
Effort is not betrayed
Hafru
Production
I won't give up!
No matter how tough the road is,
I'll believe in myself and go on!
Nakayama out!
Nakayama was pulling quite a bit.
We're the kings! We're the kings!
We're the kings!
We're going to a fun place.
Welcome!
I'll give you this!
Chie-san, you're like Okamaba.
Stop it!
I'll give you this!
So, the next one is the final round!
What's the song for the final round?
It's SADOWN!
The final round will be Hirota and
Kashiwagi!
They'll battle for the 100-second note!
Who will win?
But before that...
Sakura Ebi's first round!
The research unit Sakura Ebi's is in the
middle of their debut.
They held their 6th one-man live last
month.
This time, it's the biggest live show
ever.
And the youngest, Serizawa Moa, will be
performing for the first time.
What kind of live will it be?
I'm looking for a peach sandals with
glasses and shoes that are beautiful and
beautiful.
Prince, only I can do that, please make
a contract with me.
Make a contract, please make a contract.
K A I K A I
Kali Kali Kali Kali Kali Kali Kali Kali
Kali
K A I Kali Kali
Kali Kali Kali Kali Kali Kali Kali Kali
Wow!
I want to be a princess
But I wonder if the prince will turn
around
I want to be a princess
Who can protect the people
I'm going to be a princess
I want to grow my hair
I want to be a princess
I'm NOT really sure about this city…
24 hours a day without leisure
and a heatwave
I'm drating past myself
with this day
Every morning I'm more energetic
I'm just concerned about tomorrow
I want love essential
I just want to be alone!
Flip the plushies!
Just look at me
Please, prince
Please look at me
A-I-A-I-A
Together
A-I-I-O-I-O
I want to shine
Right here, right now
To a beautiful future
We're connected
Don't give up on your dreams
Don't doubt it
I want to keep running
I believe
Beyond the tears
Beyond the long night
Until the day the morning sun rises
On the way to the end of the dream
We are shining now
The members who finished the live show
I was worried about my physical
strength, but I think I did better than
I thought.
This is the first one-man live show in
2017.
I want to grow more and do my best at
the live show.
Thank you very much for coming.
The next one-man live show will also be
held.
For more information, please visit the
homepage.
After this, the final battle of Karaoke
Battle will begin!
Dance Battle will also begin!
A heated 100-second karaoke battle!
The final round is coming!
The winner is Hirota or Kashiwagi?
I'm the winner!
Hey! You're my classmate, right?
No, I'm your classmate.
Wait, wait, don't be nervous.
I'm the winner!
1st, 2nd, 3rd, 4th, 5th, 6th, 7th,
8th...
9th, 10th, 11th...
I'm not good at it, but this is tough.
10th, 11th, 12th, 13th, 14th, 15th...
I'm going to go with 2 people.
Ai, Ai, Ai, Ai...
You are slow!
Ai Ai Ai, It's 2!.etty!
There's two more places left.
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hang in there!
I have nothing more to say!
Bye-bye!
Ai Ai, if you save me, Ai Ai will become
Venus.
I don't need Venus, I only need my
beloved father.
That's right, we are all cats.
We've come this far together.
Ai Ai, if you save me, Ai Ai will become
Venus.
The winner is Hirota!
That was a good match.
Thank you!
I don't know the names of the losers
anymore.
There are only 2 people left.
The winner of the 100-second karaoke
battle is Hirota Ai.
The winner Hirota will try to get the
luxury goods.
Will she get the luxury goods other than
the towels?
Will she get the miracle 1 million yen
chance?
So, Hirota, where are you aiming?
Everyone is wearing towels, so I want to
get the color.
That's right.
This block is definitely...
If you aim at the block, you can get it.
Please decide quickly.
The fate of Hirota Ai is...
What will happen?
Rock, paper, scissors!
One more time!
Amazing!
They got the annual passports of Tokyo
Doitsumura
Nakayama has one too
Nakayama has one
By the way, did Nakayama go with his
annual passports?
He's sleeping in his backpack
Sleeping in his backpack
Then, you can go with Hiroto
I want to go without sleeping
We've done 100 times commemorative
special twice
Lastly, Nana
See you again!
Ebitu Tastasu, the last two times.
Did your heart hurt?
After that, I saw the dream of getting
along with Nakayama-chan twice.
This program was brought to you by the
sponsor you are watching.
I'm going to use my physical strength
today!
AI! AI! AI! AI!