Ebichu's videos
I'm Hinata Kashiwagi, number 10.
This week's video is about...
Hinata Kashiwagi's way to Nikusomurie!
I'm at a BBQ restaurant in Nikusomurie.
I'm happy.
I'll start with the tongue.
This is the upper part of the tongue.
I'll grill it.
It's been 2 or 3 months since I had this
tongue.
I'll grill it.
It sounds good.
It's done quickly.
I'm a person who likes to grill meat.
I don't like to grill meat on an empty
stomach.
I'll squeeze lemon juice.
I'm grateful that there is no seed.
I'll eat it with a high tension.
I'll eat it.
It's soft.
The taste is elegant.
Wait, the taste of the soy sauce is like
this?
Isn't it amazing?
Next, I'd like to try this one.
I'd like to try this one.
But the difference is definitely...
The sound of grilling meat may have a
healing effect.
I can do it in myself.
Then I'd like to try this one.
Lemon.
I'd like to try this one.
I'm going to make a halami.
This is my favorite halami.
I'm going to make a Japanese beef
halami.
Can you see the difference in meat?
I'm going to put the meat in the pan.
I'm so nervous right now.
I think the best part of yakiniku is the
belly meat.
The tongue and belly meat are the best.
I'll eat it with the sauce.
This is soft.
I didn't know Harami was so good.
It's so soft.
Wagyu Harami.
It's great.
I'll try this Harami.
I can't tell the difference by looking
at it.
Itadakimasu.
I like Kitsuri Yakiniku.
I'll go.
In the past, I was limited to karaoke.
I like to go alone, but I also like to
go with a large number of people.
I like karaoke more than a large number
of people.
I wonder why.
Maybe because I can sing comfortably.
I get nervous in front of everyone.
I'll have a mirror.
I can't tell the difference.
I'll have a look.
I can't tell.
Both are soft.
I can't tell the difference.
This is difficult.
Next, I will go to Sagari.
I don't know anymore.
I will go to Wagyu Sagari.
I have eaten Wagyu before, but I don't
eat it often.
I think it is similar to Harami.
I hope there is a difference in the
taste.
I think there is.
I have already eaten one.
Well, I will eat Wagyu beef.
I will dip it in the sauce.
Let's eat.
This was my first Jack in the box in the
Old Testament.
You're a liar.
It's similar, but...
It's different from Harami, but I don't
know what it is.
Next, I'd like to go down.
I don't know.
I don't know the difference.
I usually go with the members, but I'm
the one who's in charge of the role.
Maya does most of the work.
I'd like to go down.
Let's eat.
It's difficult.
I think the lower part is more fun to
bite.
I can't explain the difference between
the lower part and the upper part.
I'm confused.
Everything is the same.
It's difficult.
Next, I will eat beef ribs.
But, there are 4 kinds of ribs.
I will eat Wagyu beef ribs.
It's melted.
This is amazing.
I was chewing on Wagyu Kalbi without
chewing.
I'm not lying. I was chewing, but it's
gone.
I'm going to eat Jou Kalbi.
It looks a little more oily than Wagyu
Kalbi.
I'm going to eat Jou Kalbi.
It melts quickly and disappears.
Oh, it's different.
It's so different.
I think I had more Japanese beef kalbi.
I'll try the red meat kalbi.
Let's eat.
It's kalbi.
It looks like the Japanese beef kalbi.
It looks like it.
I'll grill it.
It's amazing.
It's fat.
It looks like it's fat.
It looks soft.
I'll eat it.
I think the special kalbi is more fatty.
I don't know.
I don't know what I was thinking.
Next, I'm going to grill the loin.
It looks difficult.
This is the upper loin.
Upper loin and loin.
I'm going to grill the upper loin first.
I'm grilling it.
Oh, it sounds good.
It looks delicious.
Please subscribe to my channel.
It looks like this.
Well, let's eat.
Let's eat.
It's good.
I've been kissing someone who doesn't
look like me.
It's soft, but the texture is good.
But I have to check the difference
between Joe and Rose.
I can't put it in someone else's.
I can tell the difference by looking at
it.
I'd like to wear it with Rose.
I'd like to eat Rose.
It's a little greasy.
I think I can understand.
I can understand if I eat it by looking
at it.
What happens if I eat it without looking
at it?
So, I'm going to eat the loin end.
I'm going to eat the loin end.
It was delicious.
Next, I'm going to grill the hormon.
This is hormon and marucho.
I love marucho.
I'm going to grill it in the hormon.
It takes a little time to grill the
hormon.
I'm going to grill it.
Wow!
Oil!
Looks delicious!
I was told that it looks good.
I'm going to eat it.
I can tell the shape of it.
I was told that it was a tie.
I'm going to eat it.
The marucho is also completely oily.
The form is oily, but the texture is not
only soft, but also chewy.
I think you can understand this.
Next, I will make my favorite marucho.
Delicious.
The shape of the marucho is cute.
The one in the middle is squeezed.
The one on the outside is eaten.
It looks good.
So I'll try it.
It's got sauce on it.
It's definitely going to be thick.
I made a mistake.
Itadakimasu.
It's so fatty and delicious!
It's definitely a marucho.
It's delicious.
You can definitely tell the difference.
It's perfect.