Moeka is quiet.
She's not like Moeka.
If I take Moeka, I'm confident that I
can make her the cutest.
I don't have enough to talk about.
I see.
So I want you to wait.
But the audience looks really
unpleasant.
Mizuki-san is talking all the time, and
she's a little angry.
I've become a gal.
You haven't become a gal.
Oh, really?
If I like flashy things, I'm a gal.
I'm not a gal.
I'm a gal and an idol!
Hello, I'm a member of Viva Home, and
I'm a cute little baby.
Today, we have a special guest.
This is the idol.
I'm Ichika Izuki from Amefurashi. Nice
to meet you.
Ichika, thank you for coming.
Thank you for calling me.
I'm sorry, but you were on the air the
other day.
I'm with you.
We're just the same.
That's right.
November 2nd
How old are you?
I'm 19 years old.
Ichika, you're 19 years old.
I'm not your sister.
I was this small.
I'm a gal.
I'm not a gal.
I'm sure some of you have seen the last
episode.
I didn't admire the gal.
I've been doing what I want to do.
That's right.
I like fashion.
If you like flashy things, you're a gal.
I'm not a gal.
I'm a gal.
That's right.
So, since we're all dressed up like
girls today,
can you show us a girlish pose?
Sure.
Can you introduce yourself in your
current version?
I thought you'd say that.
I don't want to.
Here I go.
I'm Izuki Ichikawa, the cleaning lady of
Ame Flash.
I'm a gal.
Thank you.
I couldn't hold back.
If I could go there, I would take a
picture.
I think it's good, but I've packed
everything I've been trying to do.
Yes, it's all good.
This is good. Yuzu fans are already...
That's right.
They're already excited.
They're happy.
I'm sure.
Yes.
So, thank you for coming today.
Thank you.
I'm not good at that scene.
I'm afraid of that scene every time.
Thank you for watching.