with a bang
Happy New Year!
I'm Bananaman of the JC world.
Thank you for listening. This is Morisaka-chan.
Thank you very much.
What is it?
What's going on?
What are you doing?
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Ready, B!
Yes, that's what I'm talking about, B.
I see. That's how it works.
Himechan, please announce today's project.
Let's look back at the year 2022!
Let's look back on the year 2022!
Last year, we had a lot of news to share with the world.
Nogizaka46
Let's take a look at some of the news that happened to the members of Nogizaka46
Let's take a look at some very small news that happened unnoticed by the public.
First, let's take a look at the Nogizaka B News from January to March
Akimoto, Yaku cap hates me
Umezawa, bananas and wet ice
Kubo's eyebrows are leaking
Endo finds just the right mug
Nakamura, connected when he fell down
Umezawa cries with her dad
That's all for January through March.
I was giving away clothes and stuff like that.
That's what I was doing.
There's no reason for them to hate me.
I don't even use the group email anymore.
So you haven't moved since then.
I haven't used it once.
I should have done it before a concert or something.
I was afraid you'd think I was lying about it.
I gave it away a little bit.
It's just a project, after all.
I'd like to apologize personally to Yakuhat-chan and the others who were at the pinpoint of the project, and I'd like to apologize to them.
I sent them a message saying that I did it because it was part of the project, but that I really wanted to give them the clothes.
I sent her a message saying that I was sorry.
I haven't read it for a few months.
You haven't read it?
Yes, I'm going unread.
I didn't even read it.
Yes, I haven't even read it.
What?
I thought maybe I got lost.
Then, about two months later, I sent an email to Yakuhat-chan for something else.
And she responded.
That's a very long message.
That was January 20th.
Yes.
And the next...
March.
The MC was really good, Yakuhat-chan!
So I sent a message to tell her how great it was.
I got a reply on the same day.
I got a reply.
Please listen to me.
No, of course I'll listen.
Of course I do.
What's this?
I'm the kind of person who accumulates correspondence... from all sorts of people.
I don't even notice them until March.
But you know what?
How many are buried?
I don't know, a hundred or so.
I don't know.
I mean, how many are buried?
I don't see them on line.
They're getting mixed up with all the official coupons.
But... how many coupons do you get?
With all those buried coupons...
I get a lot of coupons.
But Akimoto, you know, he's the captain of Nogizaka, the senior member of Nogizaka.
Coupon and I, Coupon beat me.
He beat me to the coupon thing.
Are there other members who sent in coupons but never got read?
I didn't know that.
In my case, it was recorded.
I don't know how many days it will take to get back to me.
That's perfect... four days.
The town hall's scary.
You're so cool for a guy who calls himself "Saki, Saki, Saki.
That's scary.
Okay, next, Yume...
Bananas and camre...
I was really into Kamure from '21 to '22.
Kamure was really popular, right?
Yes, but I was into it even before it became popular.
I really was.
But there are people who are like that.
When my family says it's good, people say it's a fad.
I don't usually watch it, but when I do, the Japanese national team wins.
It's just like that.
And around June, I think, Bananaman did a radio show.
Bananaman did a radio show called "Kamure Kassen," right?
He said, "Did we really buy that?
June, that's really late!
Yes, we were listening to it, and during the recording.
I gave him a quick recommendation for kamure.
I didn't eat it!
You said that on the recording?
Yes, I did!
Yes, yes, yes...
Why do you say that?
You have to give it to me.
That's right... that's why we prepared it today.
If I'm lying... there was one we recommended.
That's because I've been wanting to interact with you.
I've been wanting to interact with you, too, so now...
This...
This is a kamure only in Hokkaido.
There are no stores in the Kanto region, so I order it from them.
You're ordering it?
Yes, I've been ordering it, and it's my favorite.
I like the pudding-like texture with a crunchy texture and soft inside.
I like the pudding-like texture.
I think it's the ultimate.
I know.
I'll eat it.
It's so good!
You're right... it's pudding inside.
It's pudding inside.
Is it that good?
It's good.
Yeah, it's good.
Oh, it's so crunchy.
It's so good in there.
It's so good.
This is totally different.
It's delicious.
How many packages have you eaten, by the way?
By the way, how many have you eaten this year?
I bet you've eaten a hundred.
Oh, my God.
Really?
That's a lot!
I guess they're getting bigger and bigger.
I'll see you later.
No, no, no, no...
Wait a minute.
Delicious.
Go on, then.
Ugh!
What's this?
I'm doing a morning show this February.
We had to make a video for the survey.
So we had to get some of the members to appear on the show.
Umezawa, Yamashita and I shot the video together.
And the questionnaire was sent in at the last minute.
We sent it in without checking it.
We were using an app to take the video.
What did I do wrong?
In the app's settings...
The eyebrows are set to the darkest setting.
Is there such a thing?
Yes, there is.
I took the photo in that state and sent it without realizing it.
It was broadcast on live TV.
On live TV.
It was broadcast live.
That's scary.
I have some video of it.
I saw it.
It's a little scary.
Both Ume and Yamashita are caught in the fire!
Oh my God!
This got broadcast!
I was watching the live broadcast.
I thought something had happened.
I mean... the manager...
I'm sure they were checking on me.
But the audience and the MC...
I didn't get any comments from the audience or the MCs.
Even the fans didn't comment on it.
We've been doing it all this time.
The three of us are doing it.
They think it's just the latest eyebrows, if that's what it is.
I don't know.
I mean, they're on top of the bangs.
But I don't know... I've had a lot of eyebrow jobs...
I didn't get a lot of eyebrow jobs after this.
It's on top of my eyebrows.
Be careful. - I'll be careful.
I'll be careful.
That's pretty urgent, isn't it?
You're right, it's funny.
Now, on to the end.
I really don't care about this.
What the hell?
I'm sorry.
The year before last, we had a year-end party in Nogizaka.
When Ikuta-san graduated.
At that hotel.
This is the mug I won during the game.
There it is.
I wrote "Ron Ikuta" on it.
Yes, that's right.
I use this.
Wow, it's true.
That's disgusting.
What did you drink?
I drank coffee.
It's pretty easy to use.
Oh, yeah.
You say you love this cup.
How can you make such a cute face with this cup?
But it's kind of nice.
I'm using this one.
But mine...
I don't use the Ikuta one that you wrote.
It's too intimidating.
But you're right-handed, right?
If you hold it with your right hand, you can't see it.
But it's a little intimidating.
Well, well... it's like a god living in the toilet.
Alive and kicking.
When my friends come over, I don't let them out.
No, I don't.
He uses it alone.
Next, this one.
What's this?
That's me.
Last year, me, Kazuki Mukai, and Nawa Yumiki...
Me, Kazuki Mukai, and Nawa Yumiki starred in a drama together.
Something like that?
That's right.
We were filming at school.
I was supposed to join the filming later, but they would get mad at me, so I ran to the set as fast as I could.
So I ran to the set and said good morning.
There was some kind of pit.
I got stuck in one of the pits and got seriously injured.
Wait a minute... what kind of situation is that?
It's not a surprise.
It's a natural pit.
It was Nawa Yumiki, right?
I've been told I look like I work at a construction site.
I don't think so.
Not at all.
Dramas have connections, don't they?
I was in uniform, so my knees are showing.
I didn't know what to do.
But it just so happened that I played a character who was getting dv'd.
Oh!
That's why we connected so well.
I didn't have to hurt him.
That's how we connected.
That's right.
You're all dv'd on your knees.
Knees, knees, knees...
Don't go for the knees, don't go for the knees, don't go for the knees.
It's for the sake of connection.
But in this drama, Hazuki and I both have knee injuries.
And Hazuki got called in by the director.
I didn't want to get mad at her, so I ran towards her.
Then she thought she'd get mad and ran too fast.
I fell down.
And then she came out with a boom.
And then the female supervisor got mad at me.
What the hell kind of move is that?
I told her that it would make the drama unconnected.
I wasn't the one getting dv'd.
What kind of role is that?
What kind of leading lady are you?
Three sisters with dirty knees.
Next...
This one caught my attention.
What's this all about?
I'm close with my family and we often make video calls.
My brother was about to start his freshman year of high school in April.
I congratulated him and wished him good luck.
But now that he's gone, my father and I were talking on the phone.
He started talking about my brother's aging.
He's a really nice guy.
And my dad started saying...
That's amazing.
He's a really good kid.
He said he was a really good kid when he was a little kid.
I was telling him about how he was a really good kid when he was little, and he started acting weird.
His face didn't look so good anymore.
He's so cute.
His face would fall off.
I thought he was crying, and I started crying, too.
We hid it from each other.
But you can hear it in her voice.
I mean, I'd be shaking.
He's a good guy, right?
I heard it from my grandmother.
My grandmother.
You have a grandfather too?
My grandmother told me stories about my brother when he was little.
It's really hot.
You didn't record that?
No.
Why don't you have it on tape?
I'm pretty sure I didn't.
But he was a really nice kid.
He was about four years old.
He was just a friend of mine, so my parents...
We used to spend a lot of time at my grandma's house.
And he was about four years old, and...
When grandma came home from shopping at night
She would usually say, "Welcome home.
A four year old says, "You must be tired, Grandma.
"You must be tired, Grandma.
What can I say?
That's too much of a turn-off for me.
That's just the beginning.
That episode.
She's a good girl.
She's a good kid, but...
But I thought he was pretty straight-laced growing up.
Did you grow up straight?
I'm so happy.
Can you turn off the camera?
Camera burn, please.
Here is the BQ news from April to June
Kuromin is about to become an idol
No, no, no, I am an idol!
I'm going to be the first of the top 3 idols!
What? Who?
The only one who eats Tsutsumi's food.
What? By herself?
He ate the cake with the sugar.
What? That's scary.
Katsushida welcomes you with his whole family.
What? What? What?
It's Abe's morning, like the Ogawa drama.
What?
That's the Nogizaka BQ news from April to June.
Oh, no...
Go to the next one.
Okay.
What, you're not an idol anymore? Kuroomine
What's going on?
Actually, I started college in April.
There was a welcome party for new students.
I'm making an idol group here at the university.
Would you like to join our circle?
Who?
But you see, Kuromi's cute, so she asked me after all.
Is that a thing?
You're not in it, are you?
You're going to do it.
You're going to teach him something.
It's not like that.
No, no, he's gonna do it.
You're not going to go back to being a senior, are you?
I'm fine.
So you got invited?
They invited me. They even sent me a flyer.
I said I'd think about it and left.
But Miyu Matsuo told me to go dance in the center.
What are you going to do?
That's the end of the line.
And then there was this amazing girl.
Nogizaka's not good enough.
I'm going to go into student wrestling.
I'm going to college.
There's one more thing.
There's a photo of me in the student chapter that's gone viral.
What do you mean?
I want to see it.
Wow!
What the hell?
Oh, my God, that's disgusting and scary.
Oh, come on.
What is that?
What is this? This is some kind of skull found and then fleshed out.
This is the kind of thing they do with an app.
That's too much!
The machine tweaked it on its own.
What's wrong with the skin?
It's nothing like that.
I didn't do it myself.
You're right, it's not that different.
The pretty heart on her face is not that thin.
It's a scythe cut, isn't it?
It's funny, but...
You put it in sickle-cutting mode.
Why did you put it in sickle-cutting mode?
Because you put it in sickle-cutting mode.
I told you not to put it in sickle-cutting mode.
That's in the picture, but this is what it looks like.
Try this picture on your passport.
You can't get into any foreign country.
It's true.
Who are you using it for?
Only in the central countries.
Why are you using it?
I like chrome.
Chrome's been great lately.
I want my favorite idol group to be in it.
April is just a chrome?
What, he's in charge of April all by himself?
He's so strong.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry for all the other Aprils.
Go on, then.
Who's this?
What's this about?
Kaki-san published a photo book.
I saw a cover I really liked.
I bought it myself.
Please sign it for me, Kaki-san.
Wow, that's great!
I think I was the first fan to get it.
I see.
Is this it?
What's wrong with his face?
What the hell is this?
We're all in stink-eye mode.
Why are they all in Kamakiri mode?
What's wrong with his face?
I took this from above.
Maybe it's the angle.
You're not in "kamakiri" mode, are you?
Kamakiri mode is all the rage.
It was my first photo book.
You can't be serious.
That's why I bought it.
and said, "I want you to write about it here.
I was really happy that he said that.
But I had never written anything before.
It's really the first one.
The very first?
Seriously?
Please don't do that.
That's amazing.
Do you buy it for yourself in the same group?
Or maybe it's a magazine or a boys' magazine or something.
Granted magazines.
You buy those too?
So maybe he has his own room...
Maybe he has some of those.
But it's really messy.
Too many Nogizaka goods?
Too much.
He also buys boys' magazines.
I asked him to clean it up.
By Ogawa?
Why Ogawa? He's so much younger than me.
It was really messy.
Why do you buy goods?
It's not that I wanted to buy them.
It's more like when I'm walking out of the convenience store.
I'm in.
That's great.
It's like the three of them have an excuse.
I don't want them to come in when they notice.
Now, on to the next one.
This is a bit of a surprise.
I had the whole day off.
I wanted to feel nature.
I went there.
I'm going alone.
I like to go alone.
You don't look like you do.
I see.
I've never been on a trip or anything.
This is my first time.
Then this is where you stayed.
Under 18.
They need a parent.
It's just May.
No.
What are we gonna do?
Eat sashimi.
Shibu.
Shibu
Go to a restaurant with a long line.
Eat wet rice crackers in the shopping street
Saw the ocean and came home.
That's a little bitter.
If I could drink alcohol...
I'd like to drink some of the best sake in the country.
I want to go there.
More in the future.
Would you like to go abroad by yourself?
I'd like to.
That's amazing.
You don't think of it as something where you're not alone.
Not at all.
I've done karaoke by myself.
I often do.
The B-grade news brings up some unexpected places.
The most unexpected is the Black Sea.
Now, on to the next one... I'm afraid of this one.
I'm going to tell you something... during the online storytelling session, during the break, Kaede came to my room with a small piece of cake.
なのを頂いたんですよ
Kaede came to my room to eat it and said she forgot to bring a fork.
I forgot to bring a fork and it was right there, but I didn't want to go get it, so I put a long piece of cake all over the room.
ものを探し始めた
I don't know what I'm going to do.
There was a straw and he said he'd eat it by himself and started eating it.
He's a little crass or rough around the edges.
That's why he spills things.
He drinks miso soup with a straw.
I saw that picture before, didn't I?
That's right.
What do you think you can drink anything with a straw?
I always have a straw by my side.
Nobody does that!
Then keep the self-straw with you!
He seems to break things he buys rather easily.
I went to a Harry Potter store in Akasaka with Mukai once and bought a glass jar.
I thought I'd bake cookies and put them in it.
It's cute and stylish, isn't it?
But when I tried to wash them, I dropped them in the sink, and they turned into a crispy mess that day.
The only thing I dropped was the jar, and the lid was still there.
The lid is still in the house.
I'm amazed you took this picture, there are so many great pictures this time.
I don't know how you take a picture after dropping it.
It's probably loose inside.
When I spilled the caterer's food, I brought it in without cleaning the table.
That's right.
You know what?
Desperation.
It's a good picture.
It's good to see her in such good spirits.
It's normal.
People like this definitely make mistakes in their previous actions.
For example, if someone drops this, a normal person would put it here.
But this person puts it here.
And then the person who doesn't look at this properly and doesn't take it, and takes his eyes off here...
They're doing something.
Oh, pick it up.
And...
No, that's crazy.
What kind of relationship is this?
Oh, I'm gonna drop it before you say it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'll be careful.
Next...
What's this?
Yuna and I spend a lot of time together.
When we're together, she talks about her family.
Asuka-chan said she loves talking about her family, too.
I have no one to talk to but my family.
That makes me sad.
I'm in touch with my family a lot.
I'm in touch with them.
I've always thought they're a very kind family.
I just wanted to go see them.
I said I'd go over to their house after work.
I didn't tell them at all, but they said it was okay.
They made me feel so welcome.
I told them I'd have dinner with them at night, and they served me dinner.
I didn't cook for them, but they served me dinner.
Yuna-chan called her mother and told her I was there.
Even though it was nighttime, my mom, brother and sister came to see me after taking a bath.
What a nice family!
I'm going to make a reservation for the next time.
Make a reservation.
And bring souvenirs.
Yeah, I really didn't bring anything.
That sucks.
As an inconvenience.
I just got it and came back.
Yes, it was.
It was raining pretty hard.
Next time it rains, it'll be like a drama-filled morning at the creek.
What does it say?
It was raining on the way to school, but I forgot my umbrella.
I forgot my umbrella... and as I was walking, I fell down like a picture.
I was walking in the rain, and a nice lady put her umbrella in my hand and said, "I'm okay, too.
I told her I was okay too, but she handed it to me and said, "Don't worry about it.
すよ
That's your black body?
I didn't say that.
What kind of world are you talking about?
And it's a kamakin.
What kind of drama is that?
I tried to track him down, but he was gone.
I don't even have his contact info.
That's right.
I carried an umbrella to school for a week after that.
It's okay if I see him anytime.
I thought I could see him, but I couldn't.
So I thought if I could find her, I'd lend her my umbrella and thank her for her kindness.
That's a good story.
Really?
That's the umbrella you lent me.
That's a real umbrella!
That's right.
He gave you that umbrella?
He said he'd buy one.
That's very kind of him.
I'm sad to say, I was a little lost.
Why?
As a member of Nogizaka, I'm supposed to behave properly.
I made the terrible mistake of forgetting my umbrella.
I want to make more mistakes.
It's okay if you didn't bring an umbrella on a rainy day.
If you saw this...
I'd like to ask you to take this.
I'll take this and we'll get started.
Wow, that's a lot of drama.
There's a wonderful woman here.
I've never gotten an umbrella in the rain.
That's a good story.
I think I'm going to get a permanent spot.
Instant subscribe song.
I'll sing it. Listen to it. Subscribe song.
Subscribe to our channel!