We had a hard time with the money.
I'll say it if I can say it.
When I heard this, the audience was
happy.
Thank you.
I don't do a lot of things in front of
the camera.
I'm a professional.
When I say, the camera is rolling,
I think about what to say.
I'm a long-time actor, so I think about
a lot of things.
I thought there was something to talk
about today.
Today, we have a guest, Ms. Maika Kanji.
Hello.
We're going to talk about the history of
GAMPARE.
Maika, why did you start the audition?
I've seen the live performance of P.O.P.
I was shocked at that time.
I was like, an idol?
I was shocked by the power of the
audition.
Maika's father liked IKKI BISS.
I like P.O.P. from there.
I'm auditioning now.
Thank you for watching.
There are also post-its.
When I got a pass, I was auditioning for
VISS.
I was doing that.
If I got a pass, the auditioners would
be like,
I wonder if I'm going to be a senior.
I'm waiting for this
I'm so excited.
If I was, I would have called.
I would have called and called again.
After you got the job, you were the only
one who left the group.
How did you feel?
I thought it was bad.
Did you think you had to join the group?
No, I didn't think so.
Did you think you were going to be on
the same team?
I didn't think so, but I was like, what
should I do?
I didn't have time to think about that.
I had to learn a lot of things.
I was desperate.
I showed it to the world.
And then...
The incident happened.
Maika joined the group.
And after 4 days,
Kokori Yudoku joined the group.
At that time,
I thought it was impossible for Maika to
join the group.
I thought it was too much.
Saki-chan wasn't like that.
But Miyamiki was like...
It was sad.
I was afraid that people who were in the
audition for Gyanpare would come in.
I thought it was okay.
That's amazing.
What did Yu Yu Yuwa say?
I was commenting a lot.
Sakura.
And nobody said anything about Gyanpare.
That's right.
It was like, who is Gyanpare?
It was a very different experience.
We couldn't do it that much.
That's our responsibility.
It's a lie that I haven't heard the
song.
I just thought that I wasn't that
interested in it.
I was doing it because I was angry, but
I thought about it every time.
Because I didn't remember anyone who
liked the art of art and the art of art.
But I thought that the way people looked
at art was very different from that.
It's very different.
We don't have any secrets that I don't
know yet.
What?
But this is...
People who aren't in this place...
You should say it once.
Before the show...
Before the show, we practiced late at
night.
There were a lot of practices.
After all, it's just practice.
So...
We didn't do much makeup.
When we entered the studio, I thought
there was someone I didn't know.
When I look closely, it's Saki of Suppy.
During the audition,
I was told by Watanabe-san that I was
definitely bad.
I said, that's not true.
I was told that I was bad at drawing.
There was a person who was flowing.
By the way, who is it?
What do you think?
Is it a good interview?
It's zero.
This secret bag is the main subject.
So, the story of this bag is...
I don't need it that much.
So, I was searching for it.
I tried to put something big that I
haven't told you before.
But I couldn't put it on, so I said,
手ごたえずろ.
Wow, that's what you mean.
If I couldn't pull it out, I thought it
was myself.
I'm reflecting on myself.
I'm not talking about Mika.
Next, Yuyu?
I want you to pull out the information
that I haven't told you before.
Money, love, anything.
It's so hard.
What did you think when you said that?
I thought I shouldn't say bad things
about someone.
I thought that was the closest thing.
I thought I was a good person, but I
thought I shouldn't say bad things about
someone.
But I couldn't.
Besides when I got into an interview.
I can't do interviews.
I can't hear you, I pretend to be dumb
and give up
I can't see the future, I can see it, I
pretend to understand it