Ebitune's videos
I think the family is different.
Because we are a strong group with
strong members,
the type of fans is different.
Each person has a different impression.
I think it's different.
At the handshake event,
I talk to people who say,
I'm wearing a hat, but I'm wearing it.
It's different from the atmosphere of
the person who supports me.
It's fun to talk to people like that.
It's totally different.
I don't know if it's like a fan.
It's like a Louis Tom.
It's good to be in the back.
Each person is close.
For example,
There was an event.
We didn't go up to the stage.
When we were just standing,
We didn't say anything from the front.
Everyone was sitting down so that the
audience could see us.
It's really kind.
The kindness of a person is amazing.
As a person,
Everyone is really nice.
It's a good person.
It's a great place to be.
I've never thought I was scared.
That's true.
Everyone is amazing.
For example,
I don't have one now,
but when I was a kid,
I went to the live show on the train
and went back to the train.
Even at that time,
I was like,
It was fun.
Everyone really knows.
I understand that they care about me.
They are so kind that I feel like I'm
going to faint.
That's true.
It's hard.
I think it's the most difficult thing.
The most difficult thing is the
formation.
Formation is really difficult.
That's the most difficult thing.
I wasn't good at singing and dancing.
I was too different from when I entered
the level.
I have to do my best to get used to it.
I think the kids who enter the level
will think so.
I remember the first time I sang and
danced.
Suddenly my brain is over-stimulating.
I might go somewhere.
Everyone had that.
When we don't know what to do, we enter
the room of the members.
Cry.
Cry together.
Once, let's cry.
Only six people enter the room and close
the door.
Cry together.
Sometimes we cry.
But we can share the difficulties with
each other.
We share the difficulties.
We have to do it.
But the sense of accomplishment after
that is amazing.
I feel the sense of accomplishment and
cry again.
If you enter the level, you will think
that everything is difficult.
But we are there.
It's fun to think that it's hard.
There are many fun things.
Don't give up.
If you think it's impossible once, it
becomes impossible.
It's okay to do it little by little.
If you have any problems, let us know.
We are not afraid.
Let us know.
I want you to help us a lot.
The new member audition is on February
28th, 23.59.
I will call on everyone to the first
audition.
Some people like Ebichu.
Some people are interested in this kind
of job.
I would be happy if there were many
people.
Anyway, we are more and more Ebichu.
We are looking for people who can grow
together as Ebichu.
There are many fun things.
The atmosphere of the members is calm.
I want to work with people who can move
forward with a calm feeling.
I look forward to your application.
There are few teams with such warm
people.
I love everyone.
It depends on the person.
I think we will like people.
It's a warm atmosphere.
There are many things to do.
We are all here to do our best together.
I can't do it now, but I'm looking
forward to the new member and the plane.
Yes, well...
Hello!
We are recruiting new members for the
first time.
We are also very excited, but the person
who applies is the most excited.
But I think there are a lot of fun
things waiting for us.
We are doing various things other than
live performances, but we are full of
fun things.
I want you to go on an adventure with us
in this new world.
Let's have fun!
If you become a new member, we would
like you to rely on us anytime.
We have experienced various things, and
we know various things.
I will be a person who can rely on
everyone.
If you want to be on stage, please apply
for this audition.
We are waiting for you!
Come here!
Do you suddenly want to go on stage?
I was suddenly called by the director.
I was not originally in the 3rd
department of the entertainment
industry, but in the 4th department of
the entertainment industry.
I was called by the director.
I was introduced to the director.
I was told to sing.
I was told that I would be able to play
because I was doing an event with Uchiyu
and Momokuro.
I was not sure, but I decided to go.
A few weeks later, I was told that I
would be able to enter the entertainment
industry.
I took lessons and became a new member.
I was told that I would be added 50%.
I was told that I would be added 10
people.
I was called to the new member
development department.
I was called by the director.
I was asked if I was interested in the
idol group called Seeds Ebichu.
I was not interested at all at that
time.
I decided to go to the live show.
I was the 12th person.
I saw everyone celebrating with tomato
cake at Ayaka's birthday party.
I thought it would be fun.
I didn't join the party.
I was standing next to Rina.
I didn't know who you were.
I didn't know when I first went.
I shook hands with everyone.
I was told that I would be added next
time.
I didn't know.
I think the fans know it better.
Seeds Ebichu was a group that I didn't
know.
I didn't know the members.
I didn't know the tasks I was given.
I thought I had to do it.
I don't know now.
The early stages of Stardust are like
that.
It was shocking.
But now it's different.
From there, we made our major debut.
Kaho Riko joined the group.
Kaho, we looked like a normal group.
When I joined the agency, I looked at
the homepage.
I was wondering who the idol was.
Monocoro appeared.
I didn't know that the members of the
group were called Ebichu.
I was watching the video.
I was wondering if it was Ebichu.
I was wondering if I was included in the
group.
My mother was more cool than me.
It's a good thing, so don't do it.
I was very anxious when I joined the
group.
I was anxious to join.
I was sure to be pulled.
We were also pulled to join.
I thought I could do it because I was in
the group.
I thought it was a very comfortable
group.
I'm glad.
I'm glad everyone accepted me.
Ebichu is very cooperative.
That's right.
I've been through a lot of things.
I think we're a cooperative group.
Of course, we have a lot of fun when
we're doing a live show.
Even if we have a problem, we cover it
together.
We had a lot of fun doing a live show.
We had a lot of lessons before the tour.
When I first joined the group, I was
surprised by Kaoriko.
I was surprised.
I didn't know you were doing this much.
I think all idols are like that.
It's amazing to do something in front of
people.
Of course, there are things that we have
to make one by one.
It's fun to perform.
Of course, we work hard and have a hard
time.
I hope you can enjoy the fun of
performing in front of people.