Please select a card.
Immائепit
Extermination
Regeneration
I'm the one who imitates the others,
right?
The final episode of the I'm the one who
imitates the others tournament
The 4th episode of this week's show
Who will be the winner?
Let's start with these 4 people
First is this person, come on in
I'm talking, but my eyes never meet. I'm
Ikeada Teresa.
I can already tell.
Oh, good morning, Teresa-chan.
Good morning, Manatsu-san.
You were doing your best at the live.
Oh, it's similar.
That's not true. Thank you very much.
Manatsu-san is cute.
That's not true. Teresa-chan is also
cute.
That's not true.
It's amazing.
It's similar.
It's very similar.
Ikeada is said to have great eyes.
Ikeada certainly doesn't have good eyes.
Let's continue.
Telsa Ikeda, who is obsessed with
Aishatsu.
Again, Ikeda.
Ah, good morning.
A bento again.
Thank you for your hard work.
She is so shy.
Please bring a lot of Aishatsu.
Good morning.
She looks sleepy.
She is not sleeping.
I'm embarrassed.
Are your eyes bad?
My eyes are not bad.
My eyes are dry.
That's why your eyes are bad.
There are people who have such eyes.
Honda Tsubasa has such eyes.
Does she have such eyes?
Yes.
I have such eyes.
You are always like that.
I'm honored.
You are honored.
You are always like that.
I'm honored.
I'm Haruka Kuromi, who is blowing a
senior wind on a
day.
How are you doing?
How are you doing recently?
I'm nervous for the first time.
But I was good at dancing a while ago.
Kuromi is like this.
Thank you.
I'm getting tired of it.
Kuromi is amazing.
How are you doing recently?
I'm embarrassed.
Let's continue.
The power of her eyes is too strong, she
is more attractive than when she was
singing.
What is that?
She's putting on makeup.
Amazing.
She's writing it down.
She's doing it.
She's starting to put on makeup.
I'm scared.
What is it?
She's starting to do it.
She's starting to put on makeup.
Let's start with Kubo.
She's been following the characteristics
of Ikeda.
She's kind.
She's always greeting me.
But I can't look her in the eye.
I'm frustrated and I go to her.
I go to her, but I can't look her in the
eye.
You're being treated.
That's right.
That's why she's always bowing to me.
That's the same for Akimoto.
She's very polite.
She greets me every time we pass by.
She greets me 10 times a day.
It's okay if she says, thank you for
your hard work.
But she suddenly says, good morning in
the middle of the day.
I don't understand that.
She's being reset.
She's being remembered.
She said it in two days.
That's why she says, good morning.
She's attached to my body.
I'm like that at the gym.
I always say, good morning.
When I was getting ready for the makeup,
I was fixing my hair with a towel.
She came into the mirror from behind and
said, good morning.
I thought she would do that to me.
That's interesting.
IKEDA is dangerous.
And Kuromi is dangerous.
IKEDA Kuromi Zone.
IKEDA Kuromi Zone is dangerous.
IKEDA Kuromi is dangerous.
I walk like this with my heels.
I always carry my cell phone with me.
Is that so?
I really walk like this.
I met Kuromi on the street before the
show.
We were far apart.
She recognized me and ran to me.
Kuromi is a GANIMATA.
I said, good morning.
She is a GANIMATA.
I always walk like this with my heels.
I put my hands on my shoulders and pat
my hands.
I put my hands on my hips.
What is the word for Kuromi?
She said, how are you doing?
She said that in a polite way.
I think there are many people like that.
I think all the people are like that.
All the people are like that.
I think there are many people like that.
Why are you saying that everyone is like
that?
I don't know how to talk to them.
It's okay as it is.
It's okay.
Kuromi is like that.
It's okay because you've already been
given the order.
But Kuromi is not just a 5th generation.
What are you?
Who are you?
Don't talk normally.
I also have a lot of senior wind.
I have a habit of singing together at
the live show.
I thought I was with Kuromi.
I thought I was going to go, but Kuromi
was like this.
That's right.
I'm sorry.
I thought it was a little weird.
That's probably the kind of personality.
It's called a sister-like skin.
I hate it.
You shouldn't stop this.
You shouldn't stop.
It's natural to stop.
If you don't, everyone, staff, let's go
drinking.
Kuromi, let's go.
Let's go.
What?
Well, let's go.
No, it's okay.
Hey, Kuromi, do it.
Kuromi.
Do it.
You're not good at it.
I can't beat Kuromi's eye power.
I see.
You have great eye power.
So please let me draw it.
I see.
This area is a bad zone.
It's bad.
It's good.
New character imitation competition.
Next is this.
First of all, this person.
I don't want to stay in the room below.
What is this? What's the situation?
It's so cute.
I see.
I'm taking it, but it's a breakup.
This is terrible.
She is simply bad at sleeping.
After all tuna is a medium fatty.
She started to talk.
She is noisy.
I see.
I can't do it unless I hold something.
Next.
Inoue Nagi, who can't take off the seat
belt of the airplane forever and is
about to die.
It's like a moving scene.
I just don't know this.
That's right.
This is bad.
Everyone's going to get off.
Oh no.
It's impossible.
You can't get off.
I thought I was going to teach you
something.
Inoue, are you okay?
I'll take it off for you.
Oh, you're putting it in the right
place.
It's a perfect match for the film.
So cute.
I see.
So this really happened.
Asuka took it for me.
That's why.
What? I can't take it off at all.
It's a cute episode.
Let's continue.
The role of a person who laughs in a
unique way and eventually gets ready.
What do you mean by getting ready?
Hey, I just saw Kuromi.
She waved her hand at me when I was
passing by.
She's bad.
Oh, stop it.
I'm finally going to be a senior again.
I'm going to run away.
Bye bye, see you later.
You're a coward.
Oh my god.
It's fixed.
Why is it fixed?
Why is it fixed in that flow?
What does it mean?
It's fixed.
Kuromi was laughed at again.
It seems that Kuromi was there.
Let's continue.
Mayu Tamura who is too much even when
she is in the mic test.
She is a return.
I'm going to do a mic test, so please
come here.
I'm Manatsu Akimoto.
I'm Manatsu Akimoto. Nice to meet you.
Kubo-san, please come here.
I'm Shiori Kubo. Nice to meet you.
I'm Kubo. Nice to meet you.
Next, Tamura-san, please come here.
I'm Mayu Tamura. Nice to meet you.
They are similar.
When a mother calls the house, she makes
a voice.
It's a voice that goes out.
That's true.
What is the story of the time when you
stayed at Ichinoseki?
Both of them are from the countryside,
so they often stayed in the same hotel.
When you got a job.
I slept with Mao and slept on the first
floor.
You have a bad sleeping habit.
I hugged him, but he was stiffened and I
couldn't breathe.
I was so uncomfortable that I was in a
state of shock.
This is dangerous. You may kill him
before you know it.
He was kind to me, so I didn't tell him
directly.
But he was in a bad situation.
That's right.
Next, Asuka.
I was watching him for about three
minutes.
Did you watch him for three minutes?
I watched him from the side.
That's why I didn't tell him directly.
You didn't tell him directly.
You wanted to do something by yourself.
I was embarrassed.
Everyone was watching the video and
reading the book.
I thought I couldn't shoot it alone.
You don't like it.
But it's an experience.
Next, Hayashi.
I'm doing it.
You are a demon.
You laugh and clap your hands.
You laughed and said, ATA.
I call you ATA.
I'm a lady.
We are all ladies.
There is no one else but a lady.
I call you ATA with affection.
Next, Kaki.
I think you are similar to TAMURA.
I am not careful even when I am with the
staff of the microphone test.
I turn on the microphone.
I think he is a professional.
He is a professional.
You are a professional.
Are you making a voice?
My voice changes.
I don't know which is my real name.
You are a professional.
Your voice is similar.
Is there anyone who can imitate TAMURA?
Other people can imitate TAMURA.
I often imitate TAMURA.
You can imitate AKIMOTO.
You can imitate KUBOMO.
They are imitating TAMURA.
They are playing the game of who is the
real.
Please think with them.
Please do not imitate TAMURA.
I'm TAMURA.
I don't know this.
TAMURA is delicious.
I'm TAMURA.
Please subscribe to my channel.
What?
Yes.
This is not the order of the game.
I changed it.
I thought I would understand it
immediately, but I don't understand it.
I thought it was delicious, but I
thought it was the main character.
I thought it was number 3.
I thought it was delicious, but I also
thought it was number 3.
That's right.
I understand.
But it was number 3 that looked like an
imitation.
I did it.
He imitated it.
We can do this, too.
Let's play the video.
I'm Mayu Tamura.
You can do it.
You did it.
You played a prank and ran away.
Everyone was very similar.
You can do it.
Next is Makiko Tanaka.
Finally, the last block of this
tournament.
What kind of trick will jump out?
Please watch the first video.
In her teens, she was a very loud
speaker.
Recently, she is a very loud speaker.
First, she is a very old person.
Ms.Ito, can I ask your enthusiasm for
this stage?
This work is very popular among fans.
I like this work very much.
Please give me a good point.
Excuse me.
And lately, I'm a cat, Riria Ito.
The summer national tour is coming to an
end, what kind of appeal do you want to
make to your fans?
I would be happy if you could see it
without missing a moment.
Ah, sorry.
I see.
You put it in.
I do.
I'm a professional.
You're a professional.
Let's continue.
Go ahead.
Ayane Suzuki is too fast to come on the
road.
I'm sorry.
It's fast.
Is that so?
How did you do that?
It's not really that fast.
It's not fast.
Why is it so fast?
Let's continue.
Hayashi Luna who brings too much food to
the Shinkansen.
Now, I would like to introduce today's
products.
Thank you.
First, fried rice with fish.
Fried rice with fish?
And today's rice ball is plum miso.
Plum miso?
And steamed bread that I recently
bought.
What?
And salad.
And grapes for fruits.
This is a product of eyes.
It's a dumpling that I baked this
morning.
Now, I would like to eat it.
No way.
You bring so much food.
You were talking faster than now.
You are good.
You are good at talking.
I can talk fast.
You can talk fast.
Nakamura.
Yes.
You put food in your mouth when you eat
alone.
I usually put food in my mouth.
I say, meow.
You say that.
Do you know what I say?
I get a lot of food in my mouth.
You put a lot of food in your mouth.
I think it's good.
AKIMOTO.
Yes.
Ayane is in the center of this song.
Ayane's face and hands are in the last
cut.
Other people are like this.
Ayane is shaking three times as fast.
I am aware of that.
The last part is usually a pose.
This is a moving choreography.
There is a time until the next song.
I try to make the time go faster.
How fast is everyone?
This is completely different.
It's okay if the next person says
something.
This is like a fast movement.
I see.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm careful.
I see.
It's okay.
KITAGAWA.
No matter how fast the meeting is, there
is a lot of food on the table.
This is a big movement.
This is handmade.
This is a dumpling.
I was surprised by the dumpling.
I wrapped it in aluminum foil and ate
it.
You didn't take it off.
I thought it was wild.
Do you bring a lot of food?
He introduced me to food.
I will introduce you to food today.
Have you ever received food?
I have never received food.
Why don't you ask me to eat?
I have never wanted food.
That's true.
After this, the ultimate food is born.
This is amazing.
This is the last song.
I don't know what she is saying but I
think she is saying something important,
Manager Motohashi
I don't know what she is saying but I
think she is saying something important,
Manager Motohashi
Oh my god!
We are so embarrassed.
Everyone knows it, but we don't.
2 points.
Everyone is so embarrassed.
We don't know it, and the viewers don't
know it either.
The manager.
The manager is the one who has been
working with us for a long time.
He has a loud voice and can hear even
the nearest station.
He is full of energy.
But I don't know what he is saying.
Is that Cantonese?
Please subscribe to our channel.
Who is it?
Is Asuka similar to this?
Very similar.
I want to see it again.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't know anything.
Is it really a success?
Everyone was shocked.
The reception was the best.
This is Uchiha.
This is the most popular story in the
past.
This story was chosen from 40 famous
stories.
This is the fourth time.
This is the story of the person who is a
senior.
Thank you.
You did it, Hayashi.
I did it with all my heart. I'm glad I
did it behind the scene.
Kuromi, you did it.
Hayashi won the award for impersonating
Kuromi.
Thank you.
Thank you for your seniority.
You found a new fun in Kuromi.
You showed it to us.
I'll watch the award show again.
Are you sure?
Let's see Hayashi's winning
impersonation again.
Kuromi Haruka is making a senior wind
blow to the national team.
Good job.
How are you doing?
I'm very nervous.
But you were good earlier.
I'll watch you.
Thank you.
Good job.
She did it.
She doesn't do this.
She does this pose.
She does it.
She is not a coach.
I'm doing this.
It's good.
You have a new wind.
WADA is a graduate.
I'm sad.
You were the funniest person on the
show.
You were funny.
I was satisfied with the last showdown.
I felt that.
You wanted to win the championship.
I wanted to win the championship.
I was happy.
You were funny.
I'm glad.
WADA was able to win the championship.
You are a junior.
I think so.
Thank you.
You are still young.
You are the same birthday as me.
I was happy.
You are the same age as me.
I see.
What do you think of the show?
I was only being repaired at school.
I was given a lot of attention.
I was able to live in a world where I
could live.
You made a mistake.
You are funny.
You are talented.
You were loved by everyone.
You were not just fun.
What do you think of the show?
I was less than everyone.
I was worried that I could repay the
fans.
I was happy to hear the words like,
congratulations on your graduation.
thank you for working hard for 10 years.
You are amazing.
Please send a message to the fans who
watched the show.
I didn't do much idol-like things.
I enjoyed being myself.
I hope this message will reach everyone.
Thank you very much.
The show will be a little longer.
Until December 4th.
Congratulations on your graduation.
Thank you very much.
Congratulations.
I am happy.
A special video of the things not here
is decided.
The first time I've done this.
Please subscribe to my channel, like it,
and comment on it.
I can't do this.
This is the first time I've done this.
Can I try it again?
I can't do it, so I'll do the last one.
I don't need the second time.