Next news is this!
This week's Ebichu Tastas will be the
10th episode of Tastas!
Matsuno will be performing a new song!
And a new member will be joining!
And also!
The person who will be with Nakayama!
Ebichu Tastas, start!
Tell us about your favorite anime and
your favorite ara
I'm so into you that I can't stop
What should I do with my heart of
jubilee?
Monotrium, monotrium, monotrium
Middle school students, monotrium
Add various things to private Ebisu
middle school
Middle school students
Ebisu Chassaku!
This is a song dedicated to Jasmine.
This program is brought to you by the
following sponsors.
One, two, three, clap, wear it, rock,
paper, scissors!
The 10th Annual Ebichu Tastas News
Last week we introduced 4 news
And tonight all the news will be
released
Who will shine in the Grand Prix?
The next 10th news is this
Ta-da!
Thank you!
Kirara-chan's birth father is Takiue!
Don't drop it!
On this September's show, everyone
thought of the name for Takiue's baby
Here it is!
Dora-ko
Miku-chan
What is that?
Among the many candidates, Takiue chose
Kirara-chan as her last name
But it's not Kirara-chan
Why?
Because you chose her on this show
I chose Elena
She was born on September 28th
I looked it up and it was the same as
Okarina from the Okazu Club
Amazing!
It's a bit complicated
So it's a beautiful girl
I don't know what that means
But her face is becoming more human-like
When she grows up, I want to put her in
the shrimp tank
Why do you want to put her in the tank?
I don't know but I want to make it easy
for her to get in
You're trying to use your power as an
adult
If I put her in, she'll be a heavyweight
by then
She'll be over 30
You'll be like, ok ok
To be continued
I finally did it
Ebichu Tastasu's 10 big news
Next is
Next big news is this
Welcome!
The young and miraculous Nakayama and
Sano manager!
A year and a half ago,
they had a part-time job interview at a
cafe.
They used the cafe's name that the
members came up with
to practice being a customer.
Welcome to Smile Cafe!
That's all for the interview.
Thank you!
Due to this interview,
the relationship between Nakayama and
Sano manager is in a bad state.
Wait, everyone is coming one by one.
No!
What's wrong?
Nakayama, what's wrong?
I don't want to be alone!
But as time passed,
they became closer and closer.
They had a miraculous reunion.
How is your trauma?
I don't have any more from my memory.
You shouldn't erase your memory.
You should acknowledge his existence.
You had a reunion.
Yes, you had a reunion.
There is no point in shaking hands.
You should get along with him.
He is here.
Welcome, Mr. Taro.
You lost weight.
You are thin.
Mr. Taro lost weight.
Long time no see.
Nice to meet you.
Mr. Taro is angry today.
You are just like this normally.
That's right.
Mr. Nakayama, I want you to get along
with him.
Let's play a game.
A game?
Yes, a game.
For example,
Let's play a game of rock-paper-
scissors.
I want to play.
You want to play.
They will play a game of rock-paper-
scissors to prove their friendship.
Are you two okay with the rules?
I have never played a game.
You haven't?
No.
You haven't, right?
Have you ever played a game with him?
I have played a game with him many
times.
You have played a game with him many
You are okay with the rules, right?
By the way, Mr. Masano.
Let's play a game of rock-paper-
scissors.
The winner will hit the opponent with
this.
The loser will block the opponent with
If you hit the opponent before he puts
on the mask, you lose.
I understand.
Now that the manager has understood the
rules, let's have a match!
Let's start!
Rock, paper, scissors!
You don't know the rules of the game!
It's your first time!
Where did you put that?
Sorry, I forgot to say it
Rock, paper, scissors!
Let's go!
It's a tie!
Here you go.
What?
It was unexpected
I thought I won
It's surprisingly difficult
Let's go
1, 2, 3
Rock, paper, scissors
You're the winner
Don't move
Why are you sitting?
The manager of Sano didn't want to fight
for the first time.
But the manager gave him a suggestion.
Can I play with Matsuno?
Why me?
What?
Do you want to be friends with Matsuno?
Why?
This is the first time that Sano has
shown his will.
The manager of Sano wants Matsuno to
stand up.
So he will play rock-paper-scissors with
Matsuno.
I can't stand up.
Do you want to stand up?
I will play.
Rock-paper-scissors.
I can't stand up.
You can't run away.
I can't run away.
What are you doing?
You are very serious.
The game is exciting.
Let's shake hands.
I'm glad.
Ebichu Tastasu is serious.
Next.
The next news is this!
Hirota has won the second round and is
the best cook!
This September, at the Ebichu Unbameshi
Championship,
Hirota won the best cook award by
winning the baby's heart.
In addition, in the cooking competition,
Hirota made a toast sandwich full of
originality.
The first to shine in the Ebichu Dish
King Tournament is...
Hirota!
Four belling warriors mastered their
second month in a row!
Hirota is going to cook for us
It's time to get hungry
I'm sure some of us are hungry
The sound of the stomach is very loud
around Mayama
Let's eat together!
Hirota has prepared a special dish for
this special day.
Are you ready?
Yes, Nakayama-chan, please prepare it.
What kind of restaurant is that?
It's a perfect distance.
I've brought it.
Please eat.
You're wearing an apron.
It's a bit messy.
Hirota's Sweet Potato Tart
Did you make this?
Yes
Wow
At home?
Yes
Do you make this often?
Yes, but I'm a little worried
About what?
I always eat what I can make
But I've been traveling a lot with this
You've been traveling a lot
You might be a little tired
I'm worried
It smells good
Let's eat
Rirota made this at home for everyone
How does it taste?
It's good
It's really good
The hardness of the tart is just right
It's too hard
It's the hardness you like
It's not too hard
Yes
You should open a shop
It's really good
It will sell
Thank you
It's good
How about Matsuno?
I'm glad
Matsuno is the best
It's good
By the way, what do you want to make
next?
I always make what I want to make
What did you make recently?
Quiche
It looks good
Quiche?
What is Quiche?
It's a tart with gratin inside
It's like a quiche between an egg and
gratin
It's like a cake and rice
Do you know Yasunoto?
I know
They enjoyed the great tart of Hirota,
the chef
Nakayama, let's go home
It's already a big party
Thank you
Be careful
The worst thing is the role-playing
party
Sano-san, bye-bye
Bye-bye
Ebichu Tastas' big news
Next is
The next news is
What is it?
Bye-bye
Start the writing project!
Matsuno's talent is blooming!
Bye-bye!
Pink carpet, fluffy, fluffy
I feel fluffy, weightless
I didn't expect you to compose a song
I was surprised
Furthermore
It's a very unique melody
Ramen, ramen
It's in there, isn't it?
Kon-kon-kon
It's good
Ramen, ramen
With a songwriting project
He has created many songs
Do you get emotional?
I do when I'm in a good mood
For example, you recently bought a dog
What's the name?
Jasmine
A song dedicated to Jasmine
You can express your feelings better
with your favorite things
Jasmine is really cute
Isn't she cute?
I feel her cuteness
So, they made a song dedicated to
Jasmine
What kind of songs will be created?
Let's sing a song for Matsuno
A song for Jasmine
Go ahead!
It's a bit like a nursery rhyme
The last part is electric lingo
What? You smell your head from behind?
I smell my head and feel my hair around
here
Do you eat your hair?
I eat my hair and pull it back so I say
stop!
You're just going to keep on doing that?
I'm Jasmine!
Who are you?
I'm not talking!
I hope your talent for writing lyrics
will be used in writing songs
But you've already finished one song
So you might be able to sing that one
somewhere
I've already forgotten it
You've already forgotten?
That's not true!
It's a song for important Jasmine
Can you sing it again?
That's not it!
It's different from the first note
Ebichu Tastasu's important news
Next
Let's move on to the next news
The next news is...
This!
Finally, Ebichu and Ogataka Iki are
performing live!
After this, KIA and Ogataka Iki will
appear!
Ochanoban Rockstar KIA Ogataka Iki!
Next news is here!
Finally the live show of Ebichu and
Ogataka Iki is happening!
This year's July live show, Hia, who is
in charge of Ebichu and Ogataka, finally
has a chance to perform for the first
time
Here is the legendary stage!
I'm a little shy
I'm not a virtual girl
Monotorial
Thank you for watching!
We are the middle school students of
Toriumu!
Today, we have a special guest, Kaiki
Ogata!
Welcome, Kaiki Ogata!
How was it performing with Kaiki?
It was fun!
It looked fun!
The costumes were well balanced
The atmosphere was good
I said that just now
Why did you say the same thing?
The commenters too
At first, there was a donut
I was just standing on it and singing
I went to the rehearsal and I was in the
middle of the shrimp
Did you decide on the day?
I was told on the day
Why did you dance?
After the rehearsal, I watched the video
I watched it all the time
You remembered the day?
I remembered the day
You remembered the day so you made a
mistake
Yes
Everyone was flying
The collaboration with the shrimp was
good
Kaiki, you've been enjoying the
collaboration
Actually, Tatsu and the staff went to
the HIA! concert
I found something that I was curious
about
What did the staff find at the HIA!
concert?
Can you show us, Chuu?
This is...
What is this?
List band
This is Ebichu's...
Mayama?
Not Ebichu, this is HIA!
This is HIA!
It looks like it!
Ebichu's is...
This!
It looks like it!
The characters on the back look like it
There are many different colors of
purple, but they all look the same
Look closely
Takiyo, please
This is a bit complicated
HIA's goods are almost the same as
Ebichu's goods
And...
If only one color is right, it can't be
helped
How is it, Ebichu?
I want to see the orange one
It says it's there
If you look at the goods introduction
page, there are 5 colors
New games are also available! What is
this?
How many people were in the team?
4 people
4 people and 5 teams? That's weird!
There was a support bassist
You saw the costumes from the
collaboration right?
The members had different colors
Everyone was in Ebichu
There was one in Hia too
When did you get the image color?
Half a year ago
Half a year ago?
That's really recent
It's just that I stopped appearing in
TASTA
You said you like Ebichu so you got the
image color right?
It's just now
I will not do it again
Just for today
You got it right?
I just got it
I want to admit it
That's all
Ebichu TASTASU's big news
Next
Let's get back to the next news
The next news is this!
Shizu! Ebichu TASTASU's 7th season has
started!
The Kameido walk was broadcasted in
October
TASTASU has started the 7th season!
By the way, we've done a lot together.
Do you have any memorable scenes?
The sports day.
Mr. Akiyama appears a lot after that.
TASTASU is like Mr. Akiyama or Mr.
Ogata.
I love that sports day.
I went to pick up Mr. Akiyama.
I was just passing by.
I can't forget Mr. Akiyama's face at
that moment.
I was like this.
He was like that.
It was fun.
I've been buying a lot of things for
him.
Did you buy a doll?
Yes.
I'm used to buying things for him.
I can't take a video of him.
I have to pay for it.
You were buying things for him because
he took a video of you.
I see.
We've done a lot.
We have a happy announcement.
Please show us.
What is the happy announcement?
Please pull it
Here you go
Here I go
Shuku's 8th season has started!
The 8th season has just started!
So, Nicchoku Kashiwagi, please tell us
how you feel about the 8th season.
How I feel?
Because it's the 8th season.
Let's have fun together!
The 8th season has just started and all
the important news have been revealed.
The Grand Prix will be decided from
this!
This is pretty big though.
Well, if it's this, Kaiki will be the
winner.
But the content was really good.
It was fun.
The best one among me is the band
Respect Problem.
So, I think I'm the best among them.
So, Ebichu and Kaiki Ogata's live
performance will be decided in this
year's Grand Prix.
The members of Ebichu who were shining
in the Grand Prix will receive a
luxurious gift.
Mayuma-san, please represent us.
Can I?
Of course.
Please represent Ebichu.
Yay!
Here I go.
What's wrong?
What's in it?
It's a really cute wristband.
It's a HiAri wristband!
It's cute!
Since we're here, why don't you try on
each member's color?
Oh, yeah!
Since we're here
For those who want to try on the
member's color wristband
So everyone put it on right?
Yes
Show us
It looks good on you
It suits you
But be careful, if you start making
green, blue and light blue, it will be a
mess
Next year is the 8th season
Please support Ebichu Tastasou
Next year's last Tastasou is
Rika Mayama's birthday solo live special
Let's do our best together at 20!
Deliver the live that was held on the
same day as her 20th birthday
Mayama's solo live
This program was brought to you by the
following sponsors
I don't know.