We are Ebichu Tastas!
This time we are here at Fuji TV One-Gun
Studio!
It's been a year since we started this
program.
Hello, we are the shooting star, Daki-O!
We are the best! The best! The best!
Anarchy!
We are the best!
So, you are happy, right?
Yes, we are happy!
We moved to the new studio on Wednesday,
so I think many of you have never seen
the show.
That's right.
So, I'd like you to know what kind of
show is Ebichu Tastas.
We will show you the famous Tastas show
that even the first-time viewers can
enjoy.
Wow!
Don't lie!
It's a lie.
It's like a TV shopping show.
We have to get new viewers here.
Let's get it!
So, Ebichu Tastas moved to the new
studio on Wednesday and entered the
second year.
This time, we will show you the famous
scenes of Ebichu members' choice of the
Eri-Suguri.
In addition, a rare live video was also
released to commemorate the first
anniversary of the program.
The first anniversary of the program,
Ebichu Tastas, begins!
Chuu!
What should I do with the heart of a
chuu?
Moratorium!
Junior high school student!
Let's add a lot of things to your
private Ebisu junior high school!
Ebisu Justice!
This program is brought to you by these
sponsors.
Ebichu Tastas is an experimental variety
show where you can add various things to
your private Ebisu junior high school.
The show is brought to you by the idol
group, private Ebisu junior high school,
also known as Ebichu.
Ebichu is an 8 year old group of 17
years old who have always had the
concept of being middle school students.
At the end of last year, they performed
at Saitama Super Arena for the first
time in two years.
They are a popular group that ended
their two consecutive days of
performances with a huge success.
And the two people supporting Ebichu are
the comedy duo, Nagareboshi.
Ebichu, help me!
The program that started last April
entered the second year.
They moved to Suiyabi and became more
and more powerful.
So this time, we will look back on the
great scenes of Ebichu Tastas based on
the interview of Ebichu members.
First of all, we asked the four people
of Yasumoto, Hiroka, Matsuno, and
Kobayashi about the recommended points
of Ebichu Tastas.
It's not free. It's very free.
I think it's the state of Ebichu. I
think it's a place where you can be
natural.
It's like that.
It's good and bad.
I think it's the same as Ebichu.
What is it?
I think it's a place where everyone can
enjoy.
The first point recommended by the
members is the shrimp-chewing.
This is the project where such a natural
shrimp-chewing came out.
Shrimp-chewing plus a meeting of
staying.
In this project, only the eight shrimp-
chewing members are left in the room and
the shooting of the meeting of staying
is done with a unmanned camera.
The staff was expecting a girl's talk
before the end of the work, but...
What about the handsome-shiritori? Let's
talk about it after the meeting of
staying.
What is the handsome-shiritori?
It is a game that Ebichu has made.
The game is to talk to handsome-
shiritori with the lines that handsome-
shiritori say.
What? What? What?
Where do you want to go on the next
date?
I want to go to the next date.
Oh, that's the end?
Yes.
What is it?
I'm scared.
I love this.
There is a mouse next to you.
A mouse came.
The lipstick of the rouge.
It looks like KAIKI.
What is this?
Don't look sideways.
It's fast.
I was told to marry you.
I will be by your side until then.
I'm a fan of yours.
The members of the Ebitune team who
forget the program and enjoy the nature
were in the O-tomari team.
Next is the number 12, Riko Nakayama's
recommendation.
I didn't watch the program from the
beginning.
You didn't watch the program?
My mother and I watched the program in
the living room. I went to my room and
ran away.
She doesn't watch the program, so she
doesn't have any recommendations.
The program that Nakayama didn't watch
the program is the interview with
Ebitutus.
In this program, he will challenge the
interview with a part-time job at a
cafe.
The person who will be waiting is a fake
interviewer.
The shooting star in the room secretly
gives the order.
Oh, she came.
Excuse me.
If I were the manager, I would have
dropped her when she came wearing this
outfit.
That's right.
I would have thought she was joking.
Then, I would like to know your
shortcomings, Ms. Hoshiga.
There are some parts that are a little
messy, so I want to fix them.
I learned this at a cafe, and I want to
be able to solve such a messy part with
a calm feeling.
Is Mr. Nakayama sleepy?
He is sleepy.
I am often told that I am sleepy, but I
am awake and I am doing my job well.
Then, Ms. Nakayama.
My shortcomings are that I cannot convey
my words well to others.
I think that the communication with
customers is important for cafe staff.
I want to do my best.
Are you sleepy?
I am awake.
I am okay.
I am doing my job well.
Here, the four of them will practice
greeting at the cafe they came up with.
Welcome to Angel Relax Cafe!
Thank you.
Yasumoto-san.
Yes.
Welcome to Chotto Chotto Choco Choco
Cafe!
Yes!
Hahaha
Unable to meet her, she is very
depressed
Next, what is waiting for her?
Welcome to Happy Cafe, which delivers
happiness
Since it is a happy cafe, I want to make
it more festive
Yes, I will do my best
Welcome to Happy Cafe
The interview is over. Thank you very
much.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
I want you to appeal to that.
Good luck. Good luck.
What's wrong?
Excuse me.
Can you show me?
Please. It's okay.
It's okay.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Please show me.
Thank you.
Welcome to Smile Cafe
That's all for the interview
Thank you
The interview is over
What will the members say?
Wait a minute, everyone came one by one
I hate it
What happened?
What happened to Nakayama?
I hate it
I hate that guy, I don't want to go to
the cafe anymore
I don't know about cafes, I don't know
about cafes anymore
This is the trauma that Nakayama stopped
watching TV shows
What is the point of the show that you
recommend to the viewers?
There are a lot of questions, and I
think that if I pass the questions and
challenge to record the show, the
questions will not be reflected in the
show
I will do my best to answer the
questions
I think that if I say it in the
questionnaire, it will be a success. It
is a wonderful show that I can do what I
want to do
The Maehama show questionnaire has not
been used yet, but the recommended point
is the project that the members proposed
A project that was actually used by the
members is a photo that adds a shrimp
In this project, photo contest is held
in the hope of winning the members
This project is a project where members
become pairs and take pictures in their
favorite situations
I'll take this one
Good
I like the feeling of putting it in
The second one is like a morning
Morning
The first one is like a morning
Isn't it better to take pictures like
this?
The band is so uncomfortable
At that time, Hirota Hoshinateya was
shooting in the classroom
Here, she was using the cloak in an
unexpected way
Ref 1
Ref 1 is 気持ち
Ref 1 of 気持ち
What a surprise!
The strategy is to remove the cloak of
the costume and reflect its luster
Can she use the reflection of the light
well?
You are not a dragon.
On the other hand, the team of Yasumoto
and Kashiwagi went to the Kotei.
Ready, go!
Oh, cute!
One more time.
I can't do it.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Ready, start!
She tries to shoot a running model,
but as you can see,
the size and the focus are not right.
This is the end of the shooting of all
the teams.
This is the work that was praised by 8
professional cameramen and was praised
at the Grand Prix.
This is the work that was taken by
Mayama, the model of Matsuno.
The teacher said that the soft light
through the shoulder is beautiful.
The teacher is different from the model.
She is looking at the position of the
light.
This is a really good photo.
How is Matsuno, who has become a model?
I'm very happy.
There are many people.
I can see that you are different from
the model through this photo.
Are you the same person?
I'm the same person.
Matsuno is always in a good mood.
She was smiling.
The members will continue to choose the
best scenes.
Please look forward to the next episode.
Next, we will introduce the recommended
points of Ebitu Tastas by Tashiwagi.
It's Kido Airaku.
Tastas has all kinds of points.
There were sad moments, but there were
also happy and fun moments.
I think it's a perfect word for this
program.
Tashiwagi's recommended point is Ebitu's
Kido Airaku.
First, we will introduce the Kido
Airaku's 5 points.
Tashiwagi challenged the fear of the
air.
Yay!
You have to check it.
Please look forward.
Why?
You shouldn't look.
Dad!
And then...
Wait!
The Kashiwagi that reached the maximum
level of fear is for some reason
completely cut off.
What's wrong? Are you crying?
Kashiwagi.
It was a Kashiwagi that was so angry
that it was too scary.
Next is Kido Ailac's Rakku.
BBQ! Bang Bang Kyuza!
The members of Ebichu's year-end wish is
to have a BBQ
Let's eat!
Let's eat when we get home!
You have to eat properly!
I'm not eating!
Yes!
The smile on their faces when they eat
meat
The members are excited about the BBQ
They eat and eat and eat
And the beef tongue is good
Yasumoto is doing something
Yes, yes, yes
The number of people who waited is
increasing
What is this?
It's a dance!
It looks fun
Fujii Kocho saw this broadcast and was
excited about the members of Ebichu
Freedom is good, but it's too much
That's different
It's a little different
Is that in front of everyone?
What is the idea?
Did you get angry?
I'm not too conscious of the camera
I thought it wasn't good
Everyone is angry now
The tone is a little different
It's okay to be too excited
And sometimes such sad things
This time, I, Kaiki Ogata, will graduate
from Ebichu Tastas
From the first episode of the program,
the one who made the show more fun was
the rock musician Kaiki Ogata.
He graduated from the program in March
this year to put more effort into his
band activities.
I hope to be involved as an artist
again.
I'm happy to be able to be friends with
Mr. Ogata.
Mr. Ogata is really...
I think he's an important person.
I'm watching him closely.
When I think,
I'm in trouble,
I want him to come back
and take this.
I understand.
I'll bring it.
Ouch!
Hang in there.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I don't know what it means to keep
trying Wie to die
I'm so sad that I can't see you anymore
But from now on
I'll be your friend
Of course, we're friends
Thank you
There was a sad incident called farewell
The last one is Kido Airac's Ki!
Before her graduation, Kaiki Ogata left
this wonderful gift for Ebichu Tastas.
The members are so happy.
And that is...
Ogata-san made a song for us.
And that song has just been officially
announced.
A
bird
This is the song produced by the small
group Kaiki.
Spring break, Moratorium junior high
school students will release a new album
called Anarchy this month.
How was the special episode of the Ebitu
members' choice of Ebitu Tastas?
Lastly, a special present from the
program!
The member produce live held last
October!
The event of member self-produce is
closely connected from rehearsal to the
actual performance.
The total time of the video is 4284
minutes.
There are still some videos that we
couldn't show you.
Among them, this time we will show you a
special special live video.
It is a limited version of the single of
the Indies era, the part of the Eri-zori
Diamond.
Super rare live video start!
I shuffled everyone's part!
Please enjoy it!
14. A-FU-RA-I
I am sorry, Every Sorry
I am sorry for my lack of education
I will give you A-FU-RA-I
Please forgive me, Sanbari
I am sorry, Every Sorry
I forgot to reply to the e-mail
I will dance A-FU-RA-I
Please forgive me, Sanbari
With this smile, I'll apologize for
everything, everything
Please forgive me for laughing at things
I don't understand
Let's smile
If you smile
Everything will be alright
We're so cool
I hate hate
Your smile
Diamond
I should be saying sorry, right?
Apologize to me, alright?
I think that if we do this, we won't
have any more fights or arguments
Diamond
Happy now everyday
Let's laugh together
As long as you smile, everything will be
alright
Make sure, it's goodbye
I'll connect you with a twinkle
Diamond
Every day is exciting, the results are
alright
A life of being a middle school student
A greeting to everyone who cries
Ready, go! Ebitori Diamond!
Wow!
Ebitu Tastas has entered the second year
There are many new projects and live
videos coming up
Look forward to it!
It has started! Ebitu Tastas!
Next time on Ebitu Tastas
Ebitu's new album, Anarchy, is going to
be released!
It was supposed to be!
It's good!
What's with this attitude?
For some reason, Tsukuba is in a bad
shape!
Let's all say cheers!
1, 2, 3!
Cheers!
This program was provided by the
sponsors you see.
It's a weird feeling.
It's supposed to be nice and clean.
It's pretty difficult.
But the kashiwa is beautiful.
The kashiwa is delicious.
What is this?
It's a pen.
It's not something you can carry around.
It's a pen!