Thank you for watching!
Good evening everyone, it's time for the
morning chimes.
We are Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku.
Yes!
I took it because I was in a hurry.
It suddenly started.
I'm Yoko Yokooka.
Nice to meet you.
Before we start the show,
I'd like to decide today's MC as usual.
Everyone, please vote for your favorite
number from 1 to 3.
The person who has the number on the
card is today's MC.
Everyone, vote from 1 to 3.
It suddenly started.
It's started.
The time is short, so please be quick.
As expected of the serious person.
Quickly.
It's a rabbit.
It's Halloween.
It's a different color from the one
before.
What is this?
A fox?
It's a cat.
Is it a cat?
Is it okay if I don't do the one before?
It was fast.
When do you think I'll take it?
5, 4, 3, 2, 1
Please subscribe to the channel.
The end!
Let's check the results.
Wait, I haven't seen it.
You haven't seen it?
Wait, I'll hold it.
Number 3 is the most common.
Number 3 is...
Let's do it together.
1, 2, 3!
The winner is Sakurai Kokona with number
3!
Thank you for coming!
You said you did it.
I did it!
I'm going to say it all today.
I wanted to see Yuno's MC.
But, once again, I'm the MC for today.
Thank you.
Please.
It says it's stable.
I was the one who did it.
That's right.
Shall we start?
Yes, let's start.
Let's start.
Ebichu's Fun and Fufufu Showroom.
Today is the 50th episode.
Thank you for watching Ebichu's Fun and
Fufufu Showroom.
Thank you.
It's been about 5 years.
50 episodes.
Thank you for this precious project.
Thank you.
I'll do my best.
Ebichu's Fun and Fufufu Showroom is a
show about our sisterhood.
It's a show about our sisterhood in
Uka's Showroom.
Okay.
Let's see the ranking.
Okay, let's see.
Please tell us.
Okay.
Please subscribe to our channel.
1st place, oh, it's cool from 5th place.
Let's go from 5th place.
Ganyu Shimao Team 3. Thank you.
4th place, Riku Team 3. Thank you.
3rd place, 13th place. Thank you.
2nd place, Kazuhiko Team. Thank you.
1st place, Penpen Team. Thank you.
For the original showroom avatar, you
can register as a showroom member and
get free or free gift.
Are there many people who are interested
in this?
Oh!
There are many people who are interested
in this.
If you click the Twitter mark below the
screen, you can spread this broadcast on
Twitter.
Thank you for your cooperation.
So, from here...
It's time to spread the word!
To make this broadcast seen by many
people,
we will announce it on Ebichu's Twitter.
So, please tweet about us.
Please.
Manager-san!
Koko, don't put that on.
I can't see your face.
I'll put it on half.
Here we go.
One, two.
Thank you.
How do you like it?
They say it's cute.
They say it's sexy.
I'm happy.
So, we're going to do this today.
Yes.
We're going to do a fun and fluffy
survey talk.
We did this last time and it was a good
result, so we'd like to do another
survey.
Before we start, we'll decide on the
topic to talk about in the survey.
Okay.
Shall we start talking about the topic?
Okay, let's start talking about the
topic.
Ta-da!
Can you read the first part?
Okay, first, the first part.
About the new member announcement.
Okay.
And the second part.
It's going to be a lot.
About the 200,000 ZEP Tour.
Okay.
And from here, it's going to be a little
bit interesting.
So, from Maru-san, first, she wants to
get a mount.
What does that mean?
What a mean woman.
Okay, and next, Maru-4.
How to eat delicious food.
I'm curious.
Okay, next, Maru-5.
I'm curious about this.
It's the most serious one.
It's a serious one.
And Maru-6.
It's the most powerful animal.
Is this really?
And Maru-7.
There are.
It's totally irrelevant.
Okay, these seven.
From the top 10, please vote.
We'll decide by voting.
Which top 10 will we choose?
Start voting!
I'll do this.
You can do it.
It's okay.
I did it myself.
Who will pick it up?
We will scream.
Maybe nobody COagna will act.
We can know who wrote the four with
invite number 4.
I can see who wrote the three.
We don't know who will do that.
Who wrote number three is generally next
question.
4,3,2,1
Done!
What's the first place?
What do you think?
Number 3 is 23.8% and is the first
place!
Number 3 is...
Who wants to take a mount?
Number 3 wants to take a mount!
Let's talk about the mount!
Please!
Thank you!
Can I take a picture of you?
Can I take a picture of you guys?
Sure!
What kind of iPhone do you guys use?
12!
iPhone 13 Pro!
I'm iPhone 14!
That's great!
But you're still using 11.
Stop it!
I'm struggling with data collection.
The more I think about it, the more I
get excited.
Isn't that 11?
It's still 11.
Then it's 13.
What is that?
But I have a phone case and it arrived.
Did you buy a cute one?
But it's still 11.
I'm sorry.
I'm talking while tying it.
How about you guys?
Does anyone have a phone case?
I'm a pro.
You're wearing a mount.
Thank you.
You're using it for a long time.
That's right.
I'm 13.
I've been using it for a long time.
I want to wear a mount.
I'm 8.
You're using the 14 Pro.
I'm still 12.
You're still 12.
I'm using the 12 Pro.
I'm 7.
You have a lot.
I'm a galaxy.
There are not many people who are 14.
I wonder if I can take a picture.
I was happy.
What is an iPhone?
I took the latest one.
Thank you.
Next.
I'm 7.
Please vote for us.
3DS is a lie.
3DS is good.
BAMBAM BEAT is popular.
I'm embarrassed.
14 people are still watching.
9 people are still watching.
Please vote for us.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1, end!
I'm curious about this.
What's the result?
I'm guessing.
1st place is 19.6% and 1st place is...
1st place! This is the only one.
New members are announced.
Should we talk about it?
Let's talk about it together.
On October 1st,
New members were announced on the live
stream.
Emma and Yuna.
Number 16 is Sakurai Emma.
Number 17 is Yuna Nakamura.
I'm not in the group.
I'm not in the group either.
Everyone here is 15 years old.
I'm 17 years old.
There are a lot of people who want to
have a 07 unit.
And Yuna and Emma are 07 units.
But it's different from the school year.
Yeah, it's different.
But it's 2007.
Then I'm the only one left.
What year are you?
05.
7.
I've been taking the same thing for a
while.
But...
You two are from the same region, right?
So I'm from the same region, too.
I felt the same smell.
I think Yuna is having a hard time in
Fukuoka.
We haven't talked much yet.
I wonder what you two are saying.
It was fluffy and cute.
I remember when Yuna and the others just
got in.
Please subscribe to our channel.
We are changing year by year.
I'm looking forward to it.
I wonder what will happen.
It will be a 10-person live.
I wonder if the lessons have already
started.
It's starting now.
We haven't been able to participate in
various work.
I want to go to the lesson with Hinata
and the teacher.
I wonder.
I'm looking forward to it.
Oh, I've got a ticket. Thank you. Thank
you. The 17th and 16th tickets are
already on the way.
Sakuragi and Sakurai are similar.
Yes, they are.
Mayu-san is calling Yuna, but I think
Yuna is wrong.
So when she's angry, I think it's Yuna.
No, no, no.
That's my feeling.
When I can't hear it.
I don't know because it's Yuna and Yuna.
So when I'm praised, it's usually Yuna.
Because she's so cute.
Nakayama and Nakamaya are similar.
Yes, they are.
From now on, we'll have dance lessons.
I wonder how it will be.
We may come to the showroom again.
We'll see when they come.
I want to do it.
Shall we go to the next one?
We will choose from 7 people and vote.
Ready, start!
Is it started?
My ears are falling.
Is it mostly YUNO who gets angry?
Yes, it's usually YUNO who gets angry,
so it's not YUNA.
That's right.
Because you are the senior.
Yes, yes.
How do you feel to be the senior in a
year?
Not really.
何か? 何かは...
見せてください。
何かは、あんまり分からない言葉だけなんです。
でも一年で学んだことって絶対大きいじゃん。
学んだことは知られるといいね。
5,4,3,2,1
終了!
見てみましょう。
気になる。どうだろう?
1st place! 23.1% is 5th place!
5th place!
5th place is important.
This is important.
I've been thinking about this for a long
time.
What's wrong, Nogaka-chan?
What's wrong?
Next time, we'll have a nabe party.
Yes, the three of us.
We'll have a nabe party, but...
What kind of nabe party are we going to
do?
I'm thinking about it a lot.
What should we do? I'm always thinking
about it.
We haven't decided on the ingredients
yet.
We haven't decided what nabe we're going
to make.
It's a terrible idea.
We might not be able to do it in the
first place.
What should we make?
I don't like yaminame.
We're going to make a real nabe party,
not a joke.
We're going to make a real nabe party.
We're going to do it together.
We're going to eat proper food for the
first time.
I'm looking forward to it, but I don't
know which nabe to make.
Please recommend a nabe to us.
It's a problem.
There are a lot of yam nabe.
I don't like yam nabe.
I want to try it on a project.
I want to make it myself.
Cheese fondue? Cheese fondue is a nabe?
It's not a nabe.
There's a strawberry nabe.
Kimchi nabe?
I don't like kimchi nabe.
Is it spicy?
Kimchi nabe has a unique smell.
I like it.
It's a sesame soy milk nabe.
What do you like?
I like chanko.
I like motunabe and oden.
I like sukiyaki.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I want to eat lettuce.
I want to eat bean sprouts.
Please try this dish.
Please try Chinese hot pot.
I don't think Chinese hot pot is good
with lettuce.
I want to eat Chinese hot pot.
I don't know what it means.
Shabu-shabu!
Shabu-shabu sounds good.
Is it okay to decide so easily?
It's too fast.
What do you want to eat at the three-
storied house?
This?
This one?
I'll choose this one.
I'll choose shabu-shabu.
Please write shabu-shabu in a big way.
And there's a tomato pot.
Tomato pot? Is it good?
I like tomato pot.
Tomato is better.
Tomato is not lettuce.
There's a pot.
I want to see a pot.
Do you want sukiyaki?
Shabu-shabu, tomato pot, sukiyaki.
Three.
Let's increase it to four.
Four?
Four pot.
Please watch again.
No rice cake?
Yes, yes.
If you don't have a rice cake pot, you
can't eat it.
No, I don't want to.
Can I have these four?
I'll make it for you.
I asked you for that.
Please vote.
Shabu-shabu, tomato pot, sukiyaki, rice
cake pot.
Please vote.
Ready, start!
Yuno's food is amazing.
If it's a motu-nabe, Yuna-chan likes it.
Yuna-chan.
I called from Fukuoka.
What's going on?
Yuna-chan.
What I want to eat is Shabu-shabu.
That's what you want to eat.
That's right.
I'm not going to eat it.
I'm going to eat it.
Everyone wants to eat what we want to
eat.
Please decide what you want to eat
today.
I went to a Shabu-shabu lettuce store in
Shibuya the other day.
It was really good.
There was a Japanese style Japanese food
called Wadashi.
I went to a Japanese style Japanese food
It was delicious because it was easy to
eat.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1
End
What happened? I'll do this.
Result open
1,33 points
This is definitely Yu-no.
This is Yu-no.
I'm looking forward to this.
End
What should I put in? Lettuce and bean
sprouts are a must. What do you want to
say?
Pork belly? Pork belly is delicious.
Pork belly and enoki mushrooms. Enoki
mushrooms are delicious.
There are Chinese cabbage, so lettuce is
good.
process clove
It's delicious to cut the radish thinly.
Tofu!
I don't eat tofu.
I'm sorry.
Oyster!
I'll put in oyster!
Isn't it scary if you say it?
Oyster!
Let's think about it.
Chicken
You said it.
I like chicken.
Boil the radish thinly and put in
oyster.
Oyster is scary.
What should we do?
Lettuce, bean sprouts, pork belly, enoki
mushroom, radish, and vinegar.
Do you want to put it in vinegar?
I want to put it in.
What if we put in ramen at the end?
What if we put in ramen?
If we don't use a pot, ramen won't be
delicious.
What if we put in ramen?
Please subscribe to the channel.
It's not water.
It's water.
I said it's water.
We put the sauce in a separate plate and
put it on the ramen.
It's not hot water.
Is there a soup stock?
I don't like the hot water.
Is it soup stock?
I thought it was hot water.
I was surprised.
I want to eat soup stock.
I want to eat ramen.
We've decided. Thank you.
Let's do one more. Let's do one more.
Let's do one more. Is it the last one?
Is it the last one? Yes.
We'll do one more. Please vote.
I want to put this in a good way.
Are you voting now?
We're voting now. Please vote.
I want to put it on.
You can do whatever you want.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Sugar One.
I think I got 4 votes.
What's the result?
1st place with 28.6% votes.
1st place?
7th place.
Is there an alien?
Do you want to talk about it?
There is an alien.
If there is an alien, I think there is a
moon.
A moon?
Yes, a moon.
I've been talking about it since I was
in elementary school.
I think there is something in the moon.
Isn't it Orihime and Hikoboshi?
The moon is a star, so it's different.
I want to meet Orihime and Hikoboshi.
Can't you meet?
That's right.
I want to meet.
Are there aliens in the moon?
I think there are aliens in the moon.
There's a yellowish person.
I think I'll see you if I go to space.
If you fly into space, will you be
there?
I think there are aliens.
I want to meet you.
I believe in all that.
I want to see aliens with big eyes like
I see on TV.
It's Kaguya Hime.
Is Kaguya Hime an alien?
Isn't that Tsukijin?
Tsukijin?
Tsukijin is back.
I want to go to that world.
Do you think there are aliens?
If you look at it from space, you can
see that we are aliens.
No, no, we are aliens.
I see.
How is it?
There was a alien behind you, right?
Behind Haruta?
There was!
There was an alien.
I wonder what that face is.
I'm curious about that too.
There must be an alien.
Yes.
Is there someone who saw it?
I've seen it in the middle school.
I think the person who said he had seen
it is a liar.
I don't know.
I think there might be someone who saw
it.
I heard that Hyuui also saw it in the
middle school.
I saw it.
I don't know.
I've seen one, but I haven't seen two.
No.
I don't think there's any.
I don't know.
No lies.
I can write where I saw it.
Oh, yeah.
Where I saw it, where it was, what
happened.
Ready, go!
Ta-da!
You're not sitting in the middle.
You're not sitting.
There's someone, right?
I'm right.
No, there's no one.
I can't get through.
But, surprisingly...
The thing that aliens are thinking about
is coconut, right?
The thing that's flying around.
Sometimes, they say strange things.
Yeah, seriously.
It's like a video.
Okay, let's do it again.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Oh, it's over.
How was it?
It's not like that.
Where did 18.2% of people see it?
Please write down where you saw it.
Thank you for watching.
何色の人がいるの? 何色でした? 何色? 気になるよね。
何色か気になる。 宇宙人コミュニティでおにぎり買ってました。
それは全部予定だよ。 さっき? すごいタイムリーだね。
ゆのに不思議とだけは言われたくなかったから。 いやいや。
えー。 気のルージュだ。 アザバシだ。 面白い。
昨日ローソンで見た。 書くとUFOに連れ去られちゃうらしい。 あ、そうなんだ。
そんな説があるんですか?
関東で飲んでたってめっちゃイケメンじゃん。 えー。
えー。
すごい。 パルツアーの楽屋にいた。 足本のやつね。
いたね。 宇宙人しかいないエビチュウ。 確かに。 確かに。
スマホいじってた?
ほんとに? 見える人は見えるんじゃない? 宇宙人。
だってさ、霊的なもの見える人は見えるじゃん。 見える方は見えるよね。
そう。 見るのだって昔君の時いたって言ってた。 怖かった。
本当部屋の時怖かったもんね。
ちょっと薄暗い感じで。 電気消さずに。 電気消そう。 怖かった。
まあ、まあまあまあ。 三人の背後にいるって。
居ないじゃん。 居ないよ。 怖いの怖いから。 終わり終わり終わり終わり終わり。
違う。 ラスト質問。 何がいいかな。 可愛い犬の顔添えて。 よし、スタート。
私だ今の。 ウォウウォって私だよ。
撮られちゃった。 いつの間にか。
撮ったの? 撮ったの? 撮らなかったよ。
5,4,3,2,1,終了!
最後のトークテーマは何でしょうか?
気になる。
4番! 世界一を押したい方。
これであれですね。 三人のトークテーマは全部出してもらって。
昨日ね、東京に帰ってきたの。
ちょっと前から愛知に帰省して、ばあちゃん家に行ったり。
ばあちゃん家に行ったりしたんだけど、
行ったね。
それで、なんか。
When I came back from Aichi, I'm not
good at eating liquid noodles, but I
can't eat something with a strong taste.
That's good.
And when I got home, I saw tomatoes in
the refrigerator.
I was going to eat cucumber, but I
didn't.
I stopped paying and ate tomatoes.
Tomatoes are delicious when they are
sprinkled with white soup stock.
What? White soup stock?
Is it a big tomato?
Big tomatoes and mini tomatoes.
Do they go well together?
Peel the tomatoes.
White soup stock?
About 2 to 1.
Water and white soup stock.
1 is white soup stock and 2 is water.
And...
Please watch again.
It's really delicious when you eat it
with soup.
How long do you put it on?
About an hour.
If you want to make it like this, you
can add more white soup stock.
I'm tired of making it, so I cut the
tomatoes and put them in the soup.
What does it taste like?
It's a little delicious.
I don't know.
I know what's delicious.
Tomatoes and white soup are delicious.
I wanted to eat a little bit yesterday,
so I ate a lot of tomatoes.
I wanted to eat a little bit more, so I
ate two big tomatoes.
You ate both, right?
Yes.
I often say that I eat it with white
soup stock.
Yes, it's delicious if you put cucumber
and white soup stock.
You mean, the one who put the soup
stock?
Yes, it's delicious if you put the soup
stock.
I want to try it.
Should we do it when we make it?
Buy some cucumbers and tomatoes.
Let's do it.
That's good.
It's over.
Thank you. That's all for the fun and
fluffy survey talk.
Next, we'll do this kind of project.
Halloween that's too fun and fluffy and
can't be conveyed in detail.
I'd like to explain the rules.
It's a project that's being done every
year during the Halloween season.
Users, please comment on the characters
that are too fine and can't be conveyed.
We'll be the ones to do it.
For example, someone who talks while
hiding the stain on the clothes.
It's so detailed.
It's interesting.
Have you done it?
Yuna and Nanoka are the same.
I think it's Nakafo and Hinata.
That's right.
I think it's about the same.
Did you get it?
Thank you for your viewing.
It was surprisingly difficult. It's
difficult. Let's do our best and get it
right.
Let's get it right. We'll pick a
character from your comments.
Please write it in the comments.
Who will go first?
Nono, Yua, and Kokona.
Senpai, please. I'll go first.
Please leave your comments.
I can't look at it?
No, you can look at it.
It's hard to comment.
Right?
Oh, I can't say the heart.
Then, please choose one.
Can you see it?
Can I leave it?
Did you choose?
Yes.
Shall we start?
I'm starting.
Who is it?
This is the person who didn't get
disinfected in front of the store.
It's pretty embarrassing.
I'm going to get a body temperature
measured with disinfection.
Your eyes are a little real.
I don't want to go through it as it is.
It's a little uncomfortable.
I'm going to write a note.
Thank you for your viewing.
Let's start.
Thank you.
Next, Yuna.
You can start with Omomuro.
It started.
She's dancing.
She's looking at us.
What is that?
Who is that?
Please subscribe to my channel.
This is the person who got a lesson from
the teacher.
The person who was sitting behind.
Is it a little awkward?
I think Yu-chan and the others are
thinking that the person behind is the
one who is shaking hands.
I agree.
If you think you have eyes, please think
you have eyes.
That's right.
It's not a misunderstanding.
It's fun.
Then, I will go with this.
Everyone, please.
You can start right away.
I can't open it.
What are you doing?
Wait a minute.
The
door is locked.
I'm starting.
Do you have something?
Who are you?
I passed the opening with a bottle of
water.
I was actually a watermelon.
That's Mirei.
I'm sorry.
Mirei tweeted about this.
Is that true?
The bottle is different in shape.
It's totally different.
You must be tired.
Let's do it again.
Which one do you want?
Are you going to start?
How is it?
What should we do?
There are many comments.
There are things you can't take out if
you put an IC card in your bag.
I'm looking at the back.
Who are you?
I'm a person who can't hear from one ear
to the other.
I understand.
I'm scared sometimes.
I'm scared of not being able to hear the
sound.
I'm scared.
Shall we move on?
Yorokchan.
What should I do?
There are many comments.
How is it?
I'll go with this one.
Okay.
Who are you?
I'm the woman who mistook ZEP diversity
for ZEP wings.
There she is!
Thank you for watching!
I was like, I'm gonna get all the
comments!
I was so excited!
You're so annoying, Yuno-san.
You're so annoying.
Are you watching this?
I am.
You'll get mad if you watch this.
Please leave comments.
Is there anything?
I'm watching.
Who are you?
I was about to close the elevator, but I
got in late and got in.
This is awkward.
And if there's someone I haven't talked
to, it's awkward.
It's not bad, isn't it?
I'm trying to get on it all of a sudden.
Certainly.
And...
閉まった直後だって気づかないで開けたらさ
開けたって言うかボタン押したら開いちゃったって言うか
結構行きますよ わかるわかるわかる
混んでてね 自分にしようと思ったらね 開いちゃうんだよね
行きますね
はい ラスト1回行きます 行きますね
It's starting.
It's a bit rough.
Who are you?
I'm the one who dropped my contact lens.
Oh, really?
What do you mean?
You open it, try to make contact, and
then put it on.
If you blink, it will fall.
You can't put it on properly.
I think people who are in contact will
understand.
Oh, that's it.
That's interesting.
Thank you for your viewing.
It's hard to find.
The color is different.
It's usually light blue.
It's hard to find.
It's the last turn.
Is it over?
Last turn?
There are many.
Something is going on.
Who are you?
I'm the type of person who steps when I
feel like I'm being pushed by my hands.
That's a bit embarrassing.
It's common these days.
You don't go at all.
I know.
It's very convenient for your feet.
If you think you're pushing your
hands...
Something is going on.
Are you singing?
I'm sorry.
Oh, it's not working.
Who are you?
I'm a person who cancels because I'm too
tall in karaoke.
That's a good thing.
I'm not the one who sang it.
It's a little embarrassing when I go to
karaoke alone.
Have you ever done karaoke alone?
I have.
I've used it in practice.
What about you?
I don't have it.
I don't go to karaoke in the first
place.
I think I can do it.
I can't sing a song of a male artist
because it's too low.
I can't sing because the chorus is too
high.
That's why it's canceled.
It's a little embarrassing.
I know. Thank you very much.
Thank you for your comments.
Thank you very much.
It's over. Thank you very much.
That was Halloween that can't be
conveyed in detail.
Now, the 50th episode of the showroom in
the middle of the show is about to end.
Yes.
Do you want to announce it?
Yes, I will announce it.
Please.
Where is it?
Please come here.
Did you have fun?
I wonder if it was fun.
It's fun to do a live broadcast with
Gokuyo.
It's been a while.
It's not like that.
It's not like that?
It was fun.
I'm glad.
Thank you.
Tomorrow, October 29th,
Riko Nakayama's birthday solo live,
Riko Nakayama's birthday party,
will be held at KT ZEPP Yokohama.
Yes.
Tomorrow.
Please enjoy it.
Thank you.
And,
tada.
Yes.
10, 11, 12,
Heisei Isokin Trio,
will be held at KT ZEPP Yokohama.
10, 11, 12, Heisei Isokin Trio, will be
held at Ichikawa City Cultural
Exhibition on October 30.
Yes, it's the second part of the
Kachiyo-Agi Project.
The second part will be held with Riko,
Kaho, and Hinata.
Next?
Next!
There are a lot.
There are a lot? I'm looking forward to
it.
There were a lot yesterday.
3572.
10, 11, 12, Heisei Isokin Trio, will be
held at Ichikawa City Cultural
Exhibition on October 20.
Hoshina Mirei's Saitan Solo Live, Pink
Doll House 5, will be held from 7pm on
October 31 at KT Zepp Yokohama.
Mirei's Saitan Solo Live will be held on
Halloween.
I'm looking forward to it.
10, 13, 14, 15, and 5 of them will be
held on November 28.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Tachikawa Stage... Tachikawa Stage
Garden?
Tachikawa Stage Garden!
I'm so excited!
We were thinking about how to set up
with Hinata-chan.
We're thinking about it together, so I'm
looking forward to it.
We'll do that song.
We'll do kanji.
We'll try that.
We'll do all the songs.
I'm looking forward to it!
We'll check the top 5 of the final
ranking.
Let's read it.
11th, 28th is Hinata's solo.
Yes, 11th, 12th is the final ranking.
Sorry.
We'll read it again.
Let's check the ranking first.
Ranking.
Ranking 5, Riku. Thank you.
Ranking 5, Hinata. Thank you.
ステー ジミーさん. Thank you.
3位 エビ エビ エビ エビシー. Thank you.
1 2 1 2 1 2 3. Thank you.
2位 シャッケルフォードさん. Thank you.
1位 ペンペンさん. Thank you.
We've changed the topic.
Yes, we've changed the topic.
We'll say it again.
The 13th, 14th, 15th and 15th members
will be performing at the stage garden
on November 12th.
Yes!
We've changed the time.
Please come to the stage garden!
Please watch the live broadcast!
So, the 50th episode of the fun and
fluffy showroom in Ebichu is over!
Thank you!
We will announce the next episode again
later.
This live broadcast will be broadcasted
after this, so please check it out!
The live broadcast will end for now, but
we will be back soon, so please wait for
it!
Please leave a comment if you have
anything you want us to say in the
comment section!
That's it for today!
This was Shin-Ai Shin-Ai's shrimp
shrimp school!
Bye bye!
Thank you!
Bye!
The live performance has been decided.
I'm looking forward to it.
We have only a few more times to do a
live performance with Hina.
We said we have only five more times.
No, we have six more times to do a live
performance with the last voice.
That's right.
It's started.
Thank you.
Let's do it again.
How was it?
What was the answer?
I think it was fun.
I forgot to say one thing.
Today,
on Fuji TV2,
our fanmeeting will be broadcasted.
Please watch it.
Thank you for your hard work.
From 20 o'clock.
Yes, the fanmeeting will be broadcasted
on Fuji TV2.
Bye.
Can you tell us about the highlights?
The highlights?
The first fan meeting, Hanami and Mizu.
It was the first time.
We were having fun.
The first three of us.
All the members were having fun.
It was really fun.
It was fun.
Kaho was on vacation, so it was the
first fan meeting.
We were having fun as much as we could.
It was fun.
I was surprised to see that much water.
It was raining.
Yes, it was raining.
Please come to the concert from 10
o'clock.
Please.
How was the MC?
I always do the MC when I'm with the
members.
I study every day.
I hope I can get better and better.
You're so determined.
The stability of the MC was great.
Thank you.
As expected of the older sister.
I'm serious.
I'm not serious.
I feel like MCs tend to be like that.
Certainly.
I think it's great to finish as time
goes by.
Thank you.
How about you two?
I was really curious about Yunho.
Sometimes Yunho falls down.
Yes, he falls down when I do this.
I'm free!
I thought you were free today.
I'm not an MC today, so I'm free.
I want you to be an MC every time.
I want to be free from the pot.
I can eat a pot, but I think cabbage is
delicious.
I want to eat cabbage.
I will never give up.
Then you should say cabbage pot.
Oh, I like cabbage pot.
I'm not doing it while rolling it.
How was it?
I think I voted a lot today.
I'm glad that you have helped me a lot.
This is the good way to use the
showroom.
I didn't decide to vote here.
I was able to decide a lot of things.
I think everyone was able to
participate.
I'm glad.
Can't you hear me?
What?
I'm sorry.
I thought it would be okay because my
ears would fall off.
I'm glad I decided to make a pot.
I'm glad. I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it.
It was the first showroom where the
three of us became seniors.
I think you've grown up.
I want to see it. Thank you very much.
I want to see the first showroom where
the three of us did it.
How did you do it?
I would have relied on my seniors if I
had more seniors.
But now that we're doing it together,
I'm not sure if it's Kokubo-san, but I'm
glad I felt like I was doing it
properly.
Thank you very much.
The three of you are very interesting.
I'm glad.
I've been thinking that we have a good
balance recently.
We've been talking about various things
at work.
We've been talking more about various
things.
I think we've been thinking about it a
lot.
People are asking if you want to be a
national treasure.
Please keep going with my way.
The balance is the best.
I'm glad it's balanced.
What will happen if you welcome Ayuna?
That's right.
Will you be able to broadcast with five
people?
I'm sure it will come.
I don't know what kind of character it
is yet.
I don't know if it's something.
I'm going to be with you on the radio.
I'm looking forward to it because I
think you'll understand it from now on.
Everyone is going to be adults.
I wonder what kind of character it is.
I wonder if I will be an adult.
I'm an adult soon.
You're 18 years old.
I'm 18 years old.
This is a joke.
I knew it.
I thought it was a joke.
I'm an adult.
I'm not doing it. I'm not doing it.
Nonoka has been practicing Tsukkomi
recently. I love Nonoka's Tsukkomi.
I'm not a bear. I'm a rabbit.
I can do this kind of thing all the
time.
I like this.
Is this okay?
Kazemi-san is...
Kazemi!
Until now...
I was like, what is that?
I was really confused.
That was cute, too, but I thought it
would be cuter if I put it in.
I sometimes don't notice it and say,
Oh, I'm sure I'm saying something.
I was wondering if you were listening.
Sometimes, when it suddenly comes, I'm
like, huh?
After all, it's still not enough.
I'll do my best.
Okubo, let's do our best.
I'm Kokubo.
Kokubo!
I'm scared.
Let's wrap it up.
That's all for today. Thank you very
much.
Thank you for your hard work.
It's Sunday.
We're done with our work tomorrow.
Let's do our best tomorrow.
Thank you very much.
Bye.
Thank you for your hard work. See you
again.