The last game is over.
Amazing.
Riko Nakayama is doing only what she
wants to do.
The second half is only three games.
First, the final game.
And...
I heard shocking words.
Nakayama-san, do you want to
participate?
I don't participate. I just heard it.
Special event. Nakayama just heard it.
What is the result?
And the members who suddenly dance...
The MESS GUNDAM!
Ebi-chu-tastassu.
Or rather, Nakayama-tastassu START!
Add various things to private Ebisu
Middle School.
Ebi-chu-tastassu.
This program is provided by the sponsor
you see.
This time, Ebi-chu-tastassu.
Riko Nakayama.
I'm the MC. I'm doing what I want to do.
So, this time, we will also implement
the plan that MC Nakayama thought of.
First, Nakayama presents.
Running-in-the-dance-the second half.
10 minutes. Can you escape from the
hunter?
If you find the Nakayama stamp of the
mission, you will get the same prize.
The previous team, the first team,
couldn't escape.
And the Nakayama team.
2 minutes from the start, Yasumoto and
Hoshina are in the gym.
Kashiwagi is in the library.
And Nakayama is...
I'm scared!
Please subscribe my channel.
The hunter was chased by the big guy in
the second floor hall.
You can run away!
It's just the beginning!
Let's start!
Run!
The planner Nakayama is in a big trouble
The hunter Manote is in a big trouble
And then
Time out!
Take a break here
That's cheating
I think there are other people here
I understand
I'll go to the other people
I'll go
Go
Nakayama changed the rules
And ran away
Meanwhile, Yasumoto was breathing in the
gym
She found the mission's Nakayama stamp
I'm so scared
The mission is over
Hoshina got a stamp with team play.
However...
Yasumoto and Hoshina are being chased
Are you nervous?
I'm getting tired
I'm going to change my mind
The first round
I can feel it
I can't see the sunglasses
I can't see
Yasumoto is in danger because of the gap
in the gym
I can't see
The hunter seems to have lost sight of
the runner
4 minutes have passed
A new hunter is released
Now there are two
I'm scared
The Continue
I'm done
What's wrong?
Chie
Are you OK?
Chie is so strong
So, Chie is released instead of Hunter O
They still chase the survivors
Where are you?
Where?
This?
It's a mountain
Thank you for watching
Nakayama is doing well, but...
I can't do it.
She's a chauvinist.
I'm scared!
Please watch again.
Nakayama is ready to break the rules
Good luck!
I'm caught
Why?
Did you get caught?
I'm tired
The remaining runners are three
At that time, at the gym
There was Tashiwagi
But after that
He saw a central guard on the first
floor
He ran to the second floor in a hurry
But the hunter was also noticed on the
second floor
And he was found
I'm tired
Thank you for your viewing
I hate you!
Welcome back!
Who did you catch?
Chuuei!
That's amazing!
Chuuei Hunter is chasing after the
thief.
4 minutes left.
Will they be able to escape to the end?
I'm going to look for something.
Where is it?
It's very safe here.
I'm going to look for something.
I'm going back.
Hoshina is moving to collect the
Nakayama Stamp.
Nearby is a Chinese hunter.
Hoshina notices the hunter first.
Hoshina is nervous.
I'm nervous.
The footsteps are approaching
Why?
To secure the star
The prey is not missed
I got a prey
3 in a row of Chinese-Japanese hunters
The remaining runners are only Yasumoto
Here, new hunters are released
Now there are 3 hunters
Yasumoto is hiding his identity
Where is he?
The hunter is on the first floor
He is on the first floor
Yasumoto is moving
He is trying to complete the mission
I thought it's really afraid, it's maybe
discovering the
Too hasty to get it through
I fathered my indirectly
I found it!
Yasumoto runs away with all her might
But...
She's finally secured the power
The high school team's record is 8
minutes and 28 seconds
They can't complete the mission
This game is the victory of the front-
end team
Yay!
They couldn't complete the mission
But Nakayama's team has a prize
What is the prize for Nakayama Koan?
Jyaga, jyaga, jyaga, jyaga, jyaga,
jyaga, jyaga
Yay!
It's a cucumber
Nakayama's favorite, cucumber
And he likes it a lot
Black cucumber
It's more expensive than normal
It's gone
The winner team gets to eat
Let's eat together
Please subscribe to our channel
It's like a tour
I dressed up as the most fun person
What do you mean?
In the end, they all eat the cucumber
Nakayama san, how was it?
I enjoyed the feeling of the taste
I've never seen an ending like this
While eating the cucumber
Are you satisfied with this?
Yes
You still have more?
You're greedy
There are still things to do
What kind of project will come out next?
What are you going to do?
I want you to talk about weird topics
Even if it's a weird topic, I'll answer
it seriously
Like a conversation between Yasumoto and
Kobayashi
But really seriously
Riko, watch
I'm watching
Wait a minute
I heard shocking words
Nakayama san, please participate
I'm just listening to what everyone is
saying
This project is a new project that
Nakayama is just listening to the
members' weird topics
Weird topics
What's wrong with Hoshino?
I'm talking about the smell of the
future
That's interesting
Not Hoshino
People in the world
Weird topics
First, about the smell of the world
If the story is stuck in Nakayama, the
lamp will light up
Will the story that grabs Nakayama's
heart be born?
The smell of the world is unique
If you divide the smell into three or
four patterns
Everyone is very happy
There's someone saying weird things
Weird people
Like a stone
Weird
Everyone, please turn it up
It's not stuck at all
I think the theme is bad
This is a blood type story
It's like a blood type
I'll do it
Let's do it in blood type
I'll do the theme
The theme is blood type diagnosis
Please
I was forced to do it
Why?
The theme is changed to blood type
Can they make Nakayama hot?
Blood type?
First, blood type
A
There are many blood types
Matsu is blood type?
I was told it's B
Completely
I was told it's O
I think it's O or B
It's B
It smells the same
Let's guess what it looks like
I know Yasumoto
I know
Do you know?
O
I know
Next
It's not exciting
It was exciting
Change the theme
Let's think about the next theme
Good
Nakayama also reacted
What do you want to do with the shrimp-
shaped testis?
The debate starts
Shrimp-shaped testis in Hawaii is good
Hawaii is good
It's shining
Don't underestimate the production of
testis
I want to go to Hawaii
What about Hikari?
What?
I want to do testis with my hair free
and chic
I want to do the look with the member's
number next to the seat
I want to do it
Change the clothes
Change the hair
I want to do it
I want to wear the spring clothes
It's different
I want to do it
It's like a transformation
The result of the debate
A new project was born
Nakayama is very satisfied
Kiyo thinks it's over
The reaction was strange
The result is still the same
It's over
Nakayama, it was good
The talk corner is over
Next is Nakayama Project
It's not funny
To a more funny world
Nakayama Nico presents N1 Grand Prix
I don't know what it is, but it seems to
have started.
I will give a cucumber to the person who
NAKAYAMA laughed at.
You are NAKAYAMA.
Anyway, if you can make NAKAYAMA laugh
from the heart, you can get a cucumber.
NAKAYAMA is like this in the previous
project meeting.
I have a weird smile.
I laugh at strange things.
It is a difficult technique to make
NAKAYAMA laugh, who is aware that his
smile is strange.
If you are a shrimp member who is with
you, you can do it.
Let's make NAKAYAMA laugh.
I think it's the best way to make
NAKAYAMA laugh.
It's still there.
Nadaima-san, please touch the cucumber.
That was funny.
Who?
No, I thought Aiai would come, but Rika-
chan came.
No way.
I thought Hirota would come.
I'm good at making people laugh.
Mayama.
What?
Really?
He's really a weird person.
No, it's not like that.
It's a rule.
Let's go.
N1 Grand Prix, Yasumoto's challenge.
The flowers, the flowers,
Yasumoto's hair,
Sakata Akari's stage, Japanese
I'm getting closer
No matter how thin the hair is
It's thin
What is it?
Moraisu
No way
I sang it
Kaiki, let's go
N1 Grand Prix
Next, Oga Taro
I used to be a one-man show
But I became a two-man show
I'll show you a cool expression
I'll show you a super cool expression
What is this?
Please show me the original
I'm wearing makeup so I can't tell
I can't tell
Thank you
What timing
Will Yasumoto get a cucumber in revenge?
What do you mean?
It's good
I want a cucumber
Let's go
N1 Grand Prix
Shiro Tano's challenge
That's cheating
Why is it cheating?
Here it comes
It's coming
Moraisu
Kobayashi
I don't like that person
What is that?
It's a interview
When they did an interview for a cafe
They were scared
What's wrong with you?
I don't know
She imitates Natouma to her
Oh, no!
When she came to have dinner with her
family, she and mother, they'll come to
visit for eating
So this position musical Supphã
She is love
I got a good one.
Good job.
It's my mom's.
It's your mom's.
Good job.
No no, kashiwagi kashiwagi
Why are you laughing at me?
I have a female Gundam, a female Gundam
That's nice
You're laughing
This is
It's really funny
But it's not funny
It's not funny?
What is it?
You have to punch
It's not good
You have to punch it
It's not funny
This is a joke that gives you a good
mood
I won't let you go until you let me go
Why are you laughing?
Cucumber's earring
I can't see the point of laughter
There is such a difficult color
You're laughing
I think it's better not to do my best
I think so
Hey Riko
What is it?
That's a little weird
What are you doing?
What is it?
I think it's like a husband and wife
I got it!
Wait, why are you giving it to me?
No, it's not
It's like a serious scent is coming
closer
It's coming closer
It seems that Nakayama's stomach is
stimulated when he didn't go as expected
How will the members move after
understanding this?
These five people are currently getting
the cucumber
Who will shine as the first champion of
the L1 Grand Prix?
I see, there are still a lot of
cucumbers
I want it!
I want it too
What is that?
My body is hard
I won!
I'm sorry!
The person who can pull out this sword
is a legendary hero.
Let's pull it out!
The cucumber that I almost ate!
Dra Gimme Only!
I'm really happy
I'll do my best
Ready, set, go
I want to open all of them
Because it hurt
It hurt?
Because the back hurts
It made a sound
So the winner of N1 Grand Prix is...
Matsuno
The first winner of N1 Grand Prix is...
Rina Matsuno
N1 2016, please look forward to it
Ebichu
It's a serious sports day
Next episode, the Ebichu serious sports
day in Autumn
The red team and white team, who will
win?
And the person who missed Ebichu Tastas
will get a reward
On the Star Dust channel, Ebichu Tastas
is streaming on the monthly video
streaming site
I'm a little nervous
I don't think they'll let me win from
the bottom of my heart
The monthly video streaming site, you
can watch that scene
And there are a lot of exclusive videos
that are not on air
For more information, search on the Star
Dust channel
This program was provided by the sponsor
We will do our best to run