Next, I would like to introduce you to
this curry.
This is the curry from the Uminosachi
restaurant.
It's a spicy natto topping.
Natto? You put natto in curry?
Yes.
I love this so much that I can eat it
every day.
You know, rice and the root of the bean
sprout are separated.
I think it's up to you how to eat it,
but I have my own way of eating it.
I'll learn that.
Please follow the order and try it.
Yes.
It's very spicy.
It smells like natto.
Yes.
I usually order 8 spicy level, but I
order 10 spicy level when I want to eat
more.
I'll eat it with Mirei today.
The most interesting thing about this
restaurant is that the spiciness is
different depending on the store.
I think that's one of the points to
enjoy.
First, take only natto and put it in
curry.
Natto curry...
It's like a Kokoichi lesson.
You shouldn't underestimate the
spiciness of Kokoichi.
It's very spicy.
By adding natto, the curry will be
sticky and mild.
When you add rice, the curry will be
sticky and delicious.
Making curry well with natto, and
whenever you are at Kokoichi, you can
prepare that keihime.
You can enjoy it more than usual.
Mix it well.
It will be sticky.
I think you know that we eat at
Kokoichi.
But we have never introduced this way of
eating.
You know that.
So, please put white rice in it and eat
it.
Titanic
This is guerrilla developmentึ
It's really good.
The special thing about Coco Ichi's
curry is that it's spicy later.
So, please enjoy the spiciness and feel
the sweat coming out of your pores.
You're introducing it like you're in a
sauna.
It's spicy.
I like natto, but I've never eaten natto
pasta.
Please try it.
Yes.
I'll eat it.
It's good.
It's good, isn't it?
It's strange.
It's not spicy.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I'm going to eat two or three bites and
then I'm going to eat slowly.
That's right.
It's the charm of Coco Ichi's curry.
I see.
It's like chickpea.
Chickpea?
Natto.
It's a unique taste.
It's like eating chickpea.
It's amazing.
It's curry, so it's hot.
It's spicy.
It's different from the previous one.
It's hot.
It's really hot.
It's delicious.
I worked at Cocoichi.
What?
I can make this curry every day.
Makanai is also Cocoichi's curry.
To be continued.
I'm not good at tuna mayo.
I feel like tuna is fish on my head.
Mayo is like stomach.
I'm not good at it.
I can't eat it, but I like it.
Only takoyaki sauce?
Yes.
Only sauce?
No, I mean mayonnaise.
Is that all?
That's all.
That's good.
What's your weakness?
Celery, coriander, myoga.
I'm not good at it.
I don't think there are many people in
our group who can't eat something they
don't like.
That's good.
So, we don't have much disagreement when
we decide what to eat.
Ebichu-chan is a big age group and there
are many people.
How do you decide what to eat?
It's very difficult.
Kobayashi Kaho is a picky eater.
I think she's delicious.
Okubo Yuno and Nakamura Yuna are a
little different.
I like the food that looks like a plate
for children.
Hamburg steak and fried shrimp.
I've become a little more mature
recently, so I can eat a lot.
I can eat it plainly.
It's impossible.
I can't stop drinking tea.
And I smoke shiitake mushrooms.
I smoke mushrooms.
I clean up all the mushrooms.
I see.
And I like...
What kind of diet is that?
I like the taste of ingredients.
I can't eat something with a strong
taste.
I see.
I like hot calpis made by my
grandmother.
But I don't like the one made by other
people.
It's strange.
I don't know the standard.
I see.
It's strange.
I think that if you have a bento box or
catering, everyone will get excited.
Meat?
Of course, meat.
I agree.
If you have roast beef, it's very
popular.
It's gone soon.
Don't you have a fight with the kids
downstairs?
Food is the cause of the most fights.
I think I'm the cause of the fights.
I want to hear more about that.
People tend to say,
You can eat what you like as much as you
want.
I think so.
People say that a lot.
I like delicious food.
When I find roast beef in front of me, I
eat a lot of it because it's delicious.
Su-chan, you should think of everyone.
You're a smart girl.
I see.
When I eat it, I can't stop.
I'm scared.
I love fruits.
I eat a lot of fruits.
The president sometimes gives me some.
I like mangoes and pineapples.
I eat them without stopping.
I'm scared.
I'm a bad person.
I'm going to take a lot of pictures
before Mirei notices.
Everyone is watching Mirei.
I'm sorry.
Do you have a fight in the group?
Do you have a fight?
I don't have a fight.
But the choreography changes depending
on the teacher.
I have a fight with my right foot or my
left foot.
That's common.
I'm scared.
Please register your channel.
I often hear people say,
Hinata and Mayama,
you're so bad at this.
Isn't it definitely the right?
Left?
Right?
What I do is,
I watch YouTube videos
that are on the official channel,
and I always say, this is definitely the
left.
I'm like, what?
Is it bad to do a freestyle?
But the choreography is quite different.
Which choreography?
We have the same conversation.
It's not like we're all in sync,
but in terms of performance,
which foot was which,
the palm of the hand was up,
or down,
or the details,
or the groove, or the part,
but when there's four of us,
sometimes we split up into two.
Wow, that sounds really hard.
Who's usually in sync?
Shiorin is usually in sync,
but recently, we're all in sync.
But I'm like,
I don't care which one I'm in sync with.
It's fine if I'm in sync with the right
or left hand.
If there's that many people,
it's fine,
but we're also in sync on YouTube.
Is it different when it's freestyle?
Yeah, it's different.
It's different from time to time.
We're all in sync, but we're not in sync
with the right or left hand.
It's because it's different.
The dance in the beginning is the most
correct.
This is also common, but only when you
want to check the choreography.
Up to the camera.
Please subscribe to our channel.
I was like, that's so nostalgic!
Before you graduated, you were doing a
produce performance.
So we were doing 10 years of
performance,
and you were doing 3 performances,
and you were doing a medley of old indie
songs.
I was like, what was that like?
And it was so funny.
We were so excited that we almost lost
our necks.
We were dancing so happily.
We were like, Mirei, your neck is
broken.
I see.
But the other day,
we were like,
if we were in a group like this, we'd
push it.
We were so excited.
I thought, it's too late to be an idol
like this.
We were talking about the same thing.
RENI was dancing really hard.
I thought it was amazing.
I was moving a lot to follow RENI's
dance.
You can't follow her dance.
I was watching her dance from the
bottom.
Her neck was like this.
It's nostalgic.
I know.
I didn't know there were groups like
that.
I didn't know we were so hard-working.
We say the same thing.
It's embarrassing to say that.
Sometimes, when we don't dance or sing
for a long time, we forget the
choreography.
We're used to old songs, but we often
forget the choreography.
I'm scared of dancing to a choreography
I don't know.
It's the opposite of what I expected.
I'm scared of dancing to a choreography
I don't know.
I know.
We've been doing this for over 10 years,
so we're not good at it.
I don't want to do this song.
I know.
But we're still in our 30s and 25s.
We're still in our 30s and 25s.
We'll keep up with you.
We got some really spicy food from the
show.
Yes.
Black Bokkeum Myun.
Black noodles.
I've actually eaten this before.
It's delicious, isn't it?
Yes, Mire-chan, you have it too?
I put cheese in it and eat it at home.
It's really delicious.
That's right.
It's delicious.
When I first met this, I couldn't eat
spicy food.
I bought it in Korea and ate it.
Oh, I see.
It was so spicy that I was surprised.
I drank all the milk.
I'm going to eat it.
Let's eat.
it's easy to lay them out.
Yeah, it will be good for sure.
Really useful, makes you feel useful.
Housing got in the way recently because
of the horror nails.
I know.
Lately I was worried about it.
How mean!
When using the sitter pen mostly,
I could barely hold the ribbon
even though I can fix it here.
I agree.
Such meekness.
My thumb is a problem because I can't
hold the eyelash curler.
It's so rough.
Yeah, it's like a gyaru.
I had a gyaru at home.
You're a gyaru, right?
Yeah, I'm a gyaru.
I was a gyaru because I admired gyaru.
It's good.
This is also good.
I often eat this at home.
I want to eat spicy food while drinking.
I eat it at that time.
Mirei can drink it.
What kind of alcohol do you drink with?
I drink soju.
Recently.
I want to drink it when I have nothing.
I thought it was good to drink while
eating.
I didn't have a chance to talk to Mirei.
I was sad.
I didn't have enough time.
Please call us again.
Please subscribe to our channel.