I'm Mirei Hoshino, the voice actress for
Chibitsue Bichi.
Today I realized what I wanted to do in
my previous live stream!
Now, let's introduce our guest!
I'm Reni Takagi from Momoiro Clover Z!
Thank you for introducing me!
I heard you like spicy food, so I wanted
to try it!
I think so. We don't have many people
who can eat spicy food.
We always eat spicy food by ourselves.
I was in the staff room.
I have a question.
I heard that you were a beginner.
I couldn't eat spicy food at all.
But when I wanted to eat spicy food...
When I was in middle school, I ate spicy
food.
I was told that it was spicy, and I
asked someone to eat it.
How did you get to eat spicy food?
In our group, Arin is like that.
She can't eat spicy food.
We wanted to make a group that could eat
spicy food.
So we tried to eat spicy food little by
little.
At first, I wanted to try it.
I went to a spicy school.
I was in the 3rd or 4th grade.
I was told that it was spicy.
But I got better and I could eat it.
The teacher also said that.
Even children can't eat spicy food at
first, but they can eat it.
I was told that spicy food can be
trained.
I see.
You can eat spicy food with that.
But you can't eat spicy food now.
I like Nakamoto.
I don't know much about Nakamoto.
But Nakamoto is spicy.
At first, I ate normal food.
I wanted to eat it.
I ate it with my friends.
It was delicious.
I ate it alone after the live.
I want to eat it.
What is it after the live?
I want to eat spicy food.
I understand.
Today is New Year's Day.
I want to eat spicy food for New Year's
Day.
Do you have any spicy food you want to
eat?
Red spicy food is limited.
I want to eat it.
Is it limited?
I can't buy it on the Internet.
Red spicy food is 10 spicy.
I've never tried it.
Let's eat it.
I eat red spicy food.
Thank you for watching.
We're ready, so here's what we're going
to eat.
We're going to eat the red hot pot,
which is the 15th challenge.
It looks scary.
It looks like a demon.
I'm curious.
Let's eat.
It's bright red.
It's really red.
Isn't it great?
It's good.
There is udon.
In cold season,
it's good to eat hot food.
It's bright red.
It's great.
It's like a pond of demons.
Let's start with the soup. Itadakimasu.
Oh!
Mmm!
It's good!
It's a good level of spiciness.
It's good, it's good, it's good.
It's like a spicy level of umami.
It's a good level of spiciness.
Right?
There are some that are just spicy,
right?
There are.
To be honest, I was afraid of it.
I've only been to a level of 8 or 7.
It's like, ah!
It's like a seafood soup stock.
The sweetness is...
It's good.
It's umami.
I can eat this.
Have you ever failed to eat spicy food?
Peyoung.
Peyoung's...
The finale, where Emma cries.
We did a video of us eating that on our
birthday.
It was so spicy, it hurt so much I
couldn't talk.
You can see it on TV, but Thai people
are really good at eating spicy food.
But Thai people can't eat it either.
Even Thai people can't eat it.
It was like a death sauce. It was
painful.
It hurt everywhere I went, and I got a
stomachache.
I got a stomachache the day after.
It was a funny video.
I was like...
Ah!
Wow!
You did it!
Wow! Sorry!
You did it, Mirei!
I did it!
Check! Okay, we're good.
Okay, we're good.
I'm glad. I'll be careful when I eat.
Especially the hard ones.
We're like that too, but Ebichu-chan,
you're like a junior to me.
No, I'm not. I'm a junior.
You're definitely a junior.
I'm a junior. Let me be a junior.
Ebichu-chan, you're not a regular, but
you have a graduate student and a new
member.
I don't know about the environment
because there's no monoplay.
How is it?
It changes every time.
Even if one person graduates, the
atmosphere changes.
I think it was a big deal for Hinata to
graduate.
I've been doing it with her, so I was a
little lonely.
We're in the same group of 10 people,
and it's a strange feeling.
That's why I wanted to ask.
We'll be members in a year, but we're
like relatives.
What kind of conversation do you have
when it's hard at first?
The members of Kokubo Yuno talk about
things they don't know.
I've been talking about my relatives'
friends for a long time.
Even if I keep quiet, I'll keep talking.
Even if I say, I'm like that.
It's a great sense of relativity.
I think it's great.
She gives me gummies.
What's going on?
I'm the opposite.
It's a strange thing, isn't it?
It's strange.
At that age, you carry sweets.
I have a lot of sweets.
I eat a lot of sweets after the kids
come in.
I was surprised the other day.
When I asked my manager to buy me
something at a convenience store,
I saw an egg hole.
I'm sorry. I've asked him to buy me
something since I became an adult.
I've asked him to buy me something since
I became an adult.
It's a simple question.
I feel the generation gap.
I feel it, too.
This is a popular questionnaire.
What's popular in the group?
I think the girls who are taking TikTok
videos are the ones who are younger than
me.
I see. Kokona is taking TikTok videos
quite often.
She is taking TikTok videos quite often.
She is not taking TikTok videos by
herself.
She is taking TikTok videos.
I can feel the generation gap.
I can feel it.
I'm happy.
I didn't know what to do at first.
We are at different ages and have
different senses.
I started from the point where I could
do it.
It was difficult.
The formation and choreography of TikTok
videos are different.
The choreography of TikTok videos was
made by three people.
Last year, we made the choreography of
TikTok videos of members.
We are not the same teacher.
So, the other teachers are taught by
members.
We have grown up a lot.
We have a good relationship.
It's a mystery.
If there are middle school students in
the same group, it will be like a
parent's heart.
The most important thing is a
choreography of TikTok videos.
I want to put a test on Google Calendar.
I miss that time.
A middle school test.
It's so cute.
I miss that time.
Like a graduation ceremony.
It must be hard.
We've been through a lot of difficulties
in the same group.
How long have you been in the group? 14
years?
Yes, 14 years.
I see.
Oh my god.
I didn't know you've been doing this for
a long time.
The members around you haven't changed
much.
Did you get that old?
I feel like I'm still 21.
You're 25 now.
I'm 25.
You're not like Arin.
I'm not.
How old are you now?
Don't say that.
I'm turning 30 this year.
Isn't that crazy?
It's crazy.
When I met you, I thought you were
crazy.
Isn't that crazy?
It's crazy.
I didn't miss it.
I'm crazy, too.
I met you when I was 17.
When I first met you, I was at a concert
with Momokuro and Ebichu.
I remember that.
I was at UDX.
I was at UDX and I was asked to perform
at Q-PON.
I didn't know what to do.
You gave me a lot of clothes.
You're going to tell me that in the
episode, right?
You gave me a lot of clothes.
You're going to tell me that in the
episode, right?
I was so happy.
Isn't that crazy?
I thought you were a senior who gave me
a lot of clothes.
I thought you were a kind person.
When we formed, you said you wanted a
lady.
But Mayama said,
I said,
What's that?
I didn't mean that.
I wish you had told me.
I thought it was better.
As a result, I couldn't choose the
members I liked.
You're talking about the members with
long legs.
I'm not talking about that.
I thought it was that.
Please subscribe to the channel.
Please subscribe to my channel!
It's delicious.
It was delicious.
There are many spicy ones, but this one
has a good umami.
It's sweet. Red pepper is sweet.
It's delicious.
I want to put various ingredients in a
pot and eat it.
This soup is delicious.
It goes well with it. Please try it.
Thank you.
Let's try something else.
I'll introduce you to the next one.