Like a video of shrimp-chewed
Acting lesson at the food store
Yeah
Yes, from now on, the three of us are
Eating delicious meat
In addition, like this
It's normal, isn't it?
Like being sold in the supermarket
I ate meat and fish
The same kind of reaction
Let's do it
Practical acting lesson
I want to do it
I think
I haven't had the opportunity to eat
lately
I can't go
I'm doing it in this period
So
I'm grateful
I was surprised to think it was a big
cut
That's true
To be honest
It's okay to eat
That's right
If you eat gratefully
Is it legal?
If you eat everything deliciously
I'm not going to eat it today
I know that
It's just that
The difference is likely to be possible
Wow
The meat is like a sugar burian sold at
a department store
That's right
That and
About 500 yen in the supermarket
I'm used to it
I have to eat it as delicious as I am
It's difficult
Isn't it surprisingly difficult?
Because it's possible
After all, it's amazing and delicious
I'm impressed
Because it's delicious
How to bake today
I like to bake
But it's a waste to bake good meat
Medium
Medium rare
I'll cut it
It's okay to be well-done
Medium medium rare
Let's make it today
Medium medium medium
It's solid
It's baked
It's a little red
It's a little rare inside
Then please
Please
It's been a long time since I've been to
a restaurant
I'm looking forward to it
The other day, I went to Odawa for a
calendar shoot
It's been a long time since I've been on
a shoot
It was so much fun
It was fun
And the three of us are the first to go
to a shooting
It was a great game
After all, I think I was able to eat
delicious food when I went to such a
place
We won the tournament
It was delicious.
It was a mountainous road.
Let's start acting at the restaurant.
Let's eat.
I eat a fashionable food called Chateau-
Burian.
Have you ever eaten Chateau-Burian?
Yes.
I love it.
I can eat this normally, right?
Yes.
I can eat it all the time.
Look at this.
This is it.
I'm so excited.
I forgot.
This is not a normal project.
I want to eat it.
I eat.
It smells good.
This is soft.
This melts in my mouth.
This is not oily.
This is refreshing and delicious.
This melts in my mouth.
This is very delicious.
This is delicious.
This is not too much.
I can eat this refreshingly.
I want to eat this with various
seasonings.
This is the best.
I will do this as if I forgot.
I am happy.
I will eat this.
I eat this.
This is delicious.
This is true.
This is a good style.
I eat this.
This is delicious.
This melts in my mouth.
This smells good.
Everyone is impressed.
I want to eat delicious food.
This is very delicious.
I eat this CHATON BURRIAN.
I eat this by myself.
This is a 3-day-old baby.
I eat this.
This is really crispy.
This is very soft.
I eat this.
This is different from the beef.
This is very delicious.
This is very soft.
I don't need words.
This is delicious.
I eat this meat.
This looks delicious.
This is very three-dimensional.
I eat this.
This is very fragrant.
This is very delicious.
This is very soft.
This is delicious.
This is easy to understand.
This is a taste that I want to eat
forever.
It's a taste that you can keep eating.
What is the difference between the two?
It's different.
This is not good.
If you eat this first and eat that next
to it, you can be impressed by both.
So you're saying you can't eat it with
this?
I'm impressed if I eat it on a day
that's not today.
Is it delicious?
It's delicious.
I can't use it.
It's not out.
It's a good one.
I'm sorry.
The first bite I ate was good.
The tone of your voice was different.
I was
I'm sorry.
The first bite I ate was good.
The tone of your voice was different.
I'm sorry.
I'm happy.
Next, I will eat the meat of the
supermarket.
Please look at this meat.
This is a very salty meat.
This is very salty.
I will eat this.
This is delicious.
Your voice is low.
This meat is very salty.
This meat is very fatty.
This is a good expression.
This is delicious.
I will eat this.
Both are delicious.
This is a different taste.
This meat is fatty.
It's delicious.
I think this is easier to eat.
I like it easier and fresher.
I feel the wind.
I felt that high-class meat is not
meaty.
It's elegant.
I want to eat rice with this.
Both were delicious.
I eat the next meat.
The smell is different.
The smell of fat and red are different.
I eat this.
I like this meat.
This is delicious.
I understand that this meat is
delicious.
This is more like steak.
This is delicious.
Her taste is different.
Her basic eating skills are poor.
Her eating skills are different.
This is delicious.
The meat is also delicious.
I feel that the number of words has
increased.
I ate this for the first time.
I think so.
This is a sugar-grilled fish with a lot
of meat.
I feel this.
This is the best.
This is a mackerel.
This is delicious.
This is not a performance.
I don't know if you say that.
I'm sorry.
I was motivated to win.
I thought this was delicious.
This is delicious.
It's different.
We've done our report on food.
How was it? Did you feel it?
I felt it.
It's fun to watch the members.
It's fun.
I can understand it.
I didn't see Yasumoto-san's switch.
Mayu-san was already in a hurry.
That's right.
I was in a hurry.
I didn't want to hear your voice.
It's the same for the radio.
I'm motivated.
Who was the most cruel?
It's hard to tell.
I think it's Ayase.
I think it's Shokurepo.
It's a simple future.
I think it's Ayama.
Both are.
Ayase was not good at eating.
It's not good.
Both are delicious.
Both are flat.
I think it's easy to feel the
deliciousness of the meat.
Let's eat.
My shoulders are warm.
What kind of high-class food should we
eat next?
I'm confident in eating deliciously.
Let's increase our vocabulary and do our
best.