This week's Ebichu Tastas is the final
episode of the Tastas trial
I think you will make me feel bad so I
will put this on the wall
That's too much
Who will be judged for what crime?
The shocking verdict continues
Ebichu Tastas start
It's a beautiful day
I'm going to show you the best of me
Thank you for watching
What should I do with the heart of Jun-
Burarin?
Moratorium, moratorium, moratorium,
junior high school student
Add various things to your private Ebisu
junior high school
Ebichu Justice
I'm sorry
This program is provided by the sponsor
you are watching
RGG
In this trial, the prosecutor is the
judge, the lawyer is the prosecutor, and
the members are the
plaintiffs, and the sentence is decided.
The judge's assistant will give the
verdict.
Who will be judged tonight?
Next is this.
Ebi-chūnai Sekuhara Gawaku.
I think I know what it is.
I have no idea.
Who? What does it mean?
Two people.
What does it mean?
The defendant, Mayama Rika, is...
The member's signature, Mayama, was
written on the Sekuhara Gawaku.
What is the content of the Gawaku?
The defendant, Mayama Rika, has a
tendency to touch her butt even though
she is a female.
The members have also made comments.
Therefore, she will be punished for
touching her butt too much.
What a palm Talena
Kenji, keep your face still
Anyone has a testimony?
Yes, Yasumoto
First, Yasumoto's testimony
I've been warning you not to touch your
butt.
But this guy doesn't follow the rules.
Even if I say not to touch, he will
touch.
I want you to listen to what I said
once.
That's all.
Anyone else?
Next, we will hear details of the
accident from Hoshina
When I was riding a small elevator, I
was very close to people
And I often got hit by the car
My face is close to the car
That's very difficult
Thank you very much
Anyone who has been touched, can you
give them a hand?
Everyone has been touched
Everyone is a victim
All the members are victims
So, Yasumoto will try to recreate the
scene of the sexual harassment
So, if this is an elevator
Yasumoto, you are not just saying
But it's always crowded
It's crowded because I'm in the front
I have to pack it up
When I pack it up, I usually go to the
side
I'm usually next to it
So I just touch the person next to me
You just touch?
Yes, I just touch the wall
If I were in the front, I would make
people uncomfortable
So I would do this to the wall
That's too much
If you crouch, you will get hit
That's a different sin
Next, let's see the victim's situation
Please be healthy
I'm healthy
As usual
I'm always like this
You are completely sexual
And Nakayama-san, you don't hate it?
I'm used to it
I'm dry
What did you say?
You have a word for it
You say it's a dry skin
Dry skin
It's like a pose
You say it's a dry skin
The verdict
Is Nakayama's sexual harassment a crime
or not?
Let's move on to the decision.
This is hard.
Members, please raise your cards.
The result of the trial is 3 votes for
the guilty and 4 votes for the innocent.
The innocent is the one who turned the
tables.
It's not that they were touched too much
and got used to it.
The next basic case is this.
They still say they are lazy.
What does that mean?
They are still saying that?
The defendant, Rina Matsuno, is the
first.
What does that mean?
When I drew the loose card.
Oh, that's what it means.
Matsuno's still-losing argument is...
The defendant, Rina Matsuno, is a loose
person in this program.
She tends to be a bit of a loser, and
that's why we have a trial session.
Actually, in the last TASTA trial,
Matsuno was also accused of the same
charges.
So, when you're thinking, your actions
are misleading.
Well, I did that quite often.
I almost cried.
Now.
He has walked through his final years
with tears but he is stillpaced.
I've shown him my effort and my speaker
of the time,
that's why I've become adel always with
this performance,
However,
release time has been over.
Therefore, now I Woosh you under the
powerful support of the supporters
Please subscribe!
Are you still not good at it?
I'm not
You're not good at it?
I see
We have a proof video
Let's watch it
Are they really not good at it?
Let's check the proof video
We did it!
We did it for 5 years
5 years!
We did it!
Thank you for watching!
It's amazing!
Hey!
It's fun!
And this is the last time we've done
this, right?
Matsuno-san, you were holding the
microphone.
When you're with that kind of weird guy,
you don't seem to be interested in him.
I sometimes think he's funny, but at
that time...
Hmm...
I'm guilty!
So you're not feeling guilty?
No, I'm not. I don't want to lie. I want
to be honest with my feelings.
It's a bit of an excuse, but there's
more to it than just Matsuno's words.
When I listen to her seriously, I have
an accident that my face becomes like
that.
What did you say?
I have an accident.
You have a
accident?
That's all.
Matsuno's excuse.
How did the president affect the
members?
I'd like to move on to the decision.
Members, please raise your cards at
once.
Matsuno's decision.
Innocent, innocent, innocent, innocent,
innocent.
So, the winner of the 0-point innocent,
the 7-point innocent,
will be the defendant, Rina Matsuno.
It was a bit of a strong move, but this
time, she won the innocent with a smile,
not tears.
I've been here before.
And after this, there was a huge
controversy about Kobayashi Yasumoto.
Please be kind to me.
And before that...
Ebichu, the narrow path to a lyricist
In this project, Ebichu will challenge
themselves to write lyrics
The project aims to adopt a new song
Previously
I want to write lyrics, but the theme of
the lyrics hasn't been decided yet,
right?
Up until now, they have learned about
writing lyrics in various ways
In the first place, the final goal of
this project is to be adopted as
Ebichu's song
So, first of all, let's decide the theme
of the poem together
However...
Everyone's favorite food song
It's a very unique melody
Good
What are you talking about?
Thank you, thank you, thank you
Thank you, thank you
Thank you
It's a very
But tonight, nice ideas will pop up one
after another.
First, Kobayashi's announcement.
Ta-da!
It's a romantic reality show.
It's like people are dreaming.
Let's hear more about it.
What do you mean?
I thought I wanted to be cast by magic.
That's why I wanted to put romantic
words in the song.
I see.
I've been wondering about it all the
time. What's that picture?
It's a picture book.
Oh, it's a picture book.
I want to be cast by magic.
It's like being sucked into it.
That's right.
You're going to forget your daily life
and draw a dream world, right?
Yes.
It's like a magic book.
That sounds interesting.
Finally, they got some ideas for the
theme.
And the members gave us some nice ideas.
Next, Kashiwagi.
Youth.
You can dance.
I think it's good.
We have spent our youth in Ebitune.
And adults have their youth.
So if we sing the youth we feel now,
I think people who listen to it will
remember it.
I think it's good.
Real feelings.
I don't know about going home from
school, but I think it's youthful to go
to Ebitune.
Everyone has their youth.
Everyone goes home.
I want to hear what kind of youth
Ebitune people have.
They have a different life from people.
So it's good to sing the route of each
person's down-stream.
Sounds interesting.
Like Shin-chan is going to Shin-an.
It's a little lame.
Next, Hoshina.
Let's go.
A special day.
What does this mean?
For example, when you go to a live
concert,
you go to school or work,
and a special day is a live concert.
At that time, you want to listen to it.
On a special day?
Yes.
When there is a school festival during
the Ebitu festival,
it's good to listen to the song before
everyone comes.
It's like a Ebitu festival.
The idea that seems to be the theme of
the poem.
And a
Naver summary
Oh good
This is something that is on the net
I love Naver summary
If you know, it's convenient information
Recently, the site summarizes
information that is a hot topic in the
world
What is it?
It's a lot of information that you can't
do
It's good to be in the process of
learning
It doesn't mean anything if you know it
at all, but it's like a word that you
want to say to someone
It's like a song that summarizes bean
knowledge
For example, all gorillas are B type
Oh, that's right
Good, you are good
Please say A
Is there anything?
When water freezes, it becomes ice
It's not a general thing
That ice is
It's like eating
For example, if it's a shrimp, there's
something like a shrimp note
Aya-chan is tall with her hair
I didn't know that
I didn't know
Is that so?
Do you have it?
Yes
I don't have it today, but sometimes
Is that information?
It's like a song that summarizes bean
knowledge that you can say to someone
who has been in the family for a long
time that it's true
That's good
Now all the opinions are together
Can you decide the theme of the poem?
Which idea is likely to be the most
theme?
I asked the members
Who thinks it's easy to be Hirota?
I see
Summary
The opinion of Hirota is the best!
Next time, based on Hirota's opinion,
the theme of the lyrics is decided!
Please look forward to it!
It's not that great, is it?
After this, Kobayashi Yasumoto's
designated combination is judged.
I have to pay for it, but I'm laughing
too hard.
What is the designated combination of
the great rebellion?
Next is this.
The relationship between the two is
strange recently.
Two people?
Which one?
The defendant, Ayaka Yasumoto, and Kaho
Kobayashi are in front.
The defendant, Kaho Kobayashi, and Kaho
Really?
The defendant and Kaho Kobayashi are
competing for the same time.
What is going on between them?
The defendant, Yasumoto and Kobayashi
have a love affair.
Since Kobayashi joined the show,
Yasumoto has been his teacher.
However, their relationship has been
falling apart.
So, they are going to be the subject of
a love affair.
What does that mean?
I think it's the same as usual.
The love affair.
They are the two people that everyone is
happy with.
They have been working as a couple for a
while.
Moreover,
I was surprised to see the teacher's
love affair.
It's fun.
At the solo live held the other day,
they came to support each other's
private live.
They were able to recognize their love
again.
What is the relationship between the
two?
Is there anyone else who has a witness
testimony?
Yes.
Mayama-san.
First, Mayama will testify about
Kobayashi's strange behavior.
Recently, Kaho-chan has been too close
to Yasumoto.
She has become Yasumoto in her behavior.
She likes him too much.
For example, Yasumoto-san takes back the
snacks from the dressing room.
Kaho-chan also takes it back in the same
way.
That's a little bit annoying.
As an idol, it's not good.
Also, she likes Yasumoto-san too much.
When Yasumoto-san is shooting,
When Kaho-chan is next to her,
She says,
Master, you are amazing.
You are a human being.
She likes him too much.
I don't know what to do.
But, isn't the master at that time
amazing?
Please subscribe to our channel.
The teacher is not very good at it
And even the way he uses words
The way he uses words
The teacher is used to variety
When he goes out, he says words too much
He says it too much
And the way he uses words is dirty
That's the way he uses words
Like Panae
Kaho-chan started to imitate it
I heard that the manager is in trouble
He doesn't want to imitate dirty words
I was watching it just now
He said Panae
The student was smiling down
It's a very dangerous relationship
He smiles down like that
The testimony continues
Nakayama recently noticed something
The teacher is the teacher
What the teacher did was
He said that he had to smile properly
He is forced to smile
Somehow
I see
This is the teacher's embarrassing thing
Then, Kobayashi-san
Have you ever laughed because you had to
force yourself to laugh?
I laughed a few times
If it was like that, I would laugh too
I understand
The teacher will do something
interesting
Please react with your bare hands
We will react with our bare hands too
It's not funny
Everyone has their own standards
Please laugh according to your standards
I don't have to laugh
The teacher is already motivated
Wait a minute
So, for some reason, Yasumoto will
perform a gag
Can Kobayashi make a fake reaction to
the teacher's gag?
I can't do this kind of gag after having
a meeting with my father
It was just like that, everyone else was
laughing except the student
Only the student was laughing
The teacher was just coming in and it
was a little bit weird
That's right
That's how much it was interesting for
Kobayashi
It was interesting
What was interesting?
The existence was interesting
It's not about what to do
It was about the existence
Now, it's time for the final judgement
If you think it's ok to continue the
relationship between the two, you're not
guilty
If you think the relationship is not
good, you're guilty
What will happen?
Now, members, please raise your cards
together
Ready, set, go!
The accused, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 1 vote for
the innocent,
and the defendant, Kobayashi Yasumoto,
is now a guilty verdict.
From now on, the two of you will be in a
relationship with the principal.
You will have to go to a ramen
restaurant with the three of you.
When the verdict came out, the
prosecutor asked a direct question.
Why did you take a break when there were
so many members?
Where did you fall in love with the
prosecutor?
I asked him first, and he said Ayaka.
So I'm here now.
I see.
Here is the birth story of the
designated relationship.
What is the feeling that Kobayashi had
for Yasumoto?
It was different from my first
impression.
At first, I thought he was a pretty guy,
so I thought he was a bit strict.
But he was completely different.
I thought, I want to be like him.
This is a good story.
I see.
The decision was a guilty verdict, but
their relationship will last forever.
We just finished the second trial. How
was it?
I don't want to do it anymore!
I noticed it when I came in, but this is
the second time ive been here.
I see.
Is it a newbie?
Yes, it is.
Is there anything you want to say to the
people inside?
You are a sinful woman.
Next time is the first luck test.
Reina, please come in.
Who is the luckiest among the members?
Please come in.
Check the members' rooms.
Wait a minute.
What is a mysterious mountain?
They will guess their luck with a thin
relationship.
And...
I don't feel like going around in this
room.
Is the mountain blocking you?
Yes, it is.
I am a mountain.
《R för"?
This program was provided by the sponsor
of the program.
I was told to be kind and share the
seat.
You were told that, weren't you?
It's not interesting if you don't do
that.
You're more chivalrous than I thought.
I'm a friend who teaches me how to be
kind.