Ebichu's video
There are a lot of plans for the
November Hoshinami!
So, you probably know my November
schedule.
First of all, the opening night stage
will start from November 1st today.
I hope you can enjoy it with me.
And on the 6th, I will go to Akita.
I'm looking forward to it.
I hope you can enjoy it with me.
And on November 10th, there will be a
birthday party for me.
Thank you for your support.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm going to start the opening night
today.
Thank you for your support.
I was really happy when I decided to do
it.
The bond between the opening night
members has deepened.
I had a lot of plans for the October
Hoshinami.
I had a lot of fun every day.
The content of the performance is the
same as the last time.
The way each character thinks has
deepened.
I think it will be a work that can give
you more courage and power than July.
I hope you can come and enjoy it.
So, I turned 24 on November 2nd!
So, I'll be performing as Mai-chan on
November 2nd as an opening act.
I hope you'll enjoy it.
And please support me, Nabilen, who
turned 24!
I'm Nabilen!
I think those of you who watched my
performance will know that I'm a very
young actress.
I learned a lot from my first musical,
which was very difficult and difficult.
I learned a lot from my last musical,
which was very different from my live
performance.
But we all gathered in one scene and the
moment the curtain fell,
I was so moved by the way I performed.
It was so different from my live
performance.
I had so much fun.
So, I'll be performing as Mai-chan on
November 2nd and 3rd as an opening act.
I'll be performing as Mai-chan on
So, please support me!
Bye-bye!
Today, I'd like to talk about the
birthday party on November 2nd.
The birthday party is coming soon, so I
don't think I've ever had a chance to
talk about my past birthday parties.
So, I'd like to talk about them.
First of all, the birthday party started
in 2016.
What? It's been about 5 years?
Is that right?
Thank you for coming every time.
First of all, I'm particular about my
costumes every time.
I wanted to be mature in 2016.
I wore a
high-end dress, but I prepared two
different styles of clothes in the main
story.
The first one is an idol-like,
energetic, colorful costume.
At that time, my hair was short, but I
wore a twin tail, a twin tail volume,
for the Christmas Day, and I wore a
black twin tail and an idol-like
costume.
I changed it and the
second costume was a very black, cool
costume.
I really admired each other at that
time.
I will never forget the atmosphere that
the audience was excited when I sang
Ariana Grande's song.
I always thought that the atmosphere was
different every year,
but I thought I would do what I wanted
to do at the Christmas Day, so I
left the air of the audience for a while
and did what I liked.
I prepared two different costumes for
2017.
This was a 20-year-old Christmas, so I
didn't forget that the staff said that
it was better to open the champagne
here, so
they prepared it, but I didn't know how
to open it, so I
turned it around and it was carbonated,
but I
shook it so much and turned it around
like this, so when I pulled it out, the
cork
flew away somewhere, and it all came
out, and my hands smelled so bad, and I
drank it for a while and it was really
delicious.
I want to create a completely different
atmosphere with two patterns of
costumes, and the
first one is a ribbon or a flower.
I made it very princess-like and made a
coat.
I like the second costume, but it's a
black and pink costume, and the
black material is a shiny material when
it hits the light, and the
stylist chose the material to be
displayed on the stage and made it.
I'm particular about the fabric.
I made it.
In 2018, I like this dress.
This is a checkered skirt dress.
I wanted to be mature at this time.
I thought about my own clothes and
design.
I made it with a lot of thought.
I liked the checkered skirt dress I had
in my main dress.
I made this dress to match the style of
the dress.
In 2019, it was a rare yellow dress.
I have a pink image.
I have never worn yellow clothes.
I have never prepared a dress for this
dress.
I chose this color.
I wore a jacket on top of a yellow
dress.
I made this dress with a pattern of
wearing and taking off.
In 2020, I was 23 years old.
I thought I wouldn't be able to wear
this dress anymore.
I made a dress that looked like a cake.
The staff applauded me.
I'm sorry to say this.
I was happy to hear everyone's happy
voices.
I couldn't speak, but when I came out, I
couldn't forget everyone's facial
expressions.
I wore this dress because everyone liked
it.
I made a hat with whipped cream and
strawberries.
This hat is very light.
Those who can't be told by language.
This is like a photo goods.
When I was in my early years, I wore
this with my friends.
They took pictures and enjoyed using
this.
I was very happy.
Today is Akita High School day.
Where are you?
Are you in Akita?
Are you at home?
Where are you?
I'm in Akita.
I'm not there now.
It's been a long time since I've been to
Akita High School.
I'm looking forward to it with Akita
fans.
I will definitely eat the kiri-tanko.
I've been doing a lot of Christmas live.
This year, I will hold a talk show.
The second part is Christmas live.
It's my first talk show.
I started my own showroom live this
year.
I had a lot of fun chatting with
everyone.
It was fun to talk about things I like
and hobbies alone.
I will hold a talk show this year.
My favorite friend, SOA-WAN-WAN will be
the guest.
Thank you SOA-WAN-WAN.
I want to go to MIN-E's birthday party.
SOA-WAN-WAN said it was November 10th.
I asked which one would be good to hold
a talk show.
I was wondering which one to hold.
I was wondering if I could hold a talk
show.
I decided.
She is very interesting and a very good
person.
I think you can watch her private live.
I hope you can come to the talk show
with the feeling of going to see your
friend.