The gang parade, which was the largest
group of 13 people in the beginning, was
formed in 2014 and has a long history of
celebrating its 8th year this year.
There, while interviewing the members,
we will explore the gang parade from now
on.
I heard about the plan and gathered the
members.
The theme of this interview is how we
can bring out the story of the
back road we haven't talked about
before.
Please enjoy various human patterns such
as bringing out a story that can't be
used for real and
getting a bad air.
I can't say that.
I'm going to get a pin.
No, I don't need to use it.
It's okay.
There are various things.
Are you a man?
Man?
カメラは開くんだね。 いや、本当に。 マジで何考えてんだろう。
Nice to meet you.
It's not nice to meet you. It's been a
long time.
It's been a long time.
I've been managing since 2017.
I'd like to interview you this time.
I want to follow the history of Gang
Parade.
I want to make sure that the individual
characteristics of each member are
properly shown.
I'm going to interview you one by one.
The first memorial service is...
I'd like to ask Yamanmachi Miki, the
youngest member of the Gang Parade...
Please don't call me the youngest
member.
I'd like to ask Yamanmachi Miki, the
youngest member of the Gang Parade.
First of all, the first group called
Daiki Pisto by Junosuke Watanabe, the
representative of our organization, was
disbanded at Yokohama Arena.
Yamanmachi Miki was on the scene.
Yes, I was in charge of Kamiya Saki.
I see.
I wasn't interested in idols at first,
but I heard from a friend that there was
a group called VISS.
When I listened to the music, it didn't
sound like an idol at all. It was rock.
I thought it was really cool, so I took
my friend to the live show.
After that, you formed a group called
PLANIME.
Then you came to the Tokyo Idol
Festival.
What kind of impression did PLANIME have
on you?
It's different from BIST.
They were dancing and singing, which was
quite shocking.
And the songs were EDM.
There weren't many EDM singers back
then, so it was very new.
And then, you were asked to join the
band,
and you announced that you would recruit
new members.
Yes, I did.
الأs
What happened? 普通にこうお客さんとして行ってる時に、 When
I was with the customer,
現場でこう声をかけてくださった方が、 I was told that I
couldn't get a job. 受けないの?みたいな。 I was
told that there were people who could
get a job. 軽く言われて、 When I went through
the contact list, 面談まで通ると、 I was told
that there were people who could get a
job. サキちゃんもいるらしいよみたいなことを言われて、 I was told
job. タダで会えるチャンスだった。 I didn't have any
money. 私はお金がなかったので。 I applied for this
job because I thought I could meet my
boss for a reason.
私はお死にタダで会える可能性があるのならっていう本当に広い理由で応募しました。
I applied for this
job because I had to go to the office to
do an interview. 歴史をたどりインタビューするってもあるから、
I had to go to the office to do an
interview. その時期に今まで出してない話とかで。 I had to
go to the office to do an interview. I
had to go to the office to do an
interview. 俺も普段何やってるのか一番想像つかないし。 I had
to go to the office to do an interview.
I had to go to the office to do an
interview. 隠して生きていくタイプなんだけど。 I had to go
to the office to do an interview.
隠して生きていくタイプ。 I had to go to the office
to do an interview. 後からピーって隠すようにできるから。 I
had to go to the office to do an
interview. 何かあったかな? I had to go to the
office to do an interview.
工場に行って、冷凍食品を開けたりとか。 I had to go to the
factory, open frozen food, and stuff.
いろいろ募ったりとか。 I had to go to the factory,
open frozen food, and stuff.
そのバイト仲間と付け合ったりとか。 Did you ever work with
your part-time job partner?
ないですね。 No.
ないの? No?
いや、冷やとりのバイトで付き合うことないですか? I've never
worked with my part-time job partner.
マジで一緒にいないのないと。 I've never worked with my
part-time job partner.
同じでもLINEで働いてたらさ。 You'd be like,
なるでしょ、それは別に。 You'd be like,
金を稼ぐために言ってるんで。 I'm going to make money.
When the event was out, it was supposed
to be with Maika from the previous life.
Maika from the previous life?
What kind of group was Maika in at that
time?
It was supposed to be. I don't remember
much.
Well, if NG comes out of Maika, this is
a little...
That's right. And that you're selling
people.
That's what I'm saying.
That's it!
What are you talking about?
It's just a chat.
I'll talk about this time.
I'll talk about it with you next time.
What I really wanted to do was
I wanted you to tell me the first time
you talked about it.
I've been with Yamamachi for a long
time.
There was a moment when Yamamachi became
a woman in me.
I thought I could definitely have a
boyfriend at that time.
Unfortunately.
I haven't been able to do it since I
entered this 7th year.
Because I haven't met you.
You've met me before, haven't you?
No.
I haven't met you.
No, I haven't.
On the contrary, I'm doing it.
You don't do it, do you?
It's like matching.
No, it's not.
It looks like the worst.
I want you to talk about that.
And I heard that from Yamanmata.
You have to find out what you're talking
about.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's hard.
I pretended not to hear you, but I
pretended to be stupid and gave up
I pretended not to see you, but I
pretended to understand you and cried