This week's Ebichu Tastas is the second
episode of Ebichu Tastas Sports
Festival!
Right!
Wait, wait!
Two teams of the two teams are divided
into two teams.
They're going to have a fierce battle.
Which team will win?
Ebichu Tastas, start!
Ebichu Tastas Sports Festival
Let's add a variety of things to the
private Ebisu Middle School!
Ebisu Middle School!
This program is brought to you by these
sponsors.
The last episode was a game without any
competition.
The shrimp-chewed magic game has finally
begun.
The two teams are divided into two teams
and compete for five points.
The members who did their best will
receive a MVP prize.
The next week, Akiyama, the leader of
the Hachioji Tourism Association, will
continue to watch the game.
The first game is a defense match.
This game is a defense match.
The number of balls thrown in within one
minute is the point.
The first player is Akagi. The defender
is Ogata Kaifu.
The defense match will be held in the
red team.
The time limit is one minute.
Let's go!
I won't let you get in so easily.
It's a lot of balls.
You can go over the wall called me.
You can go in and get the ball that
fell.
I was surprised.
Can you go over the wall called me?
Please protect Kaiki.
Don't hit me.
Let me get the ball.
It's dangerous.
Come on.
Kaiki, nice defense.
There is such a rule.
It's called the defense man attack.
It's good.
10 seconds left.
10 seconds.
Come on.
5 seconds left.
3, 2, 1.
Time's up.
There are a lot of balls.
How was the red team?
I can't get in.
I grabbed the ball.
If you throw the ball to the ball of
Kaiki,
it will go in like a basketball corner.
I see.
If you throw the ball,
you will be the white team's second.
It's a basketball corner.
It's difficult.
Next, the high school white team.
Defender, Burikko Takiue.
Will he make it to the 7th or the 9th?
The defenseman is Burikko!
It's Takiue!
Good luck!
I can't cheer for him.
Burikko!
Burikko is too much.
You can take the ball you hit.
I'll do my best.
Burikko, defend properly.
Burikko, you're making a voice.
Burikko!
Burikko, jump!
Burikko, make a voice.
10 seconds left.
Break your shell.
5 seconds.
3, 2, 1.
I lost.
Time's up.
How was the first one?
It was easy.
Burikko was a bit lame.
Now, the results.
1, 2.
You jumped a lot.
2, 3.
4.
That was close.
This match was almost a tie.
Who lost the ball first?
10, 11.
No, no.
It's over.
Red team won.
The red team finished with 17 points.
And...
22...
23 points!
The white team wins!
One, two...
Good luck!
Thank you for watching! Please subscribe
to our channel!
I knew it.
Burikko is the one with the most votes.
Takiue?
Burikko!
What was his name?
Takiue.
What's your name?
Burikko.
I was the defense.
But I don't like Burikko.
Burikko came from Kobayashi.
I don't know if you can tell me from the
middle.
Kobayashi said Burikko.
I thought I saw that hand when he said
Burikko.
You should say it.
Let's ask this person.
Akiyama!
Akiyama, can I have a moment?
Cute!
Chuuya, come back.
Come back.
Akiyama, did you see the battle?
I saw half of it.
I saw the last one.
You only saw that?
I didn't see the battle.
How was it?
I'm glad.
Please watch the game.
I have to watch it.
Please watch it.
Thank you.
The white team wins.
The next game is...
The second game.
The battle between the iron and the
stick.
The rules of this game are...
1 on 1.
The one who sticks to the stick and is
caught longer wins.
There will be 4 rounds in total.
Each team will get 10 points.
Let's start the first round.
Red team, white team, both teams, please
come forward.
Who is it?
Please hurry up.
5 seconds!
What did you do?
How was it?
I was in the rickshaw.
I was in the water and I was scolded for
not being able to do it.
Hoshina, please listen.
What are you doing?
I'm drying my hands.
I see.
You have to dry your hands.
It was meaningful.
It's like a comb.
It's better to wipe it.
The first round is red team leader
Kobayashi vs white team Hoshiga
Ok, purple team Hoshida vs Kobayashi
You lose if you fall first
I can't do it
You can't do it too?
Wait, the way you stand is different
End
You are fast
Ok, it was a moment
15 seconds
Why was it so fast?
The way you grab was like this
Like this
I got advice from you
You can grab anything
But I knew I wasn't good at this
I don't care
Ok, Hoshida won the first round
White team is leading
Next is the second round
Who will go?
The second round is
Hirota and Nagayama
This is also a battle of food
How is it?
Riko is worried because her arm is
strong
Her arm is strong?
I have this but not here
Where?
Not here
It means you are strong
Yes
Nagayama and Hirota seem to be confident
Will they be able to win?
Purple team, Hirota and Nagayama
Ready
Go for it
She is stable
She is sleeping
Nagayama is smiling
She is laughing
Suddenly
Her heel is shaking
Really?
Nagayama is like
She is like
I was laughing and I lost my strength
When I heard the sound, I was like this
When you heard the sound, you were like
this
I didn't understand what you were saying
Hirota won the second round
The red and white teams are lined up one
by one
Next, the third round
Who will be in the third round?
The red team is Kashiwagi
The white team is Matsuno
How is Kashiwagi?
I'm scared
Do you have confidence?
I don't know how much Matsuno will come
out
I want to win Matsuno
What happened?
A bug came
It came to cheer
I'm not focused
Matsuno is in a good mood
But he has a great plan
The third round is Kashiwagi vs Matsuno
The red team is Ritetsubo
Kashiwagi vs Matsuno
Good luck, Hina
Good luck
I'm scared
It smells like a high level
Good luck
I'm scared
I crossed the wall for the first time
15 seconds have passed
How much is it?
It's stable
Matsuno is breathing
He is sitting
30 seconds have passed
Good luck
Matsuno is doing yoga
Matsuno is breathing
Good luck
He is breathing
It's bad
Kashiwagi is bad
Hina was sitting
1 minute has passed
How was it?
My hands are paralyzed
It's red
It's like the sun
It's like the sun is shining
Matsuno, how was it?
I felt strange for the first time
Because she was breathing deeply
I thought it was a special breathing
method
It was like yoga
Matsuno, the leader of the white team,
won with her own breathing method
And the white team is leading again
The 4th round is Mayama vs Yasumoto
I heard Yasumoto has a secret
I got advice that I shouldn't laugh
I'll do my best with a straight face
Ok, the battle between Mayama and
Yasumoto
Ready?
Go for it
This is bad
Already?
Aya, straight face
My shoulder hurts
It's going to be a muscle
Which one is better?
The bent one or the straight one?
I think the bent one is better
Like this figure
Yasumoto is cool
I thought Mayama was strong
Yasumoto is a man
He is a man
It was serious
Mayama is like that
Mayama is amazing
How was Yasumoto?
I was too conscious of the straight face
It was funny
You were a man several times
The face is sharp
After the 4th round, they won with 2
wins each
They will select the representative and
have a final battle
Please come to the front
Who is it?
Red team is Hirota, white team is
Hoshino
This is going to be interesting
Why did you choose Hirota?
Rock paper scissors
Rock paper scissors?
Both of you were strong
Why did you choose Hoshino?
Are you listening?
Hoshino is sweating
After this, Hirota and Hoshino will have
a battle
Who will win the battle?
The word game is getting more exciting
Red team vs White team, who will win?
After the match, they will have a two-
win match.
The battle between the two teams is
called the Burasagari Tetsubo-Majigaman
Battle.
The two teams will have a battle of the
top.
The battle between the two teams is
called the Top Battle.
It's the battle between Hirota VS
Hoshina.
Ready?
Go for it!
As expected, it's a battle of the top.
Are you sleeping?
I feel relaxed.
It's amazing.
It's the longest battle.
I see.
I feel concentrated.
Hoshina is relaxed.
Hirota is relaxed too.
If I were a purple, I would be fat.
I heard that if you were a magma, you
would be fat.
Don't make me laugh.
I heard that if you were a magma, you
would be fat.
If you were a magma, you would be fat.
I'm sorry.
I want to hold it.
It's almost 1 minute.
I'm tired.
You were in the middle of the battle.
It's the longest battle so far.
It's 1 minute and 28 seconds.
I'm tired.
I was surprised when I was in a panic.
I laughed and thought I would do better.
I was trying hard and heard that I was a
magma.
Why did you do magma?
I thought it was dangerous.
If you were a purple, you would be a
magma.
If I were a purple, I would be fat.
I didn't hear anything in the second
half.
It's the most important part.
White team wins.
If they add the advantage of purple,
iron, and magma,
the white team will be more leading.
It was a good battle.
Let's ask the person who won.
Akiyama.
Can you come here?
Come back.
I don't know.
Do you like it?
I'm sorry.
I was watching you.
I want to say that it was not a big
deal.
I'm happy.
Young people are amazing.
I was impressed by your power
I hope I won't lose
Did you hear the word Eien?
Yes, we heard it
Thank you very much
Thank you
You are good
Please return to the first place
Thank you
The third contestant who will be the
leader of the white team is
Koro-Gashi
Will there be a reversal?
The two of them will roll the big ball
It's a tie
This contest will be
The two of them will roll the big ball
The corn that was placed on the course
will be
Turned in the order of numbers
After a round,
Touch the next runner
The winner of the second runner
Who scored the goal first
The winner will get 50 points
Good
If I win, the red team will get the
reverse point
I see
I thought the score was quite open
But it's not
Even if it's a win
It's okay
First, they decide the order of running
and playing
The white team is very competitive
What kind of strategy will they use?
Let's do that
The runners will be announced
The first runner of the red team is
These two
Hirotapia and Kashiwagi
And the runner of the second
That's right
How did you decide this?
Good part, first place, Jas
Good part?
First place, Jas
It's a rock-paper-scissors
I'll decide after the first place
I see
And the white team
They are always playing
Seriously
The runner of the first
I see
Hoshina raised her hand like this
And the runner of the second
How did you decide this?
I think the runner should be tall
And the runner should be short
Rina taught me
I don't know
Like a stick
I see
The pair's compatibility is important
This is the point
The white team decided the height
difference
Can they stop the red team?
Let's begin!
Let's go.
coins rollingHow many coins are there,
Readyrio
Freely
This time, this is shining
Everyone stance outside
Turn heard an outside
The outside of the cone
It's going to fall
What?
The red one is going to fall
It's not done yet
It's going to fall
Is it going to fall?
It's okay
Don't do that
The outside of the cone
Who is that?
The red one is going to fall
The outside of the cone
The red one won
Good luck Shiro
The last one
How is it?
Be motivated
What happened?
My stomach hurts
The winner is the red team
It was close
There was a strategy to be more cautious
It didn't matter
But you said you were good
It depends on how you do it
You were laughing
I was laughing without doing anything
You didn't need to be the one laughing
I'm sorry
When the red team lost the white team
Matsu was holding the ball
You were holding the ball
That's why you were getting dirty
It was like a spinning wheel
Red team got 50 points
It was a great comeback
There are two things to be said
The next episode of Ebichu Tastas will
be the final episode of Ebichu Tastas
Sports Festival.
The last episode of Ebichu Tastas will
be the final episode of Ebichu Tastas
Sports Festival.
And the person who missed Ebichu Tastas
will be reported. Ebichu Tastas is being
broadcast on the Star Dust channel, a
video streaming site.
The food is free of charge for 400 yen a
month.
In addition, there are a lot of
exclusive images of the unreleased on
air.
For more information, please check the
Star Dust channel.
This program was provided by the sponsor
you are watching.
This time, the MvP of the sports
festival is...
What is a Blu-ray?