Second The Canadian bison and the idol
Then there is our third question.
Sweet Tokyo
Do you like sweet things?
I awww love them.
How about it? What's your example?
My favorite food is crepe.
The second one is pancake.
The third one is donut.
The fourth one is pudding.
It's brainstorming.
I was noticed that I was a sweet tooth
after I met my members.
Oh, really? What made you notice?
I started to go on a trip with my
members.
And we ate together.
We ate together.
We had a lot of opportunities.
At that time, my taste in food was
different.
When I was asked what I wanted to eat,
everyone said meat or seafood.
But they said pancakes for lunch.
I see.
I want to eat rice.
And sweets paradise.
Yes, sweets paradise.
I love sweets paradise.
I know that.
We ate 17 cakes.
That's a lot.
I see.
I was told that it was disgusting.
I was told that it was an excessive
sweet.
It's just a sweet.
I was told by the members that I was a
sweet.
I see.
But I think my power is...
I'm a sweet tooth.
I eat sweets and work hard on the stage.
This is one of my three best qualities.
I see.
You don't eat sweets before a live show,
do you?
I do.
Really?
When I was 19 years old, I tried to put
custard cream on my stage drink.
But I was stopped.
Please stop it.
Really?
Yes.
You want to go to the concert?
Do you have a chance to go to the
concert?
Yes, during the MC.
I can go to the concert.
I will go.
I've seen you eating fried chicken.
But you don't have a mouth.
I want to sing with a clear voice.
I want to eat sweets and satisfy my
hunger.
I want to see the sweets event.
I want to do sweets.
I want to do a sweets shoot.
I think you and ARIN have similar tastes
in food.
I love fried chicken.
I think we have similar tastes in food.
But you know, the gal aspect of you is
also...
You know, you said you admired the gal.
You took a mysterious action.
Yeah, yeah.
Then, it might be interesting if we can
shoot something.
Yeah.
Cheers!
Thank you!
Happy!
We can't grow the same crop for two
years in a row.
Because of the soil?
Yes, because the soil is not good.
I couldn't take measures against it.
This program is
by Ryosuke
by Ayami Ato-dango
by Yo-chan
Thank you for watching!
I sent it to you with the offer of
Takuya-san!
Please listen to it tomorrow too!
Rock, paper, scissors!