Good evening, welcome to DORESKI and
KORESKI. I'm MC, Hanachii Iwai.
I'm Kumada Akane. Thank you for having
us.
We have invited the members of the idol
group, BOLT, as usual.
BOLT.
BOLT, it's been 3 years since you last
came here.
Iwai, do you have any memories of this
time?
This time?
Ah, I see. You suddenly come up with
difficult questions.
That's right.
This is difficult.
Extremely difficult.
Extremely difficult questions.
Not everyone has such a question.
That's true.
Then let's talk about something else.
What is it?
I bought something recently.
I was happy.
What did you buy recently?
What did I buy recently?
TV.
You were trying to move it around a lot.
Yes, it was a TV that could move.
Isn't it amazing?
The tuner is separate from the TV.
If you have a power cord, you can move
it anywhere in the house.
Amazing!
You don't have to connect it to the TV.
Isn't it amazing?
It's amazing.
How is it? Don't you buy a picture room?
The picture quality is really good.
It's the latest version of Panasonic.
Oh, really?
That's great.
You can put it on the bed.
Isn't it really good?
Even if you try to look at it while
leaning against the wall,
Normally, you have to face the direction
of the TV.
Bring it straight to the front.
It's the best.
It's not going to get stuck in your
neck.
That's not true.
The neck is normal.
So, please watch it on TV.
What are you doing?
Don't do it randomly.
Let's start.
Music variety Dresky and Koresky
Watch the next one!
Today's guests are the people of Bolt!
We are Bolt!
I'm Luna Naito!
I'm Chihou Taka!
I'm Aya Shirahama!
Nice to meet you!
This is the second week.
Thank you!
This time, we will introduce a new
attraction with various talk themes!
Dorekore Box!
Please draw from the Dorekore box!
I will draw!
I draw one.
I drew two last time, so I will draw
one.
I draw!
This is a refreshing method.
Is there a refreshing method?
I have a dog.
I have a dog, and I come home with the
dog.
I say, I'm home!
I give him sweets and play with him.
I can refresh myself.
Do you get stressed?
I don't get stressed.
I see.
I have a stiff shoulder these days.
I have a backpack.
Really?
I often get my dog to step on me.
You get your dog to step on you?
What kind of smart dog is that?
I get a massage.
I see.
You get a massage.
Yes.
Not a high.
You get a massage.
I get a massage.
Takae, please listen to the story.
Yes.
I will start.
Ta-da!
I was disappointed.
I'm a clumsy person.
I was disappointed when I was 20 years
old.
I often go on a tour at a live concert.
I often stay alone at hotels.
I was sleeping in the gap between the
bed and the wall.
I had a smartphone in my hand.
I like to play music before I go to bed.
I was playing music on my phone.
I couldn't put my hand in my phone.
I called my friend for the first time.
I was embarrassed to be asked to play my
favorite music.
What kind of music are you listening to?
I was listening to various people.
I was playing music until the front came
to my room.
I couldn't stop playing music.
Your music is playing.
I was surprised.
This is a comment from an artist.
What did you just say?
Did you say the comment from an artist?
This is a comment from a singer.
Please enjoy the recording.
Hello, viewers of Doreski and Kore-Ski.
I'm Ishihara Kaori, voice actor.
I'm a character called Minions.
I've never liked a mascot before, but I
fell in love with it for the first time
in my life and went to see it in the US.
I'm an artist.
On August 3rd, I released my 9th single,
Musouteki Chronicle and my 10th single,
Abra Kadabu.
Musouteki Chronicle is a song that gives
you courage when you start something.
Abra Kadabu is a cool song that loves
his loved ones.
Both songs have completely different
tastes, so I expressed it in the music
video.
Musouteki Chronicle is a refreshing and
dramatic music video that makes you cry.
Abra Kadabu is a cool dance that is very
connected to the camera.
It's a music video that makes you want
to keep your eyes on it.
Please watch it.
That's all from me, Ishihara Kaori.
Next Episode
Next, please.
Thank you.
I'm not good at things.
I had a chance to go to a amusement park
at school.
I went with everyone at school.
I'm not good at ghost houses.
I can't go to a ghost house.
I don't like the atmosphere of ghosts.
I went in with a friend.
My friend asked me to shake hands.
I was given a mission to shake hands.
I was surprised to hear that.
I asked my friend to shake hands.
Did you shake hands with a ghost?
I was told to shake hands with a ghost.
I was surprised to hear that.
I laughed more than I was scared of
ghosts.
I was able to go to a ghost house.
I'm happy.
What is your recent hobby?
I eat with Takaichiho.
You take pictures of food with
Takaichiho's check.
I'm addicted to it.
Fans often take pictures of food with
our check.
I take pictures like a hamburger.
I also admired it.
I got a check from a member.
I always carry it with me.
I also take pictures of delicious food
with Takaichiho's check.
You are a bad person.
I'm a bad person.
I am a bad person.
I am always eaten by Takaichiho.
You are different.
I'm addicted to it.
I don't like your check.
I want you to tell me what kind of check
you have.
Please look forward to it.
On August 10th, the first EP, Weather,
was released!
Congratulations!
Thank you!
What kind of EP is it?
The title is Weather, but it's an EP
that has a lot of songs that have
changed depending on the weather and the
feelings that change depending on the
environment.
Even if you listen to all the songs,
it's an EP that you can listen to in 19
minutes.
It's a total of 6 songs, but I'd like
you to listen to it.
If you make it shorter, it's about 30
seconds.
It's a short time, isn't it?
Among them, By My Side is also the
opening theme of DOREKORE August.
Thank you!
Please tell us the charm of this song.
This song is a song that is also in the
MV, but it has a pop and punk feel like
a go-bot, and the lyrics are strong, but
it's a little embarrassing.
Please listen to it a lot.
That's great. Thank you.
And what kind of feeling is it in the
MV?
The weather was really nice on the day
we shot the MV.
So we shot the MV in the blue sky and
our costumes.
It's really popular, and if there's a
facial expression that everyone looks
really happy with the lyrics,
In the scene where we're dressed cool
and cool, the dance is really intense,
so it's a perfect music video for the
summer.
That's also a point of interest.
So, Kumada-san, Bolt-san, you came to
Nishu, how was it?
Everyone was so cute, and I felt like I
was a big sister.
I agree.
Shirahama-san, you're a middle schooler,
so you really want to raise your
allowance.
I feel like I'm a relative.
Yeah, like a relative.
I'll buy you things you want.
I'll buy you the latest clothes for your
classmate.
That's so nice.
I'll make you the most rich classmate.
That's nice.
I think so.
That's a great love.
You're a big brother.
Iwai-san, we'll read a message from a
viewer.
It's from Oden-dan.
Thank you.
Good evening, Kumada-san and Iwai-san.
The other day, I went to B's concert,
and the bassist of the support members
was so cool that I was struck by his
heart.
What kind of person would you like to
have as a support member, like Harai-chi
and Kumada-san's music activities?
B's.
I knew it was B's.
B's?
Yeah.
I didn't know that for the first time.
What kind of person?
I'd like someone who's bright.
I don't want a dark support member.
That's true.
The whole thing gets dark.
That's right.
We have a lot of rehearsals.
I want someone who's bright.
When I say, who's the support guitar?
I'm sorry.
If you do that, I think you'll stop the
live.
I think I'll be shocked.
I don't want you to pay attention to me.
I want someone who says, let's get
excited.
I want a support member who's like a
support.
That's right.
I want a support member who knows that
you're just a support.
I'm so surprised.
You didn't have the ability to form a
band and be able to perform on stage.
That's why you're a support.
I'm surprised.
You want a support member, right?
I'm not saying that.
You're a support member because you
can't be the main.
Please stop it.
I'm saying that we should work together.
You want someone who's bright.
I'm sorry.
I'm bright.
I want a bright person.
I'm sorry.
How many stickers do you give to Oden-
dan?
I give you 10 stickers.
We are looking for messages and requests
for the show.
Please send it to the official website
of the program.
Kumada Kokuchi chance!
If you can answer the question
correctly, you can get a notice.
Thank you.
Let's start. Quiz about Saitama.
Yes.
Which of the following is the
catchphrase of the city's image?
A. Sukusuku City, Saitama City
B. Nobi Nobi City, Saitama City
C. Anshin Anzen Heiwana Machi, Saitama
City
Which one?
This is...
This is something that a great person
would think of, right?
Yes.
I don't know if a great person would
think of this.
Really?
I don't know.
It's an image catchphrase, so I might
have asked for it.
Oh, you might have asked for it.
I don't know.
I said I don't know.
Oh, no.
Yes. C. Anshin Anzen Heiwana Machi,
Saitama City
Final answer.
Yes, it's the final answer.
You got it right.
The answer is B, Nobinovisty Saitama
City.
Nobinovisty Saitama City?
Is it a recruitment?
You mean it's lame?
Like a fool?
No, but...
If you think about the great people, it
can't be like this.
The official name was C, right?
I don't know.
I thought all of them were good.
I thought so, too.
But you thought Sukusuku and Nobinovisty
were like fools, right?
I didn't know.
It's actually Nobinovisty.
That's what they say.
Can you read it for me?
I wanted to announce it.
You did?
No, you can't.
You can't do it if you can't answer the
question.
The next one is the best.
No.
Goodbye.