Good evening everyone!
We are Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku!
Before we start the show, we would like to decide the MC for today.
Please vote for your favorite number from 1 to 3.
The person with the number on the number tag will be the MC for today.
Are you ready? I already have this one.
Let's start voting!
Start!
I wonder what will happen.
Today's MC is Jiro Santoria.
Nanoka, you are not the MC yet?
I have never been the MC for this show.
Yuno has been the MC twice, and Kokona has been the MC once.
But I have never been the MC.
I wonder how it will go today.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Time's up!
What will happen?
The result is...
Number 3!
So, who has number 3?
Today's MC is Ema.
Ema, are you ready?
Ready?
What's the meaning of this?
This is my second time.
I'll do my best.
Please do your best.
Ema, please.
I'm Ema Sakura, the MC for today.
Thank you.
Self-introduction?
Oh, self-introduction!
I'm No.15, Kazami Nonoka.
I'm No.17, Nakamura Yuna.
Let's get started!
Ebichu's
fun and fluffy showroom!
Thank you for watching the 53rd episode of Ebichu no Yukai de Fufuna Showroom.
Ebichu no Yukai de Fufuna Showroom is a show about our sisterly existence,
Yukka's showroom.
This is the first episode in 2023.
Thank you for the first episode.
We will do our best in Montreal this year as well.
You can register for the Ebichu Showroom original avatar and get it by gifting.
How is it?
How is the avatar?
There are so many!
Let's see the rankings.
5th place is
5th place, J-kun.
Thank you.
4th place, Ganyu Shimao.
Thank you, Shumai.
Thank you, Kittos.
Thank you, Monta.
If you click the Twitter mark on the screen, you can spread the ad on Twitter.
So, it's time to spread the ad.
We're going to tweet the ad on Twitter now to get as many people as possible to
see this stream.
Please retweet.
Thank you.
Today...
I'm going to the corner!
Today, we're going to have a fun and funny survey talk about this project!
Before we start, we're going to take a survey and decide what we're going to
talk about.
Yes!
We'll announce the topic of the survey.
Here it is!
1. Stapler Idol Fest 2. Momoero Otagassen 3. Ebichu Broadcasting Club 4. Junior
High School Memories 5. Marumaru Ring 6. Shimauma
Please vote for the topic you're most interested in.
Let's start voting!
There are a lot of topics we're interested in.
It's very unique.
Yes, it is.
There's a picture of what's going on.
Who is this?
Yes.
What do you think?
I'm curious about Shimauma.
I think so, too.
Everyone is saying, Shimauma, Shimauma.
Yes.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Yes, it's over!
Who is it?
So, what's the number one topic?
Oh!
Number six!
Number six! Of course!
I'm so curious.
So, Nakamura-san, you came up with this topic.
Please tell us about it.
I think a lot of people know who I am by this picture.
Oh, really?
I think they know.
It's a very unique picture.
I drew it pretty well.
You drew it well.
It's not a big deal.
My first dream when I was a kid was Shimauma.
Wait a minute.
What does Shimauma mean?
I still have a mysterious feeling about Shimauma.
I think it's the same feature as Shimauma.
What do you mean?
It's the feeling I get when I see it in the zoo.
It's like we're in sync.
You feel like you're in sync with Shimauma.
And it's cute.
Yeah, it's cute.
So, Shimauma was my dream in the future.
I wanted to bring everyone to the future and see what their dreams were.
That's why I chose this theme.
I see.
I think people think of cute things in their dreams, but there aren't many
people who have Shimauma.
It's just a picture.
I feel very close to it.
What about you, Nonoka?
When I was a kid, I wanted to be a precure.
There was a precure called Doki Doki Precure.
I had a dream of becoming a pure rosetta.
I've always wanted to be a precure.
After that, I wanted to be a baker.
And then I wanted to be a patissier.
And then I wanted to be a teacher at a nursery school.
I've been through a lot of things and I've come to this point.
What was your first dream?
I wanted to be a teacher at a nursery school.
Did you do your homework?
I did.
When I was a kid, everyone said they wanted to be a car or food.
I was expecting that, but it was completely different.
I thought it was normal.
I thought it was normal for everyone to want to be an animal.
I've never heard of it.
Is it just around me?
Maybe there are animals in the world.
I was doing it right.
I'm getting embarrassed.
What was your dream after that?
My dream after that suddenly came true.
I wanted to be a doctor.
That's a big difference.
I realized I couldn't be a nurse.
I'm glad you realized it.
Do you have any animals you want to be?
What?
I wonder if there are any.
I want to be an animal.
Me?
A giraffe?
That sounds fun.
It has a long neck.
It's hard to be too tall.
It's hard to put something on your feet.
There are a lot of people.
Cats are cute.
I want to be a shell.
Shell?
There are a lot of lazy people.
I wanted to be a lazy person.
I see. I can't move.
I want to be lazy.
A horse.
Giraffes have a high blood pressure.
Really?
Then I want to be a horse.
Why?
There are a lot.
I want to fly in the sky.
I've thought about that.
I want to be a small hippo.
A small hippo?
I see.
There are a lot.
I want to be a musasabi.
Musasabi?
A gorilla.
There are only B-type gorillas.
Really?
I'm a gorilla.
B-type?
No.
All the animals are B-type.
So, B-type humans are not gorillas.
I see.
I don't know the Japanese explanation.
Gorillas are B-type.
So, we have the same personality.
I think so.
Let's do it.
We might get along.
Let's move on to the next topic.
Please vote for us.
How is it?
Oh, I'm fine with the same one.
It's difficult.
I'm totally fine with the same one.
How is it?
But there are still a lot of things to talk about.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
That's it!
Oh! Number 1!
It's the Star Prize Festival!
Yes, on Saturday, January 14th, there was a Star Prize Festival.
This time, it was like a group competition, like a sports day.
There were a lot of competitions, and we did it.
I agree. There are a lot of things to talk about.
Yuna, do you have anything to say?
Yuna, my memories of the Star Prize Festival are all about monoboke.
That's right.
The live performance during the Ebi was a top batter.
After that, it was monoboke.
That's right.
So I was overwritten with monoboke.
I forgot about the live performance.
I was thinking about monoboke with Rina.
I was thinking about whether to do this or that.
But when I went there, the other people were doing it as it was.
That's right. Rina of Ukka.
I was doing it, and I panicked and panicked.
I was thinking about that too.
I was thinking about doing it if I had it.
I was thinking about it.
I didn't have a tool for that either.
What didn't you have?
I wanted to use a red lantern as a camera button.
But I didn't have one, so I came up with it.
I did the camera check.
Did you think about it in the actual performance?
I thought about it.
I thought it was really fun.
Was it fun?
That was amazing.
You were practicing a lot.
I heard from the manager that you were practicing a lot.
I was practicing to wear it.
You were thinking about the dance.
I was thinking about the dance of HAKASETARO.
I couldn't do it.
Next time, please show me HAKASETARO's monoboke.
And Emma?
I'm thinking about KENDAMA.
Emma got 1 point for the first time.
Until then, it was 0 points.
I was thinking about it.
Emma got 1 point.
KENDAMA is really fun.
It's difficult.
I'm sorry.
I'm scared when I laugh.
I was on the official TikTok of Ebichu.
It's not 100% of the time.
I can't get in when I can.
I practiced until the end.
It's completely different from going to the stage.
The fans are very close.
I was surprised.
I was surprised at the KENDAMA challenge.
I was very happy because I got the result.
The noise of the dressing room was amazing.
Next to me was the dressing room of CHIMUHIACHI.
I heard a lot of voices when I got a score on the monoboke.
I was talking about how loud I could hear.
I was happy to hear a loud voice.
I was able to go to Ebichu.
It was amazing.
There was a lot of pressure.
I didn't need a fan in such a big venue.
It was amazing.
I ran after the KENDAMA challenge.
I was very nervous.
I warmed up in the morning and ran.
I wanted to run properly.
I thought I would get hurt.
I warmed up in the morning and ran.
Before I went on stage, I was competing with my manager in a vacant room.
I was competing with my manager to prepare.
Only one person was faster than the others.
Everyone was faster than me.
I was surprised.
I'm glad.
I was a cheater.
I was a cheater in the room.
I got the same score.
I lost, but I'm glad I could go to the final.
I didn't think I would go.
Rock-paper-scissors is a game.
It's luck.
I felt like I was one of the Ebichu groups.
The hot-up was OK with the shirt.
It was a lot of photos.
It was fun.
It was our first STAFF LA FES.
I was able to interact with other STAFF LA idols.
What song were you going to sing if you won?
I was going to sing Cinderella.
I wanted to sing a little.
It was fun.
Thank you for coming.
Let's go to the next one.
How is it?
Start!
We are doing 16 now.
Yes, but it's okay to do the same.
It's okay to do the same.
We were so nervous today.
Before we started.
We were like, is it okay?
What should we do?
We were so focused.
We'll do our best.
Finished!
This is the last topic.
How is it?
Number 2.
The peach color song.
Let's talk about the peach color song.
We'll play it.
I'll do it.
The peach color song.
Do you have any memories?
But it's the first time for everyone.
The first time for Budokan.
The first time for the peach color song.
It was the first time for us to meet so many artists.
I was so nervous when we greeted.
I was so nervous.
It was the first time for the center stage.
I was so scared.
It's not a small place, but there are 10 of us.
There are so many people.
We were like, what should we do?
We were in the third place.
But we were in the third place, so we were nervous.
So we went in the third place and made a V.
It was a song that we wanted to sell.
It was good.
If it was another song, it would have been dangerous.
It would have been dangerous.
It was good.
It was a song that we wanted to sell.
It was the first time for us to perform.
It's been a while since we made it.
It's been a while, but we've been using the usual ULTIMATUM motion.
It was the first time for us to perform.
How was it?
It's a little different.
It was a pretty intense ride.
It was a little different.
I was happy to perform for the first time.
That's right.
The choreography hasn't changed much.
The lines have changed a little.
It's my first time performing.
I thought Voyager would come.
I was wondering if it was Voyager.
I was thinking which one to do.
But I haven't done it yet.
That's why I chose this one.
Momoka, do you have any memories of Momoyama Tagashi?
Well, I don't have any memories of her.
It has nothing to do with the stage, but I remember the catering.
I was in Momoyama Tagashi last year.
The catering was delicious.
It was a taste that was made by a professional.
It was very delicious.
There was a cannelé this time.
It was a cannelé of a person who was taking the upper part of the world.
Momokuro-san made a cannelé.
It was really delicious.
It's important to have a cell phone.
I ate it before and after the live.
Thank you for the meal.
It was my first time at Momoyama Tagashi, so it was my first Budokan.
I met Momokuro-san.
Momokuro-san was busy and I just passed by.
I greeted her.
I greeted her on Instagram.
I was able to talk to her.
It was a lot of fun to see various artists on Momoyama Tagashi.
I'm sorry.
I made a mistake.
I won't read it.
I'm sorry.
That's all for the fun and funny questionnaire talk.
Next, we have this corner.
A fun and fun adult thing.
We are all still kids because we are in the third grade.
That's right, we are still kids.
So today, the three of us will exchange information about what adults are like.
I would like to announce the adult thing.
Then start.
I will write it down.
Please write down what you think of.
What should I write?
I chose the ones that look like the members.
I was really waiting for this.
There are so many.
If you have already written something, please show it to us.
There are a lot of mature girls in the group.
I mean, not mature, but mature.
There are a lot of mature girls.
That's it.
Bye!
I'll talk!
I'm speechless, sorry.
How is it?
Did you draw it?
Then, I'll announce it first.
This is from the perspective of the older sister members.
I'll go.
Ta-da!
She has little luggage.
She always buys drinks.
She always has a makeup bag.
I see.
She looks like an adult, but she has little luggage.
She has little luggage.
When she puts a big clear hair, she carries it in a paper bag.
I see.
She is an adult.
I'm trying to make her luggage less.
But she always has a makeup bag.
That's true.
It's big.
She always has a drink in one hand.
Like a cafe latte.
She always has a fancy drink.
I always have it.
I always have a drink.
She always has a makeup tool.
This is from Mirei.
When she is busy, she puts on eye makeup and goes to her room.
But she fixes it by herself.
That's great.
I see.
Especially when she buys a drink.
She always has it in one hand.
I'll try to imitate her.
I'll ask her to bring it to me every time.
That's great.
Next is Emma.
I'll do it.
She uses emojis right away.
I don't know.
Like, in the mail?
Yes, in LINE or mail.
I think of the red one.
The one with the surprise mark.
Oh, I see.
The one that mothers and fathers use.
Yes, that one.
Not the one with the anniversary.
The one that is a little more mature.
They use it right away.
They put emojis in between sentences.
Yes, they do.
And...
They put it on the back of the hand.
Or they make a space.
They put it in between words.
They put it in between weird sentences.
It's so confusing.
Like, what is this?
They put it in between weird sentences.
It's like, it's getting longer.
It's a little hard to read.
Oh, yes, that one.
The one with the surprise mark.
You are old men.
Do you call them old men?
Yes, I do.
Young people
use it on purpose.
Sometimes.
They think they are old men.
I'm not old men.
No, you are.
You use it.
You use it a lot.
But...
I think they make it easier to read.
They use it.
Thank you for listening.
There are so many surprise marks.
I'm going to be an old man.
I dare to do it.
Some people dare to do it.
What do you mean by dare?
Some people want to show it.
Do you mean you want to show it to an old man?
I guess so.
Or it's easy to convey emotions.
I put a lot of surprise marks.
And I put a lot of surprise marks.
I can't see it.
I want to put a lot of surprise marks.
This is common.
Next is YUNA.
She always makes me do things.
She tells you to do something?
She always makes me do something.
She tells me to share my shoulders.
She does that a lot.
Does she watch your videos?
She tells me to do something for 5 minutes.
It's really hard.
I don't know what's wrong with my shoulders.
I don't think I have a reason to tell her to do something.
She wants you to do something.
But adults get sick easily.
She does a lot of stretching.
I know.
She wants you to do something.
She wants me to do something.
So?
She wants you to do something.
She wants me to do something.
She studies hard.
She has a good attitude.
She is very hard-working.
I see.
I told her to do something when I was 15, but she said I was old.
She wants you to do something.
I'll do something for her.
I see.
Do you have anything else?
There are a lot of things.
I see. What do you think?
It's really interesting.
I wonder if they can relate to us.
I think so.
There are many adults.
There are many people who are doing it.
It says, you are young.
I think so.
I have one.
I'm 15 years old.
I was asked how old I am.
I said I was 15 years old.
I said I was in the third grade of junior high school.
I was told that I was born recently.
I was told that I was 15 years old.
I was told that I was not born recently.
I was told that I was born recently.
I wonder if they can relate to us.
I think so.
I think they are 15 years old.
I'm 7 years old.
I'm 23 years old.
In the comment,
they say it's only 5 years.
I see.
I'm 15 years old.
I think so.
I see.
I know, so good.
I wrote it down, so can I read it?
This is my mom.
She holds her phone with both hands.
I know!
My mom is amazing.
She uses a folding phone case.
She opens the phone case,
and she holds it with both hands.
When she takes a picture, she holds it with both hands.
She holds it horizontally.
My mom does that a lot.
It says that I can read it.
You can read it.
But...
I don't know why.
It's easier to use.
It's hard to move around with one hand.
I can't press the top button.
That's true.
Do you hold it with one hand?
I hold it with one hand a lot.
I hold it and move it around a lot.
I feel like my hands are more stable.
That's true. It's stable.
It hurts like my bones are pierced.
If you were into everything so far, you would be shocked.
I'm not good at it.
I get angry when I hear my age.
It's quite common, isn't it?
Have you ever experienced that?
Yes, I have.
When I ask my grandma, she says,
I shouldn't ask that.
I'm sorry.
Oh, I see.
I don't know much about your age, but I heard that you are 15 years old.
I feel a little bad.
I heard that you are 30 years old.
I'm still 20 years old.
Oh, I see.
I'm being deceived.
I'm 23 years old.
I see.
Did you get angry at Mayama-san?
Well...
What?
I didn't get angry.
Emma, do you have any comments?
Emma...
I haven't written anything yet.
Oh, you haven't written anything yet.
Then, please write it.
I'll read the comments.
There are some comments about being an adult.
I think there are some people who are adults.
What do you think?
Being an adult...
I'm not sure.
I might get hurt if I say I'm a middle-aged man or woman in my 40s.
I see.
I guess so.
We're still different.
I tend to talk about my health.
I watch a lot of health programs.
I also do leg exercises.
Muscle pain comes after two days.
I often hear this.
When you get older, muscle pain doesn't come the next day.
Muscle pain comes after two days.
Is that possible?
Rika said that.
Mirei said that muscle pain came the next day.
Mirei?
Mirei is not old yet.
Wake up before you wake up.
This is my grandma.
When you become a grandma, you wake up very early.
I'm jealous.
Wow.
What is it?
It's also affected by your age.
Or do you wake up early?
What is it?
Do you wake up early?
When you become a grandma, you wake up early.
I see.
When I watch TV,
my older sister says,
my younger sister is more active than me.
When I was young, I didn't know that.
But now, I see that 13, 14, and 6th graders are active in sports and
entertainment.
I can see that.
You wake up earlier than me.
I think the age of the main character of the anime I always watched has
increased.
I see.
I'm older than Tobita.
I think young people are cold.
I can understand that.
My mom often says that.
I think young people and adults have different feelings.
I think so.
I don't know if it's because of the high temperature.
The temperature?
Yes.
I often wear a skirt or a pair of shoes.
People say, it's cold.
But I can understand that.
I can understand that it's not that cold.
I'm often told not to wear stockings.
But I can endure it if I wear a coat.
I'm often told to wear another one.
I'm glad we're the same age.
My mom often says that.
I hope they say,
I can sit down and listen to your music.
I agree.
They are dancing and singing.
I hope they say,
I can sit down and listen to your music.
I'm so grateful.
I'm tired.
I'm tired, too.
I use escalator.
I don't use stairs.
My mom wants to use escalator, but she is fat.
So, I'm trying to use stairs.
I use escalator.
Older people use it, but I think older people use it, too.
I have that image.
My mom is a fan of escalator.
But I use stairs.
So, I can't keep up with her.
That's great.
I like light-flavored things.
I've heard that you are a little sister.
I'm a little sister.
I like deep-fried shrimp.
I like greasy food.
I don't eat greasy meat.
I can't eat greasy food in a pot.
I understand.
I have that image.
I think you are a bad adult.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, I see.
What do you want to do when you grow up?
Oh, I want to drink alcohol.
I see.
You look like a strong woman.
I do.
You look strong.
I like to eat snacks.
I see.
I like snacks.
Mirei-chan said,
I will definitely become a drinker in the future.
Oh, my gosh.
She said she would take Mirei-chan to a bar.
You look strong.
Maybe because I'm a tough girl.
I have an image that I look strong.
There are many cute drinks in Japan.
For example, Korean alcohol.
Japanese alcohol has a cute package.
There are many flavors.
I often see alcohol that is sold only in Gotochi.
I want to drink it.
Well, we have talked about various things.
That's all for today.
The 53rd episode of the showroom is ending soon.
We have a lot of announcements.
First, the F.C. Family of the F.C. members will be held on February 12th at
Pacifico Yokohama.
Tickets are on sale, so please come and visit.
And...
The F.C. Family of the F.C. members will be held at the F.C. Free Live & Special
Event.
The first event will be held on February 4th at Kobe Harbourland Space Theatre.
The next event will be held on February 5th at Omiya Stella Town.
The next event will be held on February 25th at Canal City Hakata.
The next event will be held at the Sun Plaza Stage on the 1st basement floor.
The next event will be held at Ion Mall on March 11th.
The next event will be held at Tokoname Wonder Forest.
The next event will be held at Kyuryo Wonder Stage.
And the last event will be held in Kanto on April 1st.
We, Cocona and Yuna, will do our best for the first F.C. Family of the F.C.
members.
Please come and visit.
And...
The 50th anniversary event of TVK, Daikannai Devil, will be held at Kanagawa
Prefecture Hall on Tuesday, March 21st.
It will be held from 4.30pm. Please come and visit.
Let's check the top 5.
That was the first scene.
Yes.
Was it okay?
I think it was a bit messy.
I think a lot of people were messy.
Please take it back in the live.
Yes, I don't mind using a dot.
Please use it a lot.
Yes.
That's it for the 53rd episode of the showroom.
The next episode will be on February 23rd at 7pm.
Please check out the live after this.
We will be back after the show.
Please leave a comment if you have any questions.
That's it for Shiritsu's Witch Talk.
Bye!
Shiritsu's Witch Talk
Okay, then.
Yes.
Oh, is it already started?
Thank you very much.
How was it, Emma?
Well, I was the MC, but I was able to ask Nonoka to do it again.
I would like to do it again if I have a chance to be the MC.
Thank you very much.
Adults have to be proud of themselves.
This is an adult's thing.
Put yourself on the shelf.
I'm sorry.
It was interesting to see how adults are like.
It was good to know that children are looking at adults like that.
It's not good to say,
I just came here.
I've been living for 15 years.
Yes, I've been living for 15 years.
Yes.
It says, it was fun.
It was fun.
It was a nice team work.
There were a lot of things that we could relate to.
I thought it would be cold.
That's right.
It's not bad.
MC is...
I tried a lot of things.
Kazami has a little bit of experience.
Just a little bit.
I enjoyed being able to follow you.
Thank you.
As an MC, I'm more of a person who does things on the spot rather than reading
the script.
I don't have to worry about the script.
I just say what's not in the script.
For example, if I say I'm going to be an MC today, I have to pass the script.
The other girls haven't seen the script.
If I say, and then I can introduce myself.
If you're an MC, you can think, I'm the host.
I think it's better if you think that way.
Yes.
Shimano was interesting.
Shimano was great.
I think it's great to see the characters.
And when you're writing the script, you're in the frame.
You can talk about anything.
I'll be careful next time.
I think so.
And if possible, I think you should write it at a time difference.
I thought so.
You might not have time to do it.
You don't have to listen to what adults say.
You can grow up freely.
Do whatever you want.
Don't listen to what adults say.
That's right.
That's how it was.
It was a wonderful time.
Please close.
Emma, who was the MC this time, please.
Paw wah.
Is that what you mean?
Yes, that's what I mean!
Thank you for watching the show live of CHU! SANTORIO.
We have a lot of live performances coming up, so if you're bored, please enjoy
the show.
I'm sorry, but the power is a little...
I'm sure I'm saying it right.
After that, it was like a take 2.
It's a take 2.
That's great.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye.