Ebi-Chu's video!
The first video
We are Chime!
We are Shizuoka Ebi-Chu!
I'm Sakura Ikokona, number 13
I'm Kokubo Ino, number 14
I'm Kazami Nanoka, number 15
I'm Sakura Ikokona, number 14
What are you doing today?
Today, we are doing voice training and
dancing
Since then,
you've been giving advice and being
careful
mooth to say
I wonder if something happened
to such a place
I think that you can grow
Applause was only Mako
and advice
If you presidentating a jadi
I think I was able to step on all the
steps.
What is the most difficult thing about
stretching?
Stretching is the most difficult thing.
My body is very stiff.
But yesterday, I had a physical fitness
measurement.
When I did that, I was the worst in
class.
How many centimeters?
59cm.
59cm is the most difficult.
I was told that I had to do it four
times in a small place.
That's true.
I have to match it with the group.
I want to be able to match it with my
seniors.
I like to express my personality.
But I couldn't express my personality
when I danced to the song.
I thought I had to work harder.
What is the most difficult thing about
the group?
They always come to me.
Riko, Hocchan and Hinata came to me
every time.
Mie and Mayama came to me in the voice
training.
Rika came to me.
I can't say Rika.
Rika is cute.
I'm sorry.
They are very kind.
She teaches me the details.
She teaches me what I should do.
What is the most difficult thing to do?
Everyone is kind.
She tells me what to do when I tell her.
It's not difficult.
What is the most difficult thing to do?
I'm a little nervous.
But she is a powerful teacher.
She is a good teacher.
It's fun.
Is she fun?
Is she fun to dance?
I like dancing.
I do muscle training first.
I like this dance.
She told me to do muscle training every
day.
You are tough.
I want to do muscle training.
What is the most difficult thing to do?
I have to do my homework.
I have to fix this.
Next week, I will do this dance.
I remember watching the dance video of
ASSEL.
What is the most interesting thing to
do?
There is nothing interesting.
I saw a magazine of BLT.
My sister bought it.
I was sent to my family line.
My brother is transparent.
I laugh.
It was interesting because it was not
similar at all.
It's not like your sister.
Did you see the reaction in the
magazine?
My mother bought 10 magazines.
What is your favorite dance?
I'm not good at dancing.
Are you good at dancing?
I'm good at dancing.
I won the first place in the dance
competition.
I was the first dancer in the dance
I was the first dancer.
You two look like you're good at it.
That's terrible.
I often see people with a face that
can't exercise.
I don't think I can do it.
I don't think you look like you're good
at exercising.
How is it actually?
It's slow. I can't deny it.
I want to fight.
I really want to fight.
I don't want to fight.
The end.
Thank you for applying for this event.
Thank you.
Thank you for tweeting even though the
deadline is over.
Thank you.
There were a lot of questions about what
kind of food they were.
What kind of food?
Shrimp tins.
Isn't it cute?
Shrimp tins are cute.
Cute.
Chibi shrimp.
Crab.
I think it's not this one.
Is this the most memorable place?
I think so.
It's easier to remember if you eat it
quickly.
The last place is...
I've decided.
This is the place.
It's a bit boring.
If you show your personality, it may
change again.
I'm going to go to the park now.
Please call me that.
Parking.
I'm going to ask you.
I'll do my best from now on.
I'll do my best.