This week's Ebi Chu Tasu Tasu is the 7th
season special, Ebi Chu Tasu Kameido
Kanketsu.
Let's go on a walk around Kameido.
And the last episode is a surprising
development.
Will that promise finally be fulfilled?
Ebichu Tastasu Start!
I'm so into you that I can't stop
What should I do with my heart?
Monotrium, Monotrium, Monotrium, Junior
High School
Add various things to private Ebisu
Junior High School
Ebisu Junior High School
Let's do it!
This program is brought to you by the
following sponsors.
This time, too, the Ebi-Chu always split
up when moving cars.
The team that doesn't get drunk on cars
and the team that gets drunk on cars.
Separated by a mysterious team, they
stroll around the Kamedo town.
Last time, the team that stopped by a
pet shop,
they were allowed to enter the shop, so
they got permission from the shop.
Hoshina and Matsuno are going to the pet
shop.
Wow, the pet shop is big.
I'm going to go to the big pet shop.
Hello.
I'm sorry.
I'm looking for Jasmine
I'm thinking of naming her after I win
I'm thinking of naming her Jasmine
You've decided on the name only?
Yes, I've decided on the name before I
win
Matsuno-san really wants to have a pet
While looking around the store
The dog seems to have fallen in love
with this dog.
Hello.
Cute.
It's already on my face.
It's so cute.
Thank you for watching my video.
Hello!
Cute!
No way!
It looks like Goro
Goro?
Cute!
And so, the shop assistant showed us a
popular cat at the store.
In Singapore, I think the smallest dog
is a Chihuahua
I've never seen it before
It's so cute
It looks like a sweet potato
The tension of Hoshina-san has risen
when she was watching the cat
It's the same as mine, the cat at home
The color is totally different
This one is definitely energetic
Look!
It's so cute
It's playing with its hair
Wow, you're playing a lot!
Cute!
Yasumi is deep in the water.
Look!
Oh my god!
Cute!
Look!
Wow!
Thank you very much.
You're so cool!
Your hair is messy.
My nails are messy.
Cute!
I'm sorry, my costume is torn.
Oh, my!
This is a bad situation.
I'm sorry.
I can't see the back.
Oh, my!
It's your fault.
But I forgive you.
I forgive you.
You are so cute.
I don't want to leave here.
I'm sorry.
Meanwhile, the three who couldn't enter
the pet shop were taking a break at a
cafe nearby.
This cafe is famous for its Italian
soda, which is made of various flavors
of syrup and split with carbonated
water.
There are 35 kinds of soda.
It's hard to choose these many kinds.
The color pencils of the rich people are
like this.
What's the difference between this color
and this color?
It's a color pencil like this.
There are so many kinds.
We'll treat you, so you can order
anything.
Kind Takie-san treated the four of us
with toys for 1,000 yen each.
It's a brand that I don't know.
You invested 4,000 yen today.
You failed to invest, so you can't do
more than this.
I'm listening.
This is a premium.
What's popular?
Watermelon is popular.
It's a watermelon flavor that makes me
laugh.
I'll have a watermelon.
Mayama chose blood orange.
Hiroto chose melon.
It's so watermelon that you can't help
but laugh.
You can't help but laugh.
I can't help but laugh.
There are still many menus that interest
us.
Spaghetti with Japanese style mentaiko.
It's so serious.
I have to compete with you.
Tatsuyaki and sand.
You are lost.
Hoshina and Matsuno don't come back at
all.
It's time to eat.
Please subscribe to my channel.
What kind of shooting are they doing?
I wonder. This is a very good location.
They are free-spirited, so they can go
to different places.
What is the example of the members in
the animal?
Let's compare the two.
I see.
It's a kibin, so it's like a hamster.
It's a kibin.
The movement is like this.
What about you, Hirota?
I have an image of clothes.
I have a strong image of pandas.
I can't think of anything else.
I like pandas and I've been going to
them all the time.
There are times when I hear the word
panda.
There are times when a panda is walking.
Are they all pandas?
The pants, clothes, and jacket are all
pandas.
The socks are also pandas.
You were a panda.
The bamboo is delicious.
No.
No, I don't eat bamboo.
I ate ice cream with bamboo leaves.
It was very delicious.
I've been eating it since I was born.
I heard a surprising panda talk.
I was spinning in my head.
White and black.
I found out Hirota's past life.
I went to pick up Hoshina and Matsuno,
who didn't come back at all.
I'm hungry.
It's late. We've been waiting a long
time.
I'm hungry.
Look at this.
It's true.
I haven't used this costume for a long
time.
It's amazing.
Where are they going next?
It's a shopping street
A shopping street?
Hatori Daimon
Oh, a shopping street
What a great name
Oh my god
What's the name? Shoun Shoten-gai?
Kachiun?
Kachiun Shoten-gai
If you go to this shopping street,
you'll be more lucky to win
Let's win!
A shopping street with a good name
Let's go inside
Takigawa-san, should I buy this?
No, no, no
This is the second one
Hello
What is this shop?
It's a miso shop
A miso shop?
The shopkeeper is very enthusiastic
She is always like this
It's not like there is a festival today,
is it?
I want to congratulate her from the
beginning
It's very nice
She is invited by a strange shopkeeper
to the shop
The smell of miso is amazing
It smells good
Let's make miso for the shopkeeper
Is it OK?
She made instant miso soup using the
brand miso
How does it taste?
It smells good
Let's eat
It's really good!
It's good, isn't it?
It's good
It warms you up
Because it's raining
It's good
It's even better because your mother is
next to you
Thank you
Once again, they head to the rain shop
Look, everyone, we can see the shrine
The shrine!
I want to go to the shrine
Let's go
The shrine is just outside the shopping
street
And then
Wait, it looks good
Is it a baked donut?
I want to eat a baked donut
I'm curious
I want to eat
Isn't it open?
Is it?
Let's go
Hoshina-san was invited by the smell of
delicious donuts and found a donut shop
This is a rare creation, is this a shop?
Actually this is a factory
This is a factory
Please buy one
Wait a moment
What is it?
I want to eat donuts
I will buy one for each of these
children
Let's go!
Can you collect them?
If you buy 5 or more, you can get one
for 110 yen
Oh, I see. Mr. Takiruya and Mr. Donut
If you buy 5 or more, you can get one
for 110 yen
I will buy 5
You can eat it now. It's freshly made
What?
It's freshly made!
It's fresh!
I will buy one to Ma-no
It's Israel's
Is there a 640 yen?
Even you might need it
I'm going to be chased by the bad guys
The donuts are just baked
As expected of the donut factory
Thank you very much
Let's eat
It's crispy
It's so good
It's so fluffy
I've never eaten something so freshly
made
It's so crispy and fluffy
They are very satisfied with freshly
baked donuts
Let's go to the shrine together
We had a meal and arrived at the shrine
We've been to many shrines recently
Are you worried about something?
This is the Kameido Katori Shrine, where
the gods of sports believe in
at one of the merged beach fruits of
Ebichu,
and pray for the future success of
Ebichu.
And right next to it, they found a
picture of Emma with her wishes written
on it
Since we're here, let's write our wishes
on this
Hello
I'd like to write my wish on this
picture
Thank you
I'm sure you'll get used to it
I'd like to write my wish on this
picture
Can you tell me your name?
My name is Ryo
It's a must-win.
It's going to be a hit.
What kind of wishes will the four of
them write?
At that time...
Can I have a moment?
Are you going to do it every time?
At least take a picture of me paying.
You're blocking the camera.
It's weird that you're not taking a
picture.
I'm just paying behind the scenes.
Is that possible?
At least take a picture of me.
I was surprised.
Ema went insideITY and wrote wishes for
the ema.
Let's see it!
Let's start with Hirota. What did you
write?
Win against the weak me.
I will like myself more.
Next, Mayama-san.
I want to win against life.
Next, Matsuda.
When the chance comes, I want to give
100% of myself.
That's important.
You can't be absent-minded when you are
drawing.
Drawing is a chance.
That's right.
Next, Hoshina.
I want to be blessed with good luck and
luck.
What does that mean?
I want to be happy all the time.
I hope that luck will come.
I hope everyone's wish will come true.
So, we've been hanging out in the city.
How was it?
It was fun!
Thank you for taking care of us,
everyone!
Thank you for your hard work!
Thank you!
If we do a location shoot in the city
again, I'll leave my wallet here.
I'll bring only my water bottle.
It's a regular project!
It's not a regular project.
By the way, we took a picture, right?
It's done!
It's so cool!
The photo was taken by the five people
at the photo studio
What kind of photo will it be?
It's really good!
Photo studio!
It's like a photo studio!
It's like a host club
It's amazing!
It's good! It's a good memory
The team that doesn't get drunk by the
car that was given by Mr.Takiyue is
finished
After this, for some reason, that person
appears
It's an unexpected ending
We have now gathered at the Machibura
location
There are only two of you, right?
Kobayashi and Yasumoto are not here
Why?
Look at this
You guys look familiar, right?
The principal is eating ramen
Why is the principal here?
The principal is next to the ramen shop
In the previous trial, Yasumoto and
Kobayashi said that they would eat ramen
with the principal
I thought I'd go today
You didn't do it
In the past trial, Yasumoto and
Kobayashi were told to go eat ramen with
the principal
We will do a prank on the ramen shop
Monitoring the situation
Yasumoto and Kobayashi finished their
walk happily
They told the manager that they have to
shoot the ending scene
and called the manager to the ramen shop
What will happen?
Sit down
Here?
It's a prank
I was surprised
It's hot
Sit down
What?
Order something
I'm full
You're full?
Order something
What?
Order ramen
You're a ramen lover, right?
What did you order?
This is char siu
I'll have bean sprouts
Let's eat together
Do you want to eat gyoza?
I'm going to eat
It's so good
You haven't organized your mind yet,
right?
I'm upset
Aya-chan's usual habit has come out
What's this?
This is a habit
I'm in trouble
It's a habit when you're in trouble
Thank you
I can hear you because you're next to me
What did you order?
Bean sprouts ramen
Two?
Two, please
Thank you
I went to a delicious bread shop
and ate local bread
Yasu-kun is always upset
He touched his hair
Yasu-kun is upset
They are different from usual
He's a little nervous
They are both calm
They just move the water
They don't drink water
They just touch their arms
I wonder if they are clenched
Yasumoto is clearly upset
The manager and ramen
Gourmet Couple
I'm so full
You haven't calmed down yet
I'm not feeling it at all
What should we talk about?
What's the next topic?
We're not in a relationship so we don't
have anything to talk about
You two are totally different from
before
You're so excited
Oh no
Kaho's...
She's listening to us
She's listening to us even though she's
not listening
What's going to happen if we keep
pushing them?
Here it comes!
It's a big one!
It's bigger than the one in the factory
It's because it's bean sprouts
By the way, this ramen shop has a lot of
customers
Really?
It's a nice place
It's a big one
You look a little sad
It's good
It's good but it's a little hard
Kaho is also a little sad
Kaho was eating bean sprouts
Yasumoto was eating a lot of jellyfish
Jellyfish!
The one you ate the most
It's like a treasure
I protected the girl at home
You guys ate a lot of jellyfish
I ate a lot
It's hard for us to watch the ramen
until it's finished
How was it?
It's the ending
Is that so?
It's healing
The staff will be happy with these three
Everyone will be happy
I'll do the closing
Let's say it out loud
Ebichu Tastasu, see you again
It's like a reaction
We enjoyed the team today
We hope to do this again
Ebichu Tastasu
Come and see again
See you next week!
It's over.
Next episode.
The first episode.
The cooking battle.
I love the thick one.
The members are cooking seriously.
It's done.
The unique menu is done.
It's good.
Is it good?
Unexpected results.
This program is brought to you by these
sponsors.
This is a lot.
That's too much for a trial.