Nogizaka, let's go!
Don!
We are Nogizaka Gojichu, and I am your
host, Banana Man.
Nice to meet you!
Welcome, Nogizaka-chan!
Yay!
Thank you.
Here's what's not here.
Let's get started.
The 31st single, Hitkiga!
So, this is the 31st single.
It was released on December 7th.
It's a cocoa stew.
That sounds bad.
Everyone is predicting how much you'll
get it wrong.
I'm just saying it randomly.
I'm not predicting.
I'm sure no one will get it right.
It's not here.
Asuka announced her graduation.
She'll be active until December 1st.
But she'll be on this show forever.
I heard that.
I didn't hear that.
So, it's coming soon?
It's the end of the year.
That's sad.
So, you're going alone this time?
Yes, I am.
Really?
You're not going to climb a hill by
yourself, are you?
No way.
The 31st single, Hit Kigan!
Where is this?
This hit Kigan is not only about the
single hit, but also about the last
student, Asuka Saito, who has seen the
history of Nogizaka Kesseiji.
The rest of the members will make a
journey to wish for further activities.
So, on the way to the trip, the members
will think of a passionate message for
each of the 40 people.
At the end, with that thought, we will
make a hit wish at the shrine in the
destination.
And the location is Asuka, Nara
Prefecture.
Please make a wish to connect to the
future of Nogizaka in Asuka Yukari's
land.
Oh!
Asuka station.
Hello, Bal, I was brought here.
So, this time we came to Nara
Prefecture.
A relaxing journey to wish for the
members in Asuka, a land where Yukari is
not yet.
It's a location where nothing happens,
but will you find something that is not
here that leads to the future of
Nogizaka?
I came here for the first time. I came
to Nara.
How is it?
No, but I brought Asuka to Asuka.
Everyone thinks of it at first, so no
one did it.
I came here and did what no one had
done, and I can do it at the end.
But it's really full of Asuka.
It's really Asuka.
It's written there, too.
It's written from Asuka in Japan to
Asuka in the world.
What is Asuka?
I really want to take a picture of that.
It's like I got a message.
Asuka is really good.
It's true.
It's me.
What do you mean?
Asuka is really good.
What?
I feel good.
Asuka is really good.
There is a Japanese future and origin.
It's amazing.
It's like a cheap prank.
It's the future and origin.
I was told that for a while.
I was young and energetic.
Asuka's dream sales place.
I'm going to buy a lot of Asuka's.
I'm excited.
I've heard of Asuka Ruby.
Strawberry?
Asuka found the Asuka Ruby's cream.
This is the last Asuka mission.
Let's get permission from the shop.
Let's enjoy the soft.
Hello.
You are cute.
Thank you.
I'm an idol in Tokyo.
Really?
I'm glad.
Why do you know?
I know.
Really?
I'm glad.
I'm in Asuka.
I was told that there is Asuka Ruby's
soft.
Can I eat it?
Thank you.
I'm glad.
She got the cream.
It smells good.
She will eat it.
I want to be seen eating the cream.
I hate it.
I'm not.
You are too conscious.
I hate it.
It's good.
It's refreshing.
It's sour.
It's a little sour.
She is eating it secretly.
She is listening to the shop's thoughts.
I've been a fan of Sanki since I was a
child.
At that time, Sanki students were having
a meeting to talk about their memories
with Asuka.
I heard that Sanki is going to the
concert alone.
I wanted to go with her.
I didn't want her to come.
I like her alone.
Do you like her alone?
How do you feel?
I was strangled in the past during the
concert.
The first time I was strangled was at
the Oide Shampoo concert.
I was strangled in the place where I was
cleaning.
I was very happy.
Asuka is a person who is very shy.
Yoda is very persistent.
I can't see him anymore after
graduation.
I always say that I want to take a
picture and go to dinner with him.
I always refuse.
I understand it once.
I'm glad he said that.
I said, OK.
I could not feel my joy at that time.
oh the TV has changed
Asuka Saito summarizes such a night talk
in one word.
The night talk is simply a bomb rice
ball.
What is this?
The face is cute.
It's funny and the singing voice is
cute.
The dance is normal, but I think it's a
delicious type no matter where you bite
it.
It's a bomb rice ball, but I've been
growing up lately, so I feel a little
mature.
I want to plant a bomb somewhere and
have an incredible funny incident
someday.
It's a bomb rice ball.
It's really hard.
I'm looking forward to it.
Asuka's new Asuka.
It's a very embarrassing story.
I haven't changed my lesson shoes since
I joined.
When I was rehearsing in the next
position with Asuka, there was a hole in
my shoes.
I could see the white socks and I was
hiding them all the time, but Asuka
found out.
About a month after she found out, she
bought the same size as my feet.
She bought it for me and I'm still using
it.
At that time, I said,
Don't stop until this hole opens.
She said,
I can't stop until this hole opens.
I was so happy that I had no right to
stop.
I like Kubo.
I think it's easier to understand how to
worry and how to feel down.
I think I'm the one who listens to the
story.
I think Kubo has a lot of those
characteristics.
I think he's forgotten what he did.
I don't think he's been taking care of
me much.
Asuka's one word for Kubo.
Kubo is the best translucent.
What?
She's happy but not happy.
In a good way, he has love.
I always think that Kubo is not good at
something.
But Kubo can do anything.
Singing, dancing, acting, he can do
anything.
If he shows his true self, it's too
bright for us.
So I think he's trying to suppress it.
He's giving half of everything.
He's giving only half of the happiness
that all humans can get.
But I think he's cute and talented in
translucent.
He's the best.
What is Kubo's true self?
I was the first one to stand in the
center.
I was the first one to perform as an
influencer.
I was the first one to be off the
microphone during a live broadcast.
I was in a lot of trouble.
I made a big mistake.
I was angry at myself for not being able
to tell anyone.
I got a call.
I was frustrated.
I thought I was the only one who could
be an influencer.
I got a lot of calls.
I remember that call the most.
I wanted to be able to be a person who
can be a double center.
I was able to be a person who can be a
double center because I was able to be a
double center.
That was the start of my hard work.
I was chosen as a new face after that.
I knew that I was not as good as her.
But I was able to catch up with her.
That was the start of my hard work.
She gave me the best advice at the best
time.
Yamashita said the first thing she felt
lonely when she announced her
graduation.
I was surprised.
I thought I was able to predict her
graduation.
I thought she would not think anything.
She cried a lot.
She said, isn't it too early?
I was happy.
Mizuki Yamashita's one word labeling
Captain Humebaki.
That's a bad word.
He always has his eyes wide open.
He's praising you.
He always appears in the dorm.
He's always in the rough.
He's always doing his best.
That's why he's Captain Humebaki.
He's the captain of Yamashita Maru now.
He's been doing his best in Asadora.
That's what makes him great.
If Yamashita, the third and fourth
generation,
become the leader,
I want him to be the captain of Nogizaka
Maru.
I want Yamashita to do his best.
Asuka in Asuka.
Asuka in the world.
You were really mad at me.
I don't remember the adrenaline.
But I was so happy.
I kept saying, please make me mad again.
If you don't listen to this, it will be
an odd story.
I think I'm the most involved in the
group.
I don't want to say that I have a lot of
memories with Asuka.
Asuka is a very different person.
I don't want to say it myself.
When I was in the middle of my own, I
was chosen as the first selection.
I didn't talk to her at all.
After the National Academy of Arts, I
got an email.
I'm not interested in people.
I was told that I had high expectations
for the Donezawa family.
I didn't talk to her at all.
I was very happy.
I was doing my best to see it.
I wasn't confident.
That's not kindness.
I think she's really like that.
I'm the only one who stayed overnight
with Ume.
I'm wrong.
I did a video call.
I talked to Ume for the first time.
I thought it was interesting.
I told the staff that this person is
interesting.
I was happy that Ume was evaluated by
various people and became a captain.
I'm proud of it.
I was a junior at the time, but I was
spoiled.
I went home because of that.
Asuka is a lonely person.
I bought a birthday present for Asuka
the day before her birthday.
She said,
I'm looking forward to my birthday
tomorrow.
I said, I know.
She's cute.
I'm happy to see Asuka being spoiled.
I'm really happy.
Thank you.
I want to continue this relationship.
I like Ume being spoiled.
Ume is a lovely type.
Is it a little big?
Wait a minute.
I have a lot of one-sided love.
What do you mean?
Ume has a great presence.
He's hiding his presence, but he's very
particular about his makeup.
Ume is also very particular about
beauty.
He's a good person.
I don't know at all, but I have the
image of bringing a lot of people
together.
I want Ume to be a good person.
Asuka's hot pot.
Asuka in Asuka.
What's in it?
If you assist us, we will be very happy.
I feel like I'm a different person.
I feel like there are more pure girls
than I thought.
That's why I feel like I'm being
attacked.
Everyone knows me like this.
I may get cold reactions from people.
But I still contact them and say,
I'm so cute.
I felt like I was a big part of the
group.
I feel like I'm a new wind.
And the five students are talking about
their memories with Asuka.
I started playing the drums because I
admired Asuka.
I'm a fan.
I send letters on Sundays.
I've never heard of it.
Have you ever taken a picture with
Asuka?
No.
I've never.
I'm the only one who can boast.
I think I'm the only one who took a
picture with her.
I took a picture with her once.
You were hiding it.
So, I'm the only one.
I'm the only one.
I'm so cute.
The message that couldn't be written in
the bulletin board was added in Tokyo.
Ogawa is Asuka who reaches her
grandchild's age.
I don't know what that means.
What is that?
When I was introduced to him, he said I
looked like Asuka.
I apologized to him, saying I'm sorry.
I apologized to him, saying I'm sorry
that I'm cute.
But he was very happy about it.
He's been so nice to me since I started
playing drums.
I think he's cute like a grandchild.
I'm glad that Asuka has reached such a
young age.
I'm often asked to talk to him.
But when I go to talk to him, he cries.
I remember a flashback of a girl who
came to me and cried.
I want to talk to him again, but I'm
afraid I'll cry again.
I talk to him a little bit.
The first time I talked to him, he
refused to give me a watermelon.
Why?
I was depressed.
I asked him if he wanted to eat it, and
he said he didn't want it.
I was crying, and he was smiling.
He was smiling with me.
I thought he was a good guy.
He didn't look like he was crying.
He was honest.
He said he didn't want it.
His nickname is Akutori Daikichi.
What?
Akutori Daikichi?
There's a nickname called Shokichi.
I thought that nickname was perfect.
I'm so jealous of that nickname.
I think Shitara is a genius.
I think Daikichi is the one who can get
such a nickname.
I think Daikichi will be a great person
someday.
Akutori has a strong personality.
I'm wondering how to put it together.
Sugawara is also an MC.
I think Sugawara's MC is a person who
can express the strong personality of
the MC.
Who will be the next MC?
Nakanishi has a great sense of humor and
a calm personality.
Nakanishi is a person who is very calm
and calm.
I think he has a great sense of humor,
such as the content of his speech, the
sentences he writes, and the way he
looks at people.
I think he has a very funny personality.
But I think that his personality is
twisted, so I don't think he will be
accepted by the audience.
But I think he will be stronger if he
conveys his personality.
It's difficult for him to convey his
personality.
He is a very normal person,
so he has a great sense of humor and a
calm personality.
If he can do that, he will be a very
interesting person.
He is an idol, or rather, he is a very
I think he will be a person who does not
fit in the framework of an idol.
Anyway, I want him to do his best to
convey his personality.
I think it's a little weird to say that
he is too kind.
Before I did the actual performance at
the Nissan Stadium,
I was alone in the backstage.
At that time, Asuka came to me.
I didn't ask her, Are you okay?
I asked her, Are you okay?
I think she made me feel better.
I've been helped a lot, so I don't have
anything in return.
I've been helped too much, so I'm sad
that I'm graduating without anything in
return.
After this, Asuka finally made a hit
with Asuka.
I'm going to say some bad things about
her.
But her shoe episode was a super star
episode.
And she was poor, so she was in trouble.
She wore a shoe with a hole in it.
It was like a Takeshita episode.
Everyone told me to use it if it sold.
Asuka is amazing.
At first, she was like a baby.
But she's grown up a lot.
Asuka is a good girl.
I laughed at her, but I felt
comfortable.
Birthday Live will be held at 4days in
February.
Under Live tickets will be available
from December 10th.
Next, the tearful episode.
I'm sorry for facing the camera.
I'm sorry for my costume being torn when
I danced hard during the live.
Please subscribe to my channel.