Second Idol
So, hole schedule
Because this is for second idol, could
you please?
Please,"Girl WithிCute"...
OK
My Third Expectation
Thank you!
Now, it's time to introduce the three
elements that make up Yuzuki Ichikawa.
Let's learn more about our guest idol.
Can you tell us the three elements?
Yes, I'm ready.
Ready?
Yes, please.
Here we go.
Ta-da!
The first element is...
talking.
Talking.
The second element is...
friends.
Friends.
The third element is...
That's it.
Then, please explain one by one.
Thank you for watching.
The first is talking.
I have the image that you talk a lot and
do various things on the spot, but do
you really like talking?
I like talking, not being good at MC,
but I really like talking.
I want to talk to someone all the time.
I'm talking to someone all the time
during my break time.
Who is the one who talks the most in the
group?
Who is it?
Is it a secret?
Aira talks a lot, too.
I like talking, so I talk to her during
my break time.
Hana likes to play jokes, so we play
jokes while talking together.
Moeka is quiet.
I'm not talking.
I'm laughing at that.
What do you talk about?
I'm talking about things that I can't
remember forever.
I'm not good at silence.
I'm not good at that scene.
I'm afraid of that scene every time.
I'm afraid of the 1-2 second scene.
I'm afraid of looking back on the
broadcast.
I'm worried about that scene, so I talk
a lot.
Do you talk to your fans at the special
event?
There is a rule that the special event
is held for a few seconds.
I don't have enough time to talk.
I see.
I want you to wait.
I don't have enough time to talk, but
I'm going home because I'm told I'm
late.
I want you to wait a little.
It's not bad for the audience.
I want to talk to you and the audience.
The audience looks very unpleasant.
I've never heard of that.
I'm going home with a bad face because
I'm told I'm late.
I'm talking all the time, so the staff
is late.
The staff is late.
I was scolded by the staff because I was
talking on Twitter.
That's the worst spiral.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I said I was late.
I'm sorry I talked to you all the time.
I was scolded by the staff, so I said,
stop.
I talk so much that the audience hates
me.
But Mario Kart is good.
Oh, is that so? Then it's okay.
Can I go?
If Mario Kart is okay, it's okay.
This program is
Pyonpyon Mano-chan
Yuzu-chan Toshikazu
Naoto Osaka
Kamugichi-san
This video is brought to you by Myon-no-
shi.
Thank you very much.