I think the world's 1.5 billion people
are mistaken for being able to make a
band with that.
They focus on music more than they see
us.
I thought I was raising it myself, but I
wonder if it's dark.
Thank you for the interview.
Thank you for having me.
I'm looking forward to the next
interview.
I'm happy.
I'm happy too.
Just listening to your voice makes me
feel happy.
Thank you.
Please sit down.
We used to be a group of artificial life
forms that had nothing to do with music.
You were being done?
Yes, we were.
We were doing things that we couldn't
broadcast much except music.
But after that, the professor who made
us,
locked us up in the ice of the South
Pole.
You were frozen for a while?
Yes, we were frozen for a while.
While we were being frozen, we were the
ultimate life forms.
Music that is being broadcast all over
the world.
We were able to hear it. We were not
able to stop the function.
While we were listening to it, we
thought that a wonderful culture was
emerging in the world.
If we can get out of the ice and walk on
the ground again,
I thought that we should do something
with music.
But in 2010, global warming was a
problem.
The ice melted a little, so we thought
we could get out.
Well, we got out.
We decided to start a band.
That's why we're here today.
What kind of music did you hear during
the ice melting?
We've listened to a lot of different
kinds of music, but the one I've
probably listened to the most is the
90s.
It was a time when the big trends like
UK rock and alternative rock were
starting to emerge.
I want to focus on the alternative rock
and the mixture.
I remember that I was a fan of the music
that was played in that era.
Are there any other Japanese works
besides your overseas works?
I think there was a huge trend in Japan
during that era.
There were many bands called the Air Jam
generation,
and there were bands that were
represented by the High Standard.
There were Bluff Bandatti, Scaffold
King, and Backdrop Form.
They were very popular.
The High Standard is a Melo-core band,
and they were very popular.
But also the club's
fans have absorbed it sad,
which is generally what would happen
with a famous band playing здесь on
stage.
I've been listening to a lot of songs
from different genres.
I want to know what it was like to meet
the guitar.
It was a copy.
I think the first one I copied was
Nirvana.
They are the most famous bands in the
90s.
The first point is that it's easy to
copy.
It's a very simple guitar riff and chord
composition.
I think about 1.5 billion people in the
world misunderstand that they can make a
band with that.
They think they can do it.
It's the same phenomenon as when Pistols
came out.
It's very simple.
It's not easy to do that simple thing
emotionally.
I think so.
I started copying the bands I liked and
studied the lineups.
So the song you played for us today
was...
It's a song by a smart band.
What was the song you played for us?
It was in 1993.
1993?
It was in the middle of the 90s.
What was the song you played for us?
What kind of influence did this have on
you?
This question itself is a very deep one.
It's like choosing a song.
That's right.
I think that music in the 90s was a part
of our lives.
It was definitely a very innovative and
experimental world.
I think there were a lot of times when
music that made you feel excited was
born.
Rather than one, it was a time when all
the fans of this era were fans.
However, when I was told to choose one
song,
I was definitely a composer and a
creator.
As a band that was greatly influenced by
this kind of music,
Master cultural
上げさせていただきましたねはいなるほどなるほど
楽曲そのものはまあおそらくそのオルドラギター6とかがものすごくメインストリーム
調流なり始めた時に
彼らが大手レコード会社とか周りに
動めくその大人たちのなんかその商売機の匂いを感じたのに
反するその反抗心を表したような楽曲でもあったりするんですけど
ものすごくポップでヘビーなサウンド感なのにメッセージ性としてはすごく土下がって
そのなんか両面性というか ものすごくすごいなってこんなにポップなアンサンブルでも
のすごくエモーショナルなんだけれども
すごい毒を吐いてるなみたいなそこにも
心を打たれたりしてこの時代の音楽だったりメッセージって結構そういうものも多かった
りましてちゃんとあの本物を見きやめろよって観客に促すような歌詞ですもんねいや多か
ったと思います
オルタナーティブって言葉自体がやっぱりもう一つの選択肢っていう意味もあってそのア
ティテュードというかその精神性っていうのがすごく
折り込まれた時代だなというふうには感じましたねそうチェラブって言葉自体は天使みた
いなことだそうですだから直訳すると天使のロック
天使のロックでサウンドもあんな感じでメロディアスで美しいけど歌手はドッキョフクで
いろんな面がある曲なんですね
本当にそこがやっぱり一番なんか衝撃受けましたね僕がそれまでに聞いてた音楽ってあの
言い方は変かもしれないですけどもうちょっと分かりやすく例えば
すごく明るいことを歌ってるんであればその明るい方向に行く暗いことを歌うんであれば
サウンドもそのリークもそっちに行くっていうような
解析しやすいような音楽は聞いてた記憶があるんですけどもこの時代の音楽は
like 귀 het
I think there were a lot of artists who
were expressed in this way.
The sound of the smart pan is also
dramatic.
The drumming is also dramatic.
It's shocking that he shows such a
delicate world in a certain way.
If I were to write music, I would like
to be a band that can express this kind
of thing.
I'm very influenced by that.
I'm actually a bit difficult in terms of
production.
But you have always been passionate
about this instrument.
Yeah. I've developed that part in guitar
vocal,
and at the same time have been a big fan
of Billy Politik.
Of course he's good, but he's got more
emotions than words.
He's a great guitarist.
He's got a beautiful side to his music,
and a bad side.
His double-sidedness is one of the
things I always keep in mind when I
write songs.
I'm not a guitarist.
No, I'm not.
You're a great guitarist.
Really?
I'm not.
I'm more interested in the sound and the
arpeggio.
Simple but beautiful melody.
I'm attracted to that.
I think I have more ideas for guitars
than you do.
For example, the music of the era of Air
Jam and the music of the era of Smashing
Pump,
such as the flow of the Ultras,
are directly connected to the music of
the MAMIZU.
I'm very interested in what kind of
music was heard before that.
I listened to Billy Joel a lot.
Billy Joel? Oh!
Billy Joel is good.
I like it a lot.
You can listen to it now.
It's a piano man.
That's a very bright melody.
What I'm singing is a song that I don't
want to end as a bassist.
You're pretty good at it, Billy Joel's
lyrics.
That's it.
That's where it all started.
Oh, yeah.
I'm sure that's what you're attracted
to.
At first glance, it sounds like this,
but it's actually quite...
I don't know. It's kind of broken.
But that's where the fragility is.
I think I'm attracted to the side of
music that's understood enough to
deliver that song.
There's a drama, isn't there?
There is.
The music in Japan is before the air
jam.
What music did you hear?
I heard Nakajima Miyuki.
Really?
I love him.
I love him very much.
I was born in the 90s.
I've heard many artists.
I've heard Koko.
I've heard a lot of them.
I love him very much.
He's captured all of my alternate souls.
And he's also full of Japanese pop
sense.
I've heard a lot of it.
I thought about it while I was uploading
it myself, but I wonder if it's dark.
What about the Japanese music scene
these days?
I listen to it.
Rather than inputting,
I don't want to service the antenna that
imputes the sound.
Now I listen to BDM,
and also track makers,
and Yoasobi,
and Boundy.
I always listen to it thinking it's
really cool.
It's really cool.
As a member of the music scene, I always
have a fight with myself about whether I
should challenge myself in the new trend
or do it in my field.
I also feel comfortable.
When something new is born, where do we
define our music?
I think it's a struggle that everyone
has, but when a new artist with such
high quality is born,
some people may be impatient, but I'm
excited. I think it's amazing.
We should be free to create new music.
We should try to create from a different
perspective.
That's right.
Sometimes we talk to members,
or we talk to friends from the same
genre.
I think it's amazing that in the last 10
years,
the rock scene in Japan,
or in a bad way,
has been sinking.
It's not about surviving,
but how to create our own music.
We talk about it later.
It seemed as if you stand up for all
people that you don't see.
We may be a very flexible band.
The genre of music is also a factor.
Our flexibility may be strange to say,
but there are parts that help us a lot.
And I've heard music of that era.
When the world is trying to choose an
alternative rock band,
I think it was a time when the power of
cooperation was also very wide.
It may be true.
The structure is also there, and cool
things will come out as track music.
When Chemical Brothers came out, it was
shocking.
The guys who play the track music are
more punk and rock.
But they didn't forget the respect and
love for the band.
I think that respect for each other and
the crossover feeling was a very
important period.
I still want to do that.
After all, things are allies.
That may be so.
Thank you for watching.
Is there a moment you feel you're lucky
enough to be in the ultimate life force?
No matter what, the first inspiration is
the eye-catching visual.
That's what helped me get into the game.
I felt another great possibility was...
When I was on a tour abroad, I saw a lot
of enthusiastic fans.
I believe that music is beyond the
borders,
but I've seen a lot of artists who are
not going to the real world.
I've seen a lot of artists who have
performed on stage.
When people from other countries see it,
they think,
these people came from Japan, these
people came from the UK.
I think that's what people think.
Sometimes it's not good to work on a
negative thing, but it's not good to
work on a positive thing.
Our band is a band that can be used to
control our imagination.
It's not just an icon, but it's more
focused on music than on what we see.
We've been working on a new channel for
a while now, and we're working on a new
channel.
In that sense, I think it's necessary to
work on a channel that's borderless, but
in our case, it's a coincidence.
I've felt the possibility of making a
channel that focuses on music by
removing it from the audience and
listeners by delivering it in this way.
I think it's a good idea to make a
channel that focuses on music by
removing it from the audience and
listeners.
The album is a 3 and a half year-long
album.
Not only us, but people all over the
world are sick with the disease.
It's a great opportunity.
That's right.
Because of that, the music industry is
the same as the whole.
Music listeners are always live like
they used to be.
It's a great opportunity to be able to
see the world.
Music listeners are always live like
they used to be.
We can't enjoy music anymore.
We thought about releasing a big album
as a gift for the fans.
We were able to feel the emotions we
felt during this period.
We are still in the middle of something
other than a disease.
I don't want the world to be affected by
the music itself.
I wanted the music to have an
independent concept and philosophy.
But even so, there are things that we
can't ignore in this age.
The attitude of putting my feelings into
the sound and message of the music has
changed.
The natural way to do it is...
幸せなことなのかなと。 起きてしまってることは大変なんですけども。
非常に純粋な、今自分たちが思うことを ホントにナチュラルに落とし込んでる
2枚のアルバムになりましたので。
もちろん思うところは皆さんそれぞれ違うと思いますけれども、 僕らがね、その思って
いることがこの2枚組でもう12分に詰め込ませていただいたので、
皆様の毎日のね、ちょっとした光になってくれたら嬉しいなと思います。
ではですね。 マウイザーミッションの...
I'd like to hear about your future.
It's difficult.
In various interviews, I get asked a lot
about what I want to be in the end,
and what stage I want to be on in the
future.
I wonder if I was able to answer it
properly once.
I just walked around with the image of
wanting to start a band.
It's not that...
I don't have a specific goal.
But I have a strong desire to become
like this.
In my case, I think that rock music and
the beauty of the band are the most
important.
I think that's what I want to do in this
program.
I always check what I think about music.
The more I talk, the more I talk about
myself.
I want to continue talking about what I
talked about in this program.
I want to be able to perform live as
soon as possible.
Will you go abroad again?
Yes, I will.
The current world is changing,
and the way we think is different from
one country to another.
But little by little, I've been told to
come to Japan's Tandems.
I'm going to go whenever I feel like it,
so I'll see you again.
We are also looking forward to the day
when we can share music with you as
usual.
Of course, the Marmizu mission will be
sent overseas, but do you ever think
that it would be nice if there were
Japanese young musicians who were aiming
for overseas?
Oh, there is.
These days, we release underground music
because it's all the moreulating to
artists as much as we do in Affiliate
Chords.
We want to make a sound that's not
inferior to the overseas sound,
and that's something that's common even
abroad.
But now, no matter where we are, we can
do international music with natural
bones.
I think that's the era where people like
that are born.
So I have nothing to say. Please go and
do it.
I want to make a sound that's not
inferior to the overseas sound.