Yakan and Idol
Yakan's YouTube has a main corner.
I will go to that corner.
Let's go to the main project.
Cutely
Title
I can't say it to the audience.
Please be cute.
Yes
My three-dimensional elements
I will go to that corner.
Now, it's time to introduce the three
elements that make up yourself.
Let's learn more about the guest idol.
So, please show us the three elements.
I'll do it.
Ta-da!
Can you see it?
The first one!
Artistic appreciation
The second one?
Idol
And the third one?
Gold kiwi
I see!
That's amazing!
I'd like to ask you about your artistic
experience.
Yes.
What is artistic experience?
I go to see musicals and plays.
I see.
I actually walk there.
I go to the art museum alone.
I also go to see movies alone.
I'm also very indoor.
When I'm at home, I usually watch a
drama at once.
I also watch movies at home.
Do you watch all those things and input
them into your brain?
I was interested in the entertainment
world when I was in the second grade of
elementary school.
I've been watching dramas since then.
That's amazing.
At that time, I was younger than me.
I've been watching medical dramas since
I was 21 years old.
I've been playing a teacher since then.
I've also played a detective.
I was interested in acting because I was
playing a different role at the same
time.
I've been watching a lot of Horde Blue.
I've also been watching dramas such as
Sea Monkey.
Do you cry?
I cry.
I still cry.
So I watch movies alone.
I don't want to show my friends or
someone next to me.
You don't want to show your friends.
I watch movies alone.
I'm sorry.
I haven't met you yet.
Do you go to the museum?
I go to the museum.
I don't know about modern art.
I don't know about modern art, but I
feel at ease there.
That's amazing.
I don't like someone's painting.
I feel like I'm immersed in various
paintings.
I heard that Ayaka Sasaki likes art.
It's the second time I've heard that.
I was very happy to be on the Ayaka
Nation.
I'm glad I met you.
What's the story of the Ayaka Nation?
I was on my way home from school when my
manager called me.
I see.
Ayaka Nation
This program is brought to you by
Takuto
Yarinofu
Innu's Monster
Gugudan Hirono
I sent it by the offer of Mr. So
Thank you everyone for today
What day is tomorrow?
Please find a jacket photo of a red
costume