Yuka's idol!
So, what's the second factor?
You don't have a tooth?
I'm a senior in high school,
I'm graduating this year, but I'm going
to the silver medal.
Congratulations!
I'm going to the silver medal.
I'm not going to the top anymore.
I'm being promoted now.
I'm going to do my best with one tooth.
The front teeth and the back teeth are
still in the
teeth, but it's still in the teeth.
Is that so?
Is it still in the teeth?
I'm a little surprised.
Why did you know that?
My teeth hurt a lot.
When I went to the hospital, I was told
that my teeth had not changed.
That's why I couldn't get a job for
about six years.
You can't get a job because you're not
an adult yet?
That's right.
I'm a little bit of a baby, but I'm not
an adult.
You're a baby?
That's right.
I'm looking for a mom.
That's a failure.
That's right.
Is that so?
Yes.
I'm waiting.
Do you tell your fans about it?
I do.
Do your fans give you any information?
No, they don't.
They just tell me that I'm a baby.
They just tell you that?
Yes.
But it's a great element.
That's right.
I'm in trouble.
Are you in trouble?
Yes.
I want to get a job soon.
But it's not because you want to be on
the front of the stage.
I'm worried about people's eyes.
That's the problem.
I see.
I understand.
I'm worried about people's eyes.
Do you want to do it when you sing?
I want to do it.
I want to laugh.
That's right.
You're funny.
I want people to laugh.
I see.
I get angry when I do that.
You get angry?
Yes.
It's a winter party.
I sing songs.
I want to make the audience happy.
You want to make the audience happy?
I'm worried about people's eyes.
Who is worried?
I don't know.
You don't know?
I'm worried about people's eyes.