We are Mouko-Tanmen Nakamoto's favorite
idol
Yummy
This time, we will eat Mouko-Tanmen
The song that made me cry this morning
is...
C-C-B-C-G-F-C-C-B-G-L-U-G-E-7
I am Best tiempo!
I am the senior of the new member mix,
Zenmashi Mix
Today, we will have a special project
So today, we will have a special project
with new members
Let's call Emma and Yuna who don't know
anything
Today, we will have a special project.
Do you know what project?
No, I don't know
Let's start
We are Mouko Tanmen Nakamoto's favorite
idol
Mouko Tanmen Nakamoto is a super popular
ramen restaurant that has 27 stores
The product is a spicy ramen with a
combination of spiciness and umami
They sounded like enjoying the ramen so
much
Hoshina, who loves spicy food, joined
Nakamoto Mania
She went to the restaurant, of course
I was hungry before the game
Ta-da!
I ordered Nakamoto over
The best
She always has Nakamoto with her
The reason why Hoshina invited two new
members to Nakamoto Mania
Do you remember the promise you made
with Yuna?
Oh, the day before the game
I remember
I'm Yama, nice to meet you
They've been together for a month
The three members who made a promise on
the day before the game
I love spicy food
You love spicy food
Yes, I do
What do you like?
I like hot pepper
Let's go to Nakamoto Mania together
I found it
Let's go to Nakamoto Mania
I've never been to a tempura restaurant,
so I'll have cup noodles
She's going to eat cup noodles
She was in Nakamoto Mania
She said she would go to Nakamoto Mania
She couldn't go to Nakamoto Mania, so
she's going to Nakamoto Mania today
Let's go to the restaurant I go to three
times a week
Emma is also involved
The three of them are going to Nakamoto
Mania
I'm here! This is the place I often come
to, Shibuya Tenzan in Nakamoto, Okutame
I come here a lot
Do you usually line up?
Yes, we do
When there are many people, we line up
at the station or the stairs
We often line up
She got permission to enter the store
Yuna, what do you want to eat?
This is my first time eating this, so
I'll have miso ramen
If you order the ladies set, you'll get
half of the mapo tofu, half of the rice
and half of the noodles
And the spicy mapo tofu
I'll have the ladies set
I'll choose the noodles too
If you can, I want you to try it
I want to eat it
And Hoshina Jouren bought
I bought my favorite one
I bought the 4 times spicier one
The most spicy one in Nakamoto's menu is
the Hokkyoku Ramen
The first customer said to be careful
And the 4 times spicier one
I'm so happy
Thank you very much
4 times more spicy and less oily
4 times less oily
Hoshina is
Thank you very much
Can I have a point?
Of course
Thank you very much
Excuse me, 4 points please
And Eron, please
Thank you very much
You will get 60 points soon
I'll do my best
What will you get if you collect points?
If I collect points, I can exchange
products
I have 60 points now, so I can get a
chance
I want a T-shirt, so I have to do my
best for 40 points
I'll do my best
I'll wear black clothes
I failed
I'll be eliminated if I don't wear black
clothes
I always wear black clothes
Do you always come alone?
I wear a hat and a hat
I eat alone when I go to the nail salon
or the beauty salon
I go home
Sometimes I drink beer alone
I'm different from what I thought
Do you come after the live show?
Yes, after the live show
After the show?
I always want to eat Nakamoto
You are a member of the live show
Nakamoto talk doesn't stop, so they
change the topic
Are you two getting along well?
Yes, we are
I spend more time with Yujin than with
Emma
That's good
We like each other
You like each other?
You put your love hand in every
conversation
Even if I say I'll eat, you say yes
You are like a shop assistant
That's good
You are kind but you say something when
you are not in the conversation
You forget to throw away the trash
You throw away the trash
You are a big sister
I thought Yuna was a big sister
She is a big sister
I heard that from my manager
Thank you for waiting
This is the special menu of the set
Thank you
If you eat this, you won't feel cold
even in the North Pole
The North Pole ramen is the best
They have 4 times spicier
It's unimaginable
I'm happy to eat this after a long time
Thank you for the food
It's good
It's been a while since I had this
I'm happy
It's spicy but it's delicious
It has a good taste
I like it and I can change it
I can enjoy every time
Thank you
It's not spicy at all
It looks good
Emma is not good at spicy food
Order cold soy sauce noodles with zero
spiciness
This is a popular menu since the
beginning of the company
Let's eat!
How is it?
It's just delicious
It's chewy and delicious
The soup is delicious
And finally the main dish
Thank you for waiting
This is the Miso noodles and set meal
Thank you
YUNA, who is experiencing for the first
time in Nakamoto, will challenge the
third level of Karasa Miso noodles
It's a little red.
It's really good.
Let's eat.
First.
First time in Nakamoto.
Oh, no. It's already gone.
Let's eat.
It's good.
I can eat it. It's really good.
If you put this on top, it's a bit
spicy.
It's really good to eat just this.
It's also good to put on rice and eat it
like a mapo tofu.
This mapo tofu is really good.
I love it.
Hoshina recommends the famous Karashi
mapo in Nakamoto.
How does it taste?
I'll try it.
Can I do it?
How is it?
It's good.
I can eat it.
But I can still eat it.
It's really good to eat just mapo tofu.
Then...
There is also a soup of Hokkyoku.
I've tried it.
Is it this one?
Do you want to try it?
I'll try it.
I want to try it.
Yuna is a big fan of spicy food.
But...
I think I can do it.
Thank you.
Oh, I got it! I'll drink again.
Oh, I can stop it.
Yay!
I'm glad.
I have more friends.
I'll go to the water.
You'll go to the water?
Sorry, I got points today.
I'm very happy.
I had a good experience.
It looks like a very fun scenery, but
what they are eating is
Japanese-style spicy ramen.
Did they get stimulated by such two
people?
They are still trying to challenge spicy
ramen.
I'll eat it.
Can I put it on the plate?
Is it better to put it on the plate?
Just a little bit?
I'll eat it with tofu.
Cheers!
It's so spicy!
It's too spicy!
This is so hot It's too spicy and it's
too hot
I think you brought heat
It's hot!
Thank you for watching!
This is crazy.
Mirei-chan, you're so mean.
Yuna is mean too.
Was it too spicy?
I'm glad it was a little.
There's a lot of sauce left.
Mirei-chan, this is...
This is the fourth one.
Once again, they found out Hoshina's
abnormality.
Thank you for the meal.
How was it?
It was spicy.
It was delicious.
Thank you for hanging out with me.
I wanted to come here all the time.
I ate cup noodles, but I didn't have a
place to eat at the restaurant.
I was very happy to come here.
It was spicy, but it was very delicious.
I decided to come here.
Thank you.
I want to work hard with the new members
who are trying to be a member of the
group.
Please look forward to the next episode.
That's all for today.
This is Mouko-tanmen, Zenmachi Mix.
Please look forward to the next episode.
My mind is changing.
I came to visit the shrine.
Ema and Yuna wish for the success of
their first live.
There's a disaster.
What?