Hello, I'm Izuki Nakashima.
Today, I'm going to introduce my
favorite things.
I'm in the mountains of Tenpai Mountain
in Fukuoka.
I'm from Fukuoka Prefecture.
When I was in elementary school, I lived
in a town called Saiki City in Oita
Prefecture.
I like nature because there was only
nature.
I'm good at fine work.
I'm good at hair arrangement and nail.
I'm not good at sports.
I'm not good at sports, but I'm not good
at sports.
I can't swim.
I'm going to eat now.
It smells good.
There are shops selling mentaiko and
green tea.
I chose a flavor called Monaka.
It's packed with red bean paste and the
inside is crispy.
It's delicious.
I'm going to have a mentai-chazuke.
I'm happy.
I'm happiest when I eat delicious food.
I finished eating.
Thank you for the meal.
I just noticed, but I might have eaten
too much.
It was all delicious.
What kind of idol do you want to be?
I can't see myself in the future yet,
but I'm trying hard to be in front of
me.
I want to be like that in the future.
I'm pretty serious.
I don't know.
I don't think I need to change my
serious side.
I want to be an idol that people will be
glad to see me perform.
I don't think that the BUDDIES will
welcome me from the beginning because
I'm a senior fan.
But I want to do my best so that someday
the third generation will be glad to see
me perform.