As you can see, we have a strong desire
for rock bands.
We have mountains and valleys,
and the fact that we can experience rock
bands in the valleys
can help you to pursue your roles.
Welcome to Fukaboru!
Thank you.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's been a while.
Thank you.
It's a beautiful set.
It's going to be a hit.
Me too.
It's cool.
Thank you for preparing such a beautiful
costume.
Thank you.
I think the first time we saw Man with a
Mission was in 2010.
As minutes go by, things like these
start to form.
We're a visual band, and the eye-catch
has become a hot topic.
We've been making various ballads and
aggressive rock songs for the music.
After about two years, we thought about
what it would be like to be the main
vocalist.
When I saw my band, and when I made this
song called Distance, I was like...
It came naturally to me.
I think the sound of The Man With A
Mission is one of the songs that can be
said in a few words.
I think this is the most important
reason why I thought it was an axis.
We, all the band members, are...
We're all different genres of music.
Really?
Yes, we're all different.
I'm a 90's alternative guitar rocker,
and Kamikaze is a bass player.
We're both from the same generation, but
we're both melo-core and punk.
We both like club music and vocal music.
We're both different, but I think we're
both from the same generation.
We're both rockers from the 90s. We're
all in the same hybrid.
We're all working on a new genre.
We're all influenced by that generation.
So, what do we do if we're in this
generation?
We've been working on this song for a
long time, and this song has a lot of
elements.
There's the aggressive guitar sound, the
rap, the melody, the essence of the
track music,
a mixture of all that, the
They're supposed to be connected in
these aspects.
It all just happened, then.
As soon as they ended it was like,
this really started if we were really
satisfied.
This is an 있at we all recognize,
we had this song,
that was Fire Glow and Radioflag
Ah well50
It's one of the songs that we've been
working on.
That's right.
There are songs that are more danceable
and melodious, but they are also very
sound-oriented.
The band plays various kinds of music,
and I personally think that the songs
that we can play with confidence are the
only ones that we can play.
Among them, this song is a song that
makes me think, this is Manwiz.
And we are like this, so we have eye-
catch.
We thought, ーAh, we are going to play
music that gives such a cool world view.
ー
ーThis band is like that. ー
I think it became one of the first
songs.
ーYes. I think the reaction was very big.
When you choose a genre, everyone gets
the same feeling.
It's hard to put out an original song
there.
In our case, we are reliant on the
composer.
We usually make the songs laid back by
Kabemikaze.
The original idea was left to the
composer to make it look like a hybrid.
The most important thing is the love for
the field you grew up in.
We put out a lot of love, and as a
result, our songs became a hybrid.
It's similar, but I think there's a lot
of admiration for rock bands.
Thank you for watching!
I think there's a lot of admiration for
rock musicians and rock music.
I really like everything that famous
musicians and extreme musicians do.
I think that's what we're most proud of.
I think it's one of the reasons why
we're still in this scene,
because we can tell that we really like
this band.
Do you have any memories of the process
of making this band?
At first, the composer brings us rough
demos like this.
It's when Kamikaze brought the demo
back.
It was a bit of a tribal percussion.
When I heard it, I was really impressed.
It had a lot of DJ sounds as the main
theme.
And it had a danceable beat to it.
When I heard it, it was like a real
Yumi's.
They told me to think of a riff.
I added the first intro riff quite
instantly.
The lyrics are also English lyrics.
The story is written by the composer.
I'm usually told to leave the rest to
you.
The first time I heard it, it was as if
I had a hint.
It was a song that I was very eager to
write.
Everything in there was very very fast.
You were very excited at that time.
I don't think that it's something that
can be created by spending time.
I think density is the most important
thing.
If you have concentration and feelings,
it doesn't take much time.
I think the most important thing is
density.
The relationship with the band members
is dense.
Are you close?
I think we are close.
It's a good plus alpha.
It's a bit vertical.
If it's a bit vertical, it's smooth.
In short, we both have roles.
I'm in this field.
I'm in the music and writing field.
Tokyo and Naka are in the movement and
presentation field.
We both have roles.
If you think so, you should do it.
We have five people who share roles.
You have a very reliable relationship.
I think so.
They talk about what they want to do.
But when they proceed, they don't have a
meeting.
I think it's a good idea for this wolf
to do what he wants to do.
Basically, it's a wolf who takes the
lead.
They're Tip of the
We, who were lost in the focus light,
are chasing after them again
We fall down thousands of times and even
tens of thousands of times and try to
stand up
Ignoring the ridiculous noise and the
annoying noise
We fly with the wind as we are
Ignoring the fact that it's not just a
dream
Hot
As a singer or lyricist,
I thought about where to put the message
of this band.
For example, if you make it a love song,
and it's a love song that will capture
people's hearts,
it may be a world-class song, or it may
be a little offensive,
but I want to send a strong political
message.
Thank you for your viewing.
There are many artists who are the basis
of this song.
When I thought about where to put this
band,
and where to put the strongest message
of the words,
I thought this song was the best message
for us or for myself.
The lyrics are smooth and fast.
How was it?
I think it was the melody, the chord
progression, or the rhythm pattern that
came first.
But the melody and the melody of the
song were born almost at the same time.
Really?
It was so natural that it was not an
exaggeration to say that it was a direct
line of sight.
That's amazing. Is that so?
I decided to make the lyrics in Japanese
from the beginning, but I wanted to make
it into a story that I could say in the
message.
When I thought about what a song is
about,
I thought that rock music and the
admiration for rock bands are very
strong.
I think that the most honest way to
express the passion and love for rock
music is the strongest point.
The world of the song itself is about
trying to do something in this world.
心差し半ばで。
散っていった、もしくは折れてしまった人たちに対する 参加でもあり、
今もなお前に進もうとしている人たちに対しての メッセージソングだったり。
自分たち自身に言い聞かせているところもあったりもして、
そこのテーマが自分が歌っててものすごく強くなり得るし、 色濃くも欠けて、
あとは嘘を偽りのない気持ちをかけるのはやっぱりそこなのかなと思いまして。
In a sense, it's a feeling that people
around the world have probably
experienced in common, such as love and
political messages.
That kind of frustration and hope.
But if you can draw it in a colorful
way, I think this is a strong point.
When I actually wrote the song, I really
came up with the words honestly, so I
want to sing that I wonder if this is
it.
Maybe you've been keeping what you've
been thinking in your heart all this
time.
I think so.
I think people who are in the band, such
as Shonari and Dai, have probably
experienced various scenes, both in and
out.
I'm not good at songs that are bright
from the bottom of my heart.
I always want to live.
There are mountains and valleys.
I think that I have more experiences in
my life than in the valley.
I think it's a bit of a risk to make a
song from the spotlight,
but I want to focus on that.
I think that's why I've made more songs
like that.
Do you always take care of the double-
sidedness when you write lyrics?
Yes.
I think that's the most important thing.
Of course, I think my own feelings are
important,
but depending on the listener, I can
hide the infinite possibilities.
I can take both, but the rest is up to
you.
I like the lyrics more, so I have a
sense of freedom
and a sense of world of poetry that I
can listen to.
It's abstract, but it's a strong
message.
That's the one thing I care about.
Do you write lyrics in English or
Japanese?
Or do you just write the songs?
I don't really care.
When I choose a language, I choose it by
the sound.
English is a little surprising.
It's been around for almost 100 years,
and it's been in the middle of rock.
It's really popular.
It's a language that fits the sound.
So when we write aggressive songs, we
tend to choose English.
But when we want to give a message to
the main character,
especially Japanese audiences, we are
based in Japan,
and when we write songs like that, we
use Japanese freely.
What was the reaction of the fans after
the release of Focus Light?
This song is a single with a B side to
it.
It's a song that I want to perform live,
and it's a song that makes me want to be
number one or number two.
I was very happy about that.
We thought that was the axis of the
sound mix for the rock band.
But the fans accepted the message of the
song and loved it as a live song.
I was very happy that the fans
understood the message of the song.
I became confident in myself.
I thought that it would be natural for
us to get a sense of empathy by writing
this theme.
I felt that the kindness of the wolfs
was also transmitted.
We say it with our own mouth, but we
understand the truth that we want to see
the inside of the band.
In that case, Japanese poetry is
probably very...
It's a song that gives you the
imagination to write a song.
I think that's why people love it.
What does this song, Focus Light,
mean to you, Mr. Mao?
I've been writing poetry for the past 12
years.
I don't think there are many moments
when you can get a sense of confidence.
But it's not just as a writer, but it's
also the band that's been presenting the
most axis.
I don't know when it's going to end, but
I think this theme will be the most
resonant theme in my world,
and in your world as well.
I want to write a good story and I want
to experience a better story myself.
That's what I want to make a good song.
I think we're mistaken that 1.5 billion
people in the world can make a band with
that.
They focus on music more than we do.
I thought about it while I was writing
it myself, but I wonder if it's a crime.