I can only say it now.
The way you overcame like and dislike is
dirty.
That's right. You can't be caught by
touch.
It's like Super Beaver's music.
Please come in.
Nice to meet you.
It's been a while.
You two are so cool.
Nice to meet you.
I'd like to hear your story.
Please.
Nice to meet you.
Thank you.
Thank you for finding me
Thank you for accepting me
Thank you for loving me
Thank you for remembering me
Thank you for taking care of me
Thank you for being important to me
Thank you for loving me
Thank you for taking care of me
I'm glad I met you
It's so obvious that it's not good
But hey, I have to say it
Thank you for loving me
The band you chose this time was
Arigato.
Yonagisawa-san, who wrote the lyrics,
did you feel the same way when you wrote
Arigato?
Yes, the reason I chose this song is
because I knew what kind of band Super
Viva was.
I thought it was a song that I could
understand various aspects of the band.
At the time, I was very simple.
I was just finishing my first major
debut.
I was on my own for two years.
There were four members and I was doing
various things.
I was going around the live show.
And when it was LORDN Έ de D darling
villageın SAEkill
I was thinking about what kind of song
to sing.
I remember that if I could sing the word
thank you in a simple way,
I could express the current Super
Beaver.
I remember that conversation.
At first, it was a very small
opportunity.
I was thinking about what would happen
if I used the words I usually use,
but I was thinking about what I thought
I would do now.
I was grateful that I thought about it
and made it.
And in the lyrics, there's a lot of
thanks.
At that time, I thought about what to
thank for.
I've been thinking a lot about it.
That was the first reason why this song
was made.
It's been 17 years since Super Weaver,
but I think it's a band that has been
supported by many people until the 17th
year.
That's our pride, and when we think back
on the honor of being able to come this
far,
it's because we like the activities
we've done so far that a lot of people's
faces come to mind.
When I think about the people who have
supported us, I think of them one by
one.
I want to say thank you so much that the
variation of this song is not enough.
That's true.
There are so many.
It depends on the person.
That's right.
The way the song sounds.
After all, we have been on stage many
times.
Of course, the same scenery is not
always the same.
The feelings we have at that time are
also different.
There are times when I feel grateful for
the song, but I don't feel good about
it.
It's a simple message from a simple
name.
When I made this demo, I was not
confident in saying thank you in
Hiragana's title.
I wrote thank you in Roman.
I remember sending the demo to the
members.
When I finished, I still use this as a
super Viva.
I was still shy enough to be able to
sing it as one song.
That shyness was the reason.
It was a thank you to the Roman Empire.
It was a bit of a joke.
There's a saying,
The Roman Empire is a cataclysmic
cataclysm.
It's like a little bit of a
If you're going to put the essence into
it,
Even at the demo stage,
Don't write it like this.
It's a straight line.
That's the way the thank you is.
That's the way it is.
It's better to shoot it properly.
I think it's a good word to say.
That's right.
I think it's a word that you can't hear
in bad words.
Considering the stance we can do,
I don't think we can do anything else.
It doesn't be fun to do it quickly.
You can try various things by looking at
the tree, or take a pose from various
angles.
I'm sure those who can do it can do it.
Have you tried it?
I have.
I've done it, but I'm not into it.
In short, it doesn't appear on the
surface as a form.
There was a time when I wanted to do it
like this.
I thought that this kind of music that
is popular now would be like this.
I've tried to incorporate it, but in the
end it doesn't feel good.
I think that's all we have.
So what's on the table now is all our
stance.
That's what I just shot out.
I want to convey what suits me in a
realistic way.
Oil painting allows me to become a Brian
environmentalist and director.
Otherwise it won't look like I've made
things up properly.
Mil parabens were also a result of
adding a character into my work.
I wanted to be lighting up the
foundations and beginning with feeling
the face.
The words you use when you give it
meaning are what brings you to reality.
That's why its consumers' daily
Computers.
They understand what you're talking
about.
They speak to you with carries in mind.
I guess the reason why itís not suitable
sheep's ajuss is because you're
profesional,
hence what you cour to reluctant to use.
The reason I chose this song is quite
big.
When I was able to appear in various
events little by little,
I was able to express the words of
gratitude with my voice and sound.
When I expressed it from the stage, I
felt that the way I liked it or hated it
was so dirty.
I was able to feel it in this song.
Until then, when there were many people
who performed aggressively,
we thought we should try to sell a lot
of aggressive songs to the setlist.
There were times when we thought that
way.
Now, I remember the song that Super
Beaver was proud of
and was able to sing with his feet on
the ground.
I remember the song that made me think
of myself.
I was healthy such as that Super Viva
live performance
that Shibuya cooked for me in charge of
at my live performance,
I feel very sorry for him.
I think it's great that Shibuya says,
Thank you now, not later.
Because we've been working together for
a long time,
I think it's a band that knows that
there are few things that can be done by
ourselves.
I saw the face of the person on the
floor on the stage,
and I saw the will of the person who
tried to make this day.
When I think about it, the words that
only come out at that time,
like thank you, come out with you.
If you feel that, you can only say it
now, thinking that you can only say it
now.
Really, you should say it now.
I've been connected to it, not just on
stage.
Not just on stage.
There are so many moments in life and in
daily life.
I've been self-aware of it every time I
sing.
I've been self-aware of it with the
members.
I was inspired by the words of Shibuya,
who was born.
感じたりとかするってことがまた自分の作曲だったり作詞に
活かされるってこともあるわけですよね。
そうですね。ちょうど、MCから言葉をそのまま歌詞にピックアップして
入れ始めたのがちょうどありがとうとかのあたりで。
同じアルバムにあなたっていう楽曲も入ってるんですけど、
あなたっていうのもそれぐらいの時期に
シビアが明確にあなたたちじゃなくあなたに歌ってる。
This is really wonderful.
Until then, I didn't really care about
it.
I used to use the word, you, in my
second album.
Well, I used to sing the word, you,
depending on the song.
I'll try to change everything to you.
That's how I started writing songs.
It was a word that came from Shibuya.
The fact that I changed it to you later
on was another moment of Super Beaver.
It's a song I wrote, but it's a word of
Super Beaver and a word of Shibuya
Ryuta.
The words I used on stage were more
intense than ever before.
I thought I was getting more and more
inspired by the music.
That's how much I've been using the
words on stage.
I've been listening to them all the
time,
so sometimes I can't hear them all.
But there are words that come to mind.
That's what I'm excited about right now.
When I make a song, I'm really...
I've been thinking about how to make
music that's literally Super Beaver's
words.
When you guys are on stage, you're like,
Oh, there's someone in here.
You're just thinking about it.
But when you're called,
Oh, it's me.
I'm also excited when I say this myself.
I thought I'd tell you this.
There's almost nothing I want to do on
stage.
But when I was singing, I wanted to
deliver more.
But I wondered what I should do to
It's like a pre-school reunion in
elementary school.
The reason why I can't get into the
principal's story.
Why I wasn't interested in it.
Why I don't remember anything.
gew.
I thought they were looking at us as a
group.
I thought it was thin because I was
looking at them as a group.
I thought that the words that were 100%
were divided into the number of people
in the group, so it was getting thinner
and thinner.
When I wanted to deliver more and more,
it floated.
I thought, that's right. You shouldn't
be taken by the touch.
I'm singing to you.
I thought that if I clearly thought and
clearly said that,
I thought that maybe they would listen
to the music more,
or they would feel more comfortable.
Since we were four people playing
together,
and we realized that it wasn't just the
four of us,
I thought that I had to deliver the
message,
and that I had to deliver it.
Do you feel any changes in the way the
audience has changed over the years?
I don't think the audience has changed
much.
I think the audience has felt different
depending on the song.
We haven't changed in the way we
perform.
But, as I thought...
I felt that the people who were watching
me were doing their best.
They were watching me from the floor.
That was a chance for me to realize
that.
I think music is not just about you.
You have your own way of listening.
No matter how much you admire it,
there are people who are staring at it.
I think it was a tempo that raised your
fist.
There are people who are the only one
who are proud and raising their fists.
When I started doing this song called
Thank you,
I was personally very aware of that.
What are the people who listen to it?
Thank you.
I think that's what they thought about
me at the live show.
I was very impressed.
I'm originally a person who goes to the
live show.
I always talk a lot with the members.
But since such people sing and deliver
it,
I think that kind of atmosphere is cool.
I think that was very good.
It's important to be accepted.
I think it's important to be accepted.
I've always been a fan of music.
I've never thought I was a player.
I'm a player, but I've never thought I
was a player.
I've always been a fan of music.
I think I understand.
I think it's natural that this song
changed the music of this song,
but I think the people who received it
changed because they changed themselves.
I think I'm going to betray the attitude
of trying to convey it seriously to the
gentleman,
but I think it will reach the people who
are listening to it.
I think no one will listen to the story
of a person who is just doing it somehow
and trying to convey it somehow, but
I want you to really understand, I
really want to convey it, I really
think, everyone will listen to the story
of the person who is seriously saying
it.
I think that's what I like about music.
I think that the music is only stuck in
the music of someone who seriously loves
that music and seriously throws it.
I think that stance is very important.
I think it's very important to face each
other sincerely and to do what we're
doing seriously and seriously.
So, from this song, we can do that.
I think that's how it has become.
So, I think that the people who are
watching this
are listening to it seriously,
and they are genuinely enjoying it.
That's what I thought.
It's a good starting point.
Well, not starting point,
it's not that it changed suddenly,
but it's a good start.
We've been doing that all the time.
But, I have a feeling
that it's not going to be as good as it
was before.