Thank you for watching.
On this day, in Sonic City in Omiya,
Saitama Prefecture,
the first day of the concept live MOVE
was held throughout the three cities.
And the new members appear at the venue
The first stage at the Famien, which is
approaching in two months
They study the flow of the live
performance
And then
Amazing!
The energy was amazing
It was amazing
Furthermore
This time, we will show you the moves
that ended up being a big success with
Digest
Live on the morning of the day
Good morning
What are you doing today?
Today we are going to see the live show
Checking the flow
Looking at the face of the senior
I'm staring at it
Is it your first time to have a
audience?
Oh, that's right
I wonder if there are many people
I think so
The passion of the people
This day is for the first stage of
Hitaru Kamien
Not only daily lessons
To understand the flow of the day
To visit the senior members' live
It's the first time for the three of
them to see the live show with the
audience
I think it will be very exciting
It looks amazing
It's fun
The tension and the enthusiasm
I'm looking forward to it
Usually it's fun and cute
I'm looking at it like that
Today, I'm going to dance
This is amazing
I have to do this
I think I have to see that
The live show starts at 5 pm
From morning, the schedule is full of
various preparations for the live show
新メンバーもレッスン着替えて オイストレーニングに参加
めっちゃ楽しみです めっちゃ期待してます
やっとの オイショー
オイストレーニングの終わり
I'll do my best.
Is it a tough day?
Yes. But the staff is more difficult
than us.
It's a different stage than usual.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you.
After the warm-up, the members head to
the stage.
It's a bit irregular from now on, but
today we're going to have a moving set
on the stage.
The technical rehearsal, the adults, the
staff, watch the moving rehearsal and
imagine what kind of movement they're
going to do.
We're going to do something a little
irregular ourselves.
The title of this live show is MOVE.
As the name suggests, the stage set and
the members are a dazzling and moving
live show.
That's why the members are also going to
meet up with each other from the
rehearsal of the stage staff.
Everyone, please live safely.
Check the live performance by looking at
the movement of the set.
After the set and lighting adjustment is
finished,
the rehearsal of the members in the live
performance.
Good morning. We are
SSAMCHANMUKUNARIMASHITA.
We are SSAMCHANMUKUNARIMASHITA.
Please sing the song.
Thank you.
I can't do it.
The tension of the main stage.
New members are overwhelmed by the mic
check.
I'll do my best to check the mic.
I'm going to do my best.
Thank you. How was it?
You can hear the sound from the
earphones when you sing.
I'm checking that now.
The sound is different depending on the
person.
I'm checking my singing skills.
The rehearsal is going to check the
positions and formations.
I just don't want to talk to you
Then...
How many times did you start?
I started with 4 times.
Can you start with one more time?
Yes.
Then you can start from there.
Yes, I can start from 5 times.
If you can start from the previous move,
then...
Yes, I can start from there.
Of course, she has been giving lessons
many times.
Only the rehearsal before the
performance can be confirmed on the same
stage as the original.
The members are asked to respond to the
fine-tuning.
I thought that the formation would
change a little on the day of this
performance.
I was surprised that the members were
able to do it just by listening to it.
If I was told to do it on the day of the
performance, I would forget the
performance.
Finally, they check the moving set.
The rehearsal is over!
Thank you for the rehearsal.
We'll do our best to keep you safe.
Thank you.
What happened?
It was quite a mess.
I think it's more than usual.
The staff did this kind of set on the
stage.
It was never like this before.
It took a lot of time to get used to it.
We have to check one by one.
Safety first.
I'm sorry.
I'm happy.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'll do my best.
I'll do my best to make eye contact with
you.
The guests start at 4 pm.
More and more people are coming in.
It's really crowded.
We're halfway there.
You can do it!
I forgot to bring my bag
I'll do my best!
It's already been 3 minutes, so let's go
inside and do the re-enactment
Where are we?
ORIYA!
Eri-chan!
Riku!
Riku-chan!
Thank you for your hard work!
Bye-bye.
See you later.
After seeing off the senior members,
they go to the audience seat to watch
the live performance.
Then...
The fans who noticed the new member
applauded
Yes, the three are already members of
Ebichu
With a warm applause, it became a moment
to realize it
And then
The live show will start
In a town that doesn't even know your
name
There's no one around
My lonely fingertips
Are trembling with anxiety
No matter how many times I try
I can't get out of my mind
Even if I'm left alone
I'll surely reach out
Ah, I'll sing until I reach you
There's something I want to deliver to
the world
I'm a little confused, but I'm waiting
A never-ending kickstart
Clap my attention, we are your party
Hold up, hold up, hold up
Market teak
But I guess I'll just have to dream
about it!
Let's dance, it's fun!
The show is ready now
Finally,
A performance using the moving-set
The point is her character
Money, money, money, money, money
I want you to accept it, that punch
You're a fool, don't do that
You guys are a bad kid, once more
Start off, start the fest
DA DA DA DA DA DA DA DA DA DA DA
Thank you for watching!
At the ending of the live, she sang with
the audience.
She sang with the audience.
Let's ring it, let's ring it
Please buy us more veiwe then
Don't try to stop me
Put love into my heart
With one more love
Once again, I'll put my love into it
So, that's it for today.
Have a nice day, everyone!
Thank you very much.
And the live show is over.
Thank you, everyone!
Thank you for coming!
I was surprised.
Thank you for your hard work.
I was so moved.
Please take a seat.
Thank you for your hard work.
The new members who experienced the live
performance of the seniors in the space
where the audience is
I was able to see it on May 5th without
the audience
Today's audience is more than that
It's completely different
Especially the last applause of the jump
I'm really impressed when everyone is
doing it together
Today, everyone was there
I thought it was amazing
I was looking forward to the performance
of the seniors
I think all the singing, physical
strength, and talking are amazing
I will do my best to answer the
questions
I was wondering what would happen on the
stage
The stage is 100 million times more
amazing
I was really impressed
I was doing the choreography with the
audience
It's exciting when the audience is there
I think it's easy to do
The live performance was amazing
I was worried that it would be bad if it
was like this
I will do my best in the daily lessons
Next episode, I will be on TV for the
first time