The next episode will be revealed!
Hello everyone!
We are...
The Dori-dori team!
Thank you!
This time, the four of us have finally
decided to form the Nogizaka Baseball
Club!
Yay!
This is the first video.
Until now, we've done videos of us
actually going to the stadium and
watching the game,
and we've done videos of us playing pro-
spin.
We're finally going to form the Nogizaka
Baseball Club,
but I think we'll be playing games
someday.
I hope we can do a lot of things.
We've never really talked about who's
going to play.
We don't know where to start.
So, we've invited a special coach for
the first time.
I'm surprised.
We've invited a really special person as
a coach.
This person!
Yes, thank you!
I've been waiting for this.
I'm so happy!
You're going to make it happen, right?
Yes, I'm so happy!
I've been waiting for this.
What do you think of this ugly jersey?
It's the official Nogizaka jersey.
We can make a baby doll.
I want it!
It's good to design it ourselves.
Is it okay?
Can we do it?
Yes, of course.
Please.
Everyone is saying yes.
It's decided.
Please subscribe to our channel!
We're finally getting started.
I heard you have something you want to
do.
Yes, I do.
My dream is to play in the Marine
Stadium.
So, I'd like to teach Satozaki how to
pitch.
I think you can do it soon.
Can I?
I want to learn the techniques that suit
it.
I want to learn how to pitch cool.
So, let's practice to throw the ball
well.
Thank you.
Let's start with the catch ball.
I want to see how much you can do
without teaching anything.
Wow.
I'll do my best.
Let's start.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
You're good at it.
You can catch the ball normally.
Sorry, it's high.
But I can catch the ball normally.
With a bandage.
I'm scared.
It looks fun.
It's high.
It's OK.
If you can do this, you can throw it
well.
This is very easy.
The most important thing to throw a
catch ball is the hand holding the
glove.
It's better than the hand holding the
ball.
Turn to the side and raise it.
Put your thumb in the glove.
Throw the ball from top to bottom.
Good
Yes, yes, yes.
So, in general, it's like this.
And
Right hand
I'm going to get it out.
Strongly
I'll take the role of throwing.
You want to throw it cool, right?
Then, left, right, left.
When you throw right, raise your legs.
Left, right, left.
Raise your legs.
Left, raise your legs.
I see.
You can throw it with a good rhythm.
Left, right, raise your legs, left.
Left, right, raise your legs.
Yes, yes, yes!
Wow!
Left, right, left.
Yes, yes, yes!
Very good!
It looks like it's going to reach the
target.
It's going to reach the target.
Wow!
Yes, yes, nice!
Thank you.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Nice!
Why?
Isn't it great?
Great!
It's fun!
It's only this part.
Great!
Nice!
It's fun!
It's easy, right?
Yes! It's fun!
Left, raise your leg, left.
That's right!
Nice!
It's fun!
Great!
Left, raise your leg, left.
That's right!
Thank you!
It's fun!
Great!
That's right!
It's amazing!
Great!
Wow!
Only one ball came out!
It was so quick!
It was easy, wasn't it?
And then, you can do it cool.
Left, right, left.
Left.
If you keep the rhythm, it's easy to
raise your legs.
And then, if you want to put your hands
on it,
left, right, left.
Left?
I'm not sure.
Yes, yes!
What's going on?
I lost my balance.
Where should I put my hands?
From here.
Left, right.
I see.
I did it!
You did it.
If you do it with your left hand...
Yes, yes, yes!
Wow!
Cool!
You can throw it right away.
Wow!
You got a good rhythm.
You can throw it right away.
Let's start with the mount.
Finally.
I'll try it as a beginner.
Left, right, pull
Wow, it's like a photo taken by Sato
Saki
It's crazy
First take, right?
Yes, please
Wow
Darling
Yes, yes, yes!
Wow!
A little higher!
Yes!
Here I go!
Ah! Sorry!
It's almost there!
You shouldn't put too much pressure on
it.
That's right.
A little more to the left.
A little higher.
Yes, yes, yes!
And then there.
Yes!
Here I go!
Please!
Yes!
Nice!
You did it!
Thank you!
Yes!
Wow!
Did it reach?
Yes!
But it's not like you're putting a lot
of effort into it.
Really?
I'm going to go now. Thank you!
This is the softball practice ground.
It's true.
Close!
You almost got it!
Almost there!
Aim for the pillar above.
Aim high.
Here I go.
Yes!
That was a good one!
Really?
Here I go.
That's it!
You did it!
Thank you!
The second challenge
Please
Wow
You're doing good
You can do it if you put more power into
it
Yes
The second challenge
That's right!
That's amazing!
Yes!
That's great!
I haven't played Satsumori before.
You did well.
Nice!
That was easy.
Thank you.
Next time, we will play Satsumori.
It was really cool.
The form is cool.
Good luck.
It's far.
I will go.
A little more.
The form is beautiful.
I'll nail it!
Let's have an issue-free go
Wow!
Nice!
Wow, so far
Let's go
Wow!
You nailed it!
Show us the energy that Son Kai has
gained.
Yes!
Nice!
It's coming!
Wow!
Thank you!
It's so beautiful!
It's not that difficult, is it?
I didn't have to put much effort.
It's coming.
The balance of the form was the best.
Wow!
The way you stood was the best.
Thank you.
It was strong.
And the ball's rescue was the best.
Wow!
I did it!
Konomi, the dynamics of the form was the
best.
Wow!
The dynamics were the best.
But, everyone was able to throw the ball
well.
And, you didn't miss the ball.
You didn't miss the ball that much.
I see.
I just did this.
I can control the ball with this.
I can control the ball.
You can aim, right?
Yes.
You can do this anytime.
Wow!
I can do it.
I'm sure.
We're waiting for your request.
We'll go anywhere with the 12-ball ball.
We'll go anywhere.
You should say it.
Do you have any questions?
It's a fundamental question.
How can I hold the ball?
It's forbidden.
Straighten your fingers.
The opposite of C.
I see.
Put your fingers on the top of the seam.
The reason is that the ring finger is
slightly higher.
The ring finger is longer.
The ring finger is on the seam.
It's hard to get the ball out.
I see.
It's not slippery until the end.
Does the ball change depending on how
you get the ball out?
Recently, I've been using two seams.
I can hold the ball like this.
Is the difference between two seams and
one seam?
The seam is the seam of the seam.
I see.
If you hold the ball like this, there is
only one or two air resistance.
The air resistance is distorted and
bent.
I see.
The seam is the seam of the seam.
If you put the ball in the middle of the
seam and throw it, it will be one seam.
The seam is the seam of the seam.
I didn't know that.
I can answer anything.
When I ask you to throw this, do you
notice when I throw a different ball?
I notice it.
I see.
The most common problem is that the ball
comes straight with the change ball.
Do you think the ball will bend?
If the ball bends, the ball will not
bend, so the ball will not come out.
If the ball hits the ball, the ball will
not bend, so the ball will come
straight.
I see.
If the ball comes straight with a change
ball, the ball will bend.
The ball will come out slowly.
If the ball comes fast because the ball
is slow, the ball will hit the ball.
The ball will bend.
The ball will hit the ball.
I see.
If there is no runner, the ball will hit
the ball.
If you make a mistake, you will be in
danger.
That's right.
It's the same as that.
You are in danger.
We can't say that because we are
singing.
I feel uncomfortable.
What do you do if you make a mistake?
I will call you.
I have one more thing to tell you.
I used to play softball.
I have been playing softball for 3 years
and I have never hit a ball.
Is that so?
I want you to teach me how to bat.
I will teach you.
You should be able to hit a ball.
I want to hit a ball.
It's easy to bat.
It's easy to make a shape.
Don't teach me anything.
I'm scared.
I'm glad I was able to pitch so well.
Now, show us what you can do.
Here I go.
Isn't it amazing?
I'm scared.
You can lift your leg.
It's dynamic.
That's good.
There's nothing scary about the ring.
It's not scary.
That's right.
Next.
Next
I'll go.
You're good!
Can't I hit it?
I'll definitely hit it.
That's good!
Thank you.
I'll go.
Let's practice.
I'm going to do it now.
Let's go to the next one.
Good.
It's cute.
Thank you.
It's beautiful.
Please subscribe to our channel.
The power is different.
I'll do it.
It's amazing.
Please register your channel.
Everyone is better than I thought.
I think so.
I have something to say to Kurumi.
Your hands are upside down.
I thought so.
Your right hand is up.
This is tennis.
This is a tennis racket.
I will do it today.
I will throw a mound.
I will throw a mound with no pan.
I will challenge it.
I put my weight on the base of my thumb.
I turn the center of the thumb.
The person on the right is the right
waist.
The person on the left is the left
I turn the center of the thumb.
I put my elbow on the center of the
thumb.
I put my strength on the center of the
I kick with my right foot.
Turn your right hip firmly.
Turn your left hip firmly.
End assembly
Yes, yes, yes
It's difficult
And then, when you hold it
Like this
And then, shake it
With force
I see
Yes, yes, yes
If you turn it
Like that
Yes
Amazing
Yes, yes, yes
Next, throw it a little
Match it
And hit it
It's difficult
To be continued
I'll throw.
What..is she gonna do?
I'm going to do it again.
One more time.
Wow!
Amazing!
And in one shot!
Wow!
That's amazing!
Really?
It's easy, right?
No, stop it!
Hey!
The hurdle goes up.
It's good.
Wow!
What? What?
What?
Wow!
It's a hit.
I hit it.
It's amazing.
Next, the second ball.
Wow!
It's a hit.
Nice!
Amazing!
Thank you very much!
I love it!
I'll do it.
I did it!
Hey!
No, no, no.
I'm scared.
What?
I love it!
You said you were scared of the swing,
but you hit it perfectly.
I just did the same thing as before.
Really?
I'll do it.
I can only scream.
It's perfect.
The last one was amazing.
I was surprised.
To be continued.
Wow!
That's it!
It hurts!
If you could do that, you would have hit
the ball!
Really?
I see.
Yes!
Wow!
I did it!
Great!
That's amazing!
I can't believe it!
It's a bonus!
Thank you so much!
You can do it!
I want to participate in a match!
It was like a dream.
I didn't know that I could fly like
this.
You can even fly at a good angle.
It's amazing that you can fly at a good
angle.
It's not a gorilla.
But it was good.
Thank you so much.
If you can do it well, you can win.
I'm imitating batting form.
Oh, I see.
You should try it.
Should I?
You want to see it, don't you?
You want to see it in person, don't you?
I want to try it.
It's my first time to try it.
Be careful of your hands.
Please subscribe to our channel.
I'll try it.
It's just right at your fingers.
Oh my God!
Ahahahaha!
Ah, but...
You always get thrown the bat, right?
Yes, yes.
Thank you.
Let's start from the beginning.
You're going to teach me?
You should start from this.
Then, Lotte fans will be happy.
Really?
Pull your left leg a little.
Start from this.
Wow!
You're good at it!
Let's do it.
You're already done.
Can you teach me?
Pull your left leg a little.
When you enter, do this.
Like this?
Yes.
And then, tighten your arms a little.
Like this?
Yes.
That's amazing.
I like the last move.
I could see the line of reward.
I could see it.
Thank you for teaching me about batting
and pitching.
How was it, Mazu?
I was very weak when I was playing
softball.
I was always on the bench.
I'm glad that I was able to get better
by teaching the professional players.
I'll get better.
I want to get better when I meet
Satozaki again.
How about you, Yuno?
I didn't expect that Satozaki, who I was
cheering for, would teach me so closely.
I was really happy.
I want to practice as soon as possible.
How about you, Kurumi?
I've never experienced it before.
I'm surprised that I can have more fun
than usual.
I want to play baseball with everyone
someday.
I've been playing softball and pro-
wrestling.
I didn't expect to play a real game.
But I like baseball. I realized that it
was difficult to play baseball.
I'm going to watch baseball from now on.
I think I was able to tell them that we
are serious.
I think the fans are excited.
I didn't know you could do that.
You've never seen it before, have you?
That's right.
I think the fans are also excited.
I'm sure the fans are also excited.
I'm glad.
I'm glad that the fans were able to
discover new things.
I'm glad.
I'm glad to hear that.
Thank you very much.
I'm surprised.
I'll practice hard and get better.
I'll go to the stadium and make a
baseball uniform.
I'm looking forward to seeing you again.
We also collaborated with SATOZAKI
CHANNEL.
Please watch that video.
I have one more request.
Let's say it together.
We are looking forward to your baseball
ceremony.
We are looking forward to it.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Why did you try to imitate me?
It's easier to imitate someone who has a
habit.
For example, Mori from the western club.
Like, I have a habit?
You have a strong habit.
Can Mori do it?
Yes, he can.
Do it properly.
Wow, it's similar!
It's similar!
You can do it, right?
Yes.
I always take pictures here.