Yakan Tidal!
Let's start the main project!
Please give us a cute title call!
Yes!
My three major elements!
Thank you for watching!
In this corner, we will introduce three
elements that make up our bodies.
What are you made of by dividing
yourself into three elements?
By touching on those elements, let's get
to know the idol even more deeply.
So, can you tell us about the three
elements?
Ta-da! Yes, it looks like this.
You draw so well! You are unique!
Thank you for watching!
I love sweets.
They make my body.
Yeah.
I always carry them in a pouch.
What kind of sweets?
I'll bring a pouch.
A pouch?
Can I?
Sure.
I love sweets.
Yakan and idol.
First, I want to have a sweet and salty
taste.
I see. These are the two main elements.
Well...
I want to have a combination.
What's your favorite food?
I like jagariko. It's my favorite.
You like jagariko?
Yes, jagariko is my favorite.
And then...
I want to have a summer sub day.
Country mom.
The key point is that you often get a
lot of food.
That's a must.
I'll bring it home.
I'll have some sweets.
If you have a meeting at a entertainment
show,
you can get some sweets.
What's the secret to your sweet and
salty taste?
You brought all the food you want.
Did you prepare it yourself?
Yes, I always bring the food I want.
All the food is included in this field.
That explains it.
And Dukaku, please bring your marry 자
계속해서 suis CONTACT
Anytime, isn't that right?
Lets be healthy while eating.
Is that far enough?
Of course it's all right!
Yay!
Yakan and idol!
Thank you very much!
You can drink tea while eating sweets.
I heard you like sweets.
Please open the second box.
You really eat sweets.
I thought it was a food talk.
Some people don't show their eating
pictures.
I always eat sweets on the air.
Thank you very much.
You eat sweets.
You are a real person.
I'm the type of person who focuses on
the lyrics.
What kind of lyrics?
I'm nervous and can't come out.
What? What are you going to do?