We, Kiyakizaka46, will close the curtain
on the past five years.
And we will bid farewell to Kiyakizaka46
with a positive attitude.
We are always incomplete.
We, Kiyakizaka46, will continue to work
hard.
They've sent back-up.
I'm not alone anymore
This has been Hakura Suka46!
Thank you!
And then...
Welcome to the final Tokyo Dome concert
of the Kokurazaka46 national tour!
This day became a turning point for
Sakurazaka46.
There were girls who were watching the
stage from afar.
Sakurazaka46, the third generation.
The new member audition for
Sakurazaka46, which has been held since
the summer of 2022.
I'm Rika Ishimori, a college student
from Gunma Prefecture.
I'm Riko Endo. I'm 16 years old, a
second-year high school student from
Saitama Prefecture.
I'm Reina Odakura, 18 years old, a
third-year high school student from
Tokyo.
I live in Nagano Prefecture. I'm Nagisa
Kojima, a second-year high school
student, 17 years old.
Hi, I'm Airi Taniguchi, a second-year
high school student from Yamaguchi
Prefecture, and 17 years old.
I'm Izuki Nakashima, a second-year
college student from Fukuoka Prefecture,
and 19 years old.
I'm Mio Mito, a first-year high school
student from Fukuoka Prefecture.
I'm Ita Mukai, a first-year high school
student from Hiroshima Prefecture, and
16 years old.
I live in Osaka Prefecture. I'm Miyu
Murayama, a third-year high school
student, and 17 years old.
I love you so much.
It's been about four years since the
last Sakamichi joint audition.
This is the first time for Sakurazaka46
to audition alone.
There are many new members who like
Sakurazaka and have gathered here.
It's not uncommon to see new members who
talk about their admiration for the
group.
My nickname is Hikaru Morita.
She is very good at dancing and has a
high level of expression.
My nickname is Yuka Sugai.
It's the day of my graduation.
I've been watching Sakurazaka46.
I've heard that they are different from
other idols.
It's important to have a love for
Sakurazaka46.
But can you really be a member of
Sakurazaka46 with just that feeling?
I'm more excited than scared when I
stand on that stage.
I'm not ready to bear the pressure.
I auditioned with my own feelings.
I will do my best to stand on the stage.
I'm sure no one is confident from the
beginning.
It's the same for the current members.
Actually, I wrote a letter to each
member with my feelings for Yuka.
Did you write a letter?
I hope you will accept it.
When I joined the group and met for the
first time, I was worried if I could
accept it.
At that time, Mr. Sugai welcomed me with
a smile, and I was very relieved.
I came this far with just the feeling of
love.
I was worried that I might be a second
generation in Kiyakizaka.
He listened to my unbearable self-
introduction with a smile.
I've been fighting to protect my group
until today.
I've had some sad moments, but it was
the best!
Thank you for your support for 7 years!
Sakurazaka46 will continue to climb the
hill, so we hope that BUDDIES will
continue to support us.
Please continue to support us.
Good morning.
The 3rd generation came to the training
camp in Yamanashi Prefecture.
They will train for 4 nights and 5 days
here.
They will improve their singing and
dancing skills to become members of
Sakurazaka46.
The training camp is about to start.
You may be the only ones who have
survived and been selected among the
many participants.
But you are not at the level where you
can perform alone.
I hope you will catch up with your
seniors and become the real members of
Sakurazaka46.
It may be a tough training camp, but I
hope you will follow us to the end.
The members are gathered in the gym.
Good morning.
I'm Akane, and I'll be your instructor
today.
Nice to meet you.
I think everyone came here to see the
dome yesterday.
I'm sure you all had some thoughts.
You have to jump into that dome.
The first thing I thought when I came in
was that the greetings were small.
I think there's a part of you that's
relieved that you've been chosen.
I think it's not that, it's just the
beginning.
I don't know if you know the answer to
all the answers.
I think it's about the smallest of
people, so let's start with that.
The answer is great.
The song is called BANG.
It is also the most difficult dance, and
the most representative of the
Sakurazaka 46.
In the end, Mr. Takahiro will come and
see it.
I want to bring it to the level that I
can perform in front of the audience.
Mr. Takahiro, a dancer, is in charge of
many choreographies, including the band.
The goal is to perform a perfect dance
in front of Mr. Takahiro on the last day
of the camp.
Actually, during the training before the
camp, they only practiced the chorus
part.
First, they show the results of the
practice.
I want to know more
I'm glad that no one was able to stop
dancing.
Did you practice this?
Why can't you say yes with confidence?
Did you practice?
I want you to dance with confidence.
I think there was a question about
singing before the performance.
What would you do if you weren't
singing?
It's not just dancing.
It's a dance with a song, so please sing
every time.
I couldn't hear anyone singing in the
performance.
How about this compared to the seniors
yesterday?
It's not good at all.
I think that everyone doesn't have that
awareness yet.
No matter how hard you practice, you
can't do anything just standing on the
stage.
The seniors I saw yesterday will go
ahead.
You have to work hard and catch up with
everyone.
I was told that I had practiced, but I
couldn't say yes with a loud voice.
I thought I couldn't practice, so I
thought I had to be confident in the
future.
I felt that I wasn't conscious enough.
I felt that I had to get used to this
training camp to get over it.
「Somidare yo oshiete kure kumorizora ni
sakendeta 」 by Aoi
Thank you for watching!
atenami, diemehaji ni
tarishi juusou
besii bunyou
narase
shimau
hinai
axe
lerari
kono
naku
vorou
mukama
ni
mitare
yo
aries
arghu
bere
shita
takasai
mfry
think
gyuzo
nonk
Ami
uigi
I'm holding an umbrella, so I can go see
you right now
I believe in an eternity that will never
end, no matter what happens
There's no way I can find the answer,
that's love
Even you who cannot die
where all is well
Sakura Daka's members learn everything
in 3 hours.
If you don't know, come and ask me.
This lesson time is limited, so you have
to absorb it here.
I've been a subject, so I'm not good at
memorizing.
So I'll do my best.
No, this way.
Behind you.
I didn't say this during practice, but
you can see it yourself.
I can't dance at all.
I'm the worst dancer here.