to be continued...
What should I do?
I'm worried.
I'm scared.
Why are you so worried?
What's wrong, Kaho?
Grandpa?
I'll be able to do it.
There are things I can't do if I do it.
You're so naive.
I want to be like you.
Let's start the self-introduction
program.
Hello, everyone.
Hello.
I'm Kobayashi Kaho, 11th grade in the
class of private school.
I'm Riko Nakayama, 12th grade in the
Nice to meet you.
This program is a secret experiment in
the lab.
We are going to do a secret experiment
in this lab.
We are going to observe the experiment
process to make a chemical reaction in
the ebb.
This program is asking for your
questions.
Please ask questions to the short story
stream.
At the end of the program, we will
choose one and answer the questions.
We are waiting for your questions.
Please send us your questions.
What should we do?
I don't know.
Hello.
Isn't that Hiro?
Hi, Suzuki!
Hello.
You were worried about us today, weren't
you?
The staff called me.
Hiro, I'm sorry.
The part of the chest is cool.
Please introduce yourself.
I'm Suzuki Rono, the 8th student in
Shirito Ebisu Middle School.
Please do the slush.
Please continue to recommend the corner.
I'm pretty reliable.
I'm not as good as Mizuki.
But you came.
Thank you.
Good luck.
Let's go to the first corner.
The first corner is...
Right.
Who am I? Will you tell me?
The experiment corner!
Ready.
Let's carry it.
I wonder if it's okay.
Okay.
Thank you.
I want you to come here and give us a
hug.
I ate the hair.
I'll explain.
This corner is about us who just joined
the EBU.
We want you to know more about us.
We made a quiz about us that we don't
know much about.
We did this corner last time.
Today...
Are you surprised?
No, I'm sorry.
I'll ask Hiroto to answer.
Okay.
Question.
Yes.
There are four cards here.
I have a question.
Please choose one card from the list.
What is the food that makes you excited
when it's in your lunch box?
It's difficult.
Think about it.
I have to think about it first.
I have to write it down.
Please think about the answer.
OK.
I feel like I've spoken for the first
time today.
I don't know.
I have decided.
What is it?
Something like this.
Like this?
I don't think it's in my lunch box.
It's not in my lunch box.
I think it's definitely in my lunch box.
I have decided.
It's difficult.
It doesn't matter.
What should I do?
I don't know.
Riko... What should I call you?
Riko.
Please.
Kaho.
Kaho Riko.
Riko.
Riko...
I don't know about Riko.
What is it?
It's not in the box.
It's not easy to find it.
What is it?
Okay.
Have you decided?
Kaho, you choose fried chicken.
I choose omelette.
Yay!
Why?
I like omelette, but I also like fried
chicken.
That's strange. I was confident.
I choose omelette.
Omelette.
That one?
It's light.
There are salty and sweet.
Sweet?
Yes.
Yes, sweet.
It looks delicious.
Does it?
What about Riko?
I don't know.
What is it?
Hamburger.
Cucumber!
You like cucumbers, don't you?
Cucumber.
It's in the menu.
It's in the desk.
I like the cucumber in the morning.
I like it.
I always get it when I go to my
grandmother's house.
Cucumber.
I like the morning.
You don't like pickles?
I like the cucumber in the potato salad.
Hamburger.
It looks like Riku-chan.
Thank you.
Next.
Answer.
I'll get it.
Let's get a sketchbook.
Do you think?
Yes, I think.
I think.
I see.
I have a question.
Riku-chan, you can go.
I'll go?
Which one did you draw?
I don't like this.
I'm sorry.
What is your favorite Japanese old
story?
It's difficult.
Old story?
Do you need it?
No.
I don't need it.
Old story?
It's difficult.
It's like Momotaro.
Or the snow woman.
It's a bad one.
I was going to say Momotaro.
But there are many.
I can only think of Momotaro.
Old story?
I've come up with a difficult question.
There are many.
There are too many.
I don't know.
I can't remember.
I've decided.
Can I choose the one I remember?
What is it?
There are many stories from the past.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
Is this correct? I don't know.
I think so. Then, the next one is
Urashima Taro.
What was it? Sarukanigasen?
Sarukanigasen?
Huh?
Sarukanigasen.
The answer is...
Issunboshi.
Issunboshi?
I only remembered this.
You didn't remember that?
I didn't remember it.
Issunboshi.
It's a long story.
We rode on the tea boat to the city.
And we said,
No, I don't remember.
Oh, I see.
There was a little kid.
Huh?
I didn't expect that.
You didn't expect that.
I often remembered Issunboshi.
I didn't remember it.
I don't remember it at all.
It's a long story.
It's hard.
Well, this is...
It's over.
That's all.
Who am I?
You can know...
It was an experiment.
Yay!
It's a little tricky.
It's hard.
The next one is...
If you do nothing with Kaoriko,
It's an experiment.
Yay!
This time,
We've already finished the story.
Hiro's senior is here, too.
I'm going to play a game of eho.
I'm hungry.
I don't know if I can cook.
You can cook.
It's okay.
I'll do something.
Are you ready?
Let's get started.
This one.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
OK. Please take out the chair.
Oh, sorry.
OK.
Wow!
Ready, set, go!
I turned it upside down.
What should I do?
Wow, there's a cucumber!
There's a cucumber!
Wow!
That's good.
It's a Japanese roll.
Wow, it's a Japanese roll.
Let's wash our hands.
Excuse me.
Huh?
Thank you.
Yeah, that's it.
Wow, there are so many things.
Yeah, there are so many things.
Oh, I see.
Wow, it looks delicious.
It's big. What is this?
Chikuwa?
It's isobe.
Isobe?
Yeah.
I guess it's a tart.
Okay, let's make it.
Let's make it. What about the garbage?
The garbage is around there.
It's open.
Is there a vinegar in here?
This?
I can smell it.
Is there vinegar in here?
Is there?
I smell it.
There is no vinegar.
Is there?
I don't know.
I just have to eat it.
But it's okay.
Riko, you can eat it.
How?
I can eat it.
I don't have vinegar.
Is there vinegar?
There is a lot.
I'll make it with rice vinegar.
I don't know.
Riko, you can eat it.
Like this?
Is it okay?
I don't know.
I'll mix it.
Which one?
I don't know.
I like vinegar.
It's rice vinegar.
I smell vinegar.
I get excited when I smell it at school.
Is it okay?
It's like...
Children's day.
It's amazing.
It's okay.
I don't know.
I'll mix it.
It's cute.
Is it okay?
I smell vinegar.
It's amazing.
Let's go down.
It's okay.
Let's mix it.
This?
Go.
I'll pull the seaweed.
Pull it.
Are you going down?
This is...
I don't know.
I don't know. How do you do it?
I don't know how to cook.
Do you help?
No.
Maybe you haven't helped recently.
I made a dish for school summer
vacation.
Do you know how to make it?
I made a seaweed roll.
I don't know.
It's hard to see.
This much?
I don't know.
It looks delicious.
I'm going.
There was no edamame.
Edamame.
What is this?
Katsu?
I don't know the smell.
Thank you.
What is this?
I wonder what this is.
Try putting it in.
Is it sake?
It's sake.
I don't know.
With your hands.
Here.
This is that.
Then, at once.
Quickly.
Isobuyage?
So, Kaho-chan's kan is correct.
Kan.
I'm sorry.
You threw it away.
Why is the name different?
Chikuwa-age.
I think it's okay.
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
Well, let's put the colors one by one.
Red?
Red.
It's all green.
I want to put it in a whole.
Is this egg?
Egg?
This is egg.
I'll put the egg in too.
Egg fried.
Oh, egg fried!
There's something you like in there.
I'll put a lot of cucumber.
Cucumber is the only thing you want?
Then I'll put seaweed and cucumber
instead of rice.
I want to put rice.
How do you roll it?
Kuru-
Ah, but this won't work with rice.
How will it work?
Riko-chan, you did it on your own,
right?
This...
No, no, no!
Oh, but...
Ah, I see.
You can go like this...
You're just going to fly?
Fly!
Ah, if you just do this...
Oh!
I did it!
I really don't know. I'm a big fan of
yours.
I'm a big fan of yours too.
I'm a big fan of yours.
Is this okay?
Then open it.
Do you want to cut it?
Do you want to eat it?
I'm done.
I don't think there's a cookie in here.
There is.
And I did it on this.
I've got a lot of things in here.
Are you okay?
I didn't see anything.
I don't know. But it's amazing.
I've got a lot of things in here.
It's done!
Let's take it out on a plate.
It's dirty.
It's the best! It's delicious.
Do we eat it with our hands?
Let's eat it with our hands.
Is it a yomaki?
Do we cut it with a yomaki?
No.
We can cut it in half.
I'll try it.
It's a cucumber.
I found something I want to eat.
I wonder if there's only an egg in it.
There's only a cucumber and an egg in
it.
Can I eat it?
I'll do rock-paper-scissors.
I'll choose the winner.
Rock-paper-scissors.
I'll eat this.
It looks delicious.
Soy sauce.
This is it.
This one?
It's in my mouth.
It's scary. It's like it's going to get
in my clothes.
I think it's going to be okay.
It's really going to be okay.
Did something come out?
It's okay.
Is it a one-man show?
It's too much.
One person? One person?
Thank you.
I want to make a can.
I want to eat it.
I want to eat it with my hands.
Let's eat it with our hands.
I want to eat it.
It's just a egg.
I'm going to put something in.
No, no, no, no.
Cucumber, cucumber.
I'll eat it.
Was vinegar okay?
Soy sauce is salty.
Vinegar.
It doesn't taste like vinegar.
Tofu.
I might forget.
I think I should use chopsticks.
I think chopsticks are better.
I'll eat this.
Pink?
Orange.
I'll eat this.
You only eat cucumbers?
You like cucumbers as they are, right?
I like the one with the morning pickle.
I'm getting a little bit of a hand.
I really found out that I can't cook.
It's okay.
I'm getting a little bit of a hand.
It's delicious.
I'm glad.
It's so soft.
I'm eating one piece.
I ate only this.
The end of the Eho-maki is delicious.
I'm glad.
How does it look? It's just the taste.
The vinegar was just right.
Do you want more?
I want to eat more.
You can eat it.
I'm not sure if I'm okay.
Add a lot of cucumbers.
I'm not going to add cucumbers.
Let's try it.
It's similar to the one in the video.
Add this.
I'm nervous.
How do I stretch this?
Stretch it. Lightly.
I'm sorry.
I think it's not enough.
Can I use this on the back?
Are you okay?
I'm totally fine.
Wait a minute.
I found it.
This.
Japanese?
I think it's fine. I like this.
Is this sausage?
It's not.
It's not?
This is it.
What will happen if I take it?
But the taste is...
You're going to eat it?
I'm going to eat it.
I like this one too.
Is this all?
I don't like it.
I'm sorry.
But,
It's okay.
What about cucumber?
Cucumber is normal.
What do you hate?
Mushrooms.
But I can't eat all the vegetables.
It's more.
I'm sorry.
I didn't use it.
It's slow.
Should I make it hard?
I'm sorry.
Is it okay?
Is this okay?
I'm sorry.
It's sticking out.
What?
It's stuck.
Should we eat it?
It's not coming off.
It's seaweed.
It's really plain.
Okay, one more time.
I'm not a good dancer.
Are you ready?
Rock, paper, scissors.
I only have this one.
What's in here?
I don't have any.
Which one is better?
I drew it.
It's so kind.
Thank you.
I really don't have anything.
I don't have anything.
I'm sorry.
Can I make it?
It seems like there's only cucumber in
it.
Is this a meat-lover's
I haven't eaten it in a long time.
I put in the rice.
This one? How should I do it?
It looks delicious.
What are you doing?
I'm going to put it on your face.
Is it ok?
I'm not sure.
Oh no!
What is this?
What if I pour water on it?
No.
You're going to pour water on it?
Ok, I'll pour it.
I'll make it green.
I think I poured too much.
I'm not sure.
I'll make it green.
What is this?
This is...
Water?
I don't think it's water.
I want to pour this.
You're going to pour two at once?
Yes.
That's great.
I'll pour it.
I think it's good to color it.
I might lose.
I can't lose.
This?
This is the one to lose.
This is the one.
It's new to lose.
I did it.
No.
I have to win.
Wow.
This is amazing.
The direction was different.
Yes.
OK.
Let's make it clean.
No, the inside will come out.
The inside will come out.
It's OK.
The
inside will come out.
I'm sorry.
Are you ready?
OK
OK, let's cut it.
I'm sorry.
OK, I'll cut it.
There is a inside.
I'm sorry.
I cut it.
Is this okay?
That was close.
I'll eat this.
Oh, is it good?
It didn't cut.
You're kind.
This is delicious.
I have to eat this.
It's delicious.
I'm responsible.
It's okay.
Which one?
This one.
It's not gone.
It's not gone?
It's gone.
I'm responsible.
It's okay.
It's cut.
Good.
Then, this one.
It's a little...
It's in.
Maybe this one?
That's right.
It's cut.
It's not the time to ride.
What happens if I cut it?
Oh, it's not working.
Hello, Keiri.
Hello.
It's not good.
Cut it.
It's cut.
This one too.
It's not working.
I put the middle part too.
It looks better.
It looks good.
I'll eat this.
There's all the chicken.
It's beautiful!
It's open.
Should I put this in?
I'll eat the chicken.
I'll eat it.
I can't eat it.
It's all broken.
There was no rice in it.
I don't like it.
Everyone doesn't eat it.
I'll eat one seaweed.
I'll eat it.
It's delicious.
It's not the taste.
It's the taste.
What is this? Pork cutlet?
Pork cutlet.
What is this?
Oh no, it's all broken.
It's good.
What is this?
Takuan?
Pickled radish.
Is it good?
It's good, but...
Based on the experiment results,
we shouldn't cook.
I see.
We won't do it from now on.
Hanana
What is it?
Vinegar!
It's in there!
It's sour!
What about vinegar?
I put it in the bag earlier
You did?
It's really in there
That's good
It's sour
Are you tired?
No, it's fine
This is delicious
Excuse me
I'm sorry
It's good, right?
I'm glad
When we were in the final,
we ate that
I'll eat it all
It's not a rice roll, it's a hand roll
At that time, I was good at wrapping it
I'm not good at it today
I wonder why
Well, it's okay
Cucumber is delicious
I only eat cucumbers
I'm eating properly
Well, that's why
It was a little messy, but
I enjoyed it, so I'm going to leave.
Oh, yeah.
How was it? Was it delicious? It was
delicious.
It was delicious, but it looked a little
weird.
But it was good. It was delicious.
It was delicious.
I'm glad.
I want to do it again. But I can't do
it.
I'll do it after I've improved a little
more.
I can't do it.
Surprised.
I'll take it home.
Good luck.
Thank you.
It was Suzuki Hirono.
Bye.
I'll clean up this.
Sorry.
I want to eat this later.
Thank you for your viewing.
I forgot to put the chair.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
The chair is a little...
Is this okay?
Chair.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
So, the experiment is over in no time.
I have an announcement for you.
Ta-da!
March 9th, Mokuhai Messe Event Hall,
Shiretebushu School.
I can't read English.
Read it.
Look to...
What was it? I can't read English. What
should I do?
Look to the...
What?
Sorry.
March 9th, Makuha Remesu Event Hall.
Shiriti Ebisu Middle School.
March 21st, Osaka Grand Cube.
Shiriti Ebisu Middle School, Part 2.
We've decided to do a live viewing.
I think there are a lot of people who
missed it.
Please watch it on live viewing.
Please.
Is this okay?
I have to make it in English.
Osaka Grand Cube is our first live...
...live viewing.
We'll be watching it.
So please watch it.
Question?
Question corner.
Question.
Wait.
What do you want to do?
What should I pick?
This one.
Wait.
This one?
Which one do you want?
This one.
Let's go.
Today's question is...
What if I were to bring something to the
island?
That's the question.
What should I do?
I wonder...
I...
Meat?
I mean, I have meat and drinks.
I have to bring the same food.
But...
I wonder...
I have to bring a futon?
I have to sleep.
I have only one.
I have only one. I said meat.
Then, meat...
Food. I have all the food.
Really?
Only meat?
What should I do?
Then, cucumber.
Cucumber is not good.
It's not good.
I'll make sakura mo.
I'll make cucumber.
Which one?
I'll make dachitama.
You can't make dachitama with one.
This is not good.
This is the end.
How was it today?
It was delicious.
It was fun.
Hiro's senpai came.
It was the first time we talked.
But we got along.
I think we got along well.
I think so too.
So, it was good.
It was delicious.
Okay, then.
Let's go.
Wait.
I'll put it here.
Okay.
And, No.11, Kobayashi Kaho and No.12,
Riko Nakayama,
Soremiro, Kaho Riko.
Bye-bye.
Self-study.
I can't do it without a cat.
Bye-bye.
It's not working.
It's going to disappear.
It's amazing.
Did they see it?
Is it okay?
I wonder if it's okay.
Thank you for watching!
What should I do?
Is it okay?
I can't see.
I'm sorry.
What should I do?
I can't see.
Are you okay?