This time's Ebichu Tastas is a special
project for the new season, the Dream
Let's Make It Come True Special!
Here!
When the members' dreams come true,
there's a surprising development!
Who is this person?
At the end, everyone is in a serious
hide-and-seek!
Here he comes!
Ebichu Tastas, start!
The feeling of love is so high
I'm so crazy about you
What should I do with my heart?
Moratorium, moratorium, moratorium,
middle school
Add various things to private Ebisu
Ebichu Tastas
To be continued
This program is brought to you by the
following sponsors.
This time, I, Kobayashi, will be your
host
I'll start with the car-shaped-yokan
It's a unique atmosphere
It's modern
Modern, modern
What's this mysterious dance?
There's no Hoshina
There seems to be another job, so I'll
be late
Oh, is that so?
So please wait a moment
What are you going to do today?
This time, Ebichu Tastosu
I'm coming
This is a dream
It's written here
New Year's special project, Let's make
our dreams come true special
A project suitable for the new year to
make the members' dreams come true
Coming this year
If there is a dream that will come true,
there is a dream that won't come true
That is reality
Whether the dream will come true or not,
the judge is the director of the dream
selection
What kind of dream are the members
dreaming of?
And how many will come true?
First, the first dream is this
The members want to do a Hawaii location
Who is this?
Matsuno
What does this mean?
We have always wanted to go to Hawaii
If we do a Hawaii location and have a
sports day, I think we can get something
Like a prize
Let's think of Hawaii location
Matsuno, you are from Japan
This is Hawaii
Behind us is the sea
It's a sand beach
Ready, start!
We've also been drinking during the
week.
So, this time we've had it up our
sleeve.
Woohoo ~~
The top three reached hundred cells
Thank you!
Yes!
You're here!
What are we doing for the sports day?
Sports day?
First, let's do beach flag together.
Oh, that's good!
That's good!
And?
Let's decide the team!
Oh, team!
Like that?
Yes!
Let's go to the judgment.
Will Matsuno's dream, Hawaii location,
come true?
Let's go to the judgment.
Which team do you want to go to Hawaii
with?
1, 2, 3!
Team Hawaii!
The budget is really high
By the way, from the producer
It's possible if Matsuno-san is alone
Really?
What do you think?
I'm not sure
I'll answer later
I'll go later
Next is this
I want to record Ebichu Tastas under the
aurora
Who is this?
NG!
So fast!
It's more expensive than Hawaii
Two consecutive dreams didn't come true
It's hard to make it come true
What will happen next?
Here!
Uno!
It's me!
What is this? Uno?
Uno is funny
No, no, no
It's really funny
We've been doing Uno in Guam
When we were in Guam during the photo
shoot
The rooms were divided into 4 rooms
It was a big room
So we all got up late at night and did
Uno together
It was really fun
It was fun
You wanted to do it together like that
night?
Yes
I understand. Then, the president of the
committee
Please!
I want to do it
I want to do it too
1, 2, 3
Yes!
We did it!
If Uno didn't make it, the game would
have been over
Yasumoto's dream, Uno will make it
Let's have fun as much as we want
Let's do it with the music of Paxi
Yes
What is it?
Paxi's music
Let's start with Kao
Paxi Paxi
Music start!
What is this?
Yasu, you can't do it!
The people who are watching this
probably find this interesting
Did he make it?
Yasu, you can't do it!
Yua, Yua, Yua.
Can you do it?
I can't do it!
Rinna, you did four!
I don't know why, but they are excited
for 20 minutes.
20 minutes.
Matsuda, you won!
Damn it!
How was it? Did you make your dream come
true?
I did! It was fun!
It was fun!
I want to do it again!
You did this in Guam?
I was next to you and I was like, what
the hell is this?
Shut up!
Next, Kobayashi's dream to come true
He wants to go to a shrine
What the hell is this?
I have a role
Hirota Kashiwagi is the main role
And Riko and I are the supporting roles
Rina-chan and Ayako-chan are the
translating roles
That's good
This is...
To be continued
Why?
Recently, there are many people who wear
a Tastasu
That's right
It's amazing
It's a Jinja look
Yes
Personally
Let's go to the end
Everyone, please do it personally
Let's go
The next question is this
I want to wear a costume and give
balloons to children
This is me
Mayama
What is this?
You are an idol, right?
There are many children who admire me
At a handshake party, I heard that I was
admired and loved by children
I thought that they would say that
When I thought that I wanted to make
children smile
What can make me smile the most?
I thought it was a costume
You can't see the face?
I can't see the face
If you wear a costume at a theme park
and give balloons
Children will come to you
How about the director?
Here it is
I did it
Great
Mayama's dream will come true
Immediately change into a costume and
give balloons to the person who does it
It seems that Mayama is ready
Let's call her
I'm looking forward to it
Mayama
She came
Cute
So cute
Super cute
Mayama
It's big and heart-shaped
In your dream, you want to give balloons
to children
If you give a lot of balloons to
children, the heart rate will increase
Let's make children smile from one
person
I see
The cute child is waiting down there
Mayama, please give the balloon and make
children smile
Mayama, please be motivated
Thank you
What will happen to Mayama after this?
Mayama's dream
Dress up as a doll and give the balloon
to children
Start
It's coming
What?
The child is watching
I think it's a little scary
It's solidified
What is it?
There is something like this
Is the child looking at the way it comes
out?
It's cute
How is it?
I don't know
Are they being cautious?
It's better if one of them go and help
Then Yasumoto
Yasumoto, go and help
Thank you
Maybe it's not something that comes out
of the room
It's coming!
Wait, something weird is coming
Oh no! I'm scared!
It's talking!
It's saying pyon pyon!
Oh, it's a candy!
It's a candy!
Mayama is surprised!
Let's see the balloon!
The balloon!
There are a lot of children on it!
It's amazing!
It's moving a lot!
It's a candy!
Mayama!
It's amazing!
Yasumoto took Mayama's dream, so it's
over.
Good job.
I'm so disappointed.
Mayama, did your dream come true?
It did.
I don't think so.
Mayama said her dream came true.
Let's see the next dream.
This is it.
I want to do Gorilla World 2.
What is this?
What is Gorilla World?
Gorilla World is a show where 8 members
of Ebichu members go to eat.
There is no manager.
We reserve a restaurant and go together.
You want to do Gorilla World 2.
Please give us a decision.
This is difficult.
Please.
Ebichu.
No Gorilla!
Why is this No Gorilla?
This is a private show.
Please don't use this show.
Huh?
Gorilla!
Hoshina is late and they meet at the
clock tower.
The last is Kashiwagi's dream.
What kind of dream is it?
Here it is!
A hide and seek game!
It's a really big place!
What does it mean?
If it's small, you can find it easily
If there are 8 people, you can find it
easily
So if you play it in a big place, it's
fun
So you want to play it seriously
It looks fun
You might want to play it when you were
a kid
It's a really big place
Please judge
I'm nervous, nervous, nervous
Please
I can see it, I can see it
You shouldn't take it easy there, Chie-
san
I did it!
I can see it from the beginning
At the end, the dream of the Kashiwagi
will come true
The Kashiwagi's dream, a very large
hide-and-seek venue is this 4-story
building
Use all 4 floors and enjoy it to the
fullest
In this building, the Kashiwagi will
become a demon and find the 7 members
who are hidden within the time limit
First, the other 7 members will find a
place to hide to make their dream come
true
What should I do?
Kobayashi is waiting at the door of the
terrace.
What?
Is this place open?
I'll go to the front.
Matsuno is waiting at the wall on the
third floor.
And...
Can I enter?
Hiroto goes to the storage room on the
stairs.
In this way, all the places to hide are
decided.
As you can see, all the places where 7
people are hiding are decided.
I'll do my best.
Let's go. You have 10 minutes.
Start!
Now, the hidden treasure of Kashiwagi,
start!
What? But, well...
First, search the first floor.
I'm going to go to the first floor.
Everyone!
There are many doors.
Where are you?
I'm going to play with the ball.
I passed the ball.
Who is it?
Riko-chan?
Good morning!
I found you!
Riko-chan, look!
The first one!
I found the first one!
Riko-chan?
Good morning!
I found you!
Riko-chan, good morning!
This is difficult
Please subscribe to my channel!
Who is it?
I found you!
Matsuno, look!
I was so nervous!
I found you!
So, after...
Kashiwagi decided that she was not in
the third floor, so she went to the
fourth floor.
Yasumoto and Kobayashi are on the
terrace.
Is she coming?
She is coming!
Here they come!
Wait, everyone is hiding
What? They are not here?
To be continued
Someone is there! Who is it?
I found Kaho-chan!
I found it!
She found it!
I caught a lot
There's someone here!
Who is it?
My legs are numb
There are 3 members left
Can they find it in the time limit?
5 minutes left. Kashiwagi goes to the
first floor again.
Everyone!
3 minutes left.
Time is running out. 4 minutes left.
4 minutes left.
I was thinking.
Kashiwagi, without noticing Hoshina
wrapped in cloth, goes through the door.
I was thinking.
To the 3rd floor again.
No one's here
Can I go in here?
Who's there?
I'm scared
To be continued
I was so close to the end
Were you hiding in such a place?
Really?
In such a place?
That means
I can't enter this room
It's light
Wait, is he not here?
He's not here
I found you!
I found the love!
30 seconds is a little cruel!
I tried my best!
Only Hoshina is left.
Will she succeed?
I found the love!
30 seconds is a little cruel!
Please subscribe to my channel!
Where is Miyu-chan hiding?
10 seconds left!
I can't open this, can I?
9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1
Wait, is she gone?
Time's up!
Amazing!
Even though they were able to catch up
to one person, Hoshina was able to
escape and the team that was hiding won!
They lost the game, but they were able
to achieve their dream!
Let's find Hoshina!
It's this floor
Really?
I knew it!
Let's all look for her!
Let's look for her hiding place!
I found her!
It's so bright!
Did you see where she was hiding?
I saw her!
Her clothes were red and she was hiding
in the closet
I didn't even notice she was there
Amazing!
You did well!
I did well!
I can't get out!
And this is a unique event with FRECASO,
a kuno-iksushi-s Lorience harvester.
Please find it hard to guess it!
I want to believe that I can change the
world,
that it's just boring to think about it.
This life that was born
is a dream that can't come true.
It's a miracle
No matter what future we face tomorrow
Let's look at the hope that just
surfaced
Even if it rains, even if it rains
Let's draw a big rainbow
Even if we can't see it
Let's smile with our hearts
And they will show their new song for
the first time!
They will show their new song for the
first time!
Filled with a beautiful color
The dry sky, you're not there anymore
I was smiling at the scent of spring
The announcement is...
Sakura Ebi's 6th One-Man Live will be
held at Shibuya Duo Music Exchange on
February 19th!
After the live, Sakurai Bees...
After Moa joined, we decided to do it
with 6 people.
We wanted to make 5 people's song into 6
people's version.
We'll do our best together.
Please look forward to the success of
Sakurai Bees this year!
Next time, the winter festival, the
festival of the midwinter, or the
festival of the winter.
Ready, go!
Under the cold sky, a big hustle!
Thank you for watching!
You're fast!