Ebi-chu no douka toka!
Please subscribe to my channel!
Thank you for watching!
Today, I'm going to shoot a video of
Kimoto Ebu.
We are here.
This is a sauna.
Let's get ready.
What is this?
This is a sauna.
I want to sleep here.
I like girls.
I've never been in a sauna.
I'm looking forward to it.
What about a bath?
Is there a bath?
No.
We have a very friendly guest.
This is a guest.
Please come in.
We are SHIJI CHE MI SHIYUKU.
We are MAYAMARIKA and GINATO.
We are friends.
Let's go inside.
I'm looking forward to it.
I want to sleep here for the first time.
I'm interested in this.
This is a sauna.
This is cute.
This is very noticeable.
This is not unusual.
This is a fit.
This is Hira.
This is cute.
This is Panda.
I like this design forever.
I'm happy.
I don't know how long it takes.
5 minutes is short.
It's about 5 minutes.
Was Panda really good?
Yes.
Why?
I was surprised when I put all my hair
in.
I'm going to do a challenge.
Let's go to the sauna.
Let's go.
Thank you.
Oh, it's a shark.
It's so cute.
It's a shark.
It's a little...
The principal came in with me.
Oh, yeah.
I love the principal's shark.
Oh, my God.
It's cool.
It's cute.
How is it?
It's like a pocahontas.
It's going to make your nose look good.
Oh, yeah.
That's right.
It's really good for your skin.
Have you ever heard of the dragon?
Oh, dragon.
I've heard of it.
Didn't you say dragon?
There's a song called Jyoshiruku Hatsude
Oji-san in our song.
There's a dragon.
You're going to turn the table.
I'm going to turn the towel.
Did you say you understood the meaning?
Who wrote the lyrics?
Hyadain.
I was taught how to use the sauna by
Really?
He's the teacher.
I'm going to do the laundry now.
I'm going to clean the room.
It's really clean.
The temperature has risen.
It's hot.
It's all cloudy.
It's cloudy.
It's really cool.
It's cool.
Breathe in.
Wow.
It's not cold at all.
It's like a hot spring bath.
It's cold.
But I think it's still okay.
Breathe in.
Three seconds.
It's cold.
What is this?
It's like a bag.
It's a sledgehammer.
What is this?
This is a
box.
It's a box.
It feels good.
How do you feel?
It's amazing.
I'm not sure if I can talk.
You can talk.
I can't talk.
I'm here.
I want to make it easier for you to
imagine.
Please close your eyes and face me.
Close your eyes.
Let's walk around the city until we get
to the park.
The park is full of people.
It smells so good.
It smells really good.
It smells like raspberry.
Let's go to the raspberry store nearby
and have some.
It smells so good.
Let's go to the raspberry store.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
You feel good, right?
So, I'm glad that we can do this
outside.
We will do a whisking in order of two
people.
We don't know what it is yet, so please
do it.
Thank you.
It's fun to see the whisking.
I'm looking forward to it.
I think the first time was faster.
I thought I had to stand in a white
chair and make a proper posture.
I couldn't do that, so I was confused.
I was in a big trouble.
I didn't know what it meant to make a
proper posture.
But when I entered the room, I was
surprised.
I was really surprised.
Then I was surprised.
I was happy to be able to make a proper
posture from the first shot.
It's fun.
I feel good.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for watching.
Did you enjoy it?
I didn't think that the sauna was so
attractive.
What did you think when I talked about
sauna on the radio?
You are a sauna uncle.
You are a sauna uncle who says a lot.
But you already understood.
I understood.
I understood the reason why you
recommended it.
I thought I could do it.
When I went there myself, I didn't get a
bath.
But when I got a bath, I got used to it.
It feels good.
I think it's enough to warm up your body
to get a bath.
That's good.
Please make a sauna club in the future.
Please make a sauna club in the office.
That's good.
There seems to be a sauna club in the
office.
It's like a sauna club.
Where are you going?
It's the best common place.
It's the best sauna club in STARDUST.
I'm sorry to be honest.
I will appear in STARDUST soon.
Thank you.
Please take your time.
I'm sorry.
It's time to say goodbye.
Thank you very much.
Goodbye.
That's good.
There are two people who listen to the
sauna on the radio.
Today, we visited Kimotube.
We taught him how to organize the sauna.
How was it?
It was very organized.
It was a very organized place.
I thought it was difficult to think
about the sauna.
But it was very nice.
I really enjoyed it.
I'm really grateful.
And our cute Sayonara hat.
Who did you buy it for?
Kimoto-san.
I'm glad you bought it.
Thank you very much.
Please spread this to girls.
I want to spread it to members.
Miele-chan, if you're a private, you can
wear it.
Yes, yes.
I want you to wear it in private.
And Kimoto-ube.
You can't bite Kimoto-ube.
Kimuchi.
If you want to learn, please come out
again.
We'll let you out again.
Please.
Thank you for your hard work.
Kimoto-ube.
I don't have one.