Good evening, welcome to Doreski Doko
Doreski MC, I'm your host, Iwai.
I'm Akane Kumada.
Thank you for having us.
Today's guest is the second guest.
We have the guests of the idol group,
BOLT.
It's been a while.
BOLT, it's been a while.
I've been doing it for a while.
You've been doing it?
Yes, I have.
I was doing Dore Dore Box.
You were doing Dore Dore Box?
Yes.
I see.
And I heard that some of you are middle
schoolers.
What kind of middle schooler were you?
I'm sorry.
I thought you were a middle schooler.
I'm not wrong.
What kind of middle schooler were you?
Please be clear.
I was a soccer player.
Soccer boy.
I was a sportsman.
You were very athletic.
I was very athletic.
I was the best in physical fitness.
Really?
I have fast legs and great jumping
power.
I have great grip power.
I can crush an acrylic board like this.
I'm scared.
You should be careful.
If you touch it, it will be broken.
I always control it.
I control it.
I'm scared.
If I'm not careful, I can't speak.
You speak at this speed to get used to
the human world.
Yes.
I'm a monster.
Are you a monster?
You are a monster.
You should be careful.
I'm just controlling it.
If you are irritated, you will be
crushed.
I will be crushed and I will not be able
to speak.
You are a monster.
I'm a monster.
Please be careful.
Everyone, please be careful.
Let's start.
Music variety DRESKI & KORESKI
Today's guests are from Bolt!
We are Bolt!
I'm Runa Naito.
I'm Chihou Taka.
I'm Aya Shirahama.
Nice to meet you!
We are a group of four, but today we are
three.
Nice to meet you!
You gave us a chance to come here.
Yes, I'm always the first.
You are kind.
I thought you were talking about me.
I did it on purpose.
You are kind.
Thank you.
First, I will introduce Bolt.
The four-member idol group, which
consists of Momoiro Clover Z, Shiritu
Ebisu Junior High School, and Stardust
Planet, was formed in July 2019.
This year is the 3rd anniversary year,
and they have held tours and anniversary
live concerts all over the country.
This time, we will look back on the
history of Bolt, who celebrated its 3rd
anniversary.
In July 2019, there was a group
presentation.
Do you feel like you've grown since
then?
Yes, in July 2019, the two members were
still elementary school students.
I feel nostalgic.
How old were you?
I was in the second year of junior high
school.
I was 14 years old.
And in November, the official website
was opened for the first time.
It took three months to open the
official site from the announcement of
the group.
I was happy.
I was able to make it to the official
site.
How is the official site doing recently?
Recently, it has only changed to this
new image.
You used to wear different costumes.
I used to wear a costume of a seasoning
company.
I'm back to a human being.
And in February, there was an event
regulation due to the infection.
In March, TAKAI graduated from high
school.
I entered the situation of COVID-19 at
the time of graduation.
I was only allowed to hold the
graduation ceremony in the classroom.
I couldn't do it in the gym.
I heard that.
The staff was surprised.
We have a program called VOLTV that we
live stream on YOUTUBE.
They held a graduation ceremony for me.
This is a graduation ceremony for
adults.
I haven't graduated yet.
I graduated from a university.
In July, the major debut album POP was
released.
In October, ZEPP TOKYO was held for the
first time.
ZEPP TOKYO is the first one-man live.
I had a POP one-man live.
This is the first one-man live.
VOLTV is also the first one-man live.
This is the first one-man live for us.
I took lessons every day.
I was able to see a great view.
It was a big step.
It was very big.
It was full.
The performance of the laser was very
beautiful.
It was the first one-man live.
I can't forget it.
Dore Dore
We have a comment here.
Comment.
The first three-piece band in Kyoto was
formed in 2017.
It's Hakubi.
Let's see the comments we got.
Hello to everyone watching DRE Ski and
KORE Ski.
Good evening, Mr. Iwai and Mr. Kumada.
I'm Katairi, the vocalist of Hakubi.
I'm Yasukawa, the bassist.
I'm Matsui, the drummer.
Which one do you like?
Nice to meet you.
I like watching MMA.
MMA.
I want to fight too.
That's okay.
I like watching MMA.
I think it's a little connected.
I have a routine before the live show.
I have a lot of routines.
I have to do this, do that.
I started boxing three minutes ago.
It's been five minutes lately.
I've been doing that all the time.
I'm getting tired of boxing.
I'm getting more and more into it.
I'm into boxing these days.
You're a boxer.
Yes.
How about you, Yasukawa?
We're both a little bit of a mess.
I like camping.
Where do you like camping?
We're fighting.
I like camping.
Please calm down.
It's not that I'm upset.
This is a stress relief.
Camping is also a stress relief.
I like camping.
I think so.
So, we released a new single, AITAGAI,
on July 29th.
Congratulations.
This song is about love.
The title AITAGAI contains a lot of
emotions.
I hope you can think about the meaning
of the song.
We will hold two one-man live concerts
in Japan in November.
We will hold a one-man live concert in
Ebisu Garden Hall in Tokyo on November
3rd.
We will hold a one-man live concert in
Osaka Big Cat on Thursday, November 17th
in Kansai.
Please come and see us.
HAKUBI.
Yes.
I'm sorry to let Yasukawa in the right
side show up.
It seems like you weren't in the mood.
But you talked about camping.
I was just about to.
I think the staff was a little upset.
The staff was laughing under the
sunglasses.
I think they said, let me shoot.
You talked about camping.
I was just about to.
I'm glad you were just about to.
I'm grateful.
I'm sorry.
The crew of DORESKI and DORESKI.
The crew.
I guess I made you do it.
Thank you.
Please check out HAKUBI.
In July, the 2nd anniversary live
concert was held at the Ryuo Music
Exchange.
How was it?
It was the 2nd anniversary, and we
released a new song on that day.
The 2nd anniversary live concert was a
happy cry, but the 3rd anniversary live
concert was a happy smile.
I was wondering what would happen in the
4th anniversary.
I was wondering if it would be 2nd, 3rd,
or 4th anniversary.
You were able to have a happy live
concert.
In September 2021, we released our
second album, ATTITUDE.
In December, we released our third
single, MORE FANTASTIC.
How was it? Did the song change?
At first, we were just starting to sing,
so we danced and sang together.
But in September and December, we were
able to sing a lot.
That's great.
In July 2021, we had our 3rd anniversary
live concert.
What was the impression of the concert?
We were able to have a live concert on
the day of the 2nd anniversary.
It was a weekday, but we were able to
sell out tickets.
We were able to see a lot of people.
The moment we went on stage, there were
a lot of fans behind us.
We were able to see the people we hadn't
met yet on the 2nd anniversary.
I was so happy that I can't forget that
day.
When the concert was over, the staff
suddenly asked us to open the door.
Open the door?
When we opened the door, we were all
surprised to see the big cake.
There were many messages around the
decoration.
I was so happy and surprised.
Please subscribe to the channel.
Iwai-san, we will read a message from
the viewers
It's from Pana-san, thank you
Good evening, Iwai-san and Kumada-san
I always enjoy watching your videos on
YouTube
Here's a question for you two
You two are active in your real names
If you were to give a stage name, what
would it be?
I like the name Saotome Zenichi because
it's cool
That's what it says
That's lame
It's cool
Saotome Zenichi is cool
Saotome Zenichi, that's lame
What do you think, Iwai-san?
I don't look like Iwai
Really?
What do you mean?
In Haraichi, Iwai is Saabe and Saabe is
Iwai
Iwai is Saabe
That's true
Sa is me
It's the opposite
It's like Sawai-san
Right?
Let's think of a name for each other
Something that's similar to each other
Let's go with something similar
Something similar
I opened it
Give it to me
I'll go
騒いたく
騒いたく?
It's like this, you know?
Oh really?
It's like タク
Oh really? I'll think about it too
タドコロヨネミ
I'm Yonemi Tadokoro.
You're lame.
I'm lame.
You're lying.
I'm Yonemi Tadokoro.
I'm like an idol of Akita.
I love rice.
I'm Yonemi Tadokoro.
I understand.
I'll call you Yonemi from now on.
Please call me Yone.
We'll send you this program sticker.
How many do you want?
I didn't get excited.
You got excited.
I'll add one.
There are two.
We are looking for messages and
requests.
Please send it to the official website
of the program.
KUMANA's announcement chance.
If you can answer the question
correctly, KUMANA will give you a chance
to announce.
OO quiz.
There are more than 1000 elementary
schools in Saitama Prefecture. OO or X?
There are no 1000 schools?
There are many people.
1000 schools, right?
I don't think so.
X.
Final answer.
Thank you.
Correct!
I'm so glad!
I was surprised! I didn't know there
were so many!
But, there are 812 of them.
That's a lot!
That's a lot.
There are a lot of them.
You can announce them.
Thank you.
On Sunday, August 28th, we will be
performing at the 68th Ooi Don-Taku
Natsumatsuri 2022 Music Stage!
I'm singing, so if you're interested,
please come and see me.
We don't know what time it is yet.
We don't know yet.
It's 12 hours and 15 minutes.
Ooi Don-Taku is playing.
It's my favorite festival.
Really?
Ooi Don-Taku.
It's like a festival in the countryside
of Tokyo.
I'm so happy.
It's very local.
They play rock and people dance twist.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'll decide the song I'm going to sing.
Please make it up-tune.
Up-tune.
I'll make it a song that everyone can
enjoy.
And there's one more.
Why are you trying to say two?
Well, it's okay.
Is that okay?
It's okay.
On Friday, September 23rd, we will be
performing at Toyosu Pit at the Listen
Any Live Special Edition in the fall
vacation.
Akane Kumada will be performing here.
Thank you.
Please check the official website for
more information such as tickets.
I'll do my best.
Please.
Well, then.
Goodbye.