What is the meaning of the name of the
group?
I've been wanting to be with the members
and the staff for a long time.
I've been thinking that it's the end of
my life to see everyone's smiles.
So I thought I'd bury the outside.
I was wondering if I could bury it.
As I went around various places,
everyone's smiles increased.
I was very happy.
Thank you.
Good morning!
Sapporo!
Yay!
I got it wrong, Hokkaido!
I'm so excited!
Good morning!
Yay!
I can't see anything.
Good morning.
Thank you.
Ah ah.
Ah.
Please say hello.
We are the stars of the music video.
Thank you.
Yeah, I don't know the unit number.
!
This outfit is soK!
We're K!
ุ
We'll start the excellent, More than
ever.
More than ever!
Is this the end?
Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching.
Thank you very much for coming to
Hokkaido today!
The two of us carried athe9 car
procedure.
Thank you for watching.
Please subscribe to my channel!
Let's go to the top!
Hey hey, shining, moving, on, feelin'
Let's smile and celebrate our lives
And go!
Let's go!
In the hall
Say out loud what you want to do
Hey hey hey hey hey hey hey
Thank you for watching!
Hello, Kakashi-no!
Today, we are going to have a live
performance at this Kakashimi Park!
Everyone, please dance with us!
I'm glad we forgot about shirts!
That went well!
I think we looked too tired.
Let's hold our tears a little longer.
2019 is a very Сild year!
Thank you!
I'm tired.
Thank you! Hokkaido is the best!
Yay!
Somehow...
I'm not sure if I can do it.
I'm tired.
I'm going to do my best. I'm looking
forward to it.
We are twin-tail brothers.
We are both highlight.
I thought it was a good idea.
We are twin-tail brothers.
I'm going.
I'm Harima.
Hello.
I'm Smile from Nibu, Hokkaido.
But I can hear her voice from the
speaker
So I'm really motivated
I'm really motivated when I do Datesanba
I can do it
Harima is also cute
I'll do my best
I hit the mic.
I got strawberry in my elbow.
I like strawberries so much.
What is this?
It's a drink.
I can't believe it.
Everyone.
Funny.
Thank you for watching.
Please subscribe to the channel.
I'm a girl who's obsessed with the word
of love
I'm not the one who's going to be in a
couple
I'm a girl who's going to give you a lot
of love
I'm not the one who's going to be in a
couple
It's over!
Happy Birthday!
It was nice!
Thank you!
Bye bye!
The competition is almost over.
Please look forward to the next one.
We'll keep working hard.
Please keep working hard.
I love you.
Thank you for your hard work.
It was fun!
Bye bye!
He is terrible.
Thank you!
Shrek!
Thank you very much.
I'm embarrassed to do this.
Nowadays, I unfortunately have to hide
my double chin.
I'm a sudden wife. I'm going to have a
rehearsal from now on. Thank you.
Please subscribe to the channel and give
it a high rating.
There's a camera room?
What?
Hello!
Everyone!
I want to eat omurice, but I want to eat
pancakes.
And if RUN-chan eats pancakes, it will
be a good value for a woman.
Then I'll give it to you.
Look at my甲板!
I'm going to the Tokyo Ikanai Tour,
Miyagi Park Part 1!
I'll do my best for Kaya.
I got Kaya's feelings, so I'll change
Kaya's soul into a costume.
Kaya came up with the new costume.
I'll do my best!
Twin-Tae Attack!
Momiyagi Attack!
She's so kind.
I'll do my best!
I'll do my best for Kaya.
I'm so nervous!
I can't do this!
This is gross!
Let me introduce you.
Two Classandy connects detail
La dunka
Go!
I'm good
Thank you
You're good
Pecaun
Beautiful
I'm not
Look
He's singing
Me
Yke
Yuna
Karu!
Miyu!
Ran!
Rine!
Kaya!
Rina Ito!
Kamen-Chan!
OK!
Yeah!
Let's do this!
Everyone, let's do this!
30 seconds left.
I'm going.
Look at this.
Thank you for watching!
Happy people!
Once again, we are
Nijiroku's Stardust!
Thank you!
So, we should play in a waterfall
someday.
That's a good idea.
I want to do it.
The water is flowing.
I'm going to the waterfall in the middle
of the house.
What kind of live show is it?
It's funny, isn't it?
I want to see it.
It's an underground show.
Underground show?
On Twitter, the manager asked,
If you sell it at Yamazaki Saber's
Sentai Pit, will you buy it?
I asked.
Almost a percent of the answer was yes.
It was about 80%.
And it was about 1,500 yen.
Why didn't you buy it?
Suddenly, she appeared.
It's long.
Let's see.
Ready?
One, two.
Okay.
Amazing.
Show it to everyone.
One, two.
Ready?
We decided to release our new song, Fuku
wo Kite Koi Shitai on July 31st!
It's our new song!
This is the new song.
We're going to take pictures with you
guys.
We finished the last part of the
concert!
It was fun!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
It's a little difficult to get out of
the train.
The train goes down when I get out.
That's right.
It's easier to get out of the train.
Thank you very much.
First, left.
Like this.
You're pushing me.
I see.
Raise your leg.
Like this.
I see.
Which one?
The leg.
Second time, right.
Like this.
Thank you.
I'm going to go first
I'm going too
Do you have invisible socks?
Thank you
If you drink this, your tongue will turn
yellow
You can't show it
It's okay to show it
I'm going
Let's have fun
Can I put it in?
You can put it in the box
If you feel stable, put it on
Thank you
It's definitely light, so two people can
go.
Hide it.
Princess!
Princess, come here!
Please come here.
How do you feel?
I'm in a good mood.
Thank you.
You're in a good mood.
Are you okay?
I'm in a good mood.
You're the best.
Thank you.
I want to wear clothes and fall in love.
I'll be your one and only
So let's go on
It was so fun.
It was fun.
It was crazy.
It's definitely not a scene of the city.
That's what I thought.
I thought it was a scene of a crime
scene.
It was so fun.
It was like a scene of a movie.
Something came.
It was like a fantasy.
It wasn't a scene of a movie.
It was so funny.
It was crazy.
The fire in my heart was the fire of
youth.
I couldn't help it.
Please put it in.
Hey!
It's cute.
It's a good match.
Good match.
Do you want to shoot together?
Okay.
Let's do it.
Now, we are going to have a rehearsal
for the Osaka concert.
It's the day before Osaka.
We bought canelé yesterday and we
gathered in the same hotel room and had
a canelé party.
We did it until 1 in the morning.
We are doing our best.
But this time, we can do it together.
We are practicing for the canelé show.
Do your best.
We are doing our best.
Look, Rui.
Do your best for the canelé show.
I will do my best.
She is amazing.
We are practicing for the canelé show
and we are practicing for the concert.
for an hour.
How is it?
Wow.
It's amazing.
I'm going to eat rice balls.
I'll do my best.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for watching!
ū
But then-
Playing drum,
Yeah, yeah,
180 likes are the minimum
I just wanna sleep
512 likes is the minimum
What are you doing anyway?
I'm gonna become the dubber
OK
Ka- other than that,
Thank you for watching.
So the next step is the next one
I also want to try it.
All did very passionatelyocreate
Hey, hey, Chikaru.
What?
You have something to say, right?
Yeah.
Tell everyone what you're thinking.
I got it!
What?
Thank you for your hard work.
I was seen.
Good morning.
It's our first day of the tour.
Bye bye!
Bye!
Good bye!
Thank you for watching!
I'll do my best.
Manji!
What am I doing?
Please don't use this. I'm tired.
I'm only doing a light makeup.
I'll do my best.
RU-chan, you're the most excited.
I'm the most excited.
Well, one is above.
Please go to the 5th floor.
Yes.
It's not big.
Karen-taso isn't here.
Please come here.
Then, I'll go.
Excuse me.
Thank you very much.
It will be a good song.
Everyone, please put a lot of cute
hearts on the camera.
Let's go!
Thank you very much.
I can't do it.
What?
Sorry.
Thank you very much.
in radio
gt
At the meeting
I apparently
want to make a promise
like that
said
a
do you want
Thanks for watching!
I'm going to the next stage.
Are you hurt?
No, I was hurt at the end of the last
event.
You were hurt at the end of the last
I twisted my leg.
My leg was hurt because of this.
I'm sorry.
You're not anyone else but me
Dun dun dun
Hey hey hey hey
I have an unyielding feeling
In my left hand is a dream
In my right hand is a dream
Hey hey
I'll make a miracle
I'm going to Osaka
See you later
I'm not talking in front of the camera
I don't have time
I noticed
I haven't looked at the camera since the
rehearsal
I don't have time
My goal this year is to be a woman with
time
I can't do it anymore
I'm done with my hair
Now
I'm going to meet her
Thank you
I broke it
Oh
I'm sorry
It was a bad luck
Bye
I'm going to meet her
I broke it
Bye
Thank you for watching!
It's too early.
Too early.
Thank you for watching!
Thank you very much for coming to the
Osaka show that will not go to Tokyo.
Thank you very much.
Well, well, you said that the girl
outside the house is cute.
What are you talking about?
The world that sewed that mouth, come
here!
God is unfair
We only one, even if we close our eyes
We'll surely reach it
If you remember the promise we made that
day
Oh~~ he makes the path
tablespoons
that did theแでは
beach
whirlpool
of instead
Please subscribe to my channel!
You can do it!
Can I tie my hair?
Where is the TV?
Bye bye!
Thank you!
Good morning.
Amazing.
Thank you.
I'm so tired.
Oh no.
Good morning.
Thank you.
Bye.
Good morning.
Would you like to end skies to
I'm going to the cafe.
Today is Fukuoka Park.
I went to the cafe in the morning
because it was the same room as Rine and
Yuna.
I woke up early.
It's rare.
I'll do my best.
It's very high.
Thank you.
The name is also Yuto Kojiki!
Don't say it! Yuto!
We are Inari Satsuma!
Thank you for watching!
It's totally different.
I'll take a picture of you.
Change the angle.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
Thank you very much.
Let's go.
I can only see the name of the store.
Wait, I have to check the name of the
store.
NANDEYAKEN
We will go to Fukuoka!
We will do our best!
Thank you for watching!
I'll be fine, you are
Self-m headline
We shoot a part.
Hey, everyone…
Thank you!
We're here!
I can't forgive you for getting angry!
I'm happy to see you!
Thank you for your hard work!
we're at the watertower!
i'm tired!
it was hot!
it's hot!
Let's raise our hands and go!
Let's go like this.
Wow, I'm going to get caught.
I'm definitely going.
Where should I go?
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you!
I didn't know that.
Thank you for watching.
I almost forgot this dance machine 3
years ago….
Every smallanto is potential
Thank you for watching!
5, 6 1
You did it!
Congratulations!
I've finished, you can't run!
Thank you for waiting this long!
This is the neighbourhood I live in,
I hope you all will enjoy it with your
families and friends!
Do I have nothing to lose?
Do I have nothing to miss?
Thank you for watching!
I'll leave it in the sky
It was so easy.
Thank you for coming.
It's over!
It was good.
It was fun!
Thank you! Bye!
It was fun! Thank you!
Thank you for watching!