This week's Ebichu Tastas continues from
the last episode
Ebichu Girls' Power Challenge, the
second half
For some reason, they are doing
mysterious things continuously
For the time being, they are doing it
By cleaning, Ebichu's girls' power is
clearly seen
Furthermore
The first cooking battle in Ebichu
history
The taste of the cooking made by the
members
Hahaha
What?
So, this week also‥
Gently add to the atmosphere
Add with Kanda
What should I do?
Moratorium, moratorium, moratorium,
junior high school student
Add various things to your private Ebisu
junior high school
Ebichu Dance Class
This program is provided by the sponsor
you are watching
Check out the women's power of Ebichu!
Ebichu Women's Power Championship
Last time, we checked out the women's
power of eating
against Mayama, Yasumoto, Matsuno, and
Kashiwagi
Thank you!
When she is eating, she smiles, which is
a sign of her high女子力.
Matsuno loves to eat.
Matsuno eats deliciously, and with that
happy expression, she gets a high score.
As a result, Matsuno is currently in the
top of her girl's power.
The second place she chases is the
oldest, Mayama.
This time, Hirota, Hoshina, Kobayashi
and Nakayama will check their cleaning
ability.
They will monitor the living room where
clothes are scattered.
How will they deal with the dirty dishes
in the kitchen?
Next time, we will have a communication
manner teacher, Nana Yoshii, to check
their cleaning ability.
What is the point of this?
The point is to be polite.
The most important thing is facial
expression.
And the last is the thought.
It's not like, I'm done, so I don't
care.
It's like, is there anything I can do?
That's right.
Not only the cleaning ability, but also
facial expression and thought are the
key to the girl's ability.
How do these four move?
It hurts!
This is a
cute
I like it
I'm going to put on a tatami mat
I'm going to put on an iron
Who is the leader now?
Hoshina
I don't know what to do now
It's great to be a leader
I'm a
leader, right?
It's rough
That's Nakayama
When I was in middle school, I cleaned
my special class
I liked it unexpectedly
I liked it
But here, both wet and dry
I'm not good at folding
Nakayama has it
I have it
I started to put it on my shoulders
I put it in one place
I put it in
Thank you
It's kind
Oh, this is...
Will they notice the dishes here?
I see
What will happen?
Will they do it from now on?
They will wash it from here
While the three are cleaning in the
living room
Kobayashi is heading to the kitchen
How will he move after seeing the dirty
dishes?
He did it!
He came
He is like Kobayashi
Great
He is holding a sponge
He is like, Oh, he is here
He is like, Oh, great
He is going back
Nakayama came to see Kobayashi
He thought he would help him
But he went back immediately
Why?
Wait a minute, Nakayama
You didn't do anything
He looks so tired
He is showing on his face
He is showing that he is doing something
He is like a father
He is going again
He is not like a father
Hirota and Hoshina are discussing him
They are just dancing
Nakayama
He is doing
They are going back to Kobayashi
Will he show his womanly power?
He is watching
He is dancing
He is supporting
There are other people who do this kind
of thing, right?
Yes, there are. Hoshina and I are good
at it.
Is this the power of girls like
Nakayama?
But she is just dancing, so she gets 0
points.
On the other hand, Hirota and Hoshina
are ironing.
But Ayami is good at it.
Isn't it easier to iron it sideways?
Yes, it is.
I think it's easier to use this table as
a corner.
You have a strong feeling for ironing.
I love ironing.
Hoshina is ironing clothes.
She is doing her best.
Hoshina finished ironing.
After ironing, she is ironing and
stretching it.
Hoshina is helping her.
She is good at it.
She is helping her with 1 point.
Hoshina's ironing is very elegant and
beautiful.
She is not standing on her knees.
She is standing on her knees like this.
Isn't it like a knee-zuma?
Yes, it is.
Each of you has your own color.
Hoshina got 1 point.
The women's power monitoring is over.
Good job.
You are beautiful.
Thank you.
I want to do it again.
Do you have any points that you did
while thinking about this part?
I don't have any points.
I stopped thinking about anything.
I see.
I was impressed that Kobayashi was
having fun.
Did you see the scenery of Nakayama?
Did you see it?
I saw it outside.
What is the weather like in the sky now?
Because you like the sky.
We saw various things.
As a result, the two top players will go
to the final round.
The results have been announced so far.
Who are the two women's power top
players who will advance to the final
round?
The first one is...
Hoshina.
And the last one is...
Matsuno-san
Really?
I don't think it's good enough
No, no, no
Why?
It's a very good thing
That's right
What's wrong, Matsuno-san?
I can't open my mouth
You can't open your mouth
Matsuno can't hide her surprise at her
high女子力
Who is the member with the highest
female strength in the group?
The final round is a cooking competition
But before that
エビチュウ 作詞家への細道 This project is a project
aimed at making a new song.
What is the theme of this time?
This time, we are calling a lyricist
I'll give you a hint
Hyah!
Hyah?
Eh? Mayumine-san?
Let's go! This person!
Everyone!
It's been a long time!
We are Mr. Hustle, here, Ogata Kaiki!
And here is the guest of TASTAS member,
here, Ogata Kaiki!
This time, he will teach us the lyrics
of the song, Iroha, as a professional
musician.
I want to go to the reunion with Ogata
san, but we had a live show a while ago.
It's been a week, right?
I feel like we are meeting each other
more often these days.
I'm a fan of you, Tsukiji.
Tsukiji, right.
You are not just a fan.
I'm going to go to Tokyo Iroha.
This time, he will challenge to sing a
song.
By making a song, he will learn the
basics of lyrics.
Kaiki san, what kind of song do you want
to sing?
The same song, Donguri Korokoro.
To learn the lyrics, he will put the
song on the melody of Donguri Korokoro.
He will make the original lyrics of
Ebichu member, and Ogata san will
evaluate it.
The number of letters is decided.
If it's longer, it won't fit in the
song.
Ah, I see. The number of letters that
fit in the song.
The words that fit in the song.
First, Kobayashi's presentation.
One, two, three, four.
Thank you.
What does it mean?
The place where sweet potatoes become
dried sweet potatoes
Ah, that kind of song?
The song that becomes dried sweet
potatoes?
This is double meaning
What does it mean?
It sounds like a love song
But actually it's a sweet potato song
There are two meanings
It's deep
This is very high-class
Actually this kind of thing happens
often
The person who makes it thinks it's
different from what everyone else makes
It depends on the fans
That's right
Next is Mayama's presentation
If the rice and the rice are well-
matched, it's a rising!
This is beautiful
Donburi
I see, donburi is taken as donburi
And donburi namimori is a good
expression
It's a good expression
I like the combination of rice and beef
It's written as beef
That's good
That's amazing
Next is Kashiwagi
Who do you want to eat?
Curry, stew, and hayashi
I like hayashi
Do you want to put milk in curry?
I see
I want to eat it
Mayama too, but I think she's hungry
There are many food songs
I'm hungry
She must be hungry
Do you want to put milk in curry?
She's asking
This can be used in a love song
There are 3 people who are interested
Different types
I like the type like Hi-Hat-Rise
If you put milk in curry, you are also a
type
You can be a curry person
Amazing
What's Mayama?
What about stew?
That's right
That story is spread here
Did you make it for that reason?
No
I wanted to eat it
Next
I don't want to eat it
Who has the highest female power?
After this
Cooking battle of happening
The final battle is cooking battle
We can see cooking battle in this
program
How about you two?
We can make sweets but we can't make it
because the fire is dangerous
That's an excuse
That's why I don't have confidence
I'm a cow
I'm sorry
It's hot
I thought it was hot
How about Hoshina-san?
I'm good at cooking
So I'm good at cooking too, leave it to
me
Is that right Hoshina-san?
The back is noisy
It doesn't matter because I lost
Because you were released from the
pressure
Both of them look not confident
The final is a very basic dish
Check the woman's ability
What is the dish they will make this
time?
Well, we will make a fried egg
Teacher, what do you think?
Taste, appearance and
I don't know if they are making it while
thinking about me
I see
The point is whether you are thinking
about the opponent who will make you
lose
That's right
So, shall we start?
Let's start
Why did we come this far?
Everyone, let's start
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven,
eight, nine, ten!
You can't match the eggs.
Now, the final round. The cooking battle
starts!
Hoshina is the first to move.
Which do you like, sweet or salty?
I like sweet one
Same
You think about your opponent
Matsuno is defeated
Which one?
Both of you
Matsuno is faster
I need 3 eggs because it's for 3 people
You can decide that
It's tasty
You have eggs
Matsuno said she will make sweets
She will use eggs
You are so good at it
Thank you
You can only do this
Which way?
Actually, Matsuno is good at making
sweets
But she is not good at making omelette
How can she make this omelette with high
female power?
How much sugar do you usually put in
your omelette?
It's a question of temptation
How much do you put in?
I don't know
It's okay to make it with your home's
taste
My home's taste?
It's a cooking competition, but it's not
about cooking
It's about female strength
I was just talking
I'm scared of that area
Are you an angel or a devil?
You can touch it
Hoshina also put eggs in it
I want to do it
She is cute when she tastes it
I want to do it with my finger
It's getting salty
It's warm
Maybe
The point of the taste was high, but how
to taste it
Can she cover it with her feminine
power?
And wait until it's done
However
You can do it all at once
What should I do?
You can do it
You can do it all at once
Scramble eggs are the worst
The devil's voice
Hoshina is now in the egg-baking stage
She is pouring the eggs into the frying
pan little by little
She seems to be keeping the basic way of
making
Don't do that
I'm not talking about cooking
It's all done
Yes, it's all done
No matter how much you grill the egg
It's beautiful
Oh, she did it
She did it
Can she do it?
It's OK
I don't want to do it anymore
She said she doesn't want to do it
anymore
And Matsuno who grilled the egg first is
preparing the dish
It's beautiful
What about Kobayashi?
What are you doing?
Don't stand in the way
You came in suddenly
Kobayashi is in high spirit
It's OK
It's really good
Wait
And Hoshino
While we are waiting, Hoshina's is also
ready
It's almost done
Do you want to try it?
Hoshina, there is still more, what are
you going to do?
I'll try it
Ouch
It's good
The amount of seaweed is high
Finally, Hoshina's omelette is also
ready
It smells good
It's related to Kobayashi
I think Kobayashi is hungry
It's delicious
Really?
What is this?
Put it on the plate
Put bacon on the surface and it's done
Matsuno's first tamagoyaki
And Hoshina's voluminous tamagoyaki with
bacon
Both look delicious, but what about the
taste?
First, Matsuno's egg-yaki. By the way,
do you have a theme?
I did my best
Is it bland?
Delicious
I'm glad
This is delicious. It's a kind of egg-
yaki that goes well with rice. I'm glad
it's in a bento
By the way, is this the first time you
made this?
This is the first time I made egg-yaki
You have a good sense
I thought the amount was about this
By the taste?
I don't know
It was delicious
Next is Hoshina's
I think it's better to add something
It's a play on words
Can't hide his impatience in Matsuno's
high rating?
Does he have anxiety about the taste?
Confident Hoshina
Hoshina's anxiety is the enemy
Let's eat
What?
How is it?
I'm full now
I'm full
Wait a moment
Oh my god
It's amazing
It's not delicious or bad
She is sweating
She is dancing so much
She is so cute
Why?
Why are you all so surprised?
Look at the camera!
Why are you all making faces?
This is amazing
Why?
What's wrong?
This is bad
This is amazing
You're making faces
You're making a mistake with sugar and
salt
This is a fish!
Hoshina, who showed her high female
power by smiling even if she made a
mistake
This battle is not decided by the taste
alone
Who will be the winner of the Ebichu
Girls' Power Championship?
Please announce the winner of the Ebichu
Girls' Power Championship
The winner is...
Matsuno-chan!
Matsuno, congratulations!
Thank you very much!
By the way, can I ask you a question?
When you were cooking, you looked like
you were having fun.
I was watching you and I was really
proud of you.
I think you have a lot of girl power.
Thank you very much!
Next time, the first trial will be held
again.
I'll give up!
You're so mean!
Did you join the Gundam for peace?
The Gundam is for peace!
Is he guilty or innocent? Let's see the
verdict!
This is the second episode of Cyber!
This program was brought to you by the
sponsors you see.
The fruit fight of the fruit world.
The fruit fight.
You can eat whatever you want.
What is this?