Ebichu's video!
This is the final of the Sashana series.
I'm Yoko Hasegawa.
I cut my bangs by myself.
I cut my hair myself at night.
I'm Kaoriko.
I'm Rie.
Rie has already left?
Rie is in Kanagawa Prefecture, so she's
coming with a camera.
Bye-bye!
Say bye-bye!
This is the final of the tour.
I haven't performed since April 2nd, so
I feel like I'm in the final.
I'm wearing this today because it's my
first day.
I'm getting beautiful.
It's the last day of SIX VOCES, so I'm
looking forward to it.
Anyway, I'm looking forward to it until
the end.
I'll do my best!
I'm looking forward to it until the end.
I'm glad that the fans are coming to the
tour final.
I'm looking forward to it because it's
the last day.
It's the final, but I'm nervous because
it's my first day.
I'm looking forward to it.
I think my friends will come.
Yes!
Anyway, I'm looking forward to it.
It's the last day, so I'm looking
forward to it.
I'll do my best today.
I'm going to Japan!
Today is the tour final.
I'm going to do my best.
I'm wearing this.
I'm going to the final!
Thank you!
Yeah!
Please come!
I'll do my best with the manager!
I'm glad you came!
We're doing a rehearsal on May 5th.
Today is May 2nd.
I'm going to do my best!
It's over now.
It's been a long time since we've done a
rehearsal like this.
It's already the 3rd day.
It's already the group of 9 people.
It's been a long time since we've done a
rehearsal like this.
I'm here.
I'm always looking at you.
We're going to be out of time for a
month.
It's a new set.
We didn't think of it.
Ayaka's personality was very similar to
Ayaka.
Ayaka's voice was very similar to Ayaka.
I want you to say Ayaka's voice someday.
I'm looking forward to it.
May 5th is the end of the live
broadcast.
We don't know how we feel yet.
When you watch this video, you will know
that we are a 9-member group.
We will continue to live as a 9-member
group.
Please support us.
I will do my best someday.
It's a party.
Goodbye.
Please take care of your wrist.
Thank you.
I will do my best.
I'm sorry for the kiss.
It's my style.
Kiss me.
I'm scared of Niko.
I'm scared.
I kissed you because I didn't know.
I'm also kissing you.
Good morning.
We are SHINCHE BISHOP.
Please take care of us.
It's outside.
It's Nakayama time, but I'm alone.
I'm going to do it.
I'm going to do it a little more.
I'm done.
I will change clothes.
Please take a picture of the calm.
We are wide-angle on the sieve.
Let us take a photo.
This is an outfit that you picked.
What about you?
What about Maki?
natural.
She is cool without clothes.
Thank you for watching.
Has the next training psychological
impact?
When you come here, the image of the
scenery comes out.
So it's only your face can go on air.
What's up
Are you surprised?
Smiling
It's finished.
After this, we'll be able to put on new
artists' photos at 9 o'clock, so let's
hurry up and change!
It's over!
Everyone, hurry up!
How was it?
What did you like about the photos?
I'm the 13th place, 4th grade, Sakura
Ikokona.
Thank you for your support.
What's your favorite food?
My favorite food is raw oysters and
meat. My specialty is the ice balance.
What was the most memorable moment?
It was very white. The light hit me.
I thought that I was once again a
shrimp. I was very impressed.
What's your favorite food?
I think it's the people who are full of
personality and are energetic and
bright.
I get a lot of comments like,
I'm here!
What is your next stage?
I'm looking forward to it.
Maybe there's a fan meeting next time.
When I become a brave audience,
I want to be able to perform
in a way that doesn't lower the quality.
What is your next stage?
I'm going to be a Sakura Yoko Natt from
Ebichu.
Please support me.
What is your first name?
Nice to meet you.
I'm No.14,
I'm a junior high school student, Kukubo
Yuno.
Nice to meet you.
What is your favorite food?
My favorite food is
Kakiwakame Ume Aji and
Jagariko Tarako Butter.
My specialty is Kendo.
I'm a 7th grader, but I'm good at Kendo.
I'm also good at Takeumama.
Please support me.
What is your favorite song?
I like Kurenai no Uta and
Kindan no Karma.
I like all of them.
What is your favorite anime?
I'm going to do my best with the three
of us.
I hope the members of the Min family
will be happy to have Yuno.
Please support me.
What is your favorite character?
There are many kind people.
I'm happy to have the kind people
support me.
What is your favorite costume?
I was very nervous when I first got into
the costume.
Until then, we were dancing together
while watching the live video.
I was very nervous from then.
What was the most memorable moment?
It was a moment.
I couldn't answer the questions well,
but it was fun.
What is your favorite anime?
I'm glad to meet you.
I will do my best.
I'm the second-year student of the 55th
class.
Thank you.
What is your favorite anime?
My favorite food is dumplings.
My specialty is birthday card making and
physical training.
What was the most exciting thing about
the show?
I was nervous until the show started,
but it was fun to finish it in one go.
Do you have any memories?
Yes, I do.
I don't remember the last part, but I
remember the last part.
What was the most exciting thing about
the show?
I was nervous even when there was no
audience.
I thought it would be a little dangerous
if there were fans, but I thought it
would be nice because it would make the
audience excited.
I think I'm nervous, so I practice a lot
to be confident and dance.
What do you like about the show?
I think I like Ebichu a lot.
What is your favorite part of the show?
I'm the youngest, so I'll do my best.
Please support me.