So, the 10th, 11th, and 12th Heisei
Isokintorio's gathering is now over.
Thank you everyone.
This time, Heisei Isokintorio is a unit
held in 2016 by me, Hinnata Kashiwagi,
and Shikaho Kobayashi, and Riko
Nakayama.
This time, we are going to the unit held
in the university hall, Heisei
Isokintorio.
This time, we are going to the venue, so
we have to go to Heisei Isokintorio.
We only did one or two times at the
concert, so we thought it would be nice
to sing the song that we have grown up
singing.
So, we decided to put together the title
of Heisei Isokintorio's gathering.
The members of the 10th year team were
friends who had been together for more
than 10 years, and we were doing a live
performance that felt the history of
Ebichu.
This time, we will put together the
favorite songs of all three members
rather than the history.
Of course, there is a big selection to
do the Heisei Isokintorio's gathering,
but there is a song called Diving.
Originally, it was not Ebichu's song,
but it was a song of 3B Junior.
It's a song that was played when I was
in 3B Junior, and there was a group
called Team Daioika before entering
Ebichu.
Can you be quiet for a moment?
I'm sorry, my eyes are noisy.
I was also doing Diving, so I thought it
was better to do it. I didn't put it in
the 10th year team, so I didn't put it
in the audience.
I thought it was a good song, but it
wasn't here, so I brought it to the
first song. The second song is Butterfly
Effect.
This song keeps,​
telling the own story, but
changes things a lot.
I work on the previous one.
What was the new one?​
If you listen to it from now onto, it
kind of feels like...​
I really like Kaho's songs, which are
very expressive, and have a good
atmosphere.
Riko is powerful and fun, and I liked
the song with power and coolness.
I wanted to put this on the set list, so
I thought I'd put it on the set list.
So, before we sang in a room, we had
memories with each other in our heads.
After that, the four songs were a little
more blue than Riko's.
Like the star name Armure Manager.
That was Riko's, and the block was asked
after the unit was over.
From the 23rd Summer Night to the set
list of Kaho's,
and finally, the song that Kaho wanted
to do the most, Chupacabra.
The song that Riko wanted to do the
most, Forever 15.
And the three songs, Tamageta, Koi no
Elunini.
It was a really fun live performance.
It was the same as last time, when we
were 10 years old.
It was a live performance that could be
performed only because of this member.
And, well, it's an encore, right?
I think everyone was surprised.
Well, before this Kashiwagi project
started,
we announced that we would do four
performances of the Produce performance
that was a family performance.
From there, we asked for things that we
wanted to do with the hashtag Kashiwagi
project,
and asked if there were any requests for
things like this.
When I asked on Twitter,
well, it's not an exaggeration to say
that it was a lot of chaos.
So that6 people...
最後のライブを見たいですという声が 本当にありがたいことに多くて
ライブの中でも言ったんですけど 6 voicesっていう
スワーじゃないですけど 何か所かでやらせていただいたときは
綾香が療養中でお休みで 綾香以外の5人でステージに立って
声は綾香の歌をそのまま使うっていうような
6人の声というのをテーマにしたライブを
we decided to have a new member.
We were doing that.
Before that, Mirei-chan was injured,
Ayaka was on leave,
and we couldn't really do a live with 6
people.
What was it?
The first one was 2018.
It felt like we were doing a spring tour
with 6 people.
We wanted to do a live with 6 people,
but it was hard to do that.
We got requests for a live performance,
so I thought I could do it.
So we contacted everyone and said we
wanted to do a live performance with 6
people.
They said they didn't think we could do
it,
so we were really happy.
So we decided to do it.
The set list was the same.
Everyone wanted to do it,
so we decided to do it.
We were doing it,
and we remembered a lot of things from
the 6 of us.
We almost cried on the road.
The first song was the beginning of the
6 of us.
There were a lot of things that I
thought about.
I thought that the encore wasn't an
encore.
I was planning to put this in and do a 2
hour live.
I heard that I was doing a 2 hour 40
minute live.
It's been a while since I did a live.
I think everyone at Isokin did a good
job.
I think we did a good job of making the
volume of the university stage.
And I'm really grateful to Maya, Aya,
and Mirei for coming.
I'm really grateful to all the fans who
have been waiting for me to do a live
performance.
I was really happy to see a lot of
people watching the last live
performance, including the delivery.
Isokin is full of the personality of
Kawa and Riko.
I think that's another attraction and I
think I was able to do a live
performance.
It was a really big volume live
I hope you all enjoy it.
It's really a live performance that will
be remembered and remembered by us.
Thank you very much.