Thank you for watching!
I'm not moving at all.
I have a night view at my house, but it
was my first time to talk to you like
this.
It was really fun.
What is the most memorable thing you did
in Japan?
I wonder.
I like the skin of potatoes, but I also
like the hard part of the potato.
I also like the hard part of the potato.
I often cook, but I often add potatoes
to curry, stew, miso soup, and rice.
I often use potatoes.
I changed.
Is it been a while?
Yes.
I didn't expect to take a bath.
What kind of conversation do you usually
have with the members?
I don't know.
I usually talk about social life.
I share delicious food with them.
How old are you?
I'm the oldest, but the youngest is in
the third grade of junior high school.
How old are you?
I'm about eight years old.
Do you talk to each other?
Yes.
I sometimes feel a generation gap.
I'm excited with the members above, but
I'm also excited with MIYU and RINA.
What should I do?
I will interview RIKO.
The content is...
RIKO's laughter is very loud.
I want to know where it comes from.
Do you know the feeling of laughing from
the tip of your feet?
It feels like it's coming out of your
tongue.
I wonder where he is laughing.
Ah, but...
Can I say a lot?
I mean, Yuna from Iginari Tohoku said
she likes saunas.
And Luna said she likes saunas too.
So I want to talk about that.
And Chihocchan said she loves potatoes.
And Ayla said she loves potatoes too.
I want to eat potatoes with her.
That's it.
This is the end of the year.
Yes.
Ah, is it open? Congratulations.
Not yet. Not yet.
Really?
That's it. This is the end of the year.
That's right.
It's a fast-paced video.
It's a video of the demon laughing.
It's fast.
It's okay to say congratulations on the
new year.
What kind of year was it for the Gattem
Girls' Club?
This year, we had a lot of events and
live performances.
We had a tour of the spring, a tour of
Kyushu, a 7th anniversary live
performance, and a one-man live at
Nakano Sun Plaza on November 26th.
It was a very intense year.
You were able to do a lot of live
performances.
That's right. In the summer and autumn,
I'm often away from home on weekends.
I was very happy to continue my long-
awaited excursion.
I also met a lot of new fans.
It was a very fun year for me and the
people who always support me.
I see.
What kind of year was it for you
personally?
It was fun.
It was a year.
It's fast, isn't it?
It's fast.
I'm sorry.
September is over.
That's fine.
It's over.
I only had a day to remember August.
You only had a day to remember August.
What day do you remember?
The first day.
The first day of August?
I remember.
You remember.
You don't remember at all.
That's right.
It's not like that.
It's surprisingly so.
It's fast.
Was it fast?
I'm surprised.
My character that had no braids?
My own opinion about ui
I had a lot of work this year.
Yes, I was invited to a fan event this
year.
I was very nervous because I was the
only member.
I'm not good at fan events.
I thought it would be difficult to write
a theme on the spot.
Do you want to try it?
Now?
It's a theme.
I'll ask the teacher.
I'm nervous.
It seems to be a long question.
I'm scared.
What is the title of the song that was
too
bad and became a bad point?
This is too long.
Bad point?
Too bad.
Yes, it became a bad point.
The title of the song.
Result is…
No rice in the everything
All right!
придia
I'm sorry for being so sharp.
You're so mean.
I'm a bit of a weirdo.
You're a weirdo.
I drew it because I thought it was
sharp.
I'm not going to draw it.
This is difficult.
But there's something called idols.
If you draw this, you'll definitely get
a lot of money.
I don't think so.
It's difficult.
It's hard to draw after that.
Is there a correct answer?
I'm not sure if it's correct.
I've been doing this for a long time.
I'll ask you at the end.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'd better not waste time.
Let's go to the sauna.
I want to go.
I'll ask you at the end.
Thank you very much.
Now, let's see the work of a man who is
a writer.
I also saw his work as a psychologist.
Now, I'll ask you a question.
What was it?
The topic is...
The title of the song that became the
boss because it was too
What?
Ta-da!
Ba-
Ba-Ten-Shou-Ju-Tai-Biz
H-A-R-I-G-A-N-E-H-A-N-G-A-R
Fuku-O-Ka-Ken
Don't say that!
Fuku-O-
What's wrong?
Fuku-O-Ka-Ken
Oh, I see!
Amazing!
Fuku-O-Ka-Ken
What if I get told that I'm amazing?
Oh, I see!
I'm a genius!
Thank you very much!
Wow, amazing!
Please subscribe to my channel!
Let's go again!
Let's go!
What is the title of the song that was
the first song of the Batten Girls?
Batten Girls with Sponge
We love Kyushu!
What is this?
It's a sponge.
You are right.
I can't reach it.
Wow!
I see. This is what it means to be a big
fan of Kyushu.
Thank you very much.
I can't believe it.
I've been watching your videos.
You are so good at it.
Thank you very much.