I'm Reina Odakura, a third-year high
school student from Tokyo.
I played the violin a little bit when I
was in junior high school, so I will
play the violin today.
Thank you very much.
Today, I came to Gunma Observatory,
which has the largest telescope in
Kanto.
Today, I came to the two corals, which
are my charming points, to see the sky.
I will also see the whole of Coine's
Procyon and the whole of Coine's.
The reason I fell in love with stars is
that when I was in elementary school, I
heard from my teacher that there are
much bigger and brighter stars than the
sun.
I was interested in how small I was.
I'm going to see the stars now.
Etergius is a red star, but it's a
little bit brighter than the sun.
I can see the red star clearly.
I'm impressed.
I can see the small stars, too.
Next, I'm looking forward to seeing how
it looks like with a bigger telescope.
Wow!
I can see the red star.
It's a planet.
I can see the red star clearly.
It's about 9 to 10 times the size of the
Earth.
It's huge.
It's amazing.
It's really amazing.
It's the first time I've seen it with my
own eyes.
Next, let's look at Jupiter.
I'll move the telescope toward Jupiter.
Jupiter is a little bigger than Saturn.
It's about 11 times bigger than Earth.
If you go from Earth to the speed of
light, it's about half of Saturn.
It's about 40 minutes.
I used this telescope to see the Jupiter
and Saturn.
The starry sky was beautiful, and I
could see Saturn very well.
I could even see the rings.
I was so impressed. I'm glad I came.
I'm so impressed that I could see it.
I'm in Koenuza. I saw Koenuza.
It's around here.
I've been waiting for the sun to rise,
and I could see it.
I'm glad I came.
It's the same shape as my bag.
It's very similar.
The alpha protein of COINUZA is one-
dimensional.
I will do my best to shine like that
star.