Yakan and identity
To be continued
But this is not me being an idol.
Oh, really?
I like idols.
Yes.
I like cute girls more than idols.
I like girls.
I like girls who are trying to improve
themselves.
I want to support them.
I look for cute girls on Instagram and
like them.
I recommend Yuzu. She's a cute idol.
I look for cute girls.
I like Maika Sasaki of Equal Love.
She can be dyed in any color.
She can do both cool and cute styles.
She has a cute face, but she's a
refreshing girl.
I recommend her.
Do you go to the venue?
If you have time, I'll go to see the
live.
The other day, Masquerade of 26 o'clock
was performing at the Budokan.
I bought a ticket and went to see the
live with my best friend.
You like her.
I really like her.
How was it?
She's cute.
I like her figure.
She's an idol and an otaku.
I think her setting is amazing.
I like her outfit.
I like her style.
I go to such places.
I think it would be nice if there was
such a performance.
Do you often say that when you perform?
I don't say that.
I see.
I'm not the type to say that.
I'm thinking of Moeka Suzuki.
I can tell if you say that.
Moeka Suzuki is a little older than you.
I don't feel old in a good way.
I feel like I'm getting older.
Moeka says she wants to do her best on
Instagram.
Moeka's goal is to upload more photos.
She wants to have more Instagram
followers.
So, I tell her what to post.
I tell her what to write.
I see.
I give her advice.
I sometimes deceive her.
I'm not good at this.
I don't know.
I want to try it once.
What is your goal?
I want to produce a photo book.
That's your goal.
You have a lot of goals.
I want to take a picture of a cute girl.
I'm confident that I can make the cutest
girl in the world.
That's a good plan.
I want to produce a cute girl.
Thank you for watching this video.
Please subscribe to this channel.
I don't drink green tea.
What is that image?
It's my own image.
I'm going to decide.
This program is
Toshikazu from Yuzuki Hime
Makika Ruzel
Bake-chan
Keisuke
delivered by Hbase Edo of the Yuzao
Shinohide-san in life!
Thank you very much.