How did everyone start?
It's starting normally.
Hello, I'm Asuka Saito.
Today I jumped out into the city and
came to shoot a collaboration with
someone.
This background is known to those who
know.
I'm here.
Hello, I'm as family as it is.
What should I do?
Wait a minute.
I have a different aura.
I'm a collaboration partner.
Are you Asuka Saito?
Hello, I'm Asuka Saito.
I'm glad to meet you again.
Is it okay?
I'm Jimon Terakano.
I'm a meat lawyer.
That's amazing.
I'm amazing.
Do you eat meat?
I like meat.
I went abroad to eat steak.
I went to Okinawa.
I want to know a good restaurant.
I only have Jimon.
You are in the worst place.
You are in a bad place.
Let's go to the restaurant.
My acquaintance's restaurant is next to
this restaurant.
Is that so?
I don't have any acquaintances.
I have more acquaintances in the meat
industry than in the entertainment
industry.
I have more acquaintances in the food
I'm sorry for my hair.
Thank you.
Thanks for watching!
This is the restaurant.
This is D29.
This is a restaurant with a female
owner.
So you can't eat a lot.
I'm glad.
This is fashionable.
This is the most popular restaurant in
Osaka.
This is a restaurant with a lot of real
beef.
You should decide the restaurant when
you enter.
If you smell good, you can eat it.
Is it so easy?
It is important.
If you smell bad, you can't eat it.
You can't smell bad when you enter a
good restaurant.
This is one point.
It is important not to put a picture
here.
I don't go to a restaurant that says
it's on TV.
I don't go.
If you call people in the restaurant,
it's not a big deal.
You should decide the restaurant when
you enter.
You judge the restaurant.
You are making fun of me.
I'm a man who goes to eat with Akiboshi.
I'm looking forward to it.
This is TAKABURA.
This is NIGHT ASUKA.
I'm doing my best to make you come.
Thank you.
It's completely different from who
comes.
That's not true.
This is a big deal.
I'm a comedian.
Let's eat first.
Thank you for the meal.
The most important thing for a YAKINIKU
restaurant is not the meat.
It's a restaurant far from meat.
It's kimchi and salad.
I always say that meat is delicious.
But I'm not sure if it's delicious.
I brought this meat.
I want to eat the best meat first.
There are many ways to eat meat.
Lemon, tofu, etc.
I think the best meat is the fillet.
I like fillet the most.
I eat the fillet of the fillet.
What is that?
I'm shooting a video.
I'm shooting a video from right to left.
I'm a little smart.
I'm a little fast.
I'm a little slow.
I'm good.
I haven't taken a video yet.
What is the big difference between a
female and a male?
Even if the fat of the female is
falling, the oil is different.
The fat is melted and the scent is
strong.
How do you grill the meat?
There is a way to grill the meat.
Is there such a way?
Do you grill the meat as a YAKISHI?
Can I see it?
I'm not good at grilling meat.
You are not a YAKISHI.
I'm not a YAKISHI yet.
This is a difficult way.
This is a fillet.
You don't have to shape the meat.
You grill the meat.
I don't shape the meat.
This is the essence of female meat.
Be careful.
This smells good.
This is a good restaurant.
This smells like a female.
Please subscribe to our channel.
This is a rotating pan.
Is it so spinning?
This is to ensure that the whole is
baked.
I thought I had to put it aside.
There are various things.
This is a brown color.
This brown part is also a brown color.
This is beautiful.
This is not baked with a net.
This is a brown color.
I don't know this.
Please don't eat this.
This is a little flat.
I bake this.
This is beautiful.
This doesn't need a knife or fork.
This is cut with a chopstick.
Is that so?
This is true.
This is cut.
This is a soft meat.
This is amazing.
This is a beautiful taste.
This is cut with a chopstick.
This is good if you put it on salt.
Salt is good.
Please give me your impression.
Please subscribe to this channel.
How is it?
It's delicious.
This is delicious.
What is this scent?
This is a meat sushi.
This is refreshing.
Is this Omi Hime Wagyu?
What is this?
There was no one here.
Where is this meat?
This is a meat sushi of SAWAI Hime
Wagyu.
This is a sushi of MEZUNUSHI.
This is a sushi of SATO BURIYAN.
This is the best part.
This is a sushi of SAWAI Hime Wagyu with
soy sauce in the middle.
Please eat this with wasabi soy sauce.
This is absolutely delicious.
Please subscribe to this channel.
It's delicious.
You are annoying, but the meat is real.
It's true.
It's not true.
What is that?
It's delicious.
It's delicious, isn't it?
I will eat this.
Asuka Saito.
Please grill the meat.
I didn't look at the meat.
I will eat this.
I eat the first roast of the site Asuka.
You are excited.
Is this the right way?
Please listen to the voice of the meat.
When do you return the meat?
When I say, return the meat.
You are cute.
Is this okay?
Is it a little more?
Please wait a little more.
I'm telling you.
It's perfect.
It's a terracotta brown.
This is also a Asuka brown.
Asuka brown is coming out.
It's done.
It's perfect.
It's good.
I got it.
It's a tongue.
It's thick.
It's small.
I got three kinds of tongue.
I'll eat two.
This is too luxurious.
This is the best part of the tongue.
Look at this.
Is this all?
This is a terracotta border.
It's a border.
If you grill it, it will be a border.
If you grill it normally, it will be a
border.
But if you grill it too much, it will
not be a border.
You can't eat it yet.
It looks delicious.
You should not eat it right away.
This is a terracotta border.
It's delicious if you wait a little.
What is this?
You don't remember this, do you?
I don't know.
The moment you see this, you will get
the answer.
You will talk to it.
Don't eat it right away.
Wait a minute.
Put a little salt on it.
It's like a pan.
It said, eat it now.
Are you saying that?
I'll eat it.
Please subscribe to my channel.
It's delicious.
How is it?
It's sweet and delicious.
It's amazing.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I did it.
What is the bread you have eaten so far?
It's not bread.
It's not bread, is it?
Welcome to the Nijioen of Jimon.
This is a daily life.
That's cool.
I will bake thin sliced bread.
What?
You haven't seen it yet.
I haven't done this yet.
I will bake thin sliced bread.
I don't know.
Don't you bake the edge?
It's OK.
I don't touch it.
I'm scared.
You're usually tired of grilling meat.
But I don't grill meat.
You don't?
I'll grill it for you.
Ouch!
It's okay.
What should I do?
You can grill it yourself.
I told you.
I'm learning.
You look like a professional.
Please.
I'll put it in.
Okay.
I see.
I'll give it a score.
It's good.
It's a perfect score
But it tastes good
The bread is covering it
It's tough
Try it
It tastes good
It's sweet
It's sweet now
It's sweet after you swallow it
How is it?
It's sweet
It's different from the one before
It's good
Let's use the 10 points
I made a mistake
Do not stick to the pan.
The oil will not spread.
What is that?
It is thin, so it will be cooked.
It is cooked.
I want to drink the soup.
I'm sorry, I made a mistake.
This is the Terakado Border.
This is about this.
That's fast.
Please compare it with the tando you
baked.
Both are delicious.
The color is different.
The tando is also delicious.
It's soft.
If you bake it too much, all the inside
will be cooked.
The inside is rare.
It has a savory taste.
It's soft.
It's savory.
The most difficult thing is this thick
cut.
I bake this.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Are you getting tired of it?
I didn't think about anything.
I can tell by your attitude.
You are getting tired of it.
I made a mistake.
I put the Terakado Border in the soup.
It looks delicious.
It has a good color.
Please subscribe to this channel.
You.
Eh?
Are you making me rest?
Yes, I'm making you rest.
You can't cook cheap food right away.
I'm making you rest.
I'm making you rest the meat.
I'm making you rest the bread.
I'm scared.
Why are you scared?
I was worried, so the shop staff came to
see me.
Why are you making me rest?
I repeat this.
If you cook the meat until it's cooked,
the meat will be hard.
I see.
So, I cook it three times.
It's still soft.
It's not cooked at all.
It's a nice color.
It's coming out.
It's amazing.
The fat is coming out of the meat.
It's coming out.
Finally.
It's beautiful.
This is amazing.
This is a good product.
You said it was a good product.
I'm not used to saying this.
The following is the best週刊 Hashyme
fromillyou.com
It's amazing, isn't it?
Wow!
This is a very good one.
It's amazing!
It's like a ham cutlet.
That's right.
It doesn't make sense to compare it to
something that doesn't taste good.
This is a steak.
The best steak.
Yeah!
Wow!
How is it?
You're happy, aren't you?
Wow!
It's delicious!
This is a very good steak.
It's melting in my mouth.
It's very fragrant.
It's fragrant, isn't it?
I don't think it would be delicious if
it wasn't fragrant.
I agree.
Now, the next one is the belly meat.
The belly meat.
The best restaurant with belly meat is
the one with the best quality.
Oh!
The restaurant with the best belly meat
is the one with the best quality.
I see.
The belly meat is basically a well-done
steak.
Thank you for watching this video.
Please subscribe to this channel.
This is really delicious.
Can you understand by eating?
This is good.
If it is not so fragrant, the meat juice
will come out of the meat.
I put the cabbage on top.
This is absolutely delicious.
What is this?
Can you put this on top?
This is juicy and delicious.
What is this?
Please subscribe to this channel.
It smells good.
It's delicious.
Please subscribe to this channel.
What is this?
How is it?
This is my daily life.
Isn't it delicious?
I like your daily life.
I eat this every day.
This is in my movie called Food Luck.
I eat this.
It's delicious
Next is thick-cut fireworks
It's so big
I can't put out this much
Isn't this good?
Beautiful color
This is a flower
This is not meat, it's a sauce
I see
It's not spicy at all
It's so juicy
Thank you for watching! Please
subscribe!
It's not burnt at all.
It's so good!
I'll try the thin sliced and thick
sliced one.
It's so good!
I'm starting to eat normally
This is a yakiniku bowl
I will tell you the last answer of
yakiniku
It's free
It's true
It's yakiniku that allows you to eat
freely
Can you make it so that I don't have 10
points anymore?
That's impossible
That was 10 points
Is it delicious?
I'm not satisfied anymore
Are you okay?
I'm satisfied
Are you satisfied?
Yes
Are you full of shooting?
I'm very satisfied
Thank you
I'm already heading for the ending
The ending is from here
Now, Roy
It's a big board
It's amazing
Please subscribe to my channel
The VLOG about Halloween GIFT today!
What an amazing meat.
McNuggets should be baked longer
Well then, you can now...
Yes.
Wow!
OK?
Thank you very much.
This is the plate.
You can put this on the rice.
That's right.
I'll put this on the rice.
Look.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I will eat it with egg.
This is a cool dish.
This is a big dish.
This is a grilled meat.
This is a toy.
This is a very good meat.
This is a very good taste.
This is the taste of the end of the
year.
This is amazing.
How was the collaboration between Jumon
and Yakiniku?
It was very good.
I learned a lot.
Please tell the staff that you don't
want to do it again.
Please don't do it.
Are you okay?
We have finished eating.
It was very good.
Asuka was there, so it was very good.
I'm always annoyed.
It was very good.
I have never eaten this kind of food.
I haven't eaten such a beautiful
Yakiniku in a long time.
I'm glad you said that.
My atmosphere is beautiful.
Please consult with the agency.
Is it an offer from the agency?
I have more power.
I'm more interested in the person's
will.
It was fun.
I learned a lot.
I will cook it again.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Are you going to say that?
I'm not going to say that.
I'm always late.
I'm going to say that.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Thank you for watching!