Night view and idol!
Oh, you're going to throw away your
face?
Oh, I'm going to throw it away.
I didn't know that.
I knew it!
Thank you for watching.
The second one is...
The countryside!
Yes, the countryside.
This is also an important part of my
story.
Yes, yes, yes.
I live in a forest where I can't even
get a signal on my phone.
No, no, no, don't laugh.
But you have a house, so you can't get a
signal on your phone.
And I don't have a map.
You don't have a map?
I really don't have a map.
So when I set up a car navigation
system,
there was nothing around me.
I just had my house sign.
It's really in the countryside.
How far did you go to school?
I went to elementary school.
I was in bicycle school until I was in
the fourth grade.
You went to bicycle school from the
first grade?
Yes, yes.
What about the helmet?
I wore a helmet and I think I was about
6 kg.
That's pretty heavy.
I went to school there, but I became a
bus driver.
I went to elementary school by moving
from bus.
That's amazing.
It's the same on rainy days, right?
Yes, it's the same on rainy days.
It's the same on rainy days.
I live near my house.
I don't have a neighborhood.
I live 200 meters away.
One house.
I live in an elementary school where I
meet my friends and go to school
together.
I see.
What about your siblings?
I have an older brother and an older
sister.
I'm the youngest.
You're the youngest?
Yes.
You're the youngest.
I'm the youngest.
And you grew up in such a countryside.
That countryside is your home.
I love it.
I love my hometown.
I can breathe deeply.
It's different.
It's totally different.
I'm sorry, but it's hard to breathe in
Tokyo.
I wanted to ask you that.
There are many animals.
There are boars, squirrels, and rabbits.
Do squirrels live there?
Yes.
Do foxes live there?
Of course.
Do foxes live in Saitama?
Yes.
And Itachi.
Itachi, too.
There are squirrels.
Yes.
And there are also owls.
I cry near my house at night.
I like it.
I don't think Gyaru is the image of
Gyaru.
But I think Gyaru is the image of Gyaru.
Gyaru is very calm.
And nature makes me feel good.
I admire the city because it is a
country.
I often go to Sendai and Tokyo.
I miss the country.
I see.
The city is not noisy.
The sound of nature is beautiful.
I like stars.
The stars are beautiful.
But it's different.
There is only one streetlight around my
house.
The stars are beautiful.
I miss the country when I go back.
I think Gyaru is the image of Gyaru.
Everyone says they want to eat meat or
seafood, but they say they want pancakes
for lunch.
I tried to put custard cream on the
stage drink, but I was stopped.
Stop it!
Thank you for your viewing.
I sent it to you by the offer of Kibou
Shichu, Hasechi, and Keisuke.
I'm looking forward to seeing you live.