Oh, they're talking about themselves.
It's a big adventure.
I think this way, and you think that
way.
I think we have to be responsible for
that.
I'm sure it's risky to join with Yanaka-
san.
I was watching the tennis match between
Yanaka-san and R.
I was like, I'm tired.
Why?
I was cool.
You were defeated.
Why?
That's right.
I was in the first year of high school.
I watched Bruce Brothers when I was in
the third grade of elementary school.
I thought it was cool.
The first CD I got was the soundtrack of
the Blues Brothers.
Oh.
All my family members are cool.
It's a speciality of Matsunaga family.
All of them are insanely cool.
I grew up worrying about what I'm
listening to, what I'm wearing, and what
people are looking at.
That's why my parents lent me the Blues
Brothers.
I was really cool when I listened to it.
I was in the second grade of junior high
school.
I was always listening to it.
There are people who wake up to fashion.
A friend who was watching fashion shows
with me
said there was a Japanese rap song
called Hip-Hop.
He lent me an MD.
Fashion and Hip-Hop are connected.
Yes, we were together.
In that fashion show, there was Muro-
san.
There was a car zombie team.
We were in the same class.
There was a part that came into my head
at first.
I asked him, and he said, this is cool.
I think that the bad qualities of hip-
hop are very unusual for a boy who goes
to a school in the countryside.
And this music is not known to anyone
who is going to this school and is now
passing the class.
And at that time, the most deeply-seated
thing was Rhyme Star.
I've been listening to Rhyme Star's
radio all the time.
At that time, in 2006, Debra A 對D
released his first solo album, DL,
aka Debra A nd Admonitions,
and it was released on the Anima's show.
It was so cool.
That's the real essence of the track I'm
making now.
Debra A is a huge fan of sampling.
No good!
The most important factor is the sense
of sampling.
The drum that is mysterious, hazy, but
very catchy,
and the sound of it being put on top of
the story.
I don't know much about it, but it was
the most important to me at the time.
There's a song called Great Jaguar in
it.
Kuretsu is about a record box.
It's about a record box.
Yes.
It's a song about me digging into it.
My head is black, black, black.
Everywhere, outside, everywhere.
Every time, every time.
This is a thing.
I always get my hands dirty.
This is how you do it.
Yes, like this.
You know...
When you go to Tsukaba tour, there are
record stores all over the place.
Your hands get dirty.
Yeah, the used record is dirty, and your
hands get dirty.
And nobody's seen a shelf that gets
dirty, so there's a lot of stuff to dig
out.
Yeah, and that's all in this song.
The job of a person who is buried in a
dust-drenched jewel,
and goes to the next spot without a
compass.
And this person, this is the last verse,
but...
年柄年中、ディキネザ・クレイツ。 I dig every year, dig
into every crevice.
しかも、エビ栓針に掘る、クレイジーペース。 And I dig into
every crevice, crazy pace.
俺こそ、すごい好きなの。 I really like this one.
エビ栓針に、止まらないくらいも、掘っちゃう。 I dig into every
crevice, so much so I can't stop.
で、次に、風の噂、街の噂、引き寄せ、鍵合わせ見つけるのさ。 And then,
I find the wind and city's rumors, the
draw, the key, and the connection.
横の繋がり、縦の繋がり、情報手上がりに綱渡り。これは、デブラージュさんが。
The horizontal, vertical connection, the
information hand-to-hand connection.
This is, Mr. Debraz...
He was called to the local area as a DJ.
He asked if he knew where the local
people had good records.
He heard the live local information
there.
And he went to a recycling shop where no
other DJ had ever been to.
Like a local goods store.
He went to places like that.
He still has that.
The track new person has a pretty sticky
record...
It's a rare item.
The family sells it to a recycling shop.
So it's not a person who's looking for
records.
Right.
It's not a place where it's not.
It's like, I know it all by my eyes.
I go looking for it.
I go to Tokyo, the city of Tokyo, and
the city of Eigyo.
I search for the best sound I can get.
I make a track with sampling.
I thought it was a trackmaker's theme
song.
I was in a town called Nagaoka City in
Niigata Prefecture.
There was no record store.
I was in my hometown.
I was going to a record corner at a
recycling shop.
When I started DJing, I had a one loop
record.
I was listening to this when I was going
to a hard off with a bicycle.
I was listening to the mp3 player and
listening to the crazed jaguar with a
cheap
para-note, and I was going to a hard off
with a bicycle.
From now on, I'm going to do something
really cool.
I'm not shopping. I'm not shopping.
You guys are shopping now.
I'm doing my work.
Everyone is being careful because of the
bicycle.
I'm not shopping. I'm not shopping.
I'm a traveler, and I'm looking for a
better plate.
I'm always stubborn, and I'm always
hungry.
I'm always smiling at people who don't
look at me.
Everyone is trying to come to an
agreement at this moment.
I'm not going to lose.
I was in high school at the time.
I only know two stores.
I'm going to go on a mamba-chari.
You're listening to the adventure of
looking for a record.
It's a big adventure.
So sampling is the spirit of hip-hop.
It's still my theme song.
This is also cool.
There is a cool sampling risk.
The head of the head.
The drum sampling is the best.
Markham MacLaren's World Famous.
That snare is so impressive.
It's like, cha-cha-cha-cha.
I use it a lot.
I didn't know the original story, but I
didn't know the original story.
This drum is too crazy.
So in that sense, I'm bossing myself
with the lyrics of this song,
The King of Gansu, Buddha, Buddha, and
I'm bossing myself.
My husband is crazy.
My husband is crazy in the lyrics, but
I'm crazy in the way he talks.
I think that's what I think when I
listen to the track.
This is the original song.
Boasting is a way to show off.
Bruce's musicians are showing off their
talents.
But you're showing off by digging
records.
You're digging a whole track.
If you're a regular person, you should
buy records.
It's not like you're angry about buying
records.
It's really bad to buy my own records.
I used to go to the record store.
One of the tracks says hip hop is the
national anthem.
I thought I'd have this one.
I brought it today.
I bought it when I was digging.
Oh, it's a patch.
It's not a reissue.
Is it original?
What's the score?
I want to give this to you.
Really?
I want to give it to you.
I was in my teens, so I can't give it to
you.
Really? Thank you.
I'm so happy.
I've never heard of it before.
I got it from Yanaka-san.
It's crazy.
He worked hard with me this summer.
That's a big deal.
It's a private.
Thank you.
I was influenced by my parents.
When Sazan All Stars, Miyuki Nakajima,
and Kazumasa Oda were playing in the
car,
I was unconsciously listening to them
when I was little.
I listened to the song called Million
Monsters Attack by Sold Out, which was a
song that was played in the early days
of junior high school.
It was played in a beef bowl restaurant
when we were eating together.
The rap itself was like, I don't know
what you're talking about.
I don't understand it, but it's so cool.
Did you imitate the rap that you heard
at first?
Thank you for watching.
I didn't think I could do it myself.
I just listened to it.
And, as Mr. Matsudana said, he
immediately empez...
He thinks he's cool and he's armed with
his mental.
And hip-hop and the shocking thing was
that these people were talking about
themselves.
It's a song I've heard before, but it
wasn't like that.
I'm a gibra, I'm talking about myself.
You're going to name it.
Yes, yes, Rhyme Star is in the house,
we're here, and I'm going to say my name
and then talk.
What? These people are talking about
themselves.
Then again...
I don't sing the melody, but I keep
hearing similar sounds.
It's interesting.
I found something really interesting.
And it's so interesting that it's so
touching.
When I'm on my way home, I feel like I'm
standing on fire.
I feel like I'm standing on a white
aura.
I feel like I'm standing on fire.
It's interesting and cool.
It was really fun to see the lyrics and
the cards.
I was like, oh, this and this are in the
same place.
This is really amazing.
About two years ago, my favorite
artist's album came out.
I was so excited that I couldn't wait
until the CD was played.
I started reading the lyrics first, and
I read it as a reader.
I was like, oh, I know. I'm going to do
this album.
I was like, oh, I don't know. I like it.
I think I love lyrics so much.
The lyrics written by the rapper of the
word.
Especially, it's a blue hub.
When it becomes a blue hub, it's the
best to listen to it as music.
That was a lot of time.
That alone would be too much for my
brain.
The organ is really cool, so I want to
get up even if I'm called to.
So I call it in three steps,
and listen to it while staying still.
Then I listen to it while moving.
I listen to it while living.
That was a lot of time.
I feel like I'm being taught how to
enjoy Creepy Nut.
That's nice.
The people who influenced me, the Rhyme
Star,
have a lot of fun lyrics.
When I was in middle school,
I thought of people who had nothing to
do with me.
Like Jibura, Hanya, and so on.
I think the world I've lived in is a bit
different.
It's fun to listen to and I can be proud
of myself,
but I've lived my life as a rapper, so I
don't think I have any right to do that.
But if you listen to Rhyme Star with a
little more attention, you'll think,
maybe these people have done something
really ridiculous.
So, what brand is downtown paranoia?
It's a hook that says,
I'm a noisy analog record,
I'm serious when I'm around,
I'm a little bit of a talker,
I'm an amateur,
I don't care, I'm a
little bit of a talker,
but it's a hip-hop weapon, and it's a
very basic part.
It's not about the back bone or the
tail,
but it's about being in any position,
wherever you are born.
It's about having the transfer of your
ideas, your ideas, and the flexibility
of your head.
That's what I thought was the best part
of hip-hop.
I can't even play MAMI-D's Neko Funja,
but I can play IN Funja, you're a rhymer
too.
So I was like, oh, that's fine.
Then Utamaru-san said on the radio,
hip-hop is a culture that requires a
response from the listener,
and that the listener is a big factor in
promoting action.
So I always ask him,
I think this way, and what do you do?
There is a side that asks me that.
I was influenced by the great maturism.
I couldn't wait to sing it.
So I thought it was okay to do it.
I thought it was cool to listen to it.
I thought you liked it.
I thought you wanted to do it.
Then it's up to you.
I felt like that.
I thought it was okay to do it.
That's the great maturism.
That's a great start.
Did you start writing?
I wrote it myself after listening to
this song.
I started writing it because of this
song.
I didn't think it was cool to write
something like this.
But I didn't think I could do something
like that.
That's how I wrote it at first.
Aren't you scared of fighting?
I was scared. But I had a big one.
I tried to draw it myself, sing it in
karaoke, and imitate it.
And I was told,
You're good at it.
Wow.
I was praised by people, but I didn't
really have that point.
When I was told,
I was like,
I'm a good guy.
I'm good.
I'm glad that things like this exist.
Maybe I wouldn't have been able to stand
on the same level as people in sports
and study.
If it was rap, I might have been able to
compete with people.
Or if I was lucky, I might have won.
I found that in my life.
At first, I wanted to make a song or do
a live performance.
High Shield
There was a place where I could sing my
own rap more easily than that.
That's how I got into MC Battle.
I got into MC Battle when I was in high
school.
Oh, you were in high school.
Yes, I was.
That was the first time.
Wow.
But I lost a lot at first.
I was disappointed that I was supposed
to be good and strong, but I lost.
So I decided to raise my name.
I think the first time I had a career
was when I was with MC Battle, whether
it was good or bad.
I really respect that.
Thank you for watching.
I'd like to talk about Matsunaga-san.
You know, in MC battles, RCT is the
champion.
I've read in the papers that I have to
stand on the same podium.
I was asked when I became the world DJ
champion of DMC.
It was 2019. Two years ago.
There was no
I think it's crazy that he's going to a
competition where creepy nuts are
becoming famous.
I think he's doing a crazy thing.
When I was on MCBAT, we both didn't have
jobs, and we could focus on that.
We were trying to make it a name for
ourselves.
But the challenge in 2019 was that we
were super busy with Creepy Nuts,
and we had to choose between doing a
live performance or writing a song.
So we stepped into something that we
couldn't do in the beginning.
Yeah, we did.
And we pulled just off from what we can,
we played the Infinite Peaks and went
all!
I think it was really good.
But at first, like me,
when I started DJing,
I thought, maybe I could do better than
others.
That was the first time I found
something like that.
I thought I started it with my own
choice.
I used to be a DJ.
I used to play soccer.
I was in the first year of high school,
and I played for 7 years.
The reason why I started playing soccer
was because I was in the first year of
elementary school, and I was in the
first year of middle school.
I didn't choose soccer because I wanted
to be a soccer player.
I just wanted to be around people who
like soccer and get into the team.
I just didn't quit until I was in middle
school.
But when I was in the first year of high
school, I got a job with my own will.
When I was working on the turntable, it
was so much fun.
I wondered why it was so fun and I was
so into it.
I thought I had chosen this body
completely by my own will.
And what I really like is that I want to
think and act.
In order to get better, I have to think
about the angle of my hand, the angle of
my hand, and the angle of my hand.
I have to think about it.
You have more imagination when you are
enjoying your efforts.
I have more imagination when I am
enjoying my efforts.
My friends told me that I was good even
though I was a DJ.
I was told that I was young but good in
my hometown.
So my identity became that I was a good
DJ.
I went to the D&C for the first time.
I won the regional tournament at the age
of 19 or 20.
I went to the final in Japan.
I went to a good place.
But I really couldn't make a few minutes
without spending time, mental strength,
and everything.
I couldn't do that.
But I wanted to make a song and have a
live performance.
I wanted to be a musician.
I wanted to show the identity of DJ Mai.
But I couldn't keep my love for DJ Mai.
So I gave up on DJing.
I started making music.
I wanted to be a DJ and join the music
industry.
I've been doing this for a few years.
But while I was away, everyone around me
got better.
It was so hard for me to keep going.
I used to delete all my DMC followers on
Twitter.
I did that physically.
If I didn't do that, I'd be dragged down
by DMC.
Music activities are not that easy to
do.
It's a miracle that I can't eat.
I tried to delete it somehow.
After all, going out is hell.
It's a miracle that I can't eat.
I was wondering why it was so hard at
this time.
But I met a certain person and started
music activities together.
The more I got involved in the activity,
the more I got angry at what I was
doing.
And I was already a three-time Japanese
rapper.
After all, if I can put it on various
radios and upload it on my profile,
it will be a three-time Japanese rapper
Alisha and Matsudaira.
That's why I'm so attached to it.
If you don't expect it, you can accept
it.
But I'm a good DJ.
I'm good at what I have.
I thought that
I might not be able to make it
if I don't get it somewhere.
I got second place in 2016, and I lost
second place in Japan.
And also during the time I breaks...
I've been doing this for 4 or 5 years.
But I felt I was going to lose.
And I thought I could win.
I got second place in Japan, so I had
hope.
So I couldn't stop.
I was fighting to get rid of my curse
and cross.
I wasn't on the road full of hope.
Before I got to the DMC,
or before I realized that I was a good
DJ,
I wanted to go back to the way I was.
I realized that,
so I had to get first place.
I got first place in 2016 and 2017.
I dropped to third place in 2017.
I wasn't doing well at that time.
I didn't say I would be in the
tournament because I had a risk against
Creepiness.
If I didn't say I would be in the
tournament, I wouldn't have known I
would be in the tournament when I lost.
So I took the risk and challenged
myself.
I was the one who was the most damaged
as Creepiness.
But I was really depressed when I lost.
I was always being punished by my own
people.
I didn't care if people around me said I
should go.
I thought I wasn't angry.
I was eliminated in 2019.
I was physically exhausted and I
couldn't keep up with the routine.
I was so exhausted that I couldn't eat
anything.
I thought I would be exhausted.
I thought I would finish this year and I
had to finish somewhere.
I thought I could carry the curse
forever if I lost.
I was so angry.
I started the radio and said I would be
on it.
Everyone left and I was eliminated.
I said I'd make him the champion, and he
came out.
It's amazing.
And by becoming the world champion,
we can become stronger with equal
feelings,
and we can work as a stronger Creepy
Nut.
That's amazing.
It's a story with a lot of future.
Thank you for watching.
I've been fighting myself for a long
time, and I've been winning.
But now I feel like I'm fighting for
someone else.
I'm fighting for people through my music
and lyrics.
I really felt that this year.
I'm not a big deal.
I'm just a regular guy.
I didn't do anything at school.
I know what I'm doing the best.
I can't believe the situation we're in
right now.
I can make music and make a DJ.
I can do a tour, a dance, a tour.
I've never thought about becoming a TV
host.
I'm just a regular guy.
I couldn't believe everything that
happened.
I didn't know what I wanted next.
I thought I had no limitless thoughts.
I realized I didn't have any.
But at that moment...
I was so desperate.
I felt the fun in every day.
I was so happy and I was so happy.
I knew in my head that I was being
pushed forward.
But I didn't want anything.
I didn't know where to go from here.
I felt like I was alive but I was dead.
I was so happy when I was a DJ.
I believed that I had the purity to run
through until the end.
DJs are people who love to do things.
I thought that if I did that, I could
stay healthy.
But I also thought that there was
something I wanted to win.
I was greedy, but my greed was over.
I lost my goal and it was really hard.
I always thought that I should fight
alone.
I quit in high school and started DJing.
I made many choices to make my own
music.
I didn't make decisions with anyone.
I wanted to be a reliable partner.
I thought I had never made a partner who
would be able to be with me without any
external relationships.
I had come across all of them as my work
partner, and I was alone.
I thought I had no choice but to have a
human relationship to make it happen.
Then I realized that I was the only one
who was on the track of my activities.
I was able to make a team without being
alone.
When you think of socializing and
relationships,
you think of hip-hop as something that's
being ignored.
When you become who you are,
you realize that there's someone who's
been there for a long time.
I'm already here, though.
I have to go back.
What do you think?
I think it's a good thing.
You should be able to feel Matsumoto's
state.
I feel that he is very sensitive and he
is a person who is very objective in
looking at things objectively and making
a decision against his own feelings.
I still don't understand myself.
I can still express myself in a way that
is not organized.
But I think Matsudana's personality is
very stoic.
He doesn't care about his feelings.
I think he has a lot of feelings.
I'm grateful to the people around me.
At that time, I thought that everyone
was doing the same thing.
I want to make a song, put it on the
live, and put it on the TV.
I'm the manager of an agency.
The situation is different, but I think
it's the same.
I'm really going around in circles,
I'm thinking, I'm aware of people,
and I'm bringing a job.
And the other day, we're writing songs
and writing lyrics.
And I think it's a live performance
that we're presenting to us.
I don't think I can take responsibility
for that.
I don't know.
We're all women in the back, so we're in
the back when we're wearing makeup and
clothes.
But at that time, the stylist and the
makeup artist and the manager were the
real deal.
I wanted to have the imagination for
that.
That's what I thought.
I thought I was a good person.
I was a dead man, but I was able to see
the things around me.
I was able to hurt myself.
I think it's very realistic to be
honest.
Being honest is very realistic.
I think it's very hip-hop.
I'm not doing hip-hop.
I think so. I heard about it today.