Please watch the video of Ebichu!
I'm going to eat sushi!
Sushi, Mayama
I like sushi.
I think I like sushi at the level of a
normal human being.
I don't go to sushi restaurant often.
I think sushi is a reward.
What is your favorite story?
I always eat salmon roe.
What is the most memorable thing you
have done with the members?
I don't think I've ever been there in
private.
I think it was when I was on a trip with
Mirei.
I think we went to Harazawa together on
a front-row seat.
I was asked to take sushi to the
principal at that time.
It was delicious.
I can't forget the taste of the crab at
that time.
It was delicious.
What is your favorite food?
I haven't eaten much recently.
I'm relying on Uber.
My favorite food is cabbage.
I love NAKOZAKAWA.
I was fishing and fishing.
What was it during the self-restraint
period?
My mother bought me fish.
I did only the work of removing the
gills.
I admired the YouTuber KIMAGURE COOK.
I've been watching him for a long time,
so I wanted to touch the fish.
I did that.
I have never done it.
This is my first time.
Can you catch fish with a rice ball?
I'm not confident, but I want to enjoy
it.
I prepare the sushi, scoop it, and shape
it with one hand.
Then I scoop it, put wasabi on it, and
eat it.
Now, I'd like to introduce the teacher
who will teach us how to grip sushi.
I'm Hideki Sugiura, and I'm a sushi
master.
Today, I'd like to ask Mr. Sugiura to
teach us.
He will teach us how to grip, roll
sushi, and roll sushi.
And I'd like to ask Mr. Fujii to eat the
sushi I gripped.
I'll do my best to grip sushi.
I'll show you how to do it.
This is a piece of sushi that has been
cut and soaked in water.
Put your hand on it and spread it out.
Then, take the rice.
After taking the rice,
hold the neta on this side.
Put the wasabi on the neta and put the
rice on top.
It's a round thing like this.
Adjust the length and hold it once.
Then, turn it over and hold it again.
Turn it 180 degrees and hold it again.
Then, take it out.
This is the general way.
I'll do it.
Take it as quickly as possible and roll
it.
Roll it.
Put the wasabi on the neta.
Turn it 180 degrees.
Then, take it out.
It's finally in shape.
I'll try to eat sushi that I gripped for
the first time.
I did it well.
How is it?
I'll eat it.
Put the wasabi on the neta.
Hm..
Yes.
The ingredients are delicious, so it's
delicious.
I think I need a little less rice.
It's delicious. The ingredients are
delicious.
I'll do my best.
The thin roll is a rolling pin.
There is a back side.
Put the seaweed on it.
The rice is...
Is this too much?
I think it's more than a rice ball.
Yes.
Wow, that's enough.
Put this on the left end.
Left end.
Hold it with your right hand and spread
it with your left hand.
That's too fast.
Do this.
Yes.
Stretch it all over.
I see.
Put wasabi on it.
It's vivid.
Great.
Then put the ingredients on it.
Yes.
Hold the end.
Don't let it fall in the middle.
Put this on it.
Yes.
I'll show you the base.
Turn this 90 degrees.
Oh!
Wait a minute, this is difficult.
Isn't this more difficult than before?
I agree. I can't remember it all.
But let's try it.
I'll do my best.
First, I'd like to cut the net.
I cut one net very thin.
I'll check the back of the net.
Oh, it's time to eat.
Welcome.
Thank you for watching.
It's difficult.
I'm sure we didn't have enough rice.
It's really harder than it looks.
It's easier to watch.
From the right to the left.
Hand.
With both hands.
Like this.
I'm going to cut the rolls.
1, 2, 3.
I've gone to 3.
I couldn't do it well at the end.
Yes.
Thank you.
I did it.
It's done.
I'm going to do the same thing as
before, without putting anything in.
I'm going to make it into a sushi shape
and put the seaweed around it.
It looks delicious.
I don't know if it's easy, but I'm not
doing it.
I don't think it's easy, but it looks
delicious.
I want to eat it.
This is the point.
I'm going to challenge the military.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12,
13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20.
It's hard to get the rice to stick to
the pan.
That's a lot.
Sorry.
That's good.
You need to take 1.5 times more.
But it looks good.
I did it!
The price is 1.5 times higher.
Next, I'd like to compare the two.
I said that I'd like to have the squid
eaten by the head chef, but I'd like to
have the squid.
I'd like to have the squid, which is a
little too greedy for the squid and a
little too much.
I'll eat it.
But it's delicious.
I put too much salmon roe.
I can tell by eating.
It's not that you should put too much
salmon roe.
I'd like to have the master's.
I'll eat it.
It's delicious.
The balance between the rice and the
ingredients is delicious.
I felt that the balance between the rice
and the ingredients is really important,
even if it is one military canteen.
It's delicious.
Put the knife in the middle like this.
It's beautiful. Hello.
Now you can hold it.
Please take it out.
Now I'm going to hold the shrimp.
First, I'll put the shrimp on the rice.
I think it's going to cut.
It's going to cut.
Yes, that's good.
I opened this.
I can stand up.
Yes.
I think it's a fate that blooms.
This is a little more.
Help me a little.
Thank you for your viewing.
Thank you very much!
With the help of my master, I was able
to cut the shrimp!
The tip was difficult.
Excuse me.
This is difficult.
I forgot the steps.
What?
Like this, and this, and this.
Turn it, hold it sideways, and from the
top.
Yes, yes.
And?
Turn it the other way.
Like this?
Yes.
It's a little bit broken.
It's hard, but I did it.
I'll go to the bathroom.
I'll make a shape, and then...
Then...
Yes!
Thank you for watching!
Oh, that's good.
Okay, I'll be waiting!
This is hard.
I barely got the sweet shrimp.
Yeah, the car shrimp...
You should have put in a little less.
Oh, there were too many.
But it's hard.
There were too many.
This is the real one.
The real one.
The ones in the sushi restaurants are
called white-tailed sea breams.
Oh, I see.
This is a pretty expensive sushi.
The sea bream has a lot of wasabi, so
put in a little less.
A little less.
It's getting smaller.
It's moving.
It's moving!
I'll show you a trick.
Excuse me.
Pull it with a clip.
I did it.
Put the knife in three times.
I'll show you a trick.
Thank you for watching!
Well, yeah.
Nice!
Oh, I hit my leg.
I've been taught that I can do it many
times.
Let's do it again.
Oh, nice!
So, here's the real thing.
Hey!
It didn't shrink a bit.
It didn't shrink, but it became a very
gentle shape.
I'm going to make a Thai style.
Welcome.
I'd like a Thai, please.
Thai, Thai, Thai.
Certainly.
I'm going to make it.
I'm so nervous.
I'm getting nervous from the beginning.
I'm more nervous than any of the recent
games.
I'm going to try it.
It's good.
I'm looking forward to it.
I might post this on my Instagram.
I'll try it.
It's good.
Thank you.
It's a little thick.
I sang a flower song.
I'm waiting for the room.
It's delicious.
Thank you.
Please watch the next video.
Oh, so you don't use a lot of chili.
That's right.
But if I wanted to make her cry, I'd put
a lot on.
Oh, so you're going to put a lot on.
I'll see how it goes.
I've heard that people eat a lot of
wasabi and dried fish rolls when they
drink.
What is it?
It's nothing.
A lot of wasabi and dried fish rolls.
I see.
You like it.
I don't have it at the store.
You can make dried fish rolls with dried
fish.
Really?
He doesn't react at all.
He was in a bad mood today.
I'm waiting.
It's like a small piece of art.
It's like an object.
The crispy texture and the unique
sweetness of the shellfish are very
delicious.
Thank you.
Then, add more wasabi to the Kanpyo
roll.
Add more wasabi than you can imagine.
I see.
I'm not kidding.
Add a lot.
Yes.
Please put a lot of wasabi.
This is going to be a lot of work.
Are you sure?
I heard you like it.
Take it out and shape it.
Like this.
Okay.
One, two, three.
Hey, what's up?
I love the smell of ginger.
How is it?
It's delicious.
I'm glad. Thank you.
It's strong. Wasabi is strong.
I put a lot of wasabi in it.
It's strong.
The kante-matsu is delicious.
Thank you.
It's good.
Oops, it's too small.
Wait a minute.
A little more.
I'll eat it.
Eat up.
It's sweet and delicious.
We use good ingredients.
I'd like to have 10 bowls of rice.
What?
10 bowls of rice?
Please go to a seafood bowl restaurant.
I was training at a sushi restaurant
called Mayama.
It's hard to make sushi.
It's really hard to make sushi.
It was difficult to balance all the
ingredients.
I practiced for a long time.
But I couldn't do it well in the actual
performance.
I learned that if I master the first
skill of my right hand, I can make sushi
better.
I'd like to practice at home and make a
great sushi restaurant.
It was fun.
I was happy to have someone eat my
sushi.
I'm sorry I'm not confident in my sushi.
I had a very grateful experience.
Please go to a sushi restaurant.