I'm coming in.
It's so pink.
So pink.
It reminds me of my mom's belly.
I feel nostalgic.
This color.
Mom.
It's so pink.
I didn't do anything.
Hello, this is Taku Okazaki.
Who am I?
Hello?
Who are you?
Who am I?
Wait a minute.
Who are you?
I can't understand you at all.
Hello?
Please speak a little more.
What?
Who are you?
Do you know who I am?
Who am I?
Who is this?
Are you really small?
Really small?
How old are you?
I'm 7 years old.
7 years old?
Yes.
7 years old acquaintance?
Could it be...
Emma-chan?
That's correct.
It's Emma-chan!
How are you?
I'm fine.
Really?
You're already in elementary school?
Yes.
You're in first grade?
First grade.
You're in first grade.
Really?
Emma-chan called me today.
Yeah.
Wow.
How's your dad, Yuma?
How's your dad?
Yeah, he's fine.
He's fine? Are you?
How's Emma-chan?
She's fine.
Really? How about you, Nacchan?
Nacchan is fine too.
Nacchan is fine too?
You're so funny.
I didn't think you were Emma-chan.
Emma-chan, you haven't been getting
along with her much.
When was the last time you met her?
Recently, she hasn't been meeting me.
She hasn't been meeting you?
Don't say things like that.
Is there anything fun at school?
Not really?
I enjoy exploring schools.
You do?
I like exploring places that I don't
know about.
I like exploring places.
You like exploring places that you don't
know about.
Do you go alone? Or with your friends?
I go with my friends during my break.
You go during your break?
So you don't go to school to explore,
but you do it yourself?
Yes.
That's amazing!
You go to school to explore?
Even if I go to a place I don't know
about...
There's a staircase, and if you go down,
you just have to go down there.
Down there? What do you mean? Wait, let
me explain it in more detail.
There's a staircase, and if you go down
there, you're good to go? What do you
mean?
The first floor is the first year's
classroom.
Yeah. And if you go to the sixth grade,
you won't know where you're going.
That's right. If you go to the sixth
grade...
If there's a staircase, there's
definitely a staircase.
There's a staircase, and there's a...
There's a staircase that leads to the
bottom.
There's definitely a staircase.
If there's a staircase,
you can go back to the teacher.
That's right. That's definitely true.
The first year's class is definitely
once.
soulsick
So if there's a staircase, you can go
down it and you'll definitely reach the
first floor.
You can go back to your classroom.
That's perfect. That compass. Self-
Compass.
What's a compass?
A compass is something you can use to
understand your direction.
It's something you need to explore or
explore.
What? Ema-chan?
What? What?
Do you understand what a compass is?
What are you talking about?
A compass.
A compass?
You don't need more information about a
compass anymore?
Have you ever thought that you don't
need more information about a compass in
your life?
What are you talking about?
What?
Let's forget about the compass.
What are you doing when you come back
from school?
When I come back from school, I'm going
to school.
You're going to school already?
Yeah.
That's amazing.
I can't even think of it.
You're going to school?
Yeah, I'm learning three things.
You're learning three things?
But...
What are you doing?
I'm going to school.
I'm going to dance, play the piano, and
play the spider.
Dance, play the spider, and play the
piano?
Yeah.
You're over the level of your education.
Why are you laughing?
You're making me angry.
You're going to dance and play the
piano?
That's why you're studying at Kumon,
right?
Yeah.
You can dance, Emma-chan?
Really?
Hey, A-kun...
You're doing music, right?
What?
A-kun, you're doing music, right? At
work.
Yeah.
And you're making songs, so...
You're making videos, so...
So, A-ma, go back to work.
It's difficult.
Difficult?
Maybe it's an office-like meaning.
It doesn't match with the music of the
Okazaki Taiku.
Hema-chan's dance.
Do you need to study?
What are you suddenly doing?
Study?
Yes.
Do you think you need to study?
I think there are people who need it and
people who don't.
I don't need it.
What do you think, Emma? Do you think
you need it?
Hmm... I don't need it.
You don't need it?
Yeah.
Why don't you think you need it?
Because the teacher's voice is too loud.
The teacher's voice is too loud?
I see.
But you know, you don't have to study
for sure.
But if you do...
It's amazing how it helps when you
become an adult.
And Akkun wasn't very good at math,
right?
Yeah.
Even when you become an adult, you use
math, like what my grandma used to say.
Yeah, what my grandma used to say.
You have to calculate money!
Yeah, when you become an adult, you
start to think about money.
When you can't calculate money,
you start to think about the tax issue.
It's really hard to find a tax attorney.
Emma's parents are also a hair stylist.
If you're a hair stylist, you have to do
all the business yourself.
The sales and sales expenses of the
shop.
If you can't calculate those things,
it's going to be really hard in the
future.
So I think the calculation is very
important.
Thank you for your viewing.
Yeah. And Akku likes money.
Akku likes money?
Wait a minute.
Is there someone behind you?
There's your dad.
Your dad or your mom?
Wait a minute.
Do you like money?
You like money, right?
I like it.
Hahaha.
Of course, music is...
I'm doing music for the sake of many
people, so I don't think about money.
When I'm doing music.
By making music for many people,
I don't know why, but I think I'm
getting money.
I don't know why, but when a lot of
people sing my songs in karaoke, it's
like a system where I get money.
I don't know why this is the system, but
when people make music and sing it, I do
it with all my heart.
I don't need money.
There's a way to get money.
Yeah.
So if you ask me if I like money,
I don't really like it.
I just feel like it's coming to me.
But I just told you.
What? What?
I just told you.
I told you I like money.
You said you like money?
I guess I was just saying.
I just felt like it was coming to me.
I think I just said it.
I don't like money.
Emma, do you like money?
Yeah.
You like money, huh?
I don't like the smell of money.
The smell of money is like
a physical smell or
a police story?
The smell of money is like
a smell of gold?
Yeah, because if you smell it, you'll
get a lot of money.
A lot of money? That's too much. You
can't get that close.
Money, money.
You need to have enough money to get
into your nose.
And you know, it's a different story.
There was a really hard time at school.
Oh, what is it? Let's solve it.
A friend of mine is a really good
I don't know why, but he's a really good
guy.
There are a lot of people who are
injured recently.
injured? Why? Where are they going?
Are they going to a school for the army?
Why are they injured? Is Emma injured?
I'm not injured.
Emma is not injured, but all your
friends are injured?
Yeah, I just pinched my finger.
You pinched your finger, Emma?
Yeah. But there are people who are
already injured.
There are people who are already
injured?
Yeah.
Why? That's what you're talking about.
You want them to do something about it?
Yeah.
How do you do that?
So, when do you get injured?
When you're playing? When you're playing
dodgeball?
Maybe. But everyone is outside.
I was playing and when I came back from
my break,
the security guards were playing with
the kids.
Why?
They were playing with the kids.
They were playing with the kids? They
were getting hot.
Why?
They were playing with the kids and they
were getting hot.
That's crazy.
You were on leave.
Oh...
I would like to throw a..
I would like to throw a friend like me?
For like...
...when in need, using alO賈 friend on
the back of your car and stuff...
...you would be in a difficult
situation, don't you?
Yeah
Yeah, it's better to help Emma.
Yeah, I'm helping for sure.
Really?
Are you?
Of course.
Oh! I'm sorry.
It was really eerie.
Yeah
Really?
Uh...
Yeah
It was the 식 seat next to it.
Oh, it's the next seat. You should
definitely do that.
Yeah.
Is that a boy?
It's a girl.
Oh, it's a girl.
I see.
Is she your friend? Emma-chan?
Friend?
Oh, she's your friend.
Then you should help her.
Yeah.
If you help her when she's in trouble,
she'll help you when you're in trouble.
Yeah.
That's how society works.
Life.
If you're in trouble...
Yeah. でもまたなんか次の日来たら... Yeah.
でもまたなんか次の日来たら... Yeah. 何かうん。 And then
the next day... 怪我が長いんだよその子達が。 Yeah.
怪我が長いんだよその子達が。 What do you mean by long?
何が長いって? What do you mean by long?
怪我が長いんだよ続くのが。 Yeah. 怪我が長いの? 怪我が長いの?
怪我が長いの? 怪我が長いの? 怪我が長いの? 怪我が長いの? 怪我が長いの?
怪我が長いの? 怪我が長いの? 怪我が長いの?
What do you mean? 中能力がすごい低いんかな? That
kid. 中能力がすごい低いんかな? That kid.
Then... ではさぁ... Then...
Then... なんかさぁ...
Then... なんかさぁ... 違う話だね。 That's not it.
違う話だね。
What does it mean to grow up?
成長になるってどういうことな?
成長になるってどういうことか?
Yeah. 成長になるってどういうことか?
What does it mean to grow up?
成長になるって言うのは
Yeah. 成長になるって言うのは
When you make music, 音楽を作った時に
When you make music, お金のことが
お金のことが 頭に散らつくってことや。
you get a lot of money. 頭に散らつくってことや。
いや、それ大人になる証拠なの?
そう、これが大人になる証拠。
アックンは最近、もう32歳になってんけど、
音楽作った瞬間に、自分のCDのセールスのこととか、
印税のことを考え、お金のことを考えちゃうの。
これが大人になるってこと。
絶対わからんといて、こんなこと。
うんって言わんといて、もはや。
はいはい。
ふーん。
I'm sorry.
You look like a couple before you broke
up.
Do you have any questions for me?
You have questions for Emma?
I wonder if you have any.
Did you eat dinner already?
Yes.
No, I haven't eaten anything.
You haven't eaten?
You haven't eaten anything?
Are you hungry?
I'm hungry.
Huh?
Your dad?
Ema's dad?
You...
You scared me.
Ema called you.
What's going on?
Do you know who it is?
I do.
I need a hint.
It's Ema's dad, right?
Ema?
Correct.
I thought you were definitely a
musician.
Speaking of that, I'm surprised.
Why?
Why did you ask me to work with you?
I'm not usually like that.
I was surprised.
Emma-chan called me and said,
Who am I?
That's not what I meant.
I didn't know who you were.
That was a success.
I was surprised.
Emma-chan, you seem to be worried about
something.
I'm worried.
Your school friend is...
...following you.
He's got a bone in his throat.
To be continued...
That's because I was shocked by the
sudden appearance of the
bone in my mouth. 俺も衝撃だったから。
You were shocked too? 俺も衝撃だったから。
Yeah. 俺も衝撃だったから。
Your daughter's classroom is cursed.
呪われてるぞお前の娘の。
I wonder if I can break my bones.
骨折れちゃうかな。
Your daughter's classroom is cursed.
呪われてるぞお前の娘の教室呪われてるぞ。
I'd rather have it transferred.
そのうち折れるぞ。
Ema-chan too. エマちゃんも。
I'm surprised. びっくりした。
You're making me do too much learning.
習い事させすぎちゃう?
That's normal. 普通だね。
Is that how kids are these days?
Yeah, the times have changed.
They were talking about dance, piano,
and kumon.
Is it like 3rd grade?
Yeah, I think it's around 4th grade.
Yeah, it's around 4th grade.
Yeah, but they need dance.
They need it for elementary school kids.
But it's like a new gift.
I haven't seen you in a while.
I want to buy you something.
I'm thinking about what toy you want.
But I don't have anything I want.
Anything is fine. Something fun.
Anything is fine if it's fun.
If it's fun, anything is fine.
The difficulty will go up.
I see.
It's a little difficult.
Oh, that's...
Don't you watch Love Patrina? Emma-chan.
Love Patrina? I'm not interested.
You're not interested? No way.
Because when you say Love Patrina,
you're interested in her.
No.
You're going backwards.
Because I have love in me.
You don't know if you have love in you?
I don't know.
It's like a brick.
What?
So, what's your new song?
What's your new song?
It's a completely different story.
A new song.
I released a new song called オッサン.
Oh, a song with a lot of old men.
Old men.
Yeah, I released a song called オッサン.
Then sing it now.
Sing a dance for me.
I told you to do it, so sing it now.
You're the same as your local friends.
I told people to dance, but I didn't.
Dance?
Dance is...
Dance!
Dance! Sing!
Sing?
While dancing.
Emma-chan, listen.
Old man, old man, I've already become an
old man.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
It's going to be like that.
I'm always following origami.
You're following origami?
It's okay. I'm listening to you. I'm
listening to you with one hand.
Ossan! Ossan! Higejorijori!
You're singing along.
You're already singing along.
My new song.
But songs that do that are popular
evidence.
They are popular evidence.
Ossan! Ossan! Higejorijori!
Higejorijori!
You're laughing.
Higejori...
Ah...
Higejorijori. Not bad.
Ema, do you have a crush on someone at
school?
No.
You're kidding!
You do have a crush on someone, don't
you?
No.
You never tell anyone.
Really?
You're so stubborn.
I've never seen a guy like you.
Oh, really?
I've done the most ridiculous thing.
You've said that you really have a crush
on someone.
I've never said that I really have a
crush on someone.
In this day and age.
Wow, I'm so mean.
You're so selfish.
You're the king of self-defense.
I'm glad you learned it.
I'm sure you won't ask me if there's
anyone you like in school.
But if you ask me once and say there's
no one, I'll say there's no one.
Then you'll say, no way, there's
someone.
Is this the old man?
Why are you calling me so long?
I'm sorry. Say bye bye.
Bye bye.
Bye bye. See you later.
See you later.
Bye bye.
That was a mistake.