Oh, I'm shooting a video with a camera.
Good morning.
Today, I'm in a girl's land.
I cut my hair.
So, I think it's short.
There are many short hair around here.
I'm sorry to Meki-san when I do twin
tails.
Today, I'm doing twin tails.
I usually do twin tails with comfortable
clothes.
But, I'm doing twin tails with cute
clothes today.
I did my hair and makeup.
I'm like a girl before I met her.
I'm shaking.
I wanted to do a twin tail.
But, I didn't have time.
But, I got a hair cut by Meki-san.
I put glitter on orange nails.
Many people say that I'm pretty.
I'm happy.
I cut my nails yesterday.
But, my nails are short.
So, I think I'll cut my nails.
Hey, guys.
I'm talking to you.
Are you lonely?
No, it's okay.
I haven't forgotten about you.
I'm going to the bathroom.
I was hungry today, but I ate breakfast.
I'm looking forward to today.
I want to enjoy it.
See you later.
Good morning.
Today is Girls' Land 2022.
Endless costume!
I miss it!
This is cute.
This is Endless costume of 2nd place.
I think I was wearing a ponytail at that
time.
I think it's good that the atmosphere of
the How How Club is different.
I changed my phone.
14.
There's a limited live performance for
girls.
There's a new outfit.
I think you've seen this before.
The new outfit is cute.
It's a retro girl.
A retro girl.
It's cute.
If you haven't seen it, you'll be
surprised.
I hope I get to wear this kind of outfit
again.
I'm so excited to wear this after a long
time.
I'm waiting for the lunch box to arrive.
It looks like it's not here.
Bye bye.
Ta-da!
Today's lunch box.
I'm going to eat breakfast.
I'm hungry.
I'm going to eat.
So I just finished my hair and makeup,
so I'm going to the store.
Look at this. This is the nail polish
I'm wearing today.
It's a little orange. I'm going to wear
three nails today, so I'm going to wear
three nails.
Cute. And bear hair. It's still a little
bit of a temporary condition.
It's been a while since I wore Endless's
costume. I'm happy.
Thank you.
I'm not supposed to jump.
I'm not supposed to jump, but I'm
supposed to do it this time.
It's okay to jump, but be careful not to
touch the ground.
I'm the one who's going to fall.
It hurts!
If you jump, you have to go forward.
But I'm scared, so I don't go forward.
I'll be careful.
I'd like to start rehearsing.
Please give us a warm welcome.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
Rock on!
We are Super Kimi-chan and NiziU.
Thank you.
Thank you for watching!
Hayagaya is the best!
It's wonderful!
Is there anything else?
No?
No.
Thank you for the rehearsal.
Please give us a good performance.
It's 12.32 now.
Today is the 13th and 14th.
Please give us a good performance.
The rehearsal is over.
Your bangs are so cute.
I'll do my best not to break the stage.
I'm a ponytail.
The rehearsal is over.
This outfit is so cute.
I like little girls.
I haven't seen my hair yet.
I want to see my hair with this.
Cute.
I did it with a
little girl.
It's a good image.
Cute.
Everyone has different sleeves.
Did it fall?
It's hard.
It's coming.
It's beautiful.
I'm hungry.
I'll eat bento.
I'll do my best.
Let's do our best.
I wonder if it's tied.
I'm 70% sure.
Dumplings are cute.
Endless night show.
I was going to change my clothes, but I
came out.
I'm hungry.
I want to eat something.
But I'm in love with you
My heart is overflowing
Feelings
BAM BAM BAM BAM BAM
Two hands
Suddenly you can call me
Everything
BAM BAM BAM BAM BAM
Cute
G prediction
I'll hold you tight
Hiyori's bangs!
Hitokawa's bangs!
It's all messed up today
I got it fixed
I couldn't come. It's been a while.
I'm sorry.
There's no one here.
Oh, no.
Let's change.
Ready, go!
We'll be back soon.
Are you ready to have fun?
Let's have fun with all the girls.
Let's have fun.
Please wait for us.
Tanami, Julia, Coco, Haruko, Aki, Hiyori
Super Tokimikusen全部
Canadians
The last group is the last group!
The last group!
So, yay!
The first group is over!
It's over!
Where is it?
I don't know where it is.
Is it right?
It's over.
This outfit is cute.
It's really cute.
We haven't seen the group.
When we were on the stage,
we were saying, Aki-chan,
it's really cute.
Hitomi is cute too.
Yorichan is like Babu-chan.
Kanami is like Babu-chan.
This part is a bit...
I wonder why.
Is it the collar?
It's open here.
When Ohayari touches her shoulder,
it's like she's a knight.
She's cool.
No!
The boys are watching this.
We'll do our best!
Bye bye!
We're going to rehearse.
We're going.
This time,
we're not late for the rehearsal,
so we're a bit late.
We're going to rehearse.
It's a strange outfit,
but it's the end.
My favorite costumes are the new girls'
land costumes and the mermaid costumes.
Today's dinner!
Ta-da!
Chinese food!
I was hungry at the last minute, so I'll
eat dinner before 2 o'clock and do my
best!
I'll eat now!
Thank you!
This is it for tonight.
Why do you always do that?
I don't think it's a good idea to be a
little bit of a bully.
Hurry up! Hurry up!
I'm not going to run away.
I'll do my best.
If you have any emergency, please follow
the instructions and evacuate.
Please cooperate.
We will be back soon.
Are you ready to have fun?
Thank you!
Let's go to the space where we can have
fun!
Thank you for coming!
One, two,
Please wait for us!
Kanami, Julia, Hitoko, Haruka, Aki,
Yorin,
Chou and Kimekusen, all lock on!
Thank you.
Please.
Thank you for your hard work!
We will be back with a new video soon,
so please come to see us again!
See you soon!
Bye!
Thank you for your hard work!
You are amazing, Rima-chan.
You are so cute!
Girls are cute!
Good job everyone!
It's over!
I was looking forward to it.
We were waiting for the girls.
It was amazing.
I was surprised.
I was surprised to see the girls from
the audience.
I was really happy.
We have two more to go.
We have one more.
We are getting older.
Yuu-chan, Yuu-chan.
We have a lot to do.
We still have a lot to do.
We will do our best.
We are a live band.
Thank you for looking forward to today.
Thank you.
To all the boys.
I want to be a part of this.
Are you feeling shy?
It's okay.
We are going to do our best.
We will never forget about you.
We love you.
Girls and boys.
Please love us.
We love you.
Thank you for coming to see us.
Thank you.
Bye.
The costumes are cute.
I love you.
Bye.
I'm shy.
I love you.
We finished Girls' Land.
Thank you.
How was it?
It was fun.
The stage was cute.
The opening was cute.
I like it.
I want everyone to see it.
The costumes are cute.
The ranking is cute.
This is the new costume.
We were able to perform at a close
distance.
When we talked, everyone was happy.
We were able to perform with a close
feeling.
It was fun.
We were able to perform in a different
atmosphere.
We will do our best.
We will do our best to increase the
number of girls.
I'm happy if we can increase the number
of girls.
We haven't forgotten about it.
Let's enjoy it together from now on.
See you later.
Don't be so late.
Bye bye.
Thank you for watching.
I want to share my feelings with you
The scenery that I don't know yet
Let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye
Thank you for yesterday
The city after the rain is colored
On the broken heart's canvas
I draw a piece of the future
Will you look at me?
I can say it now, the reason for my
tears
When you're lost, it's right there
I remember it, even if it rains
So that I can laugh, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye, yesterday's me
The city lights up, the waves shine
As if my heart is a clear pattern
I play the rainbow piano
With the sound of the rainbow
Goodbye, goodbye, yesterday's me
The city lights up, the waves shine
As if my heart is a clear pattern
I play the rainbow piano
I wear a rainbow dress
Thank you for watching!