Ebi-Chu videos
Happy New Year!
From the 31st through the 1st,
there was an opening ceremony that we
had a team to press.
So, that doesn't mean we were together
all day.
But, after that, there was a little
break.
What were you guys doing?
It's a shame, but I did it for the first
time in the New Year.
I was doing a countdown at night.
It was morning before I went home and
went to bed.
I watched the sunrise and slept.
Did you see the sunrise?
I woke up until then.
I woke up before 7 o'clock.
I watched the sunrise and slept.
It's been a long time since I slept.
It's New Year's Day.
I watched the sunrise.
I went home and had a big explosion.
I went home and had an adrenaline rush.
I told my mom that I was wearing it all
my life.
The next day I went out on the sofa.
I'm not saying that I'm going to bed.
Did you eat Osechi?
I ate Osechi.
There was a time when I didn't go out
much on New Year's Day.
I ate Osechi for three days.
I ate it all.
Do you eat Osechi now?
I eat it.
I've finally come to like the food in
Osechi.
When I was a kid, I couldn't eat
anything that I could eat.
I ate only Osechi.
I can eat black beans, too.
That's still impossible.
Katsunoko?
Kombu.
Yoro kombu.
Osechi is delicious.
I had a New Year's holiday eating mochi.
I ate a lot of mochi.
We forced ourselves to eat mochi.
I was forced to eat mochi.
But I had to eat mochi because I thought
it was New Year's Day.
I cut the mochi into small pieces.
I cut it into small pieces and ate it.
You ate the mochi.
I ate the mochi.
We all ate the mochi.
I ate it.
I couldn't eat only the apple.
I forced myself to eat it.
I ate it.
I was hungry and I didn't want to eat
it.
It was very small.
I became a professional.
I'm used to it.
MIRROR eats a lot of mochi every year.
Last year, we ate 20 pieces of mochi.
20 pieces in one day.
20 pieces of mochi.
I can eat a lot of mochi.
How big is the small one?
It's a normal size.
It's like Sato's Kirimochi.
I put mochi on a rice cake.
I can eat it.
It's delicious.
I like to eat freshly made mochi.
I spread a lot of mochi on the table.
What's the most difficult ingredient?
Natto, walnuts, sesame seeds.
I put the sauce on the rice cake.
I ate it.
You ate 20 pieces of mochi.
You ate too much.
I eat a lot of rice cake.
If you want to eat mochi, please try it.
Are you from Tohoku?
We are interested in the mystery of the
rice cake.
We will enjoy it next year.
That's right.
It's a case of various things.
I feel like watching a live performance.
I drank with my family.
It was morning when I realized it.
My family likes to drink.
You are close.
It was fun.
I was surprised.
Everyone was relaxed this year.
I was busy with university activities.
I was sleeping.
It's still New Year's Day.
This is the first video of the year.
I will challenge the laughter challenge.
Yay!
The end.
So, we have Fukuhara Ai here.
Let's do this one by one.
The person who gets the closest answer
is the prettiest one.
And the winner will get a gift.
Let's do our best.
So, please think of the correct answer.
Let's do this.
Let's concentrate.
The first one.
The second one.
I don't know.
Where is it?
There.
What? I'm scared.
I don't know if I'm right or not.
Here.
Where did you put it?
I'm scared.
What?
What is that?
I'll fix my hair.
I'll do it.
I'll cut it when you turn it over.
Okay.
I don't remember.
I'll cut it there.
That's my girl.
Oh!
Oh, this one.
The last one.
Ah, this one.
Ah, it's here.
Oh!
Mayama's Kuwarae is done.
Mayama, please take it.
Seri.
But,
The eyebrows are here.
But, the mouth and nose are
Ah, that's right.
Right?
Yes, then,
Next, it will be Mie-chan's challenge.
I will do my best to make a cute girl.
Then,
I will do it.
My hands...
After all, I want to be a little bit of
a
I want to be a little bit of a
Shaki.
Where is it?
This is that.
The mouth.
Oh, good.
Oh, I will go with that.
I see.
Yes, then,
Next, this one.
Thank you.
Are you looking at me?
I thought this was here.
Do it yourself.
Is it eyebrows?
Is it eyes?
I see.
Next, this one.
What is it?
This is an eye.
How is it?
It's almost done.
I see.
Next, this one.
Oh!
Is it done?
I have to put this on my eyebrows,
right?
Oh!
Then, the last one!
This is a nose.
Where is my lip?
Oh!
OK?
OK!
So, Mie's clothing is done.
This is crazy.
This is so artistic.
This is amazing.
This is so cool.
It's like a hot dog.
I made a hot dog style.
Then, Mie's is done.
Yes.
Next, Hinata's challenge.
Mie, please put on the mask.
I'll do my best.
I haven't done this much.
I don't remember.
What?
It's getting square.
The second one.
I'll do my best.
What is this?
Is it different?
Next is this.
Really?
Yes.
Oh, good.
Cute.
Really?
Next is this.
Yes, this.
This is good.
Yes.
Oh, oh, oh.
Like this?
Cute, cute.
The last one.
Yes.
Where is it?
Like this.
OK?
OK.
Please look at it.
What?
It's a little weird.
It's a little weird, but it's the
opposite of Mirei's.
Shinme.
It's a real Shinme.
It's true.
The position of the eyes is quite...
The nose is bent.
It's amazing.
It's like a cute sister.
It's a little weird.
It's difficult.
Next.
Kaho.
Everyone's eyes are now...
This is in the brain.
It's a good idea.
Really?
So I'm going to be a little bit like
that.
I'm going to be a little bit like that.
I can't see anything.
Please look at it.
This is the eye. Right eye? Left eye?
Oh!
That's good.
Next, Tsuboroshi.
There is probably a mountain here.
You're thinking about it very well.
I was aiming for it.
I want a drop.
It's not decided as a drop.
Isn't it a drop?
Maybe.
Please come.
Around here?
Oh!
I thought it was a drop.
If Mao-chan is around here, eh?
Mao-chan?
What is it?
Next.
I see.
It's a nose.
I can tell it's a nose by the shape.
This is probably the mouth.
The nose of the mouth.
This is Mao-chan.
Mao-chan is holding it now.
Oh!
And the last one.
The end.
How was it? Did you get it?
I think the golden ratio is the most
important thing.
Golden ratio.
Please look at it.
Where is the golden ratio?
The scene is just here.
Good.
The winner is...
The last one is the most important.
The last one is Riko.
How was it? You want to win, right?
I've seen four of them.
I can't feel anything.
I'm only confident.
I'm worried.
Please put on the mask.
First of all,
This one.
Thank you.
This is a mouth.
It's a nose.
That was close.
I thought it was a mountain.
Thank you for watching.
I'll adjust later.
Next.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
I'll adjust later.
Yes, later.
This is nose, and this is eyebrow.
I'll take it off.
Oh, this is eye.
Two left.
This is.
Thank you.
This is eyebrow.
Is that eye?
This is not eye.
New.
This is the last part.
I don't know anymore.
Why?
This is done.
I can't adjust.
Really good.
I don't know.
It's really dark.
Look at this.
Teront
I'm not sure if I can say this is a
battle.
This is cute.
That's the only cute thing.
Riko is...
This is cute. This is a eye.
It's not.
But it's fun.
Who will be the winner?
Now, everyone is a good at laughing.
It was so much fun.
It was fun.
It's not easy to do a good laugh.
That's right.
Everyone's face during the show.
It's good.
Next year.
I want to do it.
The person who was closest to the
original face during the show won.
I'm not sure if I can say this is a
battle.
Let's point out the person.
It doesn't matter if it's you.
I think everyone knows.
I don't know if you're going to be a
candidate.
One, two.
It's a good thing.
It was definitely me.
It was close.
I'll give you a luxurious product.
Is it okay?
I got it.
Starbucks.
Yeah.
Can I open it?
I'm opening it.
It doesn't work.
That's it.
It's a drinkable.
It's cute.
Starbucks card.
It's a drinkable.
Congratulations.
It was good.
It was fun.
Everyone, when the Fukuarai is released,
please buy it.
I don't know if it's really going to be
released.
Everyone's face parts.
It's going to be in various shapes.
There's a possibility it'll be.
It's fun.
Have a good year.
Thank you for your continued support
this year.