The next day
Hello
Welcome to the Spirited Away channel
You usually eat something, don't you?
Yes
But anything is fine, isn't it?
Do you really know that you are eating
it?
I think so.
I wonder how it is.
I will study about the difference of
food this time.
Then, I will start.
I will go to the toilet.
I will announce what I brought.
I brought cabbage and lettuce.
This is a difficult question.
I thought that people in general
wouldn't know the answer.
How do you feel? Are you confident?
I think I know the answer.
You think so?
I think I know the answer if I eat it.
I think I know the answer when I was
born.
I think I know the answer.
I think I know the answer when I was
born.
I think I know the answer.
I will decide which one is A and B.
This is A.
This is B.
I will start from Hikaru.
I will eat this.
It's delicious.
It's great.
How do you feel like a rabbit?
I don't know.
Did you get it?
Yes.
Next, Miyu.
It's narrow.
How is it?
I don't know.
Really?
This is A.
Next, B.
Next, Hikaru.
I see.
I got it.
I can see with my pterygium.
This is more delicious.
Next,
open your mouth.
Next?
What's your name?
Mr. Bean.
Open your mouth.
This is good too.
Really?
We have finished eating.
Please take off your eye masks.
Please write down what A is and what B
is.
I don't know what it is.
Ritsuki, please open it.
A. Cabbage. B. Lettuce.
I did it.
I wrote A. Cabbage. B. Lettuce.
The answer is...
A. Cabbage. B. Lettuce.
You are correct.
Did you get it?
Yes, I did.
What's the difference?
Cabbage is hard and lettuce is juicy.
I thought it was the opposite.
But most of my answers are wrong.
So I tried to make it the opposite.
I see.
I still think A is lettuce.
A is cabbage.
I see.
Yes.
Let's move on to the next food.
Let's...
Go...heaven?
Goheaven
The food I brought is...
Kanten and jelly!
It looks difficult.
I'm done!
Try to trick her.
With your spiritual power.
Can you tell by the looks?
I can tell by the way you draw.
The A is here and the B is here.
I see.
I got it.
You can move around even though you
can't see.
I'm using my spatial ability.
Wow.
Let's move on to the challenge.
Looks good.
This is B.
It's good.
Next.
Next is B.
I only buy bunnies.
Next is C.
It's good. But I don't know.
It's difficult.
Both were good.
Please tell us your answer.
I think A was dry.
It was slimy but dry.
A was sweeter.
It was sweet and good.
Please tell us your answer.
A was Kanju jelly.
B was Kanten jelly.
Kanju jelly?
It was sweat jelly.
Was it sweat?
It was sweat.
It was disgusting.
It was not.
This one?
Yes.
That was C.
It was Kanju jelly.
It was not balanced.
B was Kanten jelly.
Kanten jelly was not good.
I don't know.
I think it was this one.
It was this one.
It was cold.
Why was it cold?
Next is...
It's Umi.
I was wrong for the first time.
It's Miya.
It was opposite of her answer.
Kanten jelly.
Kanju jelly.
Kanji was on it.
Do you have the answer?
I don't have the answer.
I'll give you a hint.
It's going to be fun.
The answer is...
Please follow us on Twitter and
Instagram.
It's me!
I was worried.
I got it on my teeth.
Congratulations, Riru.
Thank you.
It's a great present.
Riru's present
You did a good job.
I brought...
Sardine miso soup and mackerel miso
soup.
I don't think you know what it is.
If you use miso, it's the same.
I thought you wouldn't know what it was.
I'll choose A and B.
I'll choose A and B because I'll write
comments about it.
I'll write comments until the video is
over.
So, I don't know A and B.
This is A.
This is B.
I'll eat A first.
Oh no, I spilled it.
I'm hungry.
Karen, it's big.
I want you to eat it without cutting it.
Okay.
It's big.
It's good.
I'm going to eat B.
Oh, you haven't finished eating it.
I ate it.
Don't eat it.
I got it!
You did?
I'm going to eat it now.
It's a little big.
Thank you for watching until the end.
A. Maki
B. Hikakin
It was so good.
Really?
Let's start with Hikakin.
A. Iwashi
B. Saba
C. Tachi
Let's start with Tachi.
A. Saba
B. Iwashi
I got the answer.
Both were good.
But I think Saba was better.
It was good.
I eat it often.
I'll announce the answer.
The one who got the right answer
will get a fish.
Which one?
This one?
The one who got the right answer will
get a fish.
Which one is it?
It's a fish!
It's a correct answer.
Really?
A is this one.
I really don't know.
I think she likes sardines.
I think so.
I think she likes sardines more than
mackerel.
I think she noticed it.
I think so.
GET OUT OF THE WATER!
What I brought next is…
Harusame and Shirataki!
Really?
I brought pink one.
Harusame and Shirataki are similar.
Both are konjac.
So, I thought you wouldn't know.
But, I thought you wouldn't know if I
eat it as it is.
So, I'll compare Harusame and Shirataki
with this one.
I see.
The one with a circle is Shirataki.
Before that, A is…
What is this?
What?
A is...
And B is...
I'll take this one.
C is...
I like Hikaru-san.
I don't like it.
I'm going to eat this one.
It's delicious.
I got it.
I'm supporting this world.
I'm not supporting you.
I'm going to eat this.
I'm a little scared.
It's okay, Mi-chan.
I'm scared.
It's okay. Open the door.
I'm sorry. I put too much.
I put too much.
I hear a sound.
It's good.
Next, it's P.
I don't know what kind of scenery is
flowing now.
But if this video is released, I'm sure
you'll understand.
Well, Mie-chan.
Let's go.
It's good.
It's easy to understand.
Really?
We have all the answers.
Let's start with Hikaru.
A. Shirataki B. Harusame
I see.
Please give me B.
A. Shirataki B. Harusame
Shiraore.
It's not Ore.
No?
It's Shiraore.
It's not.
I'll give you the ring of the angel.
Both of them are the same answer.
Please give me B.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for watching! Please subscribe
to our channel!
Tokyo!
Wow!
You got it right!
I know what it is.
It was really good.
Really?
Is shirataki good?
It was thick.
I see.
The noodles were thick.
I think shirataki would make you full.
I was thinking of making shirataki from
now on.
Did you taste it?
It was good.
Isn't it great?
I see.
That's the result.
Please try shirataki.
It's good.
Next
Next is this.
Milk and soy milk.
It looks easy to understand.
I think so.
Do you like soy milk?
I do.
I've been drinking it since I was a kid.
I see.
I'm a heavy user.
I'm impressed.
I think I can understand it by smelling
it.
I think so.
Next is Karin.
Oh, I forgot to take off my glasses.
What's this?
You're stupid.
This is a straw.
Please drink it.
I'll do it.
I see.
Did you drink it?
You didn't drink it.
Hey.
You.
You're so cute.
It's stretchy.
Emopa?
Bye-Bing😺
It's easy.
Really?
Yes.
I'm good at it.
Let's do it.
Are you OK?
I can't speak.
I'm trying to speak.
How to pick up a flower.
I'm a lady.
I don't know.
It's easy to understand!
No way!
It's not that bad.
It's totally fine.
Are you sure?
It's not that bad.
Really?
Yes.
Then,
let's see the answer.
Please show us, Karin.
A is milk.
A is milk. B is soy milk.
Miki, please.
I'll answer.
The flower blooms.
Please subscribe to this channel!
What is this?
It's a computer!
It's easy to understand.
I didn't know the smell.
I thought it was a left over.
It's difficult.
The answer is...
Yay!
Next time,I came back with more familiar
things!
It's a rice cake and a rice ball!
I thought you wouldn't know what's
inside.
The reason is because it's rice and rice
balls.
I'll start with Hika-sama.
I'll start with A.
Please open your mouth wide.
I think it's a little too much.
It's bent.
Is it?
Karen-san, please.
Yes.
This is A.
How is it?
Is it good?
Yes.
That's good.
I'll go with B.
Yum, yum, yum.
Finished my curry.
Plentiful
I didn't want to cut my hair, but I just
opened my eyes globally.
Please open it.
You ate it by yourself, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
I'll open it.
It's a little big.
Next, I'll eat C.
I think it's a little big.
I think it's the biggest one.
It was easy to eat.
I'll definitely do it myself.
There are so many.
Are you ready?
Let's start with Hika.
A. Mochimugi B. White rice
Let's start with Tachimana.
This is the last question.
I did it.
Is there anyone who got the right
answer?
I wonder.
I'll do A. Mochimugi B. White rice.
I'm so happy.
I'll start.
It's cooler than I thought.
It's cool.
It's growing.
A. Mochimugi B. White rice
You both got the right answer.
It's chewy.
It's because it's rice.
The result is...
It's not the same.
I'll do C. Mochimugi B. White rice.
I'll let you sleep.
Let's play a commercial.
Please.
I'll announce the result of the first
match of the Spirichiri Channel.
The third place is...
I know.
I knew it.
2 points for Karen.
2 points.
The second place is not here.
What does it mean?
It means...
The first place is Chika.
Welcome.
That's all for today.
Thank you for watching.
You can see the difference.
Wait a minute.
I didn't get the cabbage and lettuce
wrong.
Did I get them right?
You did.
She is struggling.
She is called a struggler.
I'm struggling.
I see.
Please look forward to the next video.
Please.
The last one is Shime.
I'll send you a letter so that good
things will happen to you.
Oh, I'm shy.
She's sleeping.
Well, see you next week.
Thank you for watching today.
Spiritual...
Spirituality.