Please subscribe to our channel!
We are here!
Yay!
Kamakura!
We bought a bicycle while we were
building Nogizaka, right?
Yes!
Actually, I bought it because I was
lost.
Oh!
At that time, I couldn't say that I
would buy it.
I consulted with my mother and bought
it.
Oh! I see!
Yes! We bought the same electric
bicycle.
We are exactly the same.
We are the same.
We are the same. I'm happy.
Yay!
So, today, we are going to ride a
bicycle and go to Enoshima.
Let's go!
Bye!
Go!
,
Let's go!
Go!
There are so many students!
Yeah, there are so many!
Is it a middle school trip?
Yeah, it is.
I like youth.
Excuse me.
I found out.
You found out?
A middle school student noticed.
Yay!
I'm so happy.
Hello.
Thank you.
Please enjoy your middle school trip.
Bye.
They are pure young people.
They are watching the video.
Yeah.
I hope they watch it.
Let's go!
Wow, the slope was easy.
The tool is too easy.
It feels good.
This is great.
I came to Kamakura last summer.
That's nice. I'm so happy.
When I tried to go by train,
I went to Kamakura in Katsushikaku.
It's totally different.
I thought I could go by Chiyoda Line.
You can't go.
It's totally different.
It's a little bit different.
It's a little bit too different.
How many years have you been riding a
bicycle?
On Enoshima Island?
Do you ride a bicycle?
I can't hear anything.
I see.
It's a nice town.
It's nice. I want to live here.
I really want to live here.
It would be nice if it was around here.
There are so many houses.
I like to see the houses in order from
the biggest.
I can see them.
It's a crazy house.
I know.
What is the most expensive house in this
area?
I know.
I think it's a nice house.
It's a nice view.
It's a train.
I'm so happy.
Is this Enoden?
Enoden.
I want to take a picture.
I'm so happy.
It's coming.
I can take a picture of this.
I'll take a picture with the bicycle.
The bicycle is falling.
I'm okay.
Look over there.
Look over here.
The color has changed.
It's amazing.
I'm okay.
I think we can take a picture now.
I really admire small shops like this.
Do you want to do it?
Yes, I want to work.
I see. What kind of shop do you want to
do?
I want to do a Japanese sweets shop.
I want you to wear an apron and do a
half-up bun today.
It suits you.
I wonder if it suits me.
Here it is.
It's amazing.
We arrived.
This is the first destination.
It's amazing.
It's colorful.
This is a very beautiful wall.
I heard you can make a key holder.
That's a good memory.
Let's ask.
Yes.
Excuse me.
I'm shooting YouTube videos.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm afraid you won't be able to see it.
Thank you.
I want to make a key holder for my
bicycle.
That's too good.
That's good.
Cute.
What do you like? Which one do you like?
Wait, that's so cute.
The popular and rising alien.
Really?
Cute.
This is good too.
This is cute.
Everyone has a different face.
There are big and small.
Cute.
Aliens are cute.
Aliens are unique.
The brown one.
The bicycle.
It suits you.
The big and small brown one.
I'll go with the small and big one.
The small and small brown one.
The alien.
What do you put in here?
Name.
I want a name.
UFO.
A star.
It's already in.
No way.
Isn't it so fast?
Please subscribe to my channel.
Yuho?
Yuho!
Wow!
So cute!
Thank you!
Manatsu?
Yuho is so cute!
Uranio
Thank you
Renka
Can I have one more?
This is the name of my dog
Rizu?
How do you say it in Japanese?
Katakana
Rizu
I'm so happy
Thank you
So cute!
I'm going on a trip today
So I want to give you a present
What?
A sushi?
But I...
I'll give you a present
What is this?
It's a fake one
Wow!
Can I put it in?
Thank you for watching!
Are you okay?
I'm so happy!
Are you happy?
Yes, I'm happy!
Thank you!
I'm happy!
See you!
I'm so happy!
I got a present for you!
Thank you!
Is it a speaker?
A flat one?
A speaker?
It's not working?
The air is so fresh
It's refreshing
It is
It's not easy to make time and travel
When you have a day off, you go home or
go to the hospital
I only go to the otakatsu when I go
somewhere
Really?
What do you go to the otakatsu?
I go to events
I go to collaboration cafes when I have
a collaboration cafe
I go to the anime
It's amazing
It looks fun
It's fun
You always say you want to find
something
I'm not addicted to it
You say everything
I'm looking for something
What do you want to find?
I'm already addicted
You are?
You are
You are addicted so fast
I can't imagine what you want to find
Everyone recommended me a lot
I didn't get addicted
I've been an otaku since a long time ago
If someone recommended me something, I
would be addicted
I have a otaku talent
I think it's better to have a otaku
talent
I recommend anime to many people
My fans are very interested in me
You are very kind
On the contrary, my fans recommend anime
to me
I see
I share it
I recommend it
It looks fun
I want you to see my otaku
You are right
Say it to your fans
I have to talk to my fans
I will watch it until here
I'm going to die
It's amazing
It's beautiful
I'm so happy
Serious
You have a beautiful face
I was taken so much
I'm happy
It's so nice
Thank you for watching
She gets covered by the wonderful ocean
It smells like the sea
It's salt wind
I'm so happy
I love the sound of the waves
It feels good
It's the best
That bicycle looks good on you
Does it?
It looks so cute from the back
I'm so happy
I was told that it looks good on a
bicycle
I'm so happy
This bicycle is so cute
The sunset is getting beautiful
The sky is getting beautiful
I want to take a picture
It's so beautiful
It's so nice
The weather was bad
It's so bad
Let's go to another place
I want to take a picture
It's getting more beautiful
It's holding something
Here
Here?
This is...
Slum dunk
What?
Really?
No?
It's so beautiful from the top
It's absolutely beautiful
I want a train
I'm waiting for the train
I hope the train doesn't come
If the train doesn't come, it won't be a
slum dunk
Everything is beautiful here
It's beautiful wherever I take a picture
I want to come here again
I agree
I want to come here in private
Stop
Here it comes
Take this side and go to the other side
I'm risking my life
I see
Thank you for watching!
I'm scared.
Aren't you nervous?
I'm so nervous.
I'm surprised you're not coming.
Which way are you coming from?
I thought you were going left.
Left?
No, right!
Did you come that way?
Someone is behind us!
Is it someone?
What?
Only me?
I'm lost.
Let's check if we can get it.
Why someone?
Is it someone behind us?
No.
Oh, no.
What?
You're a genius.
Wow.
I got it.
You're good at this.
Yay!
I got it.
But I'm the only one who got it.
Me too.
And I'm not in the frame.
Only the legs.
What?
What should I do next?
Which one should I go first?
Wait a minute.
Just one.
I'm not sure if I can do it.
Wait a minute.
Get ready for both.
I'm going to fall.
Hurry up.
I can't.
It's so funny.
Here it comes.
This way.
Hurry up.
I'm going to fall.
I got it.
It's funny when you laugh.
I'm happy.
I got it.
It's perfect.
You're a genius.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
Let's go to Enoshima.
Hurry up.
It's getting dark.
Right?
It's pitch black.
It's like cycling.
It's fun.
Wow.
From here,
I'm going to fall.
Yay!
It's amazing.
What's that?
It's like a tower.
It's amazing.
The sound of waves is so good. It's the
best. I'm so happy.
I'm a genius. I'm so happy.
I'm really being healed.
It's a nice city.
We arrived at Enoshima. We arrived. It's
like a downtown.
There's a store called Tako Senbei that
I want to go to.
It's around here. It's right here.
Even if it's just the sound of Enoshima,
it's already good.
I'm happy.
I'm happy just being here. I don't have
to do anything.
Here it is.
It's all big.
I'm glad it's here.
I want to pay today.
No, no. Let's return it.
I got a present before the recording
started.
I gave it to you.
Can I take a picture of this?
Thank you.
Why are you in a piece?
I'm in a piece.
My feet are soft, so they get stiff.
Really?
There's Tako-chan.
Tako-chan is here.
Tako Senbei is delicious.
It's delicious.
Touching
She's touching...
It hurts!
How rudely you are.
Wow, it's huge!
It looks hot.
It does.
Let's eat.
It's good.
This taste.
Is it good?
It's good.
It's cute.
I'm happy.
I'm going on a date with Ren.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Do you want to eat?
Why?
500 yen.
Where?
It was no good.
It's not like this.
It's cold.
I want to drink Enoshima Soya.
Shall we buy it?
This is very your style, isn't it?
What are you doing? I'm solving the
problem.
I heard that B-type people are like
that.
I'm like that too.
I'm not solving the problem. I'm talking
in my head.
Hey, talk to me.
Don't laugh.
Hello.
It's a scallop.
It looks delicious.
Can I come in?
Thank you.
Please come in.
What is this?
It's a scallop.
Riku, Yutan, Maya, and Matsu.
Is that the car?
We were driving together.
What should we eat?
Hamaguri.
Hamaguri and scallops.
I like corn. I'll go with corn.
I'll go with corn.
You can go with corn, but you can go
with the
old-fashioned way.
That's good.
We were driving seriously.
I didn't feel cold,
but it was colder than I thought.
Really?
I didn't know.
Someone told me.
I'm sorry.
Hamaguri.
This is Maya's Hamaguri.
I'm angry.
I'm so happy with all the wasabi.
What?
I didn't hear a word.
I heard, I'm happy with something.
I'm happy with wasabi.
You like wasabi?
I love wasabi.
You're an adult.
I'm happy.
That looks good.
Do you like tuna?
I love tuna.
That's good.
When we go to sushi,
I eat tuna.
I eat tuna with green onions.
You're a very good person.
I eat this a lot with Aya.
Aya is a picky eater.
We eat the same food.
What do you eat?
I eat more than Aya.
I see.
I always eat udon.
Udon?
What?
Why are you suddenly saying that?
It's udon.
It's soba.
I see.
Soba.
Udon.
I always say that.
Don't you say osora?
Osora?
You're like a fool.
You say it.
Osora?
I don't say it.
What?
I said it.
Like okutsu?
Okutsu?
You're lying.
I never say it.
Please comment on which one you think is
the best.
I can tell.
Ren said osora.
Really?
I'll say osora once.
You say, what do you think?
What do you think?
I want to hear it.
I'll say ohashi.
Ohashi?
What else?
O-sara.
What?
My vocabulary is really dirty.
Your vocabulary is dirty but your face
is clean.
That's too much.
What?
I'm eating squid.
When I entered...
What do you think?
You were eating?
Is it good?
Omelet.
It's really good.
I think I'll get scolded if I get called
on TV.
People are talking.
They're eating.
Ren said she's talking to Mano.
She's eating.
I'm sorry.
This is fun.
Sorry.
It's good.
I want to eat Mano's home-cooked food.
Is it good?
What do you want?
I want to eat something.
I want to try it.
That's great.
You said it's great.
It's really good.
I don't think I can make a plan.
I think I know.
So...
I can't.
Someone has to come in.
Who is it?
I'll call Ume.
I'm counting on you.
Ume Narashiku.
I like Ume so much.
I want to hear it.
You want to hear it?
You said it yesterday.
Did I?
What is it?
You said it was all fake.
Ume's way of making fun of people is his
talent.
It was really fun.
I'm glad you were funny.
That was fun.
He's amazing.
He's a genius.
When I was in Osaka for my graduation
live show,
I was a little surprised by the MC.
I was so impressed that I was laughing.
I don't know why.
And I don't think he's overdoing it.
He's already like that.
Interesting.
I feel like I'm always right.
You were a big star, right?
After that, we changed clothes and went
back to the school.
I was always saying that it was really
fun.
I can't speak like Maatsu.
I think Maatsu is amazing.
After that, I was touched by his hand.
I was touched by his hand.
And then I was like, bye.
I was sent.
Kuromi is really funny.
I heard it from Hazuki.
When I said hello to Kuromi, she said,
I was surprised.
Why?
It's funny.
Kuromi is...
He's not like this.
He's like Kuromi Haruka.
He's the one in that frame.
I'm sorry.
You don't seem to be working.
I'm starting to get hungry.
But I'm not in the working mode.
I was like, what was that?
I wonder if the fans will be surprised.
That's how it is.
I forgot.
I'll finish eating.
Was it good?
It was good.
It was a happy day.
What song do you listen to?
I listen to old songs.
I'm surprised.
I listen to KUDO SHIZUKA a lot.
It's really good.
I'm really into it.
I want to go to a live performance.
It's really good.
I was surprised.
KUDO SHIZUKA was doing a mobile.
I became a member and read it.
I'm doing it.
The game ended at 31.
I came to my friend's house at 31.
I played games until morning.
Really?
I don't know if it's because I crossed
the NISSAN.
I didn't have any muscle pain.
Really?
I wanted to get off the bed the next
day.
On the ground.
It's good.
I'm sure.
I thought it would be two days later.
I didn't think so.
I felt like I was being carried away.
Where was the venue?
Daishita is very exciting.
What?
Daishita at Beastie Kawane?
I'm excited to go to work.
I don't want to laugh.
Yes.
So, the bicycle journey has ended.
How was it?
I was so happy. I don't know how many
times I said I was happy today.
I was happy.
I ate delicious food and rode a bicycle.
I'm really happy that I was able to come
to Enoshima.
I'm happy that you're happy.
I'm really happy. I was able to take a
lot of pictures I love.
I'm happy that I was able to take a lot
of pictures. Thank you for the good
memories.
Thank you for the good memories. Let's
use a lot of bicycles together.
If you see a bicycle that you ride in
private, please watch it.
Let's drive safely.
Let's do our best.
Thank you very much.
Please subscribe to the channel and
click the good button.
Bye bye.