On Earth, our 3rd album, Anarki, is
getting a lot of attention.
Wow!
Shake!
Anarki!
Anarki reacted!
You're here again!
We're going to do a Mama Nuki with the
members' photos.
We don't know which one is the Joker, so
we're going to do it in a so-called Jiji
Nuki rule.
If you get a pair, the person in the
photo will tell you the story of the
photo.
Oh!
By the way, the photo of this card is a
photo of the first release of the album.
Let's do this.
This is the Jiji card.
Everyone, please prepare the card.
What is this?
There's a really cute girl.
What's a?
?
You don't tell me the?
You'll know if you do it.
Mama Nuki Start!
It's like a party.
I didn't get it.
Who is it?
I don't know.
There's a kid I don't know.
Who is it?
It's me.
I don't know.
What do you mean?
When Keith first came to the station.
That's why I'm looking at Keith.
Is that my face?
I didn't know.
It's the same.
Your face is different.
Did you study?
No, I didn't.
Wait, wait, wait.
I didn't say that.
I didn't.
I got it.
Why do you look so half-hearted?
This is a nose-blowing.
It's a trend to laugh naturally.
Try it.
Start!
I'm sorry.
HAPPY CHU!
What's this?
I got it.
Is this for Hinata?
Yes, it's me.
I'm a puppy.
What a girl!
Ta-da!
Oh, a dog.
Yes, yes, yes.
I got it.
So fast!
Ta-da!
It's cute.
Who is this?
Yes.
Riko, can you ski?
I can't do it now because I'm afraid of
getting hurt.
But I've been doing it.
Oh, really?
Then, teach me next time.
Okay.
What?
All of them?
All of them
Where did you draw?
What did you draw?
It's a party!
If you chose this card, you have to add
a belphegor ear
It's mainly attached to her ear. It's
fine
And add a pin in the stomach and we can
continue a cute talking
This is Yagii Ryo, when I am going to
say PAPADAKI than you must say PION
This is Toyoshika
Wow
Hey Kanon, you have come out
I didn't
Why you only got one?
I'm not here anymore. I'm Kobashi-Kaoh.
Why are you not happy?
I'm not happy.
But, this is really a real smile.
Close your eyes.
This is a real smile.
It's amazing.
My birthday.
Is this the size of 5 years old?
I'm older than you.
I'm not younger than you.
I'm 5 years older than you.
This is cute.
Who is this?
This is me.
My mother or father is taking a picture.
I'm holding the camera.
This is cute.
January 1st.
My mother or father is taking a picture.
I'm holding the camera.
This is you.
I don't have a picture of me taking a
picture.
I uploaded all the pictures to the blog.
I was told that I didn't upload the
picture.
I took a picture of me not uploading the
I'm holding the camera.
This was the only picture.
This is the picture I took when I was in
the first grade of elementary school.
Once you removed this, your honor will
be activated.
Well done Wha...
I'm not
This is a photo of my brother
celebrating his birthday
He says he won't blow out the candles
because it's embarrassing
So I'm going to replace Yasu
It's a grandma
It's me
It's a grandpa
My grandma came to my house and said
this is the Rainbow Bridge
I'm going to replace my grandma
Then I'm going to play the card of mom
crying
I want to play the card of Hiro and Aika
Please, hurry
Which one should I choose?
I chose my own
Cute
My mom loved boarders and she kissed me
a lot when I was a kid
She said she didn't want to wear a bow
tie
I like it now
I'm going to replace my grandma
I see
Excuse me
It was very funky
I didn't get it
I'm going to replace my grandma
Zyuoh theurst!
I'm scared!
How are you feeling today?
I'm not good
You will feel like a rabbit
I'm a rabbit!
I'm so honored
Thank you always
Yay! We are all here!
We went to buy some things at Mayama's
smoothie shop
We bought it while we were working
This is Mayama's smoothie
I see
Which card do you recommend, Usagi-san?
There are only 3 cards
You are fast
You are picking up cards again
Cute
This one
I'm sad
What? Is it a secret?
There is a milk shop in Nakayama
I LINEd Riko-chan
I'm the manager of the fourth generation
of the VITA
You did it?
It's a picture of memories
It's so good!
Why is it a year?
I'm sorry, everyone!
I'm taking a picture of Rina and Mirei
I'm taking a picture of Riko
Mayama-san is like,
I can't feel their youth, so I'm doing
this
Everyone is watching
I'm next to them, so I'm like
I'm taking a picture
We're having a party!
I'm here!
So cute!
I am a bird
It's a fish tank
Fish tank Kobayashi
I'm in the fish tank
It's cute, right?
It's cute, but it's not
I'm holding it
It's a hole
It's cute!
Wow!
I was going to catch a UFO for the first
time in my life
My friend said, I'm sad that I can't
take a picture, so I'll take a picture
And she took it for me
Wow!
I did it!
Ta-da!
Wow!
It's so cute!
It's a picture of a yearling's swimming
club
It was a picture of a rabbit
It's cute
I only liked pink at that time
So, I was a rabbit with two colors
I competed with pink in orange or pink
in pink
But I was an adult
You said, it's OK
I said, it's OK, I'll wear orange
I woke up to orange
I'm wearing pink now
I have rabbit ears
It was a dream, right?
I can't believe it
A few years ago, I made your dream come
true
Did you hear that?
I did
I'm so happy
They make me happy
The girls of K-POP
Funky girl
I wanted to wear sunglasses
I have something
Yes, you have
I have
I put it on
Look at my face
Your face looks great
I'm going out
I'm walking in the city