Thank you for watching!
Good morning!
Good evening!
Good job!
This is the last YouTube video of Maya
and me before we graduate.
This is the last one!
I'm so sad!
We are going to do something that you
wanted to do.
We are going to have fun.
What do you think it is?
Let's go!
I was the right type.
I was the left type.
I'm going to start.
I'm not good at this.
I was the right type.
I'm going to make a terrarium.
I came to Shinjuku Culture School Iruha.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you for your time.
Please put it in.
I'm sorry.
This is a rotating plate.
Wow.
It's like Chinese food.
This is a clay pot.
Is there a clay pot?
It's easy to see.
It's interesting.
I should turn it around.
I see.
Like this?
It's okay.
How is it?
I can't see it.
It's like a valley.
Please make it like a valley.
How about Maya?
Do you want to make a valley?
Valley?
Is it a river?
Yes, it's here.
It's around here.
Both sides?
Yes.
I'll start.
Wow, it's beautiful.
Your eyes are red today.
I'll start from the clock.
I'm thinking about decorating my house.
Me too.
Maya and I often go to my house.
We often go to each other's houses.
Where do you put Maya?
I put her in the bedroom.
I have to make sure Maya doesn't get
attacked by a dog.
I don't let big dogs enter the bedroom.
Maya was playing on the veranda.
I went to see her.
I thought she was tired.
I took off her clothes.
Did you like it?
I was shocked.
I was angry at her.
Maya went to the river.
I'm almost done.
My living room is blue, yellow and
white.
The first house is warm and brown.
Maya comes to all of us.
Recently, I've been wanting to see
Ghibli.
I want to be able to express my heart.
I'm collecting Ghibli DVDs now.
I used to play Slam Dunk.
I play a lot of different genres.
I fell asleep at 8 o'clock while
watching Howl's castle.
That's early.
I woke up at 5 o'clock in the morning.
As usual.
I watched a movie and watched Howl's
castle from 5 o'clock in the morning.
That's crazy.
I'm living such a life.
This is what Higuchi's looks like.
I'm a little black.
Yes, you are.
Thank you for watching.
I'm doing it.
You're good.
Look at that.
It's true.
The skin is ready.
It looks good.
What?
You washed it this way?
You were the right type before.
I was the right type.
I was the left type.
I thought you were going to wash the
skin in the middle.
Right?
The skin is small.
It's a little bigger than mine.
It's good.
OK.
So, do you want to choose an animal?
There are many.
Maya is a sea type.
I'm a mountain type.
Suddenly, it's the sea of Africa.
Elephant.
Wait, it looks good on you.
Elephant is cute.
Oh, the elephant is falling.
It's cute.
I'll put it aside for a moment.
What about me?
Is this a fox?
Is it a fox?
The rock is smaller than the penguin.
That's true.
The world view is difficult.
Wow, an elephant and a penguin.
Transformation.
Did you see the penguin?
But it's in a good place now.
Then, I'll choose this penguin.
This one.
Oh, what is this?
What is this?
Is this a lady dog?
No.
It's Mia cat, the guardian of the
jungle.
Mia cat?
The guardian?
Where is Mia cat?
In the desert?
It's a wildcat.
What should we do?
It's a great world view.
The penguin and the elephant are the
same.
I'll put the wildcat here.
I think the elephant will eat it.
It looks stronger than the elephant.
The wildcat is bigger than the elephant.
I think so, too.
What about the hare?
There is a hare.
The hare is very strong among animals.
It's a hare.
Isn't it a hippo?
No way.
I thought the hippo was slow, relaxed
and calm.
But I heard it was very fierce.
It's definitely a hippo.
I learned about the hippo from the TV
show.
I'm not good at math.
I don't know information.
But I know that people don't know much
about it.
I think the hippo is very confident.
The reason why the hippo is strong is
because Shibata said it.
Shibata of UNTOUCHABLE.
Then it's definitely true.
The hippo is strong.
It's fast in water and fast on land.
It's also strong in biting power.
Wasn't it a hippo?
No?
It's a hippo.
It's different from biting power.
But it has a small brain.
So it's stupid.
Do you want to sign it?
I'll sign it.
Then let's sign it.
This is the real sign.
Only two people.
There were surprisingly few people.
That's true.
I'm counting the coins in the live
stream.
Do you want to do that again?
There are a lot of coins in the house.
I wanted to do it again.
That's true.
You saved it for me.
I saved it and divided it.
I thought I wouldn't do it again, so I
put it all together.
I see.
It was a piece of cake.
I didn't think it would come because
Kazumi and Manatsu came.
It's the usual.
It's like us.
But it's been a while since I graduated.
That's right.
I think it's a very active person.
I went for a walk with Maya's dog.
Maya?
I bought a collar for the first time.
Dogs get excited when Chima is around.
I wanted to make them tired.
I wanted to take them for a walk before
Chima came.
I put on my first collar.
I couldn't get the collar off.
A big dog started to run wild.
Chima was right in front of me.
Chima was
Maya was fighting with a big dog alone.
I was holding a puppy.
I said, it's okay.
Maya was hit by a big dog.
I was so embarrassed.
I was desperate.
I was so scared.
I thought a car would come.
I was so nervous.
My cell phone fell on my face.
I thought it was the end of my life.
I was so embarrassed.
I was so scared.
I was so excited.
I was with Maya for the first time.
A woman walking in a golden car came to
me.
I asked her what happened.
She said the lead was broken.
I was hit by a dog.
I was desperate.
I asked her if there was a new lead.
She said yes.
She gave me a new lead.
I said it wasn't the lead.
I said it was broken.
I said I didn't have a lead.
I said thank you.
I was so hurt.
I haven't seen her since then.
I was so happy.
I laughed at Maya.
I was desperate.
I was so happy.
It's hard to tame a dog that weighs more
than 40 kg.
I couldn't control it.
I didn't know what to do.
I was with Maya.
I was desperate.
I was so happy.
I wanted everyone to see Maya.
It's embarrassing if everyone sees Maya.
I was holding a big dog.
I was so excited.
I was on the road in the middle of the
road.
I was so happy that no one saw me.
I was really happy.
I didn't want to talk to anyone.
I wanted to talk to you in private.
Maya is so funny.
It was completed.
It was fun.
I will introduce Maya.
This is the ocean.
I knew the ocean.
Flamingo and penguin coexist in the
ocean.
I knew the world of the world.
Sand beach.
I made a flower.
I didn't have a complete picture.
I made it while looking for it.
It's dynamic.
I put a lot of flowers.
I think it's good.
I want to decorate it.
OK.
It's beautiful.
Maya is the ocean.
I am a mountain.
I imagined a mountain.
The water flows from here.
I came here to drink water and feed the
foxes.
I made two foxes.
Maya is also a penguin and flamingo.
It's simple.
The color is beautiful.
The color of the stone is beautiful.
They are suitable for each other.
I will put the lid on.
I will put it on.
It's done!
Beautiful!
It's pretty cute.
I'm happy.
If I put this at home, I will remember
it forever.
This time, we want to make a memory.
We want to make a memory.
The last YouTube.
It was fun.
I'm lonely.
Last YouTube.
I only talked about dogs.
We talked a lot about things in
Nagizaka.
If I didn't have you, I wouldn't have
been able to do it for 11 years.
I think so.
We might be the same.
We support each other.
I'm going to cry.
Thank you very much.
Let's meet again.
Bye bye.
But we will meet again.
We will meet again soon.
Please subscribe to the channel.
Please give us a high rating.
We are waiting for your comments.
Bye bye.
We will read all your comments.
I'm at the bathroom of the terrarium.
This is how it looks.
Ta-da!
This is where I can see well.
I used to pass by here often.
I can see penguins and flamingos every
day.
It's relaxing.
Yay!
Thank you for watching.
To Be Continued...