Leave this to me. You guys go ahead.
Night watch and idol.
Now, it's already the end of the show.
Let's hear from Negishi-san.
I'll be on the new stage of Tokimeki
Stationaries, Remember My Love, from
November.
The date is from Friday, November 25th
to Sunday, November 27th.
It will be held at Gotanda G3.
Please come and have fun!
I said please come and have fun, but I
mean, if you come and have fun, it's
fine.
Please!
How many performances will you do?
Five.
Five performances?
Yes, five performances.
That's wonderful.
This is the main act.
It's the main act. I'm so excited.
You have a lot of lines?
Yes.
Some people don't have lines in the main
act, but you have a lot of lines?
Yes, I do.
Oh, really?
What do you mean?
What? Are you trying to get me?
Yes, I want to get your support.
Oh, I see.
I want to get the support of the people
watching.
Please give me power.
You haven't started practicing yet.
I haven't started yet.
You look very nervous.
I really am.
Are you a senior?
Everyone around me is amazing.
Really?
I've been looking for a partner.
Yes.
She's really good.
Really?
Yes, she's really good at studying.
What's with this little girl?
She's probably thinking about something.
Oh, no. I'm sorry.
I'm putting pressure on you.
I see.
That's how it is.
You're all so kind.
Yes, I'm studying.
That's right.
It's not just the staff who are reading
the book.
There are a lot of staff who are
invisible.
I'm nervous.
My hands did enough job to catch up with
me!
And the final ritual!
Gakanto Idol!
...Yes?
Thank you.
Are you okay? You did it!
I hope the stage will be a success.
I'd like to have a cup of tea to cheer
me up.
Is that okay?
Today, I'll have a cup of tea.
I love tea.
Really?
Please drink it.
Thank you for the tea.
It's warm.
Ah, it's so good!
Ah, thank goodness!
My heart and soul are all warm.
Ah, warm?
It's so refreshing and delicious.
Ah, thank goodness.
Now, lastly,
towards the camera,
I'd like to ask the fans to close the
video cutely!
Okay!
Eh?
Ah, it's so good!
I don't think that's what you do.
If you close the camera, the show will
end.
No, no, no, no.
If you don't like it, it's okay.
I don't like it.
I'll do my best.
It's been a long time.
Thank you for watching until the end.
Huh?
No?
I wonder if it's okay to do this.
When I close the door, the show ends.
Thank you very much.
I thought you were a long-term
character.
I've never done that before.
I think I forgot how it feels.
Oh, really?
You've been on stage all the time?
You're lying, right?
Really?
It's like an idol.
It was Mishika.
Really?
I'm sorry.
I had a lot of fun talking about anime!
Thank you for watching! This was
Negishika Ren! Bye bye!
I sent it by the offer of No. 75.
Thank you very much. Please continue to
support me.