Ebi-chu videos
YASUMOTO AYAKA questions!
I finally did it.
Thank you very much for sending me a lot
of questions.
About 1000 questions were tweeted by
you.
Thank you very much.
Today I will answer about 80 questions.
I will answer them one by one.
I will answer them immediately.
First.
What do you want to do with nine people
in Ebi-chu?
I don't know if I can do it in this
situation.
I want to deepen our friendship.
I want to go on a school trip.
I want to go to the hotel with everyone.
I want to have a party at night with
everyone.
I want to get along with everyone.
Next.
What is your favorite kanji?
My name is AYA KANA.
My mother's father gave me this kanji.
I have a original kanji, but I don't
know if I can use it.
I'm happy.
Next.
What is your impression of the new
members?
I think everyone is mature.
Everyone is mature these days.
Next.
What is your favorite lyrics?
This is difficult.
I have been listening to my own lyrics
since I was born.
I have been reading it.
I feel very close to the lyrics.
I understand it.
Next.
What was the most fun shooting the MV
for IA HON RIOT?
This is lip sync.
I sing alone and move.
This was a scene in the shrimp MV for
the first time in a long time.
This is a very fresh scene.
I felt like I was an idol.
I had a lot of fun.
Next, is there a member you want to
date?
Is it a girlfriend?
Is it a boyfriend?
I like KAHORIKO.
I think KAHORIKO would be fun to date
both.
I think I'm excited and excited every
day.
Next, please tell me a recent episode.
This is a member's episode.
I say this every day because I want to
eat grilled meat.
Next, the vivid green hair color is very
nice.
Is there any other color you want to
try?
I want to try a lot of colors.
I want to try pink.
I want to try blonde hair like an anime.
I'm watching TOKYO REVENGERS.
I have a very cute hairstyle.
I want to imitate the characters.
Next, how is the distance between you
and TOMATO?
I think the distance is close because
it's summer.
I think everyone is close.
Next, where would you like to go if you
could play freely?
I want to go to Korea.
I want to go to the fashion center.
Next, is there a time you can't cut your
hair at this time?
I like to brush my teeth.
I have about four types of toothbrushes.
I use them every day.
I change them depending on my mood.
I can't waste my time brushing my teeth.
I think everyone is like that.
I like it.
What is your charm?
I'm a round face.
Next question.
What song do you want to listen to when
you feel energetic?
I want to listen to SADON.
I want to see it when I'm not feeling
well, including the video and dance.
I want to hear it.
I love that.
Next.
Which prefecture would you like to go to
if you were to travel?
I definitely want to go to Hokkaido.
I've been really looking forward to
going to Hokkaido lately.
I remember going to Hokkaido the most
when I was on TV and radio.
I had a lot of fun there.
I ate delicious sushi and ate it.
I had a lot of fun there, so I want to
go there again.
Next.
Do you like saunas?
I want to try to get ready for the
sauna.
I'm not brave enough to go to the sauna.
I definitely want to go to the sauna
someday.
I want to go around the sauna.
Next.
Which song do you want to listen to on
the drive?
I want to listen to SAKE SHAKE and open
cars.
Next.
What is the biggest failure you've made
recently?
I try not to think that I've made a
mistake recently.
If you look at it, it may be a failure.
I'm doing anything because I feel like
I've succeeded.
Next.
What do you want to eat for the last
time in your life?
I want to eat tomato because I'm a girl
who likes tomatoes.
I want to eat beef tongue.
Next.
What is the most impressive sport and
athlete you have seen at the Olympics?
I was interested in skateboarding this
year.
I think it's cool.
I want to try it too.
I want to try it if I have a chance.
What is your morning routine?
I only do my morning routine when I wake
up, wash my face, and brush my teeth.
I don't do much.
Next.
Who do you want to work with to make a
comic with the members of the ABiTU?
I want to work with MAYA.
I want to work with MAYA because I feel
safe.
I think MAYA and MAYA will be a good
match.
Next, please tell me what you're into
recently.
I'm into cafe au lait these days.
I often drink coffee at break time.
I think I've grown up.
How should I do it?
Next, please tell me a book you've
recently read.
I've been reading the essay book written
by Osaki Sekai-kan.
I feel like the world of the lyrics of
the song has become a book.
I'm able to imagine a lot of things.
I feel like I'm a world-famous writer.
I think it's very interesting to read.
Next, please tell me how you spend your
time at home.
I often watch movies.
I often watch the best scenes of my
favorite actresses.
I often send them to RICO, CAFO, MAYAMA,
and so on.
I often send them to pictures without
saying anything.
Next, please tell me your favorite
costume in the past.
I like the clothes of KINDAN NO KARMA.
I like the clothes of SHIKU and LABELY.
I want to wear a black costume.
Next, please tell me your favorite
student.
I am a junior high school student.
I am worried because it is my first time
to take a junior high school exam.
Please support me.
I don't feel like I'm going to take the
exam.
I look forward to the exam.
Please look forward to the exam.
I support you.
Next, please tell me your favorite idol.
He was delighted.
There is a difference between supporting
actresses, actors, and artists.
I feel that idols are only good at
giving energy.
When I watch a music program, I feel
that the moment idols appear, the energy
is coming from them.
I feel that idols only give me energy.
I feel that I am energetic and shiny.
I will participate in a conversation for
the first time this time.
How should I talk to you?
I talk to my classmates.
I talk to my classmates for the first
time.
Please talk to me like that.
Next, what song do you recommend for
beginners?
Many people want to know that EBI-CHU is
a 9-member organization.
I will start with IYAHON LIGHT.
Next.
I said that I was looking forward to the
new members entering the EBI-CHU
audition.
I said that I would practice to increase
the number of seniors.
Did you make me blow the seniors' wind?
Who is the first senior member who blows
the seniors' wind?
I think I'm blowing the seniors' wind.
I'm a little older than the seniors.
I was in a different position from when
I was in the Kaoriko team.
I was conscious of saying that I was
going to do it.
I think I'm the one who blows the
seniors' wind the most.
I have confidence in that.
Next.
What is the most funny thing that
happened recently?
What is the funniest thing that happened
recently?
I often get laughed at by YUNO recently.
I am surprised by YUNO's actions.
This is interesting.
She is a very different person.
I laugh a lot because I think she is
interesting.
Next.
Who do you want to be replaced with a
member for a day?
member for a week?
Who do you want to be reborn?
I want to be replaced with MIRAYA for a
day.
I want to be replaced with RIKKO for a
week.
If I were to be reborn, I would be a
different person.
I want to be reborn as a member of
COCONA.
I'm not a member of COCONA anymore.
I want to be reborn as a member of
COCONA.
Next.
Who do you respect?
This is a difficult question.
I respect everyone I meet.
I want to collect the good points of
everyone I meet.
I don't want to be a different person.
Next.
Who do you respect the most when you see
a new member?
I respect MONOKA very much.
I think I'm different from when I was in
middle school.
I respect that.
I think I'm a great person.
I want to learn from everyone and do my
best.
Next. What is your favorite part of
ONIGIRI?
I will say UME.
What did you think of YASUMOTO PRODUCE's
dance set?
I talked about it at the meeting.
I forgot the atmosphere of the live
performance.
I was excited.
Then everyone was tired of it.
Everyone said that I was a demon.
But I was relieved that the members said
that I was interesting.
Next, what are the words that the
members say to you?
I am happy to be called cute.
When I see the pictures of the MV, I am
excited to see the comments.
Next, what kind of conversation do you
have with NONOKA?
All three of us say something suddenly.
I look at the picture and say something.
I'm scared.
I say something that I don't understand.
I'm really funny.
Next, what is the support of Yasumoto
that you can get when you are in pain?
I get strength from the people around
me.
I get strength from the staff who
support me.
Next, shout out what you want to shout
out.
What is it?
I want to eat chocolate.
I shout out nothing.
I have a small voice.
I shouted out my feelings.
What do you call the three new members?
I call NONOKA, COCONA, and COCO.
I call them UNOPE.
I think it's a good nickname.
Next, what is the secret to your hard
work?
I think it's a habit to work hard.
I'm trying to do my best every day.
It's natural to work hard.
It's not a heavy thing.
I feel like I can work hard as usual.
I don't know if it's a body.
I think so.
Next.
What song would you like to sing if you
could sing the first take?
I want to sing this song by counting the
stars.
Our harmony is very important.
I think it will be a simple performance.
Next.
What is your job other than live
performance?
I'm used to my hair style, so I don't
have to do it.
I want to leave a lot of hair.
I want to leave a lot of memories.
I want to take pictures and make a
movie.
I want to do what I am now.
I want to be a model.
I answered about 50 questions.
Thank you for your questions.
I answered too many questions.
It was difficult.
I will continue to answer questions.
I would be happy if you could ask me a
lot of questions.
I will read the questions I received.
Thank you for your continued support.
That was the question for YASUMOTA
EYAKA.
Bye bye.