YAKA-TOU IDOL
Today's main corner.
Please give us a title call.
My three major elements.
I've learned a lot so far.
Introducing three elements that make up
yourself.
I want to know more about the guest
idol.
So, Ai-chan, please tell us three
elements that make up you.
I'm made of this.
1. Potato
2. Nature
3. Sauna
4. Potato
5.
I'm not good at drawing.
6.
I'd like to ask you one by one.
1. Potato
It was a while ago.
When I was a kid, I went to my
grandmother's house.
She gave me a sweet potato as a snack.
I've been eating it since I was a kid.
I love potatoes.
Some people eat potatoes with skin and
some people don't.
My family doesn't eat potatoes that
much.
I love potatoes so much that I can eat
the skin.
Really?
I'm not sure if I can get a lot of
potatoes.
I don't think so.
I want to go to various potato cafes
around the country.
Are there so many?
There are a lot.
Are there many potato cafes around the
country?
There are many in Shimokitazawa.
There are many in Shibuya and Ebisu.
Are there many potato cafes in Shibuya?
I often eat Beniharuka.
It's delicious.
There is a place called Benitenji.
The potatoes there are very sweet and
very sweet.
Is it a sweet potato?
Yes, it is.
I used to eat potatoes when I was a kid.
I have the image of a roasted potato.
I'm eating dessert now.
I like it.
It's good to eat potatoes.
I ate potato bread this morning.
There are a lot of potato products in
the convenience store.
I ate potato bread this morning.
I will eat the roasted potato from the
store.
Please eat it.
There are only a few in the store.
I'm looking forward to it.
I like it.
I ate a ham.
It's delicious.
The ham has sharp teeth.