Yakan and idols!
Can I ask you to tell us about it?
Yes!
We, Iginari Talk, will have a tour of
the country that will never lose in
spring!
We have a team!
There are 12 songs in total.
Oh, I see!
It's my hobby.
That's amazing!
I see.
There are 9 songs in total.
Yes, there are 9 songs in total.
Please come and enjoy!
Then, please look at the sweets in each
place and eat them.
So, can I give you a tea that will cheer
you up at the end?
I'll give you Jasmine tea.
Yay! I love it!
Really?
I like tea the most.
Oh, that's good.
I hope you'll take a deep breath and
relax.
Cheers!
Thank you!
Happy!
You're a good girl!
Let's eat!
I'm a different person!
I'm dying.
You're dying?
I'm happy for you, Yakan.
Thank you!
Oh, I almost forgot!
You have a farm?
Yes, I have a farm.
What is it?
I rent a farm at the shopping mall in
Sendai Station.
I have a farm called Yasunori Farm.
You have a farm?
Yes.
You can make a farm?
I'm on vacation now.
I grew cucumbers last year.
I have a harvest festival every year.
I didn't grow cucumbers last year.
Why did you grow cucumbers this year?
I wanted to grow cucumbers this year,
but I couldn't grow the same crops for
two years in a row.
Because the soil was bad?
Yes, because the soil was bad.
I couldn't grow the same crops, so I
didn't grow cucumbers.
But I harvested about 60 cucumbers last
year.
You harvested 60 cucumbers?
You grew a lot.
I couldn't eat cucumbers anymore.
What are you going to grow this year?
I'm going to grow bell peppers this
year.
I'm going to try.
How do you grow bell peppers?
Bell peppers?
Really?
I think it's okay.
I'm really grateful to the farmers.
I had a hard time growing cucumbers in
the last two years.
I thought I was in a supermarket.
I was about to cry.
I didn't know that the cucumbers in the
supermarket were so beautiful.
I'm so impressed.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm going to try to grow bell peppers.
I'll leave it to you to decide if I'm
cute or gyaru.
If you say something to the camera, this
program will end.
That's all for tonight.
Bye bye.
Night민 and idol
This video is brought to you by Shiro-
chan.
Thank you everyone!