The first episode
Good evening.
The Ebisu House is a place where eight
members of Ebichu can talk normally.
The only thing we have is a wonderful
house.
There is no script.
Isn't this the Terrace House?
No, please stop.
Please subscribe to the channel.
You've been to Ebisu House, haven't you?
Yes, I have.
It's an homage.
Well, this Ebisu House...
The main story is about a love story
between a man and a woman.
This Ebisu House is about the true
feelings that come out of living
together.
It's a program like that.
But it's not about love.
It's not about love.
It's about understanding the deep parts
of the members.
That's right. There's no script for this
today.
Ebichu Tastas usually doesn't have a
script with the members.
That's right.
Ebichu Tastas is almost a year old.
So, without the script, I'll have you
talk about it with your true feelings.
Wow, it's so beautiful!
I think we can have a wedding party
here.
Ayame, I want to have a wedding party
Thank you.
From the world...
Wow!
Wow! It's like a big poster!
It's like a big poster!
3, 2, 1...
Wow!
It's like a house over there!
Wow! Over there!
It's like a love kiss!
This is outside, right?
It's a world!
Look! It's a dream world!
Wait, wait! This is...
Wow! That kitchen is admirable!
It's admirable!
It's amazing!
Ah! It's so cute!
It's admirable!
Do you want to sit?
There are 8 of them.
How do you want to sit?
Where do you want to sit?
I think I'll sit here.
Wow! It's amazing!
It's a great staircase!
It's so nice!
Thank you for watching!
I'm so tired.
I'm going to take a picture.
Thank you for coming.
Welcome to our house.
Isn't it amazing?
Thank you for watching!
Sit down.
Calm down and sit down.
Take your time.
I touched it.
The TV is big.
Bring it in.
Mom!
I touched it.
I think I have to do this somewhere.
I think there were a lot of thoughts and
thoughts.
I can solve it myself.
The members are getting ready to go on
stage.
What do you think of the members?
It's been a year since we've been on
stage.
That's fast.
It's been a year.
It's pretty fast.
It's a little bit of a challenge.
Can you see Riku's face?
I can't see Riku's face.
I want to see Riku's face.
I can't see it.
I have a bad feeling about this.
That's not good.
That's what happened.
We did a good job.
What was the first one?
It's a fan club.
It was a serious fan club.
It was a social and cultural fan club.
There are a lot of different things.
I chose it.
It's a big fan club.
Kaiki-san looked up the big fan club.
The judge was...
It's a big fan club.
It's not like Ebichu.
You don't have to say anything about
people.
It's a loose feeling.
That time was a little bit like a
variety show.
It was a first try.
Mirei-chan, you were very sharp.
You were told by the principal.
Hoshino said,
I should say it.
You should say what you think in your
heart.
In TASSAS,
I was told by the principal that I was
angry at the viking.
Viking?
It's a barbecue.
I want to go to the barbecue.
You can praise the viking.
It was fun.
I was told that I was laughing at the
viking.
You can say it.
I'm sorry.
Go and see it.
I want to go.
He talks about the trial a lot.
He has a good impression.
He said something.
He didn't say much about this person.
He didn't say much about the shrimp.
He is a little bit more relaxed.
It's cold.
Let's talk here.
He is a little bit more relaxed.
What an interesting area
Amazing!
Wow, this is amazing.
I wish I could have a big veranda.
But there's no place to put the laundry.
No, but we can put it here.
How about a veranda?
Hey, this is...
What? What does that mean?
I want to go inside. It's cold.
Bye.
Go!
No!
I want to go inside.
I have this下 officially installed a
little more.
When you
puppu
and there is this
thing
site
It's pretty old.
Yeah, it's pretty old.
Everyone's black.
It's hard to do that.
Because suddenly...
I was talking to you.
I know.
I'm surprised.
Do you like bibichu?
I like it.
If you don't like it, you don't do it.
I don't know if I like it or not.
It's already part of my life.
It's like brushing your teeth.
It's like breathing.
Aica Japan says enough as long as I
don't get hit in the head by this.
I think that what you've been doing will
disappear.
be useful in some way, but if you're
doing it, you want to leave something
more.
You've been doing so much stuff, but
you're going to do it again?
Let's grab something here and start
again.
I think that's what you're doing, but
the number of years is increasing.
I'm not sure if it's been three years
since then.
It's been a few years, or rather, since
I became eight, each member has become
able to do what they want, and it's
become an environment where they can say
things, and it's become an age where
they can say things.
I think that the next year or two is the
competition.
I think it's the age.
I was in sixth grade, and Aya-chan was
in fifth grade.
I didn't think I'd come to high school,
so it was too far.
I thought so, too. I was in fifth grade.
I want to live in this house.
It seems to take electricity.
I'm watching reality.
The color of the sky today is beautiful.
It's a little dull.
I don't feel like it's night.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Sometimes I look up at the sky at night.
The moon is half full.
Half full?
That's right.
There were a lot of clouds.
I was surprised.
I've only been to the entrance of the
house.
I can see Orion Mountain.
Orion Mountain?
It's not very electricity.
It's beautiful.
I'm surprised.
She's in high school.
She's fast.
I've only seen her 15. NICO grenadée,
first year and middle school She's 12
now. But in months she'll be already 16,
2016 or something. It's been 4 years,
you know. 本当だね 速いなー It's take a while
like that. スーパーがエ ens pers ==
Niko-chan, you've changed a lot.
I thought you were different.
Yes. Thank you.
Thank you for your time.
It's been a long time.
Niko-chan's first time to meet her
friends.
I'm just 17 years old.
17 is quite big.
I feel like I'm in a situation where I'm
like, what should I do?
That's true.
Even if I have my own character,
I wonder if it's okay to have this
character even though I have a
subordinate.
That's right.
I wonder if it's okay to have this
character even though I have Kao-chan
and Riko-chan.
I wonder if it's okay to be so childish.
But that's me, so I want to be like
that.
But I'm an adult, so I have to be like
You've had a lot of opportunities to
meet Kaoriko from the beginning.
That's right.
How was it doing education?
That was pretty big.
It was pretty big.
Until then, I just thought it would be
nice to be in the third group.
I thought the upper class would do
something about it, so it was very
comfortable.
MC...
Oh, Ichiyo.
Ichiyo.
That's the timing.
That's right.
I felt a lot of weight when I was doing
the live.
I didn't want to do it.
It's a spring tour.
I was also the MC for Yasumoto.
I thought it was a joke, but I didn't
think it would really happen.
But I did my best.
There are also MCs like this.
I was pretty nervous.
I was nervous. I was crazy.
Yasu is the type who gets crazy when he
thinks it's no good.
But when I think it's no good...
I'm like this.
I was really nervous at that time.
Last year's fan club?
I was nervous when I was in the curtain.
I'm still embarrassed because I'm like
that.
I'm crying.
What did you say?
I can't do it anymore.
I'm going to fall.
I was stuck in the pine tree.
It didn't sound like it.
It didn't sound good.
I had to do it.
I talked to Natsu before.
When you're an MC, you have to be
natural.
Aika is like this these days.
I want to be like that.
When you're nervous, you have to protect
the people you want to protect.
Sometimes you can't see the person you
hate with a good eye.
You feel sorry for them.
You have to go around.
You have to go around and get the person
you hate.
I think I'm pretty strict.
I don't have a position like that.
When I turn eight, I'm like me.
I'm not sure what to do.
Sometimes I think I'm bad.
I sometimes push myself.
It's okay.
You're saved by your voice.
I think so too.
That's why I'm the only one who's not
there.
My parents told me to stop.
I don't have to go there.
I was told a lot.
I have to do that.
I think I have to go.
Are you crying?
I think I'm the type of person who says
harsh things.
I don't have that kind of position.
When I turn 8, I'm like, am I?
I'm a little bit of a mess.
But it's okay, right?
You're being saved by that voice.
I think so too.
That's why I'm the only one who's
crying.
My parents told me to stop.
They told me I didn't have to go.
That's true.
They told me a lot.
But if I don't do that...
It's the same as what I said earlier.
I think I have to go.
I think so.
Are you crying?
I'm crying too.
What's going on?
Why?
You're crying.
Yeah.
That's why I'm the type of person who
says harsh things.
I don't know what I'm like.
But I think I have to do this.
I'm here because I'm here.
You can't be who you want to be.
Yeah.
I think I have to protect myself.
I think I have to think about how I want
to be seen as a group.
People who know will know.
I have a suggestion.
I like that.
I need to be clean.
No way.
I want to be clean.
Then, I'll go with white clothes.
I want to see it first.
I feel something strange.
What is it?
Is it Tee-chan?
I don't know.
Tee-le Tee-le?
Tee-le Tee-le Tee-le.
So, you joined Ebichu.
Yes.
Was there a moment when your heart was
broken?
Yes, there was.
I don't remember the broken moment
because I was so depressed every day.
I don't know.
I was not so depressed.
It's not that important.
I was so depressed.
I was desperate. I was not a child
anymore. I was a child until I was a
mother. After that, my heart broke. I
was depressed once. I couldn't speak
well.
I heard a voice next to me.
I felt sorry for her.
I couldn't speak well.
I was so sad.
I was worried about her.
Hey.
I wonder what happened.
When I sleep, I think it's not a big
deal.
I'm the type to be depressed all the
time.
I'm depressed.
Are you the same?
I'm not depressed.
I'm depressed for a while.
I'm positive.
But I'm actually negative.
Did you know that?
I don't know.
You were negative.
I'm sure.
I'm not positive.
You are very positive.
I've never heard a negative comment.
I'm depressed.
When I sleep, I think it's normal.
I think so.
I think about it before going to bed.
I think it's normal.
When I sleep, I think it's not a big
deal.
I'm the type to think so.
I see.
I don't have any problems.
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
I can't solve it by myself.
I see.
Why do you have words?
It's communication.
It's difficult to communicate.
It's not a word.
It's a connection.
It connects the heart and mind.
I can express what I think.
I'm scared.
Words are important.
It's the first time we've talked
seriously.
I don't know what I'm saying.
It's a fresh feeling.
I'm scared.
What is this?
It's not a blanket. It's cold.
It's not like everyone's showing off
like now.
I was a child.
You're over here. You don't have a
junior high school.
I'm happy to be born.
I failed.
The fight that took a lifetime.
It's a place you shouldn't touch.
It's the first time.
If I lie here...
If I'm just like you
Would you ever ask me
Just for what I've got to want
We're all so energetic.
This program was brought to you by the
sponsor.
It's not like magic, but it's a bit of a
It's not like everyone's showing off
everything like now.
I think there's a little bit of this
album.