Hi, I'm Kouro.
Hi, I'm Iggy.
Hi, I'm Moshi Moshi.
The moment I got the call, they said it
was an animal park.
They said it was a gorilla group.
I thought it was a place where I could
be in.
It's a little embarrassing, but...
So, KANOUN, I'd like to interview you
today.
I'm sure no one's watching.
I'd like you to talk roughly.
It's an interview that follows history.
So, I'd like to hear from you about the
Gang Parade.
How did you feel?
I liked the Gang Parade as a group.
I was happy that the Gang Parade was
restarted.
I was also happy to be there.
Thank you for watching.
I really liked the Gyanpare I saw in the
movie.
I thought it was a kind of rebellious
spirit.
I don't want to lose to anyone.
Nice to meet you. We are
Enjoy Play! We are the next Gyanpare!
When did you start liking us?
I started liking us in 2018 or 2017.
Did you start working in 2017?
Gyanpare?
No, I was in a different group.
Gyanpare was the group that I was in for
the first time.
What about you, Baby?
I was also in the same group.
And then, Go to the別パラダイスズ, 5th one.
1, 2, 3, 6th one?
6th one.
Which group was the most in the group?
The last one was...
I think that was the hardest time.
I think it was hard because there were
so many people.
There are so many people in the gang.
Who do you think is the most childish?
Yuka Terashima?
That's an unexpected answer.
Everyone was attacking me for not taking
the painkiller.
I've been told that many times.
I was told that I have a painkiller but
I can't carry it.
I was told that if there were 13 people,
someone would give it to me.
I tried to hit him once.
That's right.
Interviewers are really difficult.
I haven't decided to ask this.
The period of history has come.
I think I was in the middle of that.
Anything is fine.
We participated in the training camp.
There were so many things to gain at the
camp.
We passed the test.
I also participated in the canon.
We lost the marathon at the camp.
How was it?
I was the last one to decide to go to
the camp.
I couldn't prepare at all.
My legs were slow.
I was running, but I didn't think
everyone was fast.
You said you decided right before the
camp.
Did you have any problems?
I had a lot of problems.
What kind of problems?
Men?
It has nothing to do with men.
I'll go back to the topic.
It's not a cohabitation, but 13 people
are together.
There are some difficult things.
I'm not good at group activities.
I'm a busy person, so I can't wait.
I think everyone is kind.
What if you have a favorite type of man?
What if he's a little bit thick?
I can't.
I have a lot of types.
It's impossible if you don't match your
personality.
I don't like people who are loose on
time.
So you mean there's a man who's been
loose on time?
There's no one.
I'm sure the people who are watching
this are thinking that they like the
camp.
I don't think it's a little bit of a
problem.
I want to hear about the men I've met so
far.
Did you ask me?
I was told to do it freely.
I'm going to do something different from
people.
It's only at times like this.
Ordinary interviews don't ask idols
about their love.
What was the problem?
The problem was...
I don't know.
I don't think I've ever seen you
apologize to someone.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry for what I did.
Thank you for waiting for me.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Why do you keep saying things that you
can't use?
Please explain.
It was an interview to ask a lot of P.
Oh, really?
A big success!
Ask the next person more P.
Okay.
I pretended not to hear you, even though
I could hear you
I pretended to be stupid and gave up
I can't see the future