Thank you for watching!
Yakan, and the Idols.
So, that's it for the ending of the
show.
Is there any news from Takagi-san?
Yes, there will be a Starpla Festival on
January 14th.
It will be held at Yokohama Arena.
We, Momoiro Clover Z, will be there.
I hope that Starpla will be a great
event.
Also, on February 11th and 12th,
Momokuro Club Valentine's Day Night Z
will be held at Yokohama Arena.
I hope that we can enjoy Valentine's Day
a lot on the weekend.
I hope you will enjoy it.
Also, on April 22nd and 23rd, Momokuro
Spring Festival 2023 in Fukuyama City.
It will be held at Takegahana Sports
Park in Fukuyama City, Hiroshima
Prefecture.
I can only see it on the screen, but
it's a very nice place with a lot of
nature.
I hope you will come.
Thank you.
There are a lot of things.
I'm curious about the contents of the
Starpla Festival.
I heard that you can do this here.
What?
Please give me a hint.
You can do this horizontally.
This horizontally?
You can find new endings and do it.
There are also bad endings.
So, there is a spring season.
Thank you.
Lastly, I have a present for you.
Today, I have prepared a tea for you.
Jasmine tea is also prepared.
It's interesting.
You have a high girl power.
I see.
I have a high girl power.
I'm not a high girl power.
Thank you.
I've never heard of it.
It smells good.
Thank you for the food.
I'm waiting for the tea commercial.
That's the bad part.
If it continues for a long time.
You can see a lot of things.
Delicious.
I hope you feel warm in winter with my
voice.
This was Yakan and Idol.
Thank you for your support this year.
See you next year!