New Year!
Happy New Year!
The first New Year's special, Emichu
Tastasu New Year's Party!
The annual Humanity's Greatest Party!
I'm scared of getting scolded for being
the scariest!
The end!
The Christmas University Games held at
the end of last year are also amazing!
We look forward to your continued
support this year!
I'm so into you that I can't stop
I'm a heart-throbbing love
What should I do?
Moratorium, moratorium, moratorium
Middle school students
Add various things to private Ebisu
Middle School
Ebisu Justice
This program is brought to you by the
following sponsors.
First, a New Year's greeting
2016 was a year full of things
But I think it all happened because we
had to grow up
Let's make 2017 a year where we can fly
like birds
Cheers!
This is a really good song
Ebichu Tastasu New Year's party starts
now!
What do you think of when you think of
New Year's?
What's the New Year's card?
Otochidama
Everyone, Otochidama?
Tastasu, give me this
Here you go
No, no, no
I'm not giving you my card
Wait a minute
What's this?
Is there a card like this every year?
Everyone, if you're rich, do you want
Otochidama?
There really isn't one
It's New Year's
Then, put it down
There's an ATM nearby
Nearby?
Yes, yes, yes
This is a character that is more
expensive to pay for
I'm frustrated that you took it first
There is also AT, so even without
Takiwei, the excitement won't change
Takiwei dashes to the bank
This year too, do your best!
I thought you were going to say
something
Say something to your dad
Thank you dad!
Do your best!
Do your best in your college life!
Do your best in your eating habits!
Do your best!
Do your best in dancing!
Do your best in laughing!
Nothing in particular
Why? Why? Thank you!
No, no, no, why?
Why are you laughing?
I can't get a good one!
There's no second round, right?
Is this the venue for the anniversary of
Wish You Tastas?
Oh, is that so?
What's wrong?
Wait a minute.
Who?
Sakura Ebisu.
Sakura Ebisu?
Yes.
Since we're here, let's give some to
everyone.
Here, here.
That's right.
I'm fine too. Give some to everyone.
Since Takie just gave out the New Year's
money, it's a good timing.
Line up, line up.
Say your name.
Good morning. We are Sakura Ebisu.
Nice to meet you.
Nice.
Cute.
I see. I don't have a pochibukuro
anymore.
Do you have one?
Sakura Ebisu, what about Moa-chan?
She's sick, so she's on vacation.
Then let's give Moa-chan some.
I'll take it.
That's right.
Okay, line up.
Let's line up.
Calm down.
I'm lining up.
Okay, then.
Hello.
Thank you.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Mizuha.
Mizuha-chan, right?
Thank you. I'll remember you.
Thank you.
I'm Riju.
Riju-chan, right?
Yes.
Nice to meet you.
Thank you.
I'm Sora Akane. Nice to meet you.
Sora-chan, right?
Yes.
Do your best.
Thank you.
I'm Ayame Kawashima.
Ayame-chan.
Ayame-chan, nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Misato Sakurai.
Misato-chan.
Yes.
Please congratulate me.
I'll do my best.
I'm Chueiko, Moa.
It's not Moa.
Moa-chan.
Poor Moa-chan.
Thank you.
Moa-chan is not this kind of character.
Let's start the second round.
What is second round?
It's not a handshake party.
It's not second round or third round.
Thank you for this year.
We hope you will continue to support
Sakura Ebi-zo this year.
Please.
Newly released, Shinshun Ningen Sugoroku
This year's also doing it, the old
Ningen Sugoroku tournament
Mayama team and Yasumoto team are
divided
A chill battle with amazing moves
in total we've got 20 bubbles
on those names, we've included a game
that contains the reward or a punishment
Team Challenger is Team Mayama
Wrong Name Fight
then, the çocukhśś tournament starts
What is the answer?
This is my challenge!
Masterigation
1,2,3
Matsuno
Idk
Their reward yakiniku bento
Team Mayamo's reward
Mutton kowamu had!
Look at this!
Looks delicious!
Meat!
This is so good!
The taste is so strong and delicious!
This is the best Yakiniku bento ever!
The smell is so good!
It's good, isn't it?
It's delicious!
It smells so good!
It smells good!
It's like a punishment for us, the
viewers!
It smells so good!
The best Yakiniku bento ever!
Tara!
Wow! It's spinning!
It's a Yakiniku bento with 4 people!
5 people!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5!
The white one stopped
There's something behind it
The 3 squares are back!
1, 2, 3, 4!
It's a star!
What is it?
The punishment is a Nira Neko with
Kashiwagi and Kobayashi!
Yay!
It's a star!
What is this?
Who is this for?
It's for watching the Nira Neko with
Kashiwagi and Kobayashi
The punishment is a Nira Neko with
I've never seen a competition between
two people
What's so interesting about watching it?
I don't know, but it's a punishment game
It's a punishment game
So, the punishment game for Team
Yasumoto
Hoshina's idea, Nira Neko with Kashiwagi
and Kobayashi
So, Nira Neko competition
Ready, start!
Let's play Nira Neko
Nira Neko
Oh, here it comes.
Sashimi won!
Nira Neko's last name is Kobayashi, so
it's Yoshizumo.
There are scary things like this hidden.
Be careful.
After that, Mayama team spread their
lead.
The number of squares that stopped is...
4 squares!
Hiroto's square
You can only talk with gestures!
You can't talk anymore!
OK, you can't talk anymore!
Gesture!
Why are you talking to Yasumoto?
Why is Yasumoto quiet?
So, Yasumoto's team will be able to do
it twice in a row?
That's right!
It's a chance!
We did it!
The second challenge!
The third challenge!
5!
5 squares?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5!
I have a bad feeling about this
2 squares! Go!
It's a tie!
The one that stopped was the square with
a question mark
What is this?
Oh no
To be continued
She's wearing a kasaobage
What does that mean?
So this is Kobayashi Kaho
She's wearing a kasaobage
Kobayashi-san, what is this?
I'm not wearing this
Oh you're not wearing it
It's Yasumoto-san
I don't know why this is a punishment
game
I don't know what it means
How is it Yasumoto-san?
It's good
It's comfortable
So this is really nothing
It's really a question mark
The viewers will also be in a question
mark
It's a scary thing
For the Mayama team to take a break,
Yasumoto team again
1, 2, 3
It fell
It's this
It's 2
Again a question mark
It's a question mark
Let's go
This is it
Fruit Monster Hoshinae's reward fruit
What is this?
Please explain
I'm looking at the microphone
I can't speak now
I can't speak
This is Fruit Monster Hoshinae's
So you eat it?
You eat it yourself
It's a reward
What kind of fruit is this?
Even if you eat it now, you can't say
what you think
Again a question mark
Hoshinae's reward fruit
Wow, amazing
You expressed your happiness with a
gesture
Hoshinae's reward fruit
I think it's really good
She's a crazy woman
Crazy woman
She's eating
Hoshinae's drawing is terrible
Roll, roll, roll
I hope I get first place
Wow, amazing
She didn't fall even once
Here it is
Hoshina's impersonation of Mirei in
front of her eyes
Why?
This is a punishment game that is easy
to understand
Everyone is used to it
Can I say something?
I heard that last year
Hoshina-san did it in front of me last
year
You know me
Mirei-chan, you are not the punishment
game
I'm not
Hoshina's impersonation of the
punishment game for the Mayama team
We saw it last year, so please run
Thank you for watching!
Come back overs everyone!
We'll be serious.
Vertical
That's good
Overhead
She seems afraid that
Matrac
5,4,3,2,1
This is the answer
1-1
So it's Nakayama's turn
Here it is
Kaho's scary story
What is this?
Nakayama, what does this mean?
The scary story of Kaho is that the
person she's talking to laughs and the
person listening to her is the one who's
laughing
You can only hear the laughter, you
can't tell what she's talking about
Nakayama's scary story
It's good, the ghost is making the
stairs
What should we do?
It's original
It's the scary story I experienced when
I was in 6th grade
The scary story of Kaho
The room where I stayed during my school
trip
I saw it, and when I entered the room,
a girl was there, a friend of mine,
and she suddenly started crying!
I was like, why? What's wrong?
But actually...
I saw a doll just now!
Time's up!
5th time!
This is really a punishment game
It's a punishment game
If we get 4, it's a goal
Don't sleep!
1, 2, 3
What will be the result?
Let's go back to the start line
I'm so excited
Team Yasumoto is also going to the start
line
The heated battle continues
Everyone is doing yoga
His butt is dangerous
Give him some fruits
What's wrong?
I'm not letting you eat
The time has passed
The time for the party is coming to an
end
The members are also in a hurry
The members are in a hurry
Please look forward to the next part!
I was in a hurry
My eyes are like this
So it's like this
1,2,3
Nakoyama
What was it?
This one
Aoi Shibata
Aoi's answer
Hurry up
After school, when a boy goes to the gym
bit African
A basketball was bouncing
Right now I'm shaking it, and also
thinking
Eight, bend towards my shoulders
In anyone's eyes.....
Yeah, goodbye, bye!
3, 2, 1, 3!
Okay.
Don't laugh!
You're the best!
Kono-chan's punishment!
Sit down!
Why is everyone listening?
Who are you punishing?
I'm afraid of being scolded for being
the scariest!
And so, both teams reach the goal
In any case, they all wish for it to end
soon
You're late!
1, 2, 3!
Congratulations!
Team Sarabota wins!
Thank you!
The winner is the Karakasa team!
The prize is the two-tiered bento set
from Kagurazaka Chuzan, which was
specially made for this event.
The winner, Osechi, please eat it!
Karakasa, you can eat it.
We'll let you eat it.
It looks delicious.
The winner is the Karakasa team!
Surprisingly, the losing team is eating
good food
That's right
It's so good
The smell of the dried squid is amazing
It was good
I'm the first to play the game
What is it?
Bye bye
She closed it on her own
Please do it again this year
Please
After this, we will show you the college
game show held at the end of last year
Shiritsu Ebisu Junior High School
Christmas College Game Show 2016
Challenge for Ody الحاسف Το
What's up, Chie-san?
So today...
Put it on.
So today, we're here at the first gym of
the swimming stadium!
You're looking at it too much.
Let's go!
So, at the end of last year,
Christmas University Games 2016,
Ebichu's Ocean's Guide.
Please digest the two days.
Friday, 6.30pm.
No sleep coming to home
It's all a lie
In this noisy era
I want to be the only one for you
I'll give you my love
If I can't be taken by someone
I'll break
Thank you for watching!
And I want to feel your presence
There's no meaning in giving up
Let's go, to tomorrow
Thank you for watching!
After the live, they visit the members.
I was moved.
It was really popular.
Honestly, I saw a crazy guy from another
family.
Good luck tomorrow.
They finished the first day's live.
The second day.
The first draft meeting in the history
of the university.
The unit of three groups.
Please look forward to the stage.
Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
I'll tell you my heart's desire
I want to see you give your heart
I'll make a wish, Bang Bang Bang
I want to protect you forever
I'll tell you my heart's desire
Miss, Miss Moko!
What's wrong, Nohoko?
Crab!
What?
It's Christmas, why do you have a crab?
Ah, it's my only Christmas
Ah, it's a shiny Christmas
Don't be trapped by the scenery
It's a Christmas present
It's okay to wish for a crab
Thank you for watching! Please subscribe
to our channel!
Let's play, oh yes, oh yes, yes
Our hearts are one
We'll play a civic ELISE dance!
And so, the last live of the 8 members
in 2016,
was a huge success and closed the
curtain.
Thank you for your hard work!
Thank you!
How was it after 2 days?
There were people who came in 2 days
I felt that this is the exciting part
I received the feeling that they really
gave their best
I think we enjoyed it even more
Yes!
That's a great evaluation
Please continue to support Shiritsu
Ebichu Yoko
This was Shiritsu Ebichu Yoko
Dreaming of Kanaema Show Special
Next time, the dream of the members,
Kanaema Show Special
Cute
Is it Kanaema?
Kanaema
Kanaema Show Special
That is the reality.