Ebichu's videos
Ebichu's spring tour is over!
Yay!
So, the spring tour is about to start
This is our first spring tour
and also the first Ebichu tour
It's been a while, Aya-chan
Yeah, it's been a while
So, we'll be talking about what a spring
tour is
and who we'll be talking to
Thank you
So, first of all, this spring tour
is about to start with our 7th full
album,
which was released on March 23rd
It's a tour that's about to start
with the first Ebichu middle school
It's been a while since we've had a tour
that's about to start with an album
It's been a while, right?
I think there are a lot of people who
listen to our albums
and listen to our songs
Do you have any favorite songs
that you like?
I like Sayonara Kimitsu Kichigami
What kind of songs do you like?
I like songs that are
really easy to listen to
I like songs that change the mood
and make you feel like you're in a dream
What about you, Kona?
I like Kyuun
When I first heard it, I thought
I really liked this song
When I saw it on Ebichu
I was like, wow, that's great
I thought it was a new song
that was cool on Ebichu
I think it's a new song
I'm glad we're together
We're in the same group
and we were asked to perform on the
first day of the tour
It's the first time that Ebichu has
become my favorite
and I think we might be able to meet
more people
I'm glad we can meet them
I'm glad
What's your schedule like?
For this week's schedule,
I usually take the plane or the bullet
train
rather than the train in Tokyo
I usually take a huge car
Really?
Do you have a time where you have to
stay up all night?
Yes, I do
I think I do
I think I'd rather go home
because I can sleep
We went on a trip together.
It was a great trip.
It was fun.
But I think you two might have a home-
sick.
Oh, home-sick!
I'm sorry.
I'm not sure if I'm okay with it.
I'm a home-sick in my third year of
junior high school.
I want to go back to Nagoya.
Nice. Thank you.
Can you say something?
I have a big white carry case.
Oh, you have?
I bought it in the summer.
Oh, it's full of stuff.
It's full of stuff.
It's not going to be hard.
I always carry something when I sleep.
Do you have anything like that?
No, I don't.
I'm sorry.
I'm a modern person.
Modern person.
I can't sleep without this.
It's important.
I think I can sleep in my own space.
Oh, that's true.
I feel safe without it.
I'm not going to get a break.
My surroundings are clean.
I can sleep.
I put a charger on top.
There are a lot of pictures here.
Pictures?
I only have pictures of TWICE.
I can't sleep without someone else.
I have to bring it.
You have to bring a lot of things.
I have to bring a lot of things.
I have a bad feeling.
Muscle pain.
My legs look really swollen.
I think you should buy a Beef
It's Sinn Bravo who're have changed
Even there,
Be ready normally
I like the people who are proud.
I have a sore throat.
I suddenly have a sore throat.
We were rehearsing.
We had a rehearsal for three consecutive
days.
We had a rehearsal at the university.
I couldn't fall in love at that time.
I wondered if it was strong.
Did you feel tired?
I was in a bad mood the day before the
concert.
I was in a bad mood because I was
wearing a small gachachuki.
I was scared.
You two are used to traveling.
I often stay in Tokyo.
I often stop at the hotel.
Are you used to traveling?
I'm used to traveling.
How many days are you traveling?
How many days have I been traveling?
I have been traveling for 7 days.
I have nothing to do with traveling.
I was a professional.
I was worried.
I brought only care goods.
What is your favorite thing about
traveling?
I like traveling.
What is your favorite thing?
I like eating rice.
You can definitely prepare it with
catering.
I like eating rice.
What was the most delicious place you've
ever been to?
I'm confused.
I want to eat salmon roe and salmon roe.
I'm a new member at the live show.
I know that I'm being chased by the
fans.
But that's not the only thing that I'm
looking forward to.
The reaction of the fans is different
from each region.
It's interesting.
In Kansai, the sound of taxi was loud.
The sound of taxi is interesting.
I'm curious about the sound of taxi in
Nagoya.
Many people show their excitement in a
shy way.
So it's more exciting.
It's exciting.
I'm not sure if it's because I'm talking
to you.
Is Aichi's person funny?
It's funny.
Is Ibaraki's person funny?
Ibaraki's person is kind of shy.
Every time I go to the event, I say
thank you.
My family and I have done a lot of
things.
I think it's because we're in a place
where we can't go often.
I'm the only one who's shy.
Thank you.
What is Ibaraki's person funny?
I'm a flight attendant.
What do you do when you're on the move?
I'm a water-drinking person.
We're usually sleeping.
When I went to Turkey, I had a flight
back home for about 19 hours.
It was a long flight.
I slept for half the time I spent in
human life.
You slept for half the time?
I was worried about sleeping.
I was worried about becoming an economy
officer.
I was worried about eating.
I slept before the flight.
I thought I was already sleeping because
of the sound of the flight.
I slept a lot.
After the live performance, I was very
excited.
I was worried that I couldn't sleep.
What did you do?
I watched a drama.
I ate lunch for about an hour.
I still eat.
I ate a lot of Osaka food.
I want to talk to you.
I want to watch a drama with you.
That's nice.
Do you have any friends who are your
local friends?
I have a friend who is my local friend.
Did you invite me?
I have a local friend.
I have a local friend, but I can't call
you because I have a lot of friends in
Tokyo.
I can call my relatives in distant
regions.
Did you invite your grandmother?
I was going to go and buy a ticket.
I have relatives in Osaka.
I was going to come and buy a ticket.
Do you have relatives in each region?
I have a relative tour in Yunan.
I think I have a relative tour in Yunan.
Aichi Prefecture is a friend of my
school.
My friend and I are friends.
I'm more excited than any other family.
I'm looking for a relative tour in
Yunan.
I'm glad to meet you.
I'm looking forward to the tour.
I was able to get along with my friends.
I was able to take measures.
I was worried about my health.
I was very happy.
I have to prepare for the tour.
I have a lot to do.
I want to do various things and enjoy
the tour.
The tour will start on April 16th.
The tour will start on August 16th.
Tension Anniversary Tour 2022 Drawer.
Is that right?
Drawer.
I can go to your place.
Please come to the place where you can
enjoy the tour.
We are waiting for you.